You alright there, chief?
You look like you lost your lucky bookmark
or something.
Oh, no! Did I?
It's fine. I got it right here.
It's just that now
that we're actually on the train
heading to Bad Place headquarters
this plan is starting to feel slightly...
completely insane.
This is the only way to get to the Judge?
I'm afraid so. Yes.
See, the Judge exists in a sort of
neutral zone
separate from the Good Place
and the Bad Place.
The only things there
are the Judge's quarters
the Accounting department
and the Janet Warehouse.
No, there's also an IHOP.
Dope! I'm gonna order
the Rooty Tooty Fresh 'N Fruity!
No, sorry, um...
in this realm, IHOP stands for
"Interdimensional Hole of Pancakes."
You don't really eat these pancakes
it's more like they eat you.
OK, I'll get eggs then.
So, the only way to get to the Judge
is through a Portal
which is smack dab
in the middle of the main office
at Bad Place headquarters.
And the only way through the Portal
is with one of these.
What is that? Is that jewellery?
Not that it matters.
It's just some jewellery I don't have.
Can I have it?
- These pins are very hard to come by
only upper management-types have them.
So, you guys will lay low,
while I get us four more.
Janet doesn't need one, because for Portals
she counts as a "carry-on."
I'm luggage.
I had Janet make you each
a Bad Place disguise
and everyone who worked in the Neighbourhood
has been sent back
to their previous departments
so the chances of you being recognised
are very small.
I don't know. This plan seems complicated.
To be fair, you also once said that
about an orange.
They don't make sense!
Apples you eat their clothes,
but oranges you don't?
Forget this plan.
I say we just huck a Molotov cocktail and...
Whew! Run through the Portal.
As much as I respect your explosive-based
problem-solving skills
I think we should go with Michael's plan.
I'm telling you, Molotov cocktails work.
Any time I had a problem,
and I threw a Molotov cocktail - boom!
right away, I had a different problem.
He makes a strong case.
OK, now, you're all gonna need aliases.
Cool. I'm gonna be... "Diana Tremaine."
That was the name on my fake ID
in high school.
Her address was 123 Whatever Street
Canada City, Canada.
Arizona bouncers are the best.
Character work! Such fun.
I actually dabbled in a bit of acting
after university.
Although, mostly, I just stood around
while Baz Luhrmann just threw glitter on me.
- Ooh, I shall be...
- "Rhonda Mumps"
and I work down at the hot dog factory!
- You need to be more specific.
There are nine hot dog torture departments.
Making people into, stuffing people with...
Ooh, stuffing people sounds fun.
Is that like shoving them into the throats
of vegans?
Yes.
throats.
I know what my secret identity is.
You cannot be "Blake Bortles."
Fine. Then I'll be "Jake."
Don't say "Jortles."
- "Jortles"!
And I work in the Molotov cocktail
department.
Boy, you know, I thought you guys would be
more worried about this.
We've been knee-deep in demons
for, like, 800 reboots now.
- Lying about who we are is second-nature.
- Huh.
Chidi?
I hate this, I hate lying,
it's not permissible, I can't do this!
Oh, boy.
Jeez Louise!
Looks like Chidi has a real case
of the Mondays, am I right?
Hey, uh... pass the Nascar-ketchup!
Hey, buddy.
Look, if you don't want to lie because
it conflicts with your moral principles
I get it.
No one's going to be mad at you.
Really?
No, dumbass!
I'm lying to you to make you feel better!
See? Sometimes lying is awesome!
Plus, I said "dumbass!"
Oh, cursing - how I've missed you.
Look, Eleanor, our goal here is to appear
in front of a Judge
who is going to judge us.
What if I lie down here,
and I lose 12 points
and then we get in front of the Judge
and I'm 12 points short?
Or what if the Judge won't even take our case
at all, because we lied to get there?
Kant says that lying is always wrong
and I follow that maxim.
So, you can't even lie to demons?
They're trying to torture us, man!
We're behind enemy lines!
Look, principles aren't principles
when you pick and choose
when you're going to follow them.
I won't lie about who I am.
OK.
I understand, and I'm cool with it.
You're lying right now, aren't you?
- Yes, I wanna strangle you.
What even is this thing?
I hate suits.
They remind me of court,
and going to court
and being my own lawyer
against the advice of the judge in court
and getting immediately convicted in court.
I think you look nice.
I think you look sexy.
Here.
I got you this to help your disguise.
- Whoa, a briefcase?
"Take my credit card to the hedge fund.
I'll meet you at the martini store."
Oh, you're gonna get caught.
Give me the briefcase back. Thanks.
Aw...
Janet, you need to get in character, too.
Now, I know you look like a Bad Janet
but can you act like one?
I have gained a lot of new skills recently.
For example, I learned how to be
passive aggressive.
Totally fine that you guys haven't noticed.
Oh!
- Well, let's practice.
OK.
I'm going to make a simple request
and you're going to give me that patented
"Bad Janet" attitude.
- Can I have a glass of water?
- Here you go.
No.
Let's try again. Be mean!
Bad Janet, can I have a glass of water?
No.
I would never give you that, you...
dumb person.
Janet, what's that behind your back?
- Nothing.
Give it to me.
- It's a glass of water.
Oh...
And a back-up glass. Oh, boy...
- Oh!
It's OK, we'll keep working.
OK.
- You'll get the hang of it
Or my name isn't Rhonda Apple Pie
Spiderman Mumps.
We're here.
All trains today are delayed
by three hours.
Just like they are every day.
All passengers, you all suck and you're ugly.
Keep walking.
Again. You all suck...
- Keep your heads down.
and you are ugly.
Just act unnatural.
Hey, guys.
So, you wait here, while I go get us
some more of these pins.
But what is this place?
- It's just a place.
You know, an area, or "location."
It's pretty straightforward.
"The Museum of Human Misery?"
Oh. Yeah, OK.
It's a torture museum.
Famous examples of bad behaviour,
and explanations of the torture they earned.
Is there a gift shop?
- Jason, this is Hell.
Of course there's a gift shop.
It's the least horrifying room.
It's the "Hall of Low-Grade Crappiness."
"First person to floss
in an open-plan office."
Well, she deserves to be tortured -
she's a monster.
This was the safest place I could think of
no one ever comes in here.
Guys, if you do leave this room
you're gonna see things
that will haunt you for eternity.
OK, back soon. Bye.
Hey, hey.
Be careful. OK?
"Be careful"?
Yeah.
Oh, Eleanor, are you worried about me?
Yeah, I'm worried.
I mean, cos you're our ticket
out of here, genius.
Don't go getting all goopy on me.
No, worry about them. I'll be fine.
OK.
"First man to send an unsolicited picture
of his genitals."
Heh... heh... heh...
"First waiter to approach a diner
with an empty plate"
"and, sarcastically, say,
'I guess you hated it.'"
"First white person to grow dreadlocks."
And first person to call ultimate Frisbee
"ultimate"!
This dude rules!
Alright, everyone...
we've got a lot of work to do.
Why don't you set up the bar over by that wall?
Why don't you roll off your mum
and do it yourself, ya fat dink?
Set up more of those tables.
We're expecting a big crowd.
You got it, you piece of...
butt.
Son of a bitch!
Still happy I can swear now,
but everything else about this is very bad.
Hey, boss.
I'm back.
Welcome home. Axe up.
Ho! New scent.
"Transformers."
- Yes.
It makes you smell the way "Transformers"
movies make you feel.
Still can't believe those jack-offs
got away from us.
Really zips my tip.
Yeah.
- Anyway...
I drew up some extradition papers
to get them back from Mindy's.
I think I'll take a few
of my most trusted staff
hop in the Portal, file those with the Judge
quick stop for pancakes
and then I'll head on back.
By the way, I'm gonna need, uh...
four pins, for my crew.
This is very thorough, however...
Is that where we're putting
top-priority files nowadays?
We won't need extradition papers.
Plans are already in motion
to get the humans back in a different way.
Ah.
Oh man, this is not good.
This is noooot good!
Would you chill out?
Haven't you ever crashed a party before?
No! I've only been to like,
four parties total
and all of them were thrown by Tahani
after I was already dead.
Alright, well, we can't just stand here
in a group, looks too conspicuous.
I'll go with Tahani, Chidi go with Jason.
That way, Jason's unearned confidence
let's him do all the talking
and you don't have to lie. OK?
Come on, Diana!
Let's hit the bar!
I'm gonna get me a tall glass
of pipin' hot corn syrup
and a scooter so I can roll around the mall!
That's really good.
- Thank you.
Hors d'oeuvre?
Ooh, what do you got?
Soul food from Maine, bagels from Arkansas
Hawaiian pizza, of course
and egg salad from a hospital vending machine
in Azerbaijan.
Uh, that!
Have a terrible evening.
No way! Trent? Is that you?
Uh, who else could it be?
Come on. Tap it out. Boom-boom!
Whassup? I'm Chet.
Jake is my name,
Molotov cocktails is my game.
I think school is lame, I gotta tattoo
of David Blaine! What!
Whoo! Tight!
Ball tap!
Dip! Ball tap!
Oh! That's a firm ball tap, bro.
Anyway, cha'boy Trent and I worked together
in Partial Decapitations.
When did you leave de-cap?
800 years ago?
Uh, something like that.
I just joined a new department -
Toxic Masculinity.
We torture internet trolls, frat dudes.
It actually started as a training program
to prep for when
the "Girls Gone Wild" dude gets here.
Joe Francis!
- The one.
Legend!
Ha-ha! Bro-hams!
Get over here and meet my top dog, Trent.
Dude's a straight beast
when it comes to torture!
Sup, bro?
- Sup, bro?
It's actually pretty choice that we're
running into you right now.
My top dog Dirk here,
he got stuck with a new case.
He can't crack it. Hit 'em with it, D-Money.
So, I'm trying to torture
this guy, right, Brant.
Brant was a total lord - he got kicked off
of Rob Gronkowski's party cruise
for throwing a lobster at a stripper,
and then he died doing a keg stand
in the back of a moving Jeep Wrangler.
Anyways, we run a couple hundred
torture scenarios
none of them seemed quite right, you know?
Think we can get you to crack this nut?
Well, I mean, how... how can I say no?
Yeah, I know how I would say no.
You know, I'd be all like...
"No!"
But... You know, I can't.
You're so weird, Trent, man.
You're always so weird.
I love that about you.
- Yeah...
Don't get me wrong,
I love shoving hot dogs into people
But once you've dogged every hole, you just
start to feel like you're repeating yourself.
Whew. I hear that, sister.
I'm gonna go take a dump -
you want me to grab you one?
Nah, I'm good, thanks.
Not even a little nug?
- Nah, I'm 'aight.
Alright.
Damn, you're good at this.
Well, hang out with Johnny Depp long enough
and you become pretty good at lying.
Like, "No, your whole thing isn't
exhausting at all!"
Hi there, you big stinky poop-face guys!
Ugh, it's me - Good Janet!
I'm sorry I called you big stinky
poop-face guys.
That's OK. Janet,
can you dig around a little bit
and find out what this event is,
and how long it's gonna last?
I'd love to! Punch your... teeth!
Hey.
Teeth...
What's all this?
Well, I was going to try to get the humans
back by going through the proper channels
but then I remembered -
I'm a naughty bitch.
So...
I sent a black ops team to Mindy's,
to... "extract" them.
Nobody from the Bad Place
is allowed in Mindy's Neighbourhood.
You can't do that, Shawn.
It's... it's... it's illegal!
Oh, no.
Guys, Michael says this is illegal.
I hadn't thought of that.
That was sarcasm - I had thought of that.
Listen, your experiment blew up in our faces.
The example I made out of Vicky ensured
that everybody from the Neighbourhood
has kept their mouths shut,
but we're not out of the woods
until those four are back in custody.
So, I rounded up some loyal friends,
and took matters into my own hands.
Relax, Mike. This will all be over soon,
and we can all head down to the museum.
The museum?
Yes. Your Neighborhood - our Neighborhood
is being immortalised for its success.
It's all gonna work out.
I took the form of a 45-year-old
white man for a reason -
I can only fail up.
Oh, OK, our team is five minutes out.
Bad Janet, burn us some popcorn.
Help yourselves, everybody.
Hey! Hi. So, um...
those bro demons over there
think I'm some kind of great torturer
and they want my advice
on how to torture someone.
Jason is stalling by ranking
MMA ring girls with them
but I have to do something.
Eleanor, you're wearing glasses now, help me!
You know the answer, dude.
Lie your ass off.
If Rhonda can do it, you can.
You know, I once shoved a hot dog right down
the throat of the legendary John Wayne.
She even name-drops in Hell.
I told you, lies have consequences!
I will have contributed
to someone's eternal torture
because I disobeyed a basic Kantian
moral principle.
I'm gonna be sick.
And I don't want to go back to the bathroom
because they put mirrors in the toilet
and that makes you really confront
what you're doing!
OK, OK. Sit down. Take a breath.
Rub your lucky bookmark. Hear me out.
What if lying is ethical, in this situation?
What if, uh... certain actions
aren't universally good or bad
like Jonathan Dancy says?
Jonathan Dancy? Are... are you talking about
moral particularism?
We never even covered that.
You read on your own!
You think just because I'm a straight hottie
I can't read philosophy for fun?