OK, I don't know about you guys,
but I say we leave this miserable shirthole.
No, wait, wait. Not so fast.
Now, getting to the Good Place
is pretty tricky
there's no train to catch.
I have to design a complicated,
unique transportation vehicle.
Is it Optimus Prime?
What?
- I can't believe we get to ride a real-life
Optimus Prime! I call right nipple!
That's "Shotgun" on Optimus Prime.
Look, this vehicle, which is decidedly not
Optimus Prime...
Aw!
has never been built before.
So, I'm gonna need a few days to do this.
Dude, we just escaped
by the skin of our teeth
and any second now, Shawn is gonna realise
that we are not at Mindy St Clair's.
So, whatever this magical
Good Place-mobile is
now's the time to whip it out, B!
I agree. And although I believe
I've asked you this question already...
There is no "business class."
Michael, they're right. We gotta go.
Oh. Let's do...
OK, here goes nothing. Janet, if you would?
Aaaand presto!
Oops.
Forgot to log in first.
Gotta answer my, uh... security question.
"What was the name of your childhood pet?"
Korzoff... the Ten-Headed...
Dog-Spider.
Aaaand presto!
Dope!
We did it, guys.
We won.
We're going to the Good Place.
In a frickin' gold balloon!
Shotgun!
It's a hot air balloon,
what does that even mean?
Top of the balloon! Ultimate shotgun.
Guys, just a reminder
I have no idea what's going to happen
once we actually
reach the Good Place.
You know, we're trying to slip in
through a kind of side door
and even if that works
we have no way of knowing
if they'll let us stay.
Of course they'll let us stay -
we're refugees.
I mean, what kind of a messed-up place
would turn away refugees?
Quite agree. We should get a move on.
Obviously, if I'd known we'd be ballooning,
I would've worn a proper ballooning outfit
but time is of the essence, so...
Tahani. Yeah, no, no, don't.
Don't touch that.
It's probably locked.
It's a very complicated control system.
I may need a few minutes
to get a handle on this.
Why don't you all go say goodbye
to the Neighbourhood?
Oh, then I could change into a proper
ballooning outfit!
Oh, hurrah!
Are you making fun of me?
No, I legit wanna see you in that outfit.
Oh!
So many memories of this place -
eating frozen yogurt and then having diarrhea
and then eating more frozen yogurt
and then more diarrhea.
Maybe I should've realized this wasn't
the Good Place
because of all the diarrhea.
Maybe you shouldn't be eating all that
frozen yogurt right now.
We're about to be on a balloon, man.
What do you think our new home will be like?
I'm picturing Hawaiian beach,
unlimited Mai Tais
and a phone!
Ugh, I miss my phone so much.
I bet I have so many texts.
I just want us all to be together.
Separate houses, obviously.
Large lawns.
I'd have a tasteful moat.
I don't care where I live, as long as
they have more of this frozen yogurt.
Why? Why?
An unlimited library
all of my philosopher heroes walking around
waiting to be engaged in rigorous
intellectual debate.
And I hope that library is air-conditioned
because we are gonna be working up
quite a sweat!
Oh! And soulmates!
I hope they're real.
I mean... you know...
for... for all of us.
I mean, I hope everyone gets someone special.
Uh, mm...
Good news!
We've got a handle on the controls.
Who's ready to go ballooning?
OK, I think we figured it out.
I pieced together this design
from a number of ancient manuscripts
which Janet will now interpret for you.
"The balloon will only transport those
who have attained self-realisation."
"Each traveler will step upon the scale,
and her soul shall be weighed."
"If she is the best version of herself,
it will permit her to board."
"If not, passage will be denied."
Cool.
Cool. Cool.
We got this.
I don't know about you guys, but I am
definitely the best version of myself.
I know a shirt-ton about ethics now,
because I studied.
And I read books, that weren't even written
by the "Real Housewives."
Relax, everyone. We're all gonna be fine.
Oh, man, I didn't believe anything
I was saying. I just...
Whoo! In I go.
Well, I mean...
Oh, dip!
Ah, nuts!
It's OK!
The pattern is "green-green-green-red."
Remember that when it starts up again.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I just have some worries,
as well as some concerns
that could potentially turn into
outright fears.
Ah, there they go. Ah, they're...
they're fears now. I'm scared.
OK, I know this mood.
Come with us, Doctor Freak-Out.
That was a joke.
We're actually very good friends.
OK, here's the thing.
That balloon wants us to be the best version
of ourselves, but for the four of us
that's not just a metaphor.
It doesn't just mean, "are we the nicest
that we've ever been?" or something
although I am also worried about that.
But the real issue here is that there have
been literally 802 different versions of us!
And how do I know that this version
is the best version of myself?
How do I know it's not version number 85?
Or 322? Or 558?
Or 69 or 420!
You know, and... and then you get
into the whole idea of...
of consciousness. And, I mean,
just forget about "best"
what version of Chidi is even real?
I mean, I think that "I" am here,
but what if the real "I"
is one of those other Chidis, and... and...
and this Chidi is an imposter!
What happens here?
Does he eventually tire himself out?
Usually, but this one seems to be
getting stronger as he goes on.
over time, because our consciousness
is constantly changing.
Which is just playing on the Buddhist
doctrine of the "non-self."
Plus, physically, our cells change
every seven years, which doesn't matter
because we're dead.
OK. This is pretty simple, bud.
You've been our teacher this whole time
and we are much better because of you.
If we're the best versions of ourselves,
which that balloon just proved
then you definitely are.
So, in a way, it...
it doesn't matter if I was "better"
in version 492 or whatever
because the best version of "me"
is just as much about my effect
on the world around me
as it is about my own egocentric self-image.
I really meant that much to you guys?
Of course you did.
Now let's get you back on that scale, dorkus!
Oh, good, you're back.
I had Janet make some food for the trip.
Twizzlers for Jason.
Shrimp for Eleanor.
Chidi, hard-boiled eggs.
And for Tahani, Lord Vivian's
Vinegar-Drenched Cuttlefish Crisps.
Oh, my favourite savoury dessert!
Oh, un-pickled...
No, thank you.
Chidi? Ready to try again?
Yeah, all right.
Yeah!
Dope!
Ugh!
Chidi got in my head!
It's just that thing Chidi said
about previous versions of myself
it's screwing me up, but I can fix it.
Phew!
I stole this from your house
the first night we were here.
OK. Should be the best version of myself now.
Urgh! Come on, scale! Be cool!
Guys, we're just not ready.
I think we should regroup,
and try again tomorrow—
Hang on. I know the answer.
I know why I'm not my best self.
Do you remember that version of me,
from the tape of us, at Mindy's?
Where I was vulnerable
and emotional, and honest?
That Eleanor is a better Eleanor
than this one.
And that is not an easy thing for me to say.
"You're not better than me"
was my yearbook quote.
Michael, can you tell us a little bit
about that version?
Uh... reboot number 119.
All the restaurants were kebab places.
You had a pet lizard, which I made
poop on you all the time.
No, can you tell us more about
Chidi's and my relationship
from that version?
Right. Sorry.
Well, you got really into ethics
and you spent a lot of time together.
Once, you handed him a tissue
right before he sneezed
and that simple act of anticipating his needs
made him fall for you.
One night you took a walk along the lake,
and you had your first kiss
which... gross. Kissing is gross.
You just mash your food-holes together.
It's not for that!
Anyway, it, uh... it just... you know...
bloomed after that.
Look. There are obviously
some undealt-with issues here.
I propose that everyone who is "green"
go ahead and board the magic balloon
and set out to the Good Place.
You know, sort of like an advance team.
We'll put our names in, or book a table,
however it works
and then we'll send back the magical balloon
for the "red-light people" later on.
It's a perfect plan.
No!
It's not working,
it probably thinks I'm Eleanor.
It is I, Tahani!
Wait! Wait!
I'm not really my best self, guys.
Tahani keeps trying to talk to me about
our relationship, but I keep dodging it.
Plus I haven't talked to Janet
about me and her yet.
And I haven't talked to Michael
about the band I want us to start
"The Rock and Roll Buddies."
Yes, actually you did.
I said, uh... I wasn't interested.
In case you were wondering,
I am by definition the best version of myself
because my operating system
is always updating.
I'm not sure that's true, Janet.
You still haven't talked to Jason
about your romantic baggage.
And the three of you
are in some sort of weird love triangle.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Also, love isn't a triangle.
It's a five-dimensional blob. So...
OK, if you're so perfect, step on the scale.
- Fine.
- Ooh! I think I broke it.
- No!
My beautiful balloon scale!
It's not yours!
No, no, please, stop fighting!
Ah, man. This... this stinks.
I'm having this feeling where...
what is it called?
You know where you, uh...
you did a thing and you're sad after it?
What...
"After-sad"? Is that...
No. Gah!
You humans have so many emotions.
You only need two -
anger and confusion!
Michael, what's going on?
The problem isn't any of you.
It...
This whole balloon thing is a fake.
The truth is, I have no idea
how to get into the Good Place
and I never have.
Well, Michael's right.
I'm angry and confused.
So, months ago, when you said
you had this whole complicated plan
for getting us to the Good Place...?
- It was a lie.
I assumed if I bought myself some time,
I could figure out a way in.
Guys, I tried a billion different ways.
Not an exaggeration - I actually tried
one billion and 12 different plans
but the only way into the Good Place
is by being a good person on Earth.
This is unforgivable. How many times
can you betray us?
I'm sorry. I really am.
Because while I was searching
for a way to get in
I was also taking your ethics classes
learning why it was bad to lie.
So not only did I fail at getting us
into the Good Place
I also learned the "error of my ways."
Real rock bottom for a demon, I'll tell ya.
So... how did you know
that I would doubt myself
and make the scale turn red?
I mean, at the risk of seeming blunt
I'm a puppet master
and you have long been my puppets.
But this was not torture!
I... I was stalling,
so I could keep searching for a way in.
I would have been happy if you were to live
in this Neighbourhood forever
but then Shawn came and... and...
and just ruined the whole thing.
So, what happens now?
Shawn will eventually figure out
you're not at Mindy's.
And he'll realize that someone on the inside
was helping you.
So, you'll go to the real Bad Place forever,
and I will be...
be retired.
You're... you're mad at me.
I'm not mad.
I'm just disappointed.
Aw, come on, everyone knows that's worse.
So, this really is the end.
Completely out of options, are we?
Not completely out of options.
We can do what the Shellstrops
have always done, when the chips are down
ignore our problems and drink heavily.
Janet!
A million bottles
of your finest booze, please.
You alright?
Kinda. I asked Michael if I could pop
the giant balloon
and he said no.
Then I asked if I could suck
the helium out of it
to make my voice sound funny
so it cheers everyone up...
and he just kind of sighed and walked away
so I guess that one is still on the table.
Are you and me cool?
Not exactly.
I think perhaps, given everything,
it's best we end our relationship.
It's probably about time I stopped relying
on others for my sense of self-worth
or happiness.
You know, my whole life,
whenever I encountered any obstacles
I would simply say
"I would like to speak to your manager."
But in our relationship, there is no manager.
There is no one
who can fix this for me, except me.
My mum was a manager at a pet store.
Does that help?
No, and please don't launch
into one of your long stories.
She got fired
- No, Jason...
after I robbed the pet store
- Please, please, please, please, Jason.
where she worked. We robbed it together.
- No, no, no, no, no. Please, stop.
Long story short, it was all a dream.
Thank you, Jason, for making this moment
a little easier, for me.
Dude, here's where I'm at -
feelings are stupid.
Yeah. Who needs them?
But, uh... in case feelings aren't stupid,
and, in the case that we are
eternally doomed, I thought
it might be worth mentioning that I do...
have feelings for you.
And I... I know you don't feel the same way.
And although that fills me with...
anger and confusion...
Wow, Michael was right on the money.
I just wanted you to know the truth.
You are... I mean...
- No, no, don't say anything. Don't. Don't.
- I want to, I want to.
I want to.
Here's the thing about me.
You know the sound that a fork makes
in the garbage disposal?
That's the sound that my brain makes,
all the time.
It's just this constant grinding.
About things I'm afraid of,
or things that I want
or want to want, or want to want to...
Is it grinding in there right now, bud?
- Yep.
But the... the point is, the circumstances
under which we met
are completely insane, and that just makes
the grinding harder.
I just wish we'd met the way
normal people meet
like at a philosophy conference, or after one
of my philosophy lectures...
or... or you came knocking
on my office door asking for help
with philosophy.
Is that how you think people meet?
I don't know how normal people meet.
It's not that I couldn't love you.
You're amazing
and...
fearless, and...
and clearly...
symmetrical.
You're such a nerd.
Attention, everyone!
We may not know exactly which version
of ourselves was technically our "best self"
but you know what?
I like who we are right now.
To this version of us.
To the good people we've all become.
Oh, and to Eleanor!
Our unofficial leader.
You pack a lot of heart and grit into that
diminutive frame.
Like a scrappy little auto-mechanic.
That's the nicest thing you've ever said
to me, babe, and I'll take it.
And to Janet! The best robot...
Not a robot.
- Girl...
Not a girl.
- And straight-up hottie...
I am attractive, yes.
any of us could have ever asked for.
Thanks, guys.
Because of the way
we were conceived of and created
Janets don't typically give speeches.
Oh, she's done.
She's not gonna give a speech.
Oh.
- OK. Cool.
Oh, one more toast! To Michael!
Michael!
Who is easily the best version of himself
granted the bar was low.
Mm-hmm.
- He is a demon.
- Mm...
- But...
he made a mistake and admitted he was wrong
which makes him better than 90%
of all humans.
And you know what?
It wasn't really Michael's fault.
We weren't getting
into the Good Place anyway.
I mean, look at us -
a self-obsessed socialite
a ridiculous giraffe
an absurd British aristocrat,
a narcissistic attention-seeker—
Are these all me?
- Yes.
I was gonna do eight for you,
and one for everyone else.
The point is, Michael...
we forgive you.
I mean, at least you tried to find a way
to the Good Place.
And that's the greatest thing someone can do
just try your best.
So, we hereby name you
an "honourary human"
and we would like to present you
with this Human Starter Kit.
Car keys! So I can lose them and say,
"Has anyone seen my car keys?"
Oh, and then I can do that, you know,
that thing where you... you...
Thank you!
And Band-Aids,
for your stupid fragile bodies.
Oh, and look at this - a stress ball
with a dumb corporate logo?
Oh, I can't wait to keep finding this
and then almost throw it away, and then think
"No, I'll... I'll use it!"
Oh... guys.
A Doctor Oz diet book,
because you're all such suckers.
This is all garbage
that I have no real use for.
That's right. Welcome to being human, buddy.
To Michael.
♪ I do my makeup in somebody else's car ♪
♪ We order different drinks
at the same bars... ♪
♪ Unforgettable
That's what you are ♪
♪ Unforgettable... ♪
- You don't remember?
- No!
No, of course you don't.
Oh, that's mean.
That was version one.
Michael...
there's a message coming in from Shawn.
"Finish shutting everything down."
"Sending train first thing tomorrow."
"Humans will be captured and tortured soup."
"Sorry, autocorrect."
"Soon."
"Although weirdly I did just finish turning
someone into soup."
"So random."
"OK, bye."
What do you guys think the Bad Place
is going to be, for you?
I'll probably go to a Skrillex concert
and I'll be waiting for the bass drop.
And it...