Hello, Michael.
Shut the door. Have a seat.
When you proposed this new form of torture,
we all laughed behind your back.
Some people called you names,
like "The Thomas Edison of Incompetence"
or, "That Dick."
Mm-hm.
But against all odds,
it seems you've pulled it off.
What you've done here is truly amazing.
Really?
- Yes. These reports are remarkable.
Your humans are experiencing
emotional torture
at the same level of physical torture
created by our squiggliest
Eyeball Corkscrews.
I'm... jubilant.
As a result of our success,
I'm getting a seat on the High Council.
We will greatly expand our Neighbourhood idea
and you will oversee the entire project.
You are being promoted.
Your Senior Staff Pin. Congratulations.
This is everything you've ever wanted.
This is everything I've ever wanted.
Oh!
This is everything I've ever wanted!
Oh, wow!
- You're really happy?
- Can't you tell?
I'm basically squealing like a birthday girl.
At some point, we should finish discussing
yesterday's events.
Do you mean us almost getting married
and then finding out I was married to Janet
and then Janet making a boyfriend
to forget me
and then Janet getting rid of that boyfriend?
Or do you mean when we saw that cool cloud?
The first bit.
Perhaps later, after Michael briefs us on how
we're going to be fake-tortured today
we can just sit down and have a chat?
Yes. Good idea.
Yo, Chidi?
- Yeah?
You wanna hear about a cool cloud I saw?
Come in.
I'd like to start by saying something
I've wanted to say for a very long time.
Surprise, idiots!
You're all in the Bad Place!
That's right, nerds!
Everything around you, all you can see,
is an elaborate system of torture
designed just for you.
Sorry... we're in the Bad Place?
Why are you revealing this now?
Well, it was an experiment, and it worked,
so my boss is promoting me.
Sorry, I should've introduced you.
This is my boss, Shawn.
Hello, imbeciles.
We need to study everything
that happened here.
There was a first version that collapsed,
but the second has been a huge success.
We'll be shutting this place down.
The four of you
will be brought to the real Bad Place
where your brains will be removed, studied,
and batted about a stadium like beach balls.
Your arms will be peeled like bananas -
that part's just for fun.
Right.
- And then you will be...
you know, tortured forever.
Michael, is this all true?
- Yes, Eleanor, it is.
You're such a rube, thinking you could
become a better person.
You got Chidi
to teach you stupid philosophy
like those old farts
were going to provide guidance.
"Oh, Kierkegaard is so great,
have you read 'Fear and Trembling'?"
"Well, I don't know,
have you read 'Boring and Stupid'?"
Because that's what you are.
Nice.
- Thank you.
How long will it take you
to shut down the Neighbourhood?
Better part of a day, I'd guess.
In the meantime, why don't we
have a "farewell" party here tonight?
You know, just to thank the crew
for all the hard work?
We can jam to some tunes, you know?
Destroy the place, play beer pong
with Jason's testicles...
What do you say, boss?
- Sure.
By the way, I know what you're thinking.
"Maybe Janet can help."
Ah...
- You're wrong. Janet?
Oh, hi, little cuties!
I love you guys so much.
Except for you, Jason, because I hate you.
- I hate you.
- Janet? What's wrong?
Oh! Where's my phone?
We put a Restraining Bracelet on her,
disrupting her powers.
It's made of mag-a-nets.
Magnets. Mag-a-nittens...
Magnets are supposed to make me feel drunk,
but guess what? I feel fine.
I can't believe Michael betrayed us again.
Why is it always the ones you most expect?
I should've seen this coming.
No one can ever truly "turn over a new leaf."
Sure, Ben Affleck told me he'd matured
as an artist after he directed "Argo"
but then, right on schedule, it was
"Guess what, Tahani? I'm gonna be Batman!"
There's only one option.
Shawn clearly doesn't know that Michael
has rebooted this Neighbourhood 800 times.
I say we trade that information
for some kind of reduced sentence.
Chidi, they're monsters!
Who's to say they won't agree to a deal,
hear what we have to say
and then turn around and install us
into their horrible human zoo?
There's no other option.
There's no way for a human
to get that bracelet off of Janet.
If there were, we could get her to call us
a train to Mindy St Claire's house.
We know for a fact that the people
from the Bad Place can't follow us there
- and I vote for that.
- I vote we...
No, sorry, and no offense, Jason,
but the stakes here are too high
to let someone with your limited
intellectual processing capacity weigh in.
I was gonna agree with you.
- Oh, great.
Well, that's two votes for my plan.
Eleanor. What do you think?
Trade information on Michael,
or try to escape to the Medium Place?
Neither.
I vote we ignore everything Michael just said
and blindly assume he's still on our side.
Who's with me?
Sorry, but when all this started
you're the one who told us
that Michael wasn't trustworthy.
- Now you want us to trust him?
- Yes.
For one very specific and rock-solid reason.
What's-his-name!
Who?
The dude! The super-depressing religious guy.
The real buzzkill, whose name
I can never remember.
Keeblers... car.
Kyra... Sedgwick?
Oh, I love her! Dear friend of mine.
Not important right now.
Kierkegaard?
- Yes!
Kierkegaard! When Michael was mocking us
about trying to become better people,
whose name did he use, huh?
Kierkegaard.
I think he was sending us a message.
To take a leap of faith.
Cos that was Kierkegaard's thing, right?
Yes, although it's probably
better translated as a "leap into faith."
It's so hard to be your friend.
- Yup. Sorry.
Michael was telling us to trust him!
I had a long talk with him the other night,
about the whole Derek incident.
Dude was shook - talking about ethics,
and all spiralling about human stuff.
I think he's on our side.
Or maybe, he's a supernatural demon
designed to torture people
who just got offered his dream job
and has flipped on us
like a ten-stone griddle-chip!
It's a large pancake. Come on, people,
you can get these from context!
Look, maybe Michael jumped back
to the dark side.
But I don't think so.
I think he's going to help us escape.
I know it sounds crazy,
but if it weren't crazy
they wouldn't call it a "leap of faith."
They would call it a... "sit of doubting."
I never thought I'd be the one to say it...
but this is getting out of hand.
I think we gotta go to the cops.
What cops? Where do you think we are?
Before tonight's party I'd love to talk more
about your strategy for torturing Tahani.
I'm impressed you were able
to make her fall in love with Jason.
She must be... miserable.
Yeah, humans make a lot of mistakes
when they're horny.
Ah, boss... Give me a second, here.
What the here, dude?
- Vicky...
My hard work paid off for you,
and now you're just taking all the credit.
Vicky, Vicky... this can work out great
for both of us
if we play our cards right.
Shawn thinks that this is attempt
number two, right?
Now if I tell him that you've been in charge
of this version
he's eventually gonna find out that there
have been hundreds of failed versions.
Ohhhhh! Right.
And if that happens, we're all going down.
So, spread the word.
No one talks about the reboots.
Fine. But you better make this right.
Mama want promotion, ya heard?
Hello, you dummies!
This Neighbourhood was a labour
of hate for many people here
so I thought that we should celebrate
with an art form
that we literally invented here
in the Bad Place
the "comedy roast"!
I see Jason Mendoza's here.
Jason might not be
the smartest guy in the world
but he is the dumbest guy in the world.
Ah, Jason, buddy.
All you had to do was to keep quiet
but you couldn't stop talking
about Kendall Jenner
or that dumb quarterback, what was his name?
Derek Bortles...
always ranting about "Derek Bortles."
Lucky for you, my friend, Jaguars games
are the only ones televised in the Bad Place
because they suuuuck!
No, they don't! All we need is a defense,
and an offense, and some rule changes.
Don't take it personally.
He just has to put on a show
for the other demons.
Tahani Al-Jamil.
Elegance, grace, sophistication...
But enough about your sister!
Do you know what the worst moment
of Tahani's life was?
When the last song played
at one of her parties
and she would run off and cry because
she still hadn't won her parents' approval.
You know the other worst moment
of Tahani's life?
Every other moment of her empty,
pointless life!
Hey-o!
I see Eleanor Shellstrop is here.
Eleanor and I have a lot in common.
Now here's how you can tell us apart.
One of us is a manipulative demon
who's an expert
at making other people miserable...
and then the other one is me!
You thought you deserved a Medium Place,
like Mindy St Claire?
Are you kidding me?
You're bad, Eleanor.
This is exactly the place you should be.
Not super funny for a roast, there, bud.
Oh, sorry, you want a joke? OK.
You love Chidi and Chidi doesn't
love you back. Boom!
Now, that's funny because it's
very cruel and humiliating.
I consider you one of my closest friends.
- Not now, dude.
Speaking of Chidi...
is something no one has ever said
because no one talks about Chidi
because no one likes Chidi,
because he's so annoying about ethics!
Now when you taught the Trolley Problem...
did you secretly wish that it could be you
who wound up under the trolley?
Because all your students did!
Whoo!
Oh, Chidi, sorry, I got a joke for you, bud.
Uh, knock-knock.
- Who's there?
You died alone
because you couldn't commit to anyone!
"You died alone because you couldn't commit
to anyone" who?
No...
- Jason Mendoza!
OK, that's all my time.
Let's tear this mother to the ground!
Whoo!
So, maybe I was wrong,
and Michael isn't on our side.
What up, fork sticks?
That was "She Hates Me" by Puddle of Mudd.
Coming up next,
"Grandma Got Run Over By A Reindeer!"
Idiots!
We're going streaking! Ahhhh!
Ugh.
The one time I think someone isn't lying
to me and it bites me in the ash.
I guess Michael really did flip back
to the bad side.
Oh, does one think?
That roast was the meanest thing
I've ever seen
and I once saw a waiter
bring Russell Crowe the wrong tea.
Well, we have no choice.
We go to Shawn and we tell him
that we'll trade secret information
about the reboots
if he'll go easy on us.
And if that doesn't work,
we try to get Janet free
and head to Mindy's. Agreed?
Yeah. Michael sucks now.
He pretended to be our friend,
he's gonna torture us for eternity...
And you know what the worst part is?
He doesn't remember the name
of my favourite football player.
Definitely not the worst part.
It is to me!
"Blake Bortles" is a cool name.
"Derek Bortles" is a dumb name!
♪ Grandma got run over by a reindeer ♪
♪ Walking home from our house
Christmas Eve... ♪
Hey, man, have you told Shawn
how "hugely important" I was yet?
I will get to it. Promise.
Now, you just relax, enjoy yourself,
rip a cat in half
it's a party, Vicky! Come on!
Hey!
- Mleh?
What does Michael keep whispering to you?
- Um...
"Something, something,
Vicky, something, something."
Awww! Can I braid your hair?
- No.
Please?
- No. You know what? I'm good. I got it.
- Ooh!
- Hey!
Help me get these bracelets off Good Janet.
No. Shawn put them on her for a reason.
I'm not overruling the boss.
You're such a suck-up, Gayle.
Can I braid your hair?
- No. Get this... I got it.
Ow!
- OK...
Get your own bracelets, Victoria!
OK, you fat dinks.
The sun is up,
and we're about to close it down
with one last song -
"She Hates Me" by Puddle of Mudd
and "Grandma Got Run Over By A Reindeer"
played at the same time.
Honestly, I'm still partial
to the old-fashioned scorpion diapers.
But you've done great work here.
Can't thank you enough for everything.
Shawn, wait!
- No...
I have some very interesting information
about who's really responsible
for this Neighbourhood.
Shawn! The humans are escaping!
It's Michael. Michael's responsible
for this Neighbourhood
and everything that's happening right now.
Byeee!
Ah, I...
- Bad Janet!
What's cracking, nutbutts?
Call us another train, immediately.
Party's over.
How did they get Janet's bracelets off?
It's literally impossible for a human to do.
It's like breathing underwater,
or driving without texting.
Shawn, I don't want to make any accusations,
but I accuse Vicky.
She asked me to help her take
Janet's bracelets off.
Oh, Vicky, you didn't!
She definitely did.
She's jealous, she's been trying
to sabotage me the entire time.
What, no? He's lying.
OK, I did try to get the bracelets off,
but I couldn't.
Listen to yourself. You sound crazy.
Normally I would love hearing a man
tell a woman she's crazy, but I can't.
You aided the humans just to spite Michael.
You're not a demon. You're a jerk.
Wait! This is a trick!
Michael is the traitor.
I bet they're still here somehow.
This place stretches for a thousand miles.
Fine. Bad Janet?
- What?
- Scan the Neighbourhood, please.
No sign of any humans,
but I actually did find something for Vicky.
What?
Bad Janet, great stuff as always.
- No, duh.
And as for Vicky...
- No, wait!
This is a PR disaster.
We have to keep it all under wraps.
Get her on the train.
And if anyone else says a single word
of what happened here, to anyone...
you will be in a cocoon just like Vicky
and it is gooey in there.
How do we get the humans back from Mindy's?
They bought themselves some time,
but we'll get them.
I'll start the extradition papers.
You stay here. I want every trace
of this Neighbourhood erased.
Oh, that was a bad idea!
That was so scary,
so many different times. I hated that.
You guys!
I was so scared for you!
I told you he was on our side!
You're my friends, and I wanted...
I wanted to save you...
- Hey, it's OK, bud.
This is the best summer ever, you guys!
Ohhh!
Oh!
Oh, Michael,
we never doubted you for a moment.
Thank you, Tahani.
You're lying, though, right?
Yes, I am. I doubted you very strongly.
But then I figured it out.
Kierkegaard, baby!
Leap of faith!
It's better translated as a
"leap into faith."
You remembered!
Can somebody please explain what happened?
And... and can you guys just be...
a tiny bit quieter?
Because, um...
I've been drunk on magnets all day and...
and I can literally
hear every sound in the universe.
Basically, Michael sent us a code,
and we had to crack it.
- I figured out the first clue.
- No, you didn't. I did.
- I was there, though!
- Ooh...
"Blake Bortles" is a cool name.
"Derek Bortles" is a dumb name.
Yes...
"Derek Bortles" is indeed a very dumb name.
It's a clue!
There's no way Michael
would've forgotten the name "Blake Bortles."
You say it a million times a day.
Cos he's the best.
- No, he's not.
And even I know that.
Michael was telling us to use Derek,
Janet's Derek, for something.
There were clues in the roast.
Everybody, quietly, but quickly,
head to the train station.
But let's split up so we don't draw
attention.
Ugh, you guys are the worst conspirators!
OK, what else did Michael say
in the roasts that might be meaningful?
Tahani? Do you remember?
Well, he said my entire life
was pointless and empty.
Yeah, but did he say anything
we don't already know?
Anything that stood out?
Do you know what the worst moment
of Tahani's life was?
When the last song
played at one of her parties
and she would run off and cry because
she still hadn't won her parents' approval.
That was odd.
A host never runs off during their last song
because after it's over
you're supposed to act surprised
when everyone drags you on stage
and showers you with applause.
Maybe Michael wanted us
to wait until the end of the party
when everyone was at their most distracted.
And use Derek to drive the train,
because he has some of Janet's powers.
- Janet?
- Hi... Hi... Hi there.
Janet?
- Yep?
We need you to go get Derek from your void.
OK.
Shoot, where's my void, again? I forget.
Oh, yeah, it's everywhere.
OK, hang on to your...
butt-cheeks.
Ugh... where is he?
Ow! Owwy! Ugh!
I'm never gonna find... oop, there he is!
- Derek.
- Derek!
We need you to drive this train,
and take us to Mindy St Claire's house.
Can you do that?
Derek.
Wait.
Nobody get on that train.
Derek?
- Why not?
Because of what Michael said to me.
You thought you deserved a Medium Place?
You're bad, Eleanor.
This is exactly the place you should be.
Derek!
Michael wants us to stay here,
for some reason.
Eleanor. We have a train, a conductor,
and a safe destination.
I'm gonna tell you the same thing
I told Pippa Middleton right before
we went paragliding in Gibraltar.
"Let's go!"
What? It's what I said.
- Guys, leap of faith.
Michael said we shouldn't get on that train.
Any minute now, those demons
are gonna come looking for us.
Where are we supposed to hide? Oh, no!
Now when you taught the Trolley Problem,
did you secretly wish
that it could be you
who wound up under the trolley?
Because all your students did!
All aboard the...
Shhh!
- DEREK, QUIETLY:... train is here!
It's a train!
- Shhh!
Get onboard!
Actually, Derek...
Derek.
- You're gonna wait
until the last song of the night.
- Derek.
And when you do leave,
you're gonna be flying a solo mission.
Oh! Maximum Derek!
Derek headed off
and when the new train arrived,
the four of us crawled underneath
before any of the drunk demons saw us.
That kept us from being detected
when Bad Janet scanned the Neighbourhood.
We fooled those mo-fos like the chumps
they are!
We got all four clues you left us!
Oh, that's great.
Well, I mean, I actually left you
more than 1,200 clues
because of how primitive your brains are.
But I'm so glad
you got enough to figure it out.
Wait, how did you escape detection though?
Well, I'm not ethically proud of this,
but I framed Vicky.
It was pretty easy - I just kept whispering
things into Janet's ear to make her paranoid.
I'm sorry, what... what did you whisper
to me? I don't remember.
Something, something, Vicky,
something, something.
What does Michael keep whispering to you?
"Something, something, Vicky,
something, something."
Aw!
And that made her try to take
Janet's bracelets off...
which framed her for the escape.
Oh!
Guys, I... I want to apologise
for roasting you earlier.
I had to sell it because everyone
was watching.
It was funny though, right?
Absolutely not!
- The Tahani stuff was perfect. I mean, no.
Guys. Let's just take a moment here.
They're gone.
Which means that we won
and might actually get a chance
to go to the real Good Place.
This is everything we ever wanted.
Speaking of people getting what they want...
I really hope Mindy liked the present
we sent her.
Who are you?
- Derek!
"Thanks for helping us all those times
we showed up."
"To repay you, here's a willing sex robot
and two duffel bags full of cocaine."
There are wind chimes
where my dingdong should be.
I can work with that.
- Alright!