This is daily notes log
for attempt number three
of my Neighbourhood experiment.
Obviously, I hope and assume
this will be the final version.
No, I know it will be.
All the kinks have been worked out.
This is the one.
And after I pull this off,
they're gonna hang my picture
in the Bad Place Hall of Fame
right next to the guy
who invented bees with teeth.
You, Eleanor Shellstrop, are dead.
Cool.
I'm Chris Baker.
I'm your soulmate.
- Bring it in, man.
Sorry, I must ask,
why are you wearing a sash
that says "best person" on it?
Apparently, I am the number one points-getter
in the entire Neighbourhood.
Is that so?
I always have to have my sashes
custom-made
due to my height and bosom size.
Also, apparently,
sashes are out this season.
The diagonal line really draws one's eye
to the chin bloat.
Go fork yourself, you mean giraffe.
Run! Giraffes! Giraffes! Run!
Oh! Mean giraffes are destroying
the Neighbourhood.
Gah!
- Oh, boy.
Hey, robot slave lady?
Busty Alexa?
Oh, Janet?
- Hi, there.
- Gah!
Still not used to it.
Uh, hey, what if I,
an already amazing person
who definitely belongs here,
wanted to learn even more
about how to be a good person?
Is one of these nerds, like, a teacher
or a life coach
or an Instagram fitness model
or something?
Eleanor, I'd like you to meet
Chidi Anagonye.
Chidi, this is Eleanor.
Janet tells me you were
a professor of some kind.
Yes, I was a professor of ethics
and moral philosophy
focusing on deontology.
Hang on one second, Chibi.
This guy's too big of a nerd.
Who else you got?
Michael, what do we do here?
- I don't know.
Apparently, the Bad Place knows
that one of you
actually belongs down there with them,
and they want that person
to get inside the obelisk,
or they're gonna take all of you.
I can't go. I'm too young to die
and too old to eat off the kids' menu.
What a stupid age I am.
I'd never survive down there.
They should take Eleanor.
She's a pear shape.
She'd fit right in.
- Oh, excuse me.
You wish you could have a bite
of this pear.
I'll go. I deserve to go.
You guys can stay.
Holy forking shirt.
You guys, don't you get it?
Michael is torturing us.
That's why our lives have been
so miserable
since the moment we got here.
This isn't the Good Place.
It's the Bad Place.
Ah, farts.
OK, attempt number 11.
Let's focus on the positives.
Eleanor always hates her house.
Tahani always hates Eleanor.
Jason hates being quiet.
Chidi immediately gets a stomach ache.
So there's a lot to work with here.
Hang on one second, Cheeto.
So it's gonna be a hard pass on
Superdork Jones over there.
Anybody else you got to teach me?
You guys ready for our lesson?
We're talking David Hume today,
bundle theory of the self, baby.
Sounds like a real banger,
but you guys gotta scram.
My soulmate has some sort of surprise
planned for me
and he seems very excited about it.
Well, you two are certainly getting
along very well these days.
Yeah, I'm actually kind of
into Sebastian lately.
I mean, he's a little hokey,
but he's growing on me a little bit.
My love, my sweet dewdrop
I have written you a three-hour
spoken-word jazz opera.
Cool!
- ♪ Eleanor, less and more ♪
♪ Who's it for? ♪
♪ For you, my dewdrop
cream of the crop ♪
♪ Top to the bop to the bop to the top ♪
OK, no, no.
- What?
No version of heaven for anyone
would ever include three hours of...
this.
We're in the Bad Place, aren't we?
Damn it.
That was a real trip for biscuits,
and now we're all wet, Daddy-O.
I never even got to play
my stupid triangle.
No, no, no, no
Michael, please, please, please!
Please don't kill me.
I have so much to live for.
I'm sorry, Janet, got to reboot you
every time I start over.
Oh, I know.
I'm not actually upset.
It's just the automatic fail-safe mechanism
that kicks in every time
you approach the plunger.
Go ahead.
Ah.
- Michael, you monster!
Attempt 32.
Attempt 57.
Attempt 99.
Attempt 108.
I've analysed some recent data.
Eleanor always seems to realise
that they're in the Bad Place
- just at the moment that—
- Excuse me.
Sorry, the door was open,
so I just came in.
Did you just say I'm in the Bad Place?
Attempt 109.
I've closed and locked the door.
Yep, and we're ready to go.
This is your soulmate, Greg.
This is your soulmate, Glenn.
This is your soulmate, Tahani.
This is your soulmate, Lerf.
This is your soulmate,
a golden retriever.
Hang on.
Wait a minute.
You know what?
Holy smokes.
This is the Bad Place.
This is the Bad Place!
- The pig's getting angry.
- Bees, bees, bees, bees!
Oh! Oh, this is the Bad Place.
- Shh!
Michael, Michael, if I'm gone,
who will take care of my birds?
Michael, no, no, no, no, no!
I... I'm pregnant.
And it's your baby.
I have tickets to "Hamilton" next week,
and there's a rumour
that Daveed Diggs is coming back.
Janet, we've been through this
hundreds of times.
I mean, can you just chill out?
Is that possible, Janet?
Can you just chill out a little?
Nope, it's gonna be the same every time.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
No, no, no! No, Michael!
Please, please, calm down.
Calm down. Alright...
OK, calm down. Calm down.
I mean, why even bother at this point?
I'm obviously never gonna get it right.
"I'm Eleanor. I'm so smart."
"I'm actually in the Bad Place."
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Shawn still thinks I'm on version two.
I just keep lying to him,
and it's really bad, but I...
I mean, I have to keep trying.
I'm in too deep.
And I'm really fat right now.
I'm stress-eating,
and I'm gaining weight in my thighs.
I mean, look at that...
Ugh.
So sorry. Who are you?
And where am I?
- It doesn't matter.
This one doesn't even count.
Hang on one second, Chili.
This guy sucks.
Who else you got?
I can hear you.
Michael, you simply cannot expect Chidi
to decide whether Eleanor goes to the...
Yo, yo, homies, check it.
There's something messed up
with this place.
We keep fighting with each other.
None of the TVs
get the NFL RedZone channel.
My soulmate doesn't even know
who Blake Bortles is.
I know this sounds crazy
but I think we're in the Bad Place.
Jason figured it out?
Jason?
This is a real low point.
Yeah, this one hurts.
Ow.
OK, this might be the one.
We're a week in.
Chidi's teaching Eleanor, but she hates it.
Tahani still thinks that Jason's a monk.
Everyone's miserable.
I'm so happy.
Fingers crossed.
Vicky, where is everyone?
They're not coming, Michael.
You have lost control of this experiment
so we are on strike
until our demands are met.
I speak for the entire crew, Michael.
We're sick of it.
We can barely remember what we're supposed
to be doing anymore, plus...
I spent weeks
perfecting this excellent Australian accent
I did. And then I never got a chance
to use it.
You're still upset about the size
of your part?
Yes, I want a more important role.
But that's just my demand.
All 318 of us have something
we want to do differently.
Some people want bigger houses.
Gayle wants a different backstory
where she was an MMA fighter?
Gunnar wants to bite and/or nibble
on humans while they sleep.
You do know, Vicky
that if I were to do some of these
that it would be a dead giveaway?
And I can help you explain that to them.
But some of these are doable.
And you're gonna do 'em.
So Aristotle believes your character
is voluntary, because, uh...
are you ignoring me right now?
It's day two of our ethics lessons,
and you're already tuning out?
No, sorry, I just got distracted
for a second.
The last thing I remember you saying is...
nothing.
Can you start from the beginning?
OK, I need a little break.
Can we take a walk or something,
maybe get some clam chowder?
Where is everyone?
- Who knows?
Maybe they finally figured out
clam chowder is disgusting
cos it's basically a savoury latte
with bugs in it.
Is someone smoking a cigar?
Michael really screwed this up.
The regular Bad Place was fine.
If the four-headed flying bears
ain't broke, don't fix 'em.
What was wrong with impaling?
I loved impaling.
Hey, Todd, got a light?
Uh, yeah, obviously I have a light.
You know, you guys aren't
supposed to be smoking.
You're supposed to keep
your human suit on.
Those suits are really itchy for us.
Who even cares if they see us?
They're just gonna get rebooted anyway.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
This is the Bad Place! I forking knew it!
And clam chowder is disgusting.
It's just hot ocean milk
with dead animal croutons.
OK, but what do we do, panic, freak?
I usually panic, but I am happy to freak.
We have to stay cool.
As my mum always used to say
if a cop handcuffs you to a bike rack
there's always something
you can gnaw through.
Your mum always said that?
Come on, brain.
- Janet!
- Hi, there.
How can I help you?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How do we know she's not a part of it?
- We don't, but we gotta risk it.
Janet, can we, like, leave
the Neighbourhood
get as far away as possible?
Is there anywhere we can go?
So, we're in the Bad Place, and I know why.
Almond milk.
I knew it was bad for the environment
but I loved the way
it coated my tongue with a weird film.
Who else is being tortured?
Are we the only two?
I got to assume Jason is as well, Jianyu.
You know him as Jianyu,
but his real name is Jason
and he's a dirt bag from Florida.
What?
- Also, Tahani is a candidate
as far as I'm concerned.
Yesterday, she told me
that she was Taylor Swift's best friend
but Taylor Swift wasn't her best friend.
She sucks.
No offense, but I can't believe
you and I ended up in the same place.
Hey, I'm not thrilled about it either, bud.
I always assumed the afterlife was
full of cool people
not talking sweater vests.
- You...
- We're here.
Aren't trains neat? Choo-choo!
Hi. You gotta help us.
I'm Eleanor. This is Chidi.
And see, we thought we were
in the Good Place
but as it turns out...
- Yeah, guys.
I know. You've been here 15 times already.
What?
Did you bring the cocaine I asked for?
Please tell me you somehow
remembered this time.
Mama needs her medicine.
We've met before?
I'm Janet.
- I know.
Vicky, let's look at the big picture here.
Now, if you all can just stick with my plan
and we pull it off, we'll be heroes.
You could write your own ticket.
You might even land
the "Jared from Subway" account.
Yeah, but I don't think you can pull it off.
You can't even pull off those bow ties.
That was very mean,
but I'm gonna move past that
in the name of unit cohesion.
You're gonna reboot
those four dum-dums one more time
and then I'm taking over.
I'm going to execute my version
of this Neighbourhood.
You see, I've been working on it
while all of your versions fell apart.
This is insubordination.
And if you do not do
what I tell you immediately
you are going down.
That's a complete report of every mistake
you've made, every screw-up
every reboot all laid out
in excruciating detail.
Now, I'm sure your boss would love
to hear all about how
"attempt number 2" is really going.
So actually, if you don't do what I say
you're going down.
Down under.
Is it always the three of us?
It's always at least Eleanor and Janet.
Usually Chidi's in the mix.
Sometimes Jason is here.
One time, Jason and Tahani were here.
But you know what?
No matter what the combo is
I always ask you guys to bring me
cocaine next time, and you never do.
Do you have anything I can snort?
Like a crushed-up aspirin
or some eye-shadow or...
cocaine?
- Still no.
There's only one question
we need to answer right now
and that is, what do we do next?
I mean, this place doesn't seem terrible.
Maybe we should just stay here forever.
- "Maybe we should just stay here forever."
You always say that.
And you always end up going back.
I mean, sometimes you go back
because you feel bad
your friends don't know what you know.
Sometimes you go back
because you walk in on me
while I'm masturbating
and sometimes you go back
because I walk in on you
while I'm masturbating.
But no matter what, you always go back.
You formulate a plan to defeat Michael,
and you head back.
OK, a plan.
We need a plan, but...
What if we come up with a plan
- "What if we come up with a plan"
we've already tried before?
- "we've already tried before?"
Will you please stop that?
- "Will you please stop that?"
Yeah, just to help you out a little,
I've written down every plan
you've ever come up with,
which obviously never worked
because you're here,
and you're back, so good luck.
"Physically attack Michael.
Seduce Michael."
"Make Michael think he's the one
in the Bad Place."
"Catch that magic panda.
Use her powers."
Oh, I'm guessing that was Jason.
That guy has no idea what's going on.
Hello? Hello.
Where is everyone?
Janet?
- Hey, there, Jason.
Oh, hey, homie.
Uh, I mean... Jason?
Who is Jason? I am a monk.
You know what?
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm in a tight spot,
and I could use someone
to bounce some ideas off of, OK?
Oh, yeah, real quick,
you're really in the Bad Place
and you're being tortured.
What?
- I know it says here that we already tried
throwing Tahani under the bus,
but maybe we should revisit that.
Throw her a little bit harder.
Maybe under a bigger bus.
What do you think?
- I think this is pointless.
We're trapped in a warped version
of Nietzsche's eternal recurrence.
Oh, cool, more philosophy.
That'll help us!
Well, don't you see the problem?
We are experiencing karma,
but we can't learn from our mistakes
because our memories keep getting erased.
It's an epistemological nightmare.
Ugh, even your nightmares are boring.
You... you are so mean, Eleanor.
You're just like those childhood bullies
who said I would never get tenure.
And you are so irritating!
In one of these reboots,
I probably strangled you
and then went to the Even Worse Place,
but you know what? I bet it was worth it.
Oh, nice.
Ugh! Sorry, can I just vent to you
for a second? Chidi is so annoying.
I just... I cannot believe that he is the one
I'm stuck here with.
Uh-huh, wow, crazy.
Oh, sorry, Jeez, man, I thought you could
be human for, like, two seconds
and listen to me.
- I have, Eleanor.
I have listened to you talk about Chidi
15 times in 15 different ways.
Let me just cut to the chase.
You two, you got it bad for each other.
No, we don't. Chidi's just a friend.
What am I saying? He's not even a friend.
He's just a weird teacher that I hate.
Dude, I do not want to watch
"Cannonball Run 2" right now.
Alright, what happened in the first one,
so I'm all caught up?
I don't know what's gonna happen to us,
but I need to tell you something.
I love you.
And you don't need to respond
cos I know you have trouble saying
how you feel.
- I love you too.
Very funny
but that... that's obviously not real.
Oh, that's real, baby.
That's real nasty.
Yeah, this was, like, the sixth time
you guys were here.
I saw you getting sexy
the previous three times
so I cut a little hole in the wall
so I could tape you.
Call it my lookin' hole.
- Is that a camera?
- Mindy, you pervert!
How many times have Chidi
and I slept together?
Eight different days, but, like,
20 different sessions.
And how many times did we say... that stuff?
Oh, only once. Oh, God, I hated it.
It, like, really killed the vibe for me.
See, after I watch the porno
I made starring you
I watch you talk about your feelings
to cool down.
It's, like, anti-porn.
I've only ever said "I love you"
to two men my entire life -
Stone Cold Steve Austin
and a guy in a dark club
who I mistook for Stone Cold Steve Austin.
I mean, why would you show me that?
- I don't know.
You guys are, like, trapped here together.
I feel bad.
You know, I'm rooting for you guys.
No, there is no "us guys."
We basically just met each other.
No, Eleanor.
You guys have known each other
a really long time.
Also, it doesn't matter if I told you
that or not
because when Michael finds out
he's failed again, he'll just reboot you.
Chidi, Janet, we're leaving.
I am taking this with me.
"Oh, no, it's my only copy." Don't...
How did it come to this?
I was just trying to do something
innovative and different
that would improve the way
we make humans' lives miserable
for eternity.
Mm, well...
- Shut up.
What are my options?
Do I have any?
I mean, I can't go along with her plan.
It'll be a spectacular failure.
But I can't ignore her
or she'll rat me out to Shawn.
I'm trapped.
- You're saying a lot of words right now
and I only know some of them,
like "rat" and "Jason"
but I know a little wisdom I can give you.
I know everything that happened in your life
and it was all stupid,
so I highly doubt that.
I was a member of a 60-person dance crew
in Jacksonville.
We were called "Dance Dance Resolution:
We Resolve To Dance."
One day, Donkey Doug and I got into a fight
because I'd framed his girlfriend
for boogie board theft
so he started a new dance crew
called "Hashtag DougLife"
and immediately challenged us
to a dance-off.
He said, "Meet us inside the abandoned
orange juice factory at midnight."
That night, as the clock struck 12:00,
me and my crew came together
with a determination we had
never shown before
and slashed all their tyres.
It was dope.
The end.
By Jason Mendoza.
You know, that inane story
actually contains a bit of good advice.
Thank you, Jason.
- You got it, homie.
I give good advice!
Guess that's why I'm in the Good Place.
Oh, there you guys are.
- No.
Stop, no more lies.
Jason, get over here.
That's right. We know his name is Jason,
not Jianyu.
We know everything.
I don't understand much of it,
but, yeah, I know it.
Your sick torture plan is not working, OK?
Cos we keep figuring out your little puzzle.
We're winning, which means you're losing.
So you have two choices here, buddy.
Keep failing over and over
or realise we're actually
the ones with all the power here.
Yeah, no, uh...
We're on the same page.
- What?
I want to team up with you guys.
What? Why? You do? What?
I'm in a bit of a bind,
and I could use some back-up
or as Jason put it, um...
I need a new dance crew.
So, what do you say?
New best friends?
Stop it...