So, Michael, you're saying there's
a new angle I should consider in this case?
Love that. Major drama.
Spill the tea, sweetheart.
The premise of our system is that a person's
score during her time on Earth
is final and inarguable.
But because of my accidental experiment
these four humans got better
after they died -
that's not supposed to be possible.
Over and over again, I watched as they became
thoughtful and generous and...
and caring, and... and think about
where they started.
Uh, Jason?
Growing up in Jacksonville, what did you do
for fun after school, every day?
Me and my friends whipped empty
spray paint cans at flamingos.
And now he's so much better.
I was already pretty good.
When I was six, I hit one right on the butt.
OK, let the immortal beings talk, darling.
So, they got better in your little
pretend world.
That doesn't prove anything
about what they were like on Earth.
No, see, I think it does prove something.
If I'm right, the system
by which we judge humans
the very method we use to deem them
good or bad
is so fundamentally flawed and unreasonable
that hundreds of millions of people
have been wrongly condemned
to an eternity of torture.
Damn! That was intense!
Look at my arm, y'all!
Look, I got goosebumps.
Huh, yeah.
Doesn't happen very often.
Wow. So, you saw your parents in the test?
Yes.
And I immediately fell right back
into my old pattern.
Desperately trying to impress them
and earn their admiration.
But then I heard this little voice
in my head saying
"Tahani. Don't do this."
The little voice in your head sounds like the
old lady from Downton Abbey?
Oh, yes, sorry.
Maggie Smith is my Godmother.
Anyway, I took a deep breath.
Told them I ate a Cheeto and walked away.
Man!
You have made so much progress.
I'm proud of you, hot stuff.
Whatever progress I have made
it's because you and I have become mates.
That's British for "friends."
- No, I know.
Ooh, how are your shoulders so comfy?
Well, I was voted "best shoulders"
by British Vogue four years in a row.
I get it. You're perfect.
Eleanor... I'm kidding.
I was just taking the piss out of myself.
It was only two years.
Just doubled it... for humour.
OK.
Man, think about everything
that's happened to us.
We died, Michael tortured us,
we teamed up with him...
we escaped, we went through the portal
the Judge ruled against us,
then Michael showed up.
This has been one of the craziest years
of my life.
"One of"?
Yeah. I'm not sure what I would do
if one more insane thing happened.
Hi, Jason.
I love you.
Oh, word?
Word.
I've been avoiding telling you.
My excuse was that I needed time
to evaluate my complex feelings
but that was just a rationalisation.
Hey, I guess I learned how to
rationalise too.
That's neat.
This might be the last time I ever
get to talk to you, so there it is.
I love you.
And I hereby stop avoiding this topic
and rationalizing it by saying the situation
is complicated.
Or that my brain is grinding like a fork
in a garbage disposal.
Alright.
Whatever.
You're not really a part of this, Chidi.
Hey.
Guess what?
I think I love you too, girl.
I'm not a girl.
I'm also not just a "Janet" anymore.
I don't know what I am.
Hey, man. What's up?
Hot diggity dog!
Oh, no!
Now the thing I said right after we kissed
will always be, "Hot diggity dog!"
Whatever.
It was an honest reaction. I stand by it.
Hi, guys, couple quick announcements.
Would anyone eat chips and guac
if I put it out?
It's good. It's homemade.
No takers?
Alright - second thing, we figured out a plan
to save your souls.
For the time being, the Judge
is gonna put you in your own Medium Places
like Mindy St Claire.
And while you're there,
I'll keep working every angle I can think of
to get you guys into the Good Place for real.
This is great. So, we'd all be together?
Oh, no, that's the thing about Medium Places.
It has to be tailored to what's medium
for the individuals
so if you're all together, it ain't medium.
How much time will we be alone?
Hard to say. Uh, could be a month.
Could be... a million years.
So, between a month and a million years.
Some...
Yeah.
- Give or take.
Somewhere in there.
Come on, you guys.
I know this isn't perfect but I need more
time to build my case, and it's either this
or back to the Bad Place.
- Yeah.
I'll say it.
Both those options suck.
OK, I'm sorry if that's blunt, Your Honour,
but it's true.
Also, Chidi just laid one on me,
so I'm kinda dizzy.
You two kissed?
Hot diggity dog!
That's what I said!
The point is, we've all gotten better.
Why should we have to go live alone
in a boring void
because of a messed-up system?
How is that justice?
OK, slow your roll there, Erin Brockovich.
First of all, y'all didn't get good enough
to pass the tests I just gave you.
Second, I still believe that the only reason
that you improved
in Michael's fake Neighbourhood
is because you thought there was a reward
at the end of the rainbow.
You're supposed to do good things
because you're good
not because you're seeking moral dessert.
And I still believe that they would've
become good people
if they'd just gotten a...
a push in the right direction.
Oh, no!
Nope. Nope. Absolutely not.
It's a little crazy.
- A little bit crazy? It's Looney Tunes.
What are they talking about?
- No idea.
It sets a very dangerous precedent.
- It's only four people.
And it's clearly the best way
to see if bad people can become good
without knowing anything about
what's waiting for them in the afterlife.
Shotgun!
Whatever they're talking about,
if there's a shotgun, I call shotgun.
It's never gonna work, man.
If it doesn't, then they go right back
to the Bad Place.
No one gets hurt
except them. Forever.
And me, I assume, also... forever.
Mmmm...
ughhhhh...
eeeuuuoww...
OK, let's do it.
Yes!
I don't know why,
I'm just feeling kinda funky.
But there have to be strict rules,
otherwise the results will be tainted
and I reserve the right to change my mind
at any point.
About what? Would someone who's not
an eternal being
please explain to me what the f...
Why are you like this?
Excuse me? "Why am I like this?"
You don't know me, dude.
You don't know what I'm like.
Look what you made me do, jagoff.
Ugh...
- Look out!
- Uh-oh.
Holy crap.
I just almost died.
She needs to know what was said.
That was so unfair.
- First of all, this was just yesterday.
God, Eleanor. Take longer next time.
Oh, you look like crap.
I was outside the supermarket arguing
with that little environmental twerp.
Ugh, I hate that guy.
Really? That skinny little hippie body
kinda turns me on.
Gross.
Guys, listen! I dropped the margarita mix
and when I went to pick it up
a bunch of shopping carts came right at me,
and I was just frozen.
And then someone pushed me out of the way
and the carts got, like, demolished
by a truck.
I mean, I could've died.
Oh, my God.
- Whoa.
That's crazy.
So, is the margarita mix, like, gone?
I had a near-death experience recently.
You know that old warehouse that burned down
last month and like, four people died?
That building is, like, right by
my old dentist.
If I still went to that dentist,
and I had an appointment that day
I would've been, like... right near there.
I was in Syracuse, New York
like, two weeks before 9/11.
No way!
- Yeah.
Fourteen days.
I can't believe we all almost died.
- I know!
I'm like...
My name is Eleanor Shellstrop.
And I think I might be a monster.
I'm rude. I'm selfish.
I cyber-bullied Ryan Lochte
until he quit Instagram.
But something happened to me today
and from now on I'm gonna try to become
a better, kinder, more generous person.
Hey! Can I use your credit card?
You know what? Yes, you can.
Cool. It's for porn.
I already used it.
Hey.
You look happy.
Did you get laid last night?
I didn't.
Tried. Hard.
With this chick that I met
after I followed her into a yoga class
but she wasn't into it.
Maced me - right in the eyes.
Stung like hell.
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah. Hey.
Listen, dude.
What you're doing here
selling fake medicine to people,
tricking them...
is wrong.
Yeah. And?
I can't be a part of it anymore.
I'm trying to become a better person...
and as long as I work here...
Yeah, sure, fine, whatever, you quit.
Who cares? Give me your company ID.
Thank you.
And your parking pass.
And your panties, please.
Dude!
- What? Come on.
I had to try.
By the way, technically
that is not sexual harassment
because she doesn't work here anymore.
- You're wearing a wire?
Yeah. Company's being investigated for fraud
so I'm helping the feds bring everyone down.
Good timing on your part.
Thank you?
- No.
Thank you...
for wearing open-toed shoes today.
Wow.
- Dude. Get help.
I'm becoming a better person.
You should too.
Hey, Eleanor!
Do you want to come to Lauren's baby shower?
Do you wanna chew on my ass...
sss...
sortment of brownies
that I will be bringing to Lauren's
baby shower?
Sure.
Hi, there. Do you have a second
to talk about the environment?
Hey. Remember me?
Ah! Don't hurt me!
My bones are brittle.
I have a calcium deficiency.
No, I'm not gonna hurt you, man.
I came to apologise.
There, I did it.
I apologised.
No, you didn't.
- Yes, I did, assface!
Mm... nope. You're right. I didn't.
I apologise for being mean to you,
like a thousand times.
There's really no excuse.
Thanks.
Apology accepted.
OK.
Uh, what's happening? I'm scared.
Hey, I'm on kind of, like,
a self-improvement kick.
Do you think you could help me out?
Teach me to get all horny for the environment
or whatever?
Hey, everyone. This is Eleanor.
She's joining the team.
Hi.
Welcome.
- Nice to meet you. Hi.
Alright, Eleanor!
♪ There is a sign among the remnants ♪
♪ Of all our words, best left unsaid ♪
♪ And when the truth flies in our direction ♪
♪ Do we work it through ♪
♪ Or lose our heads ♪
♪ Maybe, maybe, maybe ♪
♪ We're strong ♪
♪ But maybe, maybe, maybe we're wrong. ♪
Mm. Babes, get in on these nachos,
they're delish.
Mm-hm.
- I'm actually trying to eat vegetarian.
Ew! Why?
Is it because you feel bad
for all the widdle animals
with their cute widdle faces
because people stuff them into tiny cages
just so that we can eat them?
Yeah. That's exactly why, actually.
Also, it's the easiest way to lower
your carbon foot print
not eating meat.
- What?
OK, guys, um...
Can I say something for a second?
I love you.
- Aw!
I do. I mean, I went through a really
rough time last year
with the whole "Dress Bitch" thing and people
selling t-shirts with my face on them
but you two stuck by me.
I love you, you dumb sluts!
- Aaaah!
Come on!
OK, there's probably something
we should tell you.
Or not. We could also not.
We have to. It's the right thing to do.
I tore your dress. And then I lied about it.
And then Brittany and I were the ones
who made and sold the t-shirts.
But... we did not keep the money.
Yes, we did. We kept all the money.
And I'm really sorry.
OK.
That took a lot of courage for you
to admit that.
Mm-hm.
- And I admire your honesty.
You stupid skank!
How could you do that to me?
I hate you! You're both disgusting hogs
and I want you to move out
of my apartment, forever!
Literally starting right now!
I'm still really glad we told the truth.
Cooooool.
Mm.
OK, steamed vegetable medley and ice water.
Can I just get the check?
And can you throw these plants in the trash?
♪ For such a long time now ♪
♪ We're doing battle with our own
familiar inhibitions ♪
♪ Far away from home ♪
♪ Our trusty compass fails to find this
strange and new position ♪
♪ Maybe, maybe, maybe we're strong ♪
♪ But maybe, maybe, maybe we're strong ♪
♪ But maybe, maybe, maybe we're wrong. ♪
Damn it!
They're suing you?
This chick is claiming she has whiplash.
She wasn't in the car when I hit it.
This is on you.
You should've pretended like
you didn't see it and walked away.
Like everyone else does.
I know! I've hit your car like six times
and never said anything.
But I'm trying to be good.
How's that working out for you?
It's open, dummy!
Eleanor! Where have you been?
Oh, hey, man.
Sorry, it's been a crazy month, you know?
Moving was a hassle,
and I'm in the middle of a lawsuit
and I ate vegetables for the first time
and I got diarrhoea for, like, a week.
Uh... I know we don't pay a lot
but this is a job
and we need to know we can count on you.
We're meeting tonight to discuss long-term
strategy for the organisation.
Dude, dude, dude, dude...
- I really think it would be—
dude, dude, dude. Oh, sorry to interrupt
whatever boring crap this is
but, dude, you need to get dressed.
I got tickets to Taylor Splift
the Taylor Swift reggae cover band.
They're terrible. It's gonna be amazing!
Yeah, that sounds like more fun.
I'm-a do that.
- Eleanor!
What! What, dude?
I've been nothing but good for, like,
six months
and all I have to show for it
is this crummy apartment
a lawsuit, a loose caboose,
and an overdrawn bank account.
Being good is for suckers.
What do you even get out of it?
A feeling of fulfillment... in your soul.
Gross. That's the grossest sentence
I've ever heard.
OK? I quit.
Eat my farts, Benedict Cumberbatch.
Whew!
I still think he's kinda hot.
I guess, in like a sick Victorian boy
kinda way.
Ooh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I want to, like, feed him soup.
It is good to have you back.
You are one of the most gifted con-women
I have ever watched sleep through her window.
Thanks, bud. So, tell me about
the new business.
We sell classes at a for-profit university
and the classes train people how to sell
supplements.
So, it's a ponzi scheme
within a ponzi scheme.
That sounds kinda dicey.
Oh, it's super dicey.
But I'm in witness protection so technically
I can't be convicted of any crime.
Well, that's definitely not true,
but I also don't care.
Which one's my desk?
You realise what the problem is, right?
- Yes.
But there's no way to help.
I'm only giving that guy three stars
cos he didn't let me stick my head out
the moonroof.
Yeah!
Dude, my boyfriend just texted.
His wife's out of town,
so I'm gonna head over there.
Mwah!
What? That's lame. Boo!
Happy birthday!
Hello, bartender.
One alcohol drink, please.
It's my birthday, if you wanna
give it to me for free.
I always say that,
but it actually is my birthday.
Last year on my birthday, I almost died
and then I did a bunch of stuff
that was good, but weird
and then I stopped, and now I'm here.
Sounds like you had a pretty crazy year.
Hm.
- Wanna talk about it?
And in the end, Anthony Anderson
and Jerry O'Connell
started a successful shampoo company
and you see the kangaroo
jumping around Australia.
That is the plot to the movie
"Kangaroo Jack."
Why'd I tell you that?
It's unclear.
You know, the thing is...
the problem, really, with being a do-gooder?
What's that?
- No one cares.
I mean some people care a little bit.
The twerpy little twerps
from the environmental place, they care
but I was a good person for six months.
That's, like, five years.
And it felt OK but not as good
as I thought it would.
And what did I get for it?
Ah, see? Now you're talking about
moral dessert.
Exactly.
Wait. I am? What?
"Moral dessert" is the concept that if you
act with virtue, you deserve a reward.
Right. I did a bunch of good stuff.
I didn't get jack. Not fair, universe!
Alright, even if the universe
did function that way
who's to say that you didn't dig yourself
such a deep hole
over the first 34 years of your life
that the six months you spent being good
weren't enough to get you out of that hole?
See, there's a lot of great writing
about this, if you're interested.
Who died and made you in charge
of frickin' every...
knowing everything.
Well, you know, I recently got sort of into
ethics and moral philosophy.
You sound like a real live wire.
Whatevs.
The point is,
if I'm not gonna get rewarded somehow
with, like, a tiara
or one of those diagonal award belts.
Sash.
- Sure.
- Then why should I do good things?
You know, I had a friend that said whenever
she was doing something bad
she'd hear this... this little voice
in her head.
Distant little voice saying,
"Oh, come on now, you know this is wrong."
And then when she started doing good things,
that voice went away.
It was a relief.
Your friend sounds like
she's one pickle short of a pickle party.
I might have alcohol poisoning.
She was a little rough
around the edges, but...
she was also a really good person.
When she tried.
See, I think that little voice
was her conscience
trying to guide her in the right direction.
I gotta go home. What do I owe ya?
The real question, Eleanor
is what do we owe to each other?
What?
Did I sell you a drink? Am I a bartender?
Drinks are on me.
Good luck.
Ow...
Anybody notice I was gone?
Nope.
What do we owe to each other?
That is the question Tim Scanlon asked
decades ago
and it is the question I will try to answer
over the next three hours.
Ugh. No, thanks.
We all have a voice in our head.
That voice doesn't tell us what to do,
or not do
but it does warn us when we do things
that don't feel good or right.
The difference between...
- The term "reasonable."
What does it mean to be a reasonable person?
I may have a different definition
of reasonable...
So, why do it then?
Why choose to be good every day
if there is no guaranteed reward
we can count on, now or in the afterlife?
I argue that we choose to be good
because of our bonds with other people
and our innate desire
to treat them with dignity.
At the intersection of empathy and ethics
is the realisation
that we are not in this alone.
Thank you.
Hey, dog bait.
Didn't you get my message? Let's go!
Time is booze.
Yeah, no thanks. I'm...
going somewhere else.
Hi.
- G'day.
Where you headed?
- Saint John's University, please.
No worries.
Do you wanna talk to God?
What? No. Get away from me, freak.
Hi.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Office hours are on Tuesday.
Oh, I... I'm not a student.
Are you Chidi Ana... Kendrick?
Anagonye. And yes.
From the long, nerdy video about
the little voice that tells you to be good?
From the Kissac Foundation lecture series
on the practical applications
of ethical theory - yes.
Great. Hi.
My name is Eleanor Shellstrop.
Can we talk?
OK.
Here we go.