We're on the same page.
I wanna team up with you guys.
What? Why? You do? What?
I'm in a bit of a bind
and I could use some back-up.
So, what do you say? New best friends?
Stop it.
You wanna team up?
You've been torturing us
and lying about it.
Let's not get all caught up
on who lied to who
or which one of us created
an entire fake reality
in order to cause eternal misery
for the others.
That's ancient history.
It was happening until 20 seconds ago.
The point is that...
circumstances have changed.
And now, all of us teaming up
is our best option.
I love being on teams!
Oh, we need a team name.
Um...
the Bobcats.
- Great.
Slow down, ding-dong.
He wouldn't offer us a deal for no reason.
He needs us.
Why?
Because, as you said, you keep beating me.
Look, I built this Neighbourhood
as a way to torture the four of you
psychologically for thousands of years.
And you keep figuring it out
and taking all the fun out of it.
Fun?
Today, there was a new development
that really chapped my nips.
One of my employees is blackmailing me.
Vicky. She runs the clam chowder place
in the main square -
"A Little Bit Chowder Now".
- Oh, the place with the chowder fountain.
- No.
That's "Pump Up the Clam."
"A Little Bit Chowder Now"
has the lazy river of chowder.
Ugh! How did we ever think
this was the Good Place?
Vicky thinks that she can run
this Neighbourhood better than I can.
And she wants to start her version
in 30 minutes.
I'm supposed to reboot you,
erase your memory
and turn control over to her.
How are we supposed to team up
with you if you wipe our memories again?
Easy. I'm not going to.
You're going to act like
you've been rebooted
and pretend that Vicky
and the others are torturing you.
But then, on your own time, in private
you can study ethics, ogle mailmen
do whatever you want.
- Can I play iPad?
Sure you can, buddy.
- Yes!
Guys, there's no debate here.
My boss gave me two chances
to make this work.
Suffice to say, I tried more than two times.
If he finds out, we're all in hot water.
Literally.
They will boil us.
We will be the main ingredient
in a chowder of pain.
Oh, dear.
- But if you help me
you stop being tortured
the Neighbourhood looks like it's working,
and I never get in trouble with my boss.
Everybody's happy.
Who's in?
Human meeting. Bedroom. Now.
Oh, yeah, um, that whole no-stair thing,
that was part of the torture.
Let me... uh...
Son of a bench.
Anyone have any ideas?
- You know, believe it or not
I actually found myself
in a very similar situation
a few years ago, except in that instance,
Michael was Javier Bardem
and the Bad Place was
Vanessa Redgrave's panic room.
OK, stop talking.
Do not talk again for 100 hours.
What do we do?
- We team up with Michael.
OK, hot take, but I like your confidence.
Tell me why.
He has a bow tie.
- Oh, no.
I always trust dudes in bow ties.
Once, this guy in a bow tie
came up to me at the gun range
in a Jacksonville bus station
and said he'd give me 600 dollars
if I put these weird turtles in my duffle bag
and brought them to Daytona Beach.
I needed money at the time
cos I had just bet my friend Donkey Doug
that I could chug a whole bottle of
Dan Marino cologne and not yarf.
And I lost!
So I put the turties in my bag
I hotwired a swamp boat to Daytona
and the guy paid me the 600 dollars.
My point is, you always trust dudes
in bow ties.
Aaaah!
Look, Michael's a liar. I know liars.
It was my job to trick people
into buying fake medicine
and I was the top salesperson
seven years in a row.
I thought you only worked there five years.
Proves my point! This is a trick.
There's no way we trust him.
- I agree.
He could be lying about this whole thing.
For all we know, you three are
in the Bad Place
and I'm up in the Good Place,
where I belong, being tested.
How would that even...?
I don't know but it's possible.
Before we do anything,
we need more information.
We should ask him every question
we can think of.
Yes.
- Yes, we shall grill him
like the flank of an Iberian piglet.
I'm sorry, has it been 100 hours?
OK, man. We got questions.
First off, how can we possibly trust you?
You can't. But you have to.
Logically, you shouldn't
but you have no choice.
I mean, I wouldn't, if I were you.
It's a crazy thing to do.
But you gotta.
- What happens if we don't?
Most likely, I reboot you once more
you figure it out again, Vicky tells my boss.
He shuts everything down.
I get punished, you end up spending
the rest of eternity in the real Bad Place
up to your necks
in a volcano full of scorpions.
I'll tell you what I want to know right now
before we go any further.
Did the Jacksonville Jaguars win
the Super Bowl last year?
Oh, you're serious. Uh, no.
Will they ever win the Super Bowl?
- Jason, I can't predict the future.
But no. They won't.
OK, well I just have, like
12 more Jaguar questions—
- No, you don't.
- Hey, Janet?
- Hi, there.
Do you have something shiny
Jason can play with?
How many different versions
of this place have we been through?
Uh, let's see... 802.
The longest one was 11 months.
Uh, this current one has only been
going for one week.
Boy, you guys barely know each other.
It's gonna make this tough.
What's that super tiny line?
That's the shortest one, eight seconds.
It was a butt-reboot.
I sat on the activator by mistake.
Michael, was I also rebooted 802 times?
- Yes, why?
Every time a Janet is rebooted
she increases her social awareness
and abilities.
I might be the most advanced Janet
in the universe.
Oh.
So, Janet isn't with you?
No.
There has to be a Janet
in every Neighbourhood, good and bad.
This one is an actual Good Place Janet
that I stole to help sell the ruse.
I guess it didn't work, though.
Because you keep failing.
Yes, thank you.
- You're welcome.
If you're not human
why do you look like us?
Everyone in the Bad Place Bureau
of Human Affairs
gets randomly assigned a human body
so we can get the feel
of how best to torture you.
I gotta say, it took me a long time
to get used to the hanging bits.
Gross.
Oh, get your mind out of the gutter,
Eleanor.
I was talking about my testicles.
What about soulmates? Are they real?
I don't know. I hope not.
I mean, pretty lame idea, if you ask me.
Mindy St Claire's is fake, I bet.
No, the Medium Place is real.
So annoying how you managed
to slip away from me, all those times.
Why even tell us about any real thing?
Why not just lie about all of it?
Lies are always more convincing
when they're closer to the truth.
That's true. I crashed a lot
of open-bar weddings
as Eileen Shelbourne.
Even dated a groomsman for a few months
so I had to keep the name,
and he got "Eileen" tattooed on his neck.
Seriously?
How are she and I in the same place?
- Oh, get over yourself.
Trust me, don't trust me, it doesn't matter.
We're running out of time,
and I'm your only option.
"We're running out of time
and I'm your only option?"
A lot of guys your age said that to me
just as the bar was about to close.
But I never settled for them.
Because my ex-boyfriend lived nearby,
he was obsessed with me
and he never slept because he was
addicted to Adderall.
There is always another option.
And yes, I probably could have just said
that last part but whatever, don't judge me.
You guys do whatever you want.
I'm out.
- No!
My plan only works if all four of you
are on board.
Then you better get cracking
on a new plan, pally
because so far, I haven't heard a single
good reason why I should help you.
Alright, how about this?
You help me trick Vicky
and all those other goons
I can get you to the real Good Place.
There's a way to get to the real Good Place?
It's complicated.
It may take a while to arrange
especially since I'll have to do it
in secret but yes, yes, there is
a potential method of transportation.
Well, is it nice?
Is there a business class?
Can I pre-board?
Yeah, let's not worry about that right now.
I can get us there.
- "Us"?
You, Mr "Diabolical Torture Guy"
are gonna try
to join us in the Good Place?
- Yeah.
If I stay in the Bad Place, I'm doomed.
But if I rescue four pitiful,
foul-smelling humans
from eternal damnation
hit 'em with the big puppy dog eyes.
"Please, sir, take pity on me, I've changed"
and all that crap
maybe I can earn a spot, too.
We didn't deserve the Good Place
based on our time on Earth.
Will they even let us stay?
I gotta be honest, I have no idea.
But at least if you help me fool Vicky
your brains don't get erased every two weeks.
OK, all humans who have not
already been suckered by Michael
another team meeting.
This is definitely a trap.
We figured out his game every time,
and now he's just trying
a new way to mess with us.
Teaming up with a demon is insane.
Maybe.
But I think we have to do it.
Are you forking kidding me right now?
You take a half an hour to pick out
a turtleneck
and yet this you're sure about?
OK, look, I spent my whole life trying
to learn about right and wrong
and apparently, I failed.
I want us to get better
and I want us to stay that way.
You understand that, right, Tahani?
- I understand nothing.
Hey! Same here!
- Michael, there's been a mistake.
I belong in the Good Place.
The real one with the good people.
Who do I speak to about correcting this?
- Me, and you're wrong.
Very well.
I would like to speak to your manager.
Listen, sweetheart, you've only been
in this timeline for about a week.
So I think I'm gonna fast forward
things a bit.
There's a very good reason
why you ended up here.
You never cared about the people
you were helping.
You did it only for fame or status
or to spite your family.
That is utter tosh! I had my flaws,
just like anyone else
but I raised billions for charity.
I was a good person and I defy you
or anyone else to prove otherwise.
You know, in all the reboots,
I never showed you how you died.
I was saving it in case I ever needed
to really make you miserable.
But it's hilarious.
Of course, I mean sad.
But it might help you come to grips
with who you really were.
Do you want to remember it?
Tahani Al-Jamil, social activist
philanthropist
neck model and now cover girl for
"International Sophisticate Magazine."
The issue hits luxury news stands
this week
and regular news stands
the week after.
Tahani, welcome.
- Oh, it's such an honour.
I have long dreamt of being one
of the women or yachts
who grace your cover.
Let's begin with your sister, Kamilah.
A woman who as you know was offered
the spot on our cover but turned it down.
I actually didn't know that.
Please, carry on.
Well, next week, Kamilah will travel
to Cleveland, Ohio
to become the youngest person ever
inducted into the Rock 'n Roll Hall of Fame.
Remarkable.
Is there a question?
Don't you find that remarkable?
Kamilah is very impressive.
As you know, she released
her debut album only six months ago
and yet, the critics thought
it was so brilliant
that the Hall of Fame decided
to waive its 25-year waiting period.
Sadly, I will not be attending
the ceremony
because I will be in Haiti
on a relief mission.
Perhaps we should talk more about that.
- Perhaps we should.
But first, another question about Kamilah.
Don't you think she
and I would be friends?
We have a lot in common,
we are both Capricorn
and we're both only children.
I'm sorry, I forgot about you.
Hey, can I get an Irish enema?
That's Baileys and Sprite in a ziploc bag.
Excuse me,
do I look like a waitress to you?
Yeah.
Here.
Kamilah! Congratulations.
You have all the attention.
Once again.
- Who are you?
Really?
- Good Lord.
Tahani!
You're a cocktail waitress now.
Honestly, I think
this is the right move for you.
No, it's just that my own sister didn't
even deign to invite me to her little soiree.
So I had to weasel my way
in here like some common... weasel.
I was supposed to be in Haiti
being photographed helping people
but instead I delayed my trip by a day
to come here and tell you off.
No, you came to do
what you always do
make a scene and embarrass yourself.
So I'm just an embarrassment to you?
Is that what you think of me?
Honestly, I don't really think about you.
No! Ow.
That's it. Ah!
I'll bring you down!
Come on.
Come on!
Come down to the ground where you
belong
- Oh, no.
- Mm.
I died in Cleveland?
I don't think that should be
your biggest takeaway from that story.
Is that really all I cared about?
Just outshining my sister
and gaining praise and acclaim?
I mean, I did gain praise and acclaim.
You know, I dare say on some occasions
more praise and acclaim
than my sister, Kamilah, so...
Oh.
Oh, I see.
Oh, God.
- Oh, come on, now.
It's not all bad.
Imagine you're me
and you're designing a torture chamber
for people who think that they belong
in the Good Place.
I mean, you were perfect.
But I've always wanted
to be perfect at something
I just never thought
it would be the perfect stooge.
I want to do it.
I want to become the person
I pretended to be.
I agree with Chidi.
We should team up with Michael
and all try to build a better Tahani.
Great.
Yet again, it's everyone against Eleanor.
Because everyone
except Eleanor is an idiot.
Why am I the only person who clearly sees
what's going on here?
It's not that we don't understand the risks,
we just wanna become better people
and this is our best chance.
Oh, I get it.
'Cos you're so much better than me.
That's what this is about?
- Hang on, don't lash out at us
just because of your innate distrust.
- Lash out?
No, it's not about who's better.
I have no idea what's going on
right now, but everyone else is talking
and I think I should, too!
What is so funny?
I'm sorry, I shouldn't be laughing.
How do I explain this?
I'm basically an exterminator,
and you're cockroaches.
My job was to squish you
and poison you and yet, somehow
my very survival now depends on you,
the cockroaches, agreeing to help me.
That's funny.
- We're cockroaches to you?
Yeah. Or dung beetles.
I don't know.
Something small and gross
that creeps on the ground in its own filth.
Just being honest.
OK, OK, OK.
Alright, forget about him.
Forget about him, focus on us.
Kant wrote it is our duty
to improve ourselves.
So whatever Michael's reasons
for doing this, he's giving us
the best chance to improve ourselves.
OK, I have to admit,
you're making a lot of sense right now.
I need to just untangle all of this.
Give me a minute to think about it alone.
OK.
- Janet?
- Hi, there.
Call me a train.
Fill it to the brim with cocaine.
I'm going back to Mindy St. Clair's house.
Gonna bail, huh?
- Hm? No.
- Why... why would you say that?
- Well...
you got a bag full of clothes,
you stuffed a bunch of pillows
and a mop in your bed
to make it look like you're asleep
and you're literally sneaking out
the back gate.
OK.
I'm going to Mindy's.
I don't want to live forever in a boring,
beige house with a weird, horny cokehead
but look at what you're asking me to do.
Make a deal with an actual devil
so that I can then do homework in secret.
And by the way, you're not my friends,
man.
We've known each other for, like, a
week.
You know it's more than that.
We've been through some version
of this 800 different times.
And who cares that it's only been a week?
How long do you have to know someone
before you do the right thing?
Nine weeks, minimum.
- OK.
Look, bro, I don't owe you anything.
I gotta do what's right for me.
You can come with me if you want.
I got another mop we can put in the bed.
Good luck.
I got a couple more questions.
- Sure.
Take your time.
We're not in a hurry or anything.
How many times in all the reboots
did I ask Chidi for help
he refused to help me,
and then I had to get better on my own?
Never.
He always helped you.
God. Really?
Yep. No matter how I set it up
you found him,
confessed you didn't belong
asked him for help,
and he said yes.
Now his agreeing to help
was part of my plan.
What wasn't part of my plan
was it actually working.
Drove me nuts.
Pesky little nerd.
Stuck with you and always helped you
overcome your biggest problem.
Assuming that's my selfishness.
- No.
No, no, no.
It's that you never found a haircut
that framed your face properly.
Yes, your selfishness.
I'm not that selfish.
Eleanor, your cocaine
and escape train are ready.
- Not now.
OK.
I think Michael is a liar.
I think there's a 99% chance
he's forking with us.
But he's asking us for help,
so we should help him.
Because that's what Chidi would do.
That's what Chidi would do for me
or for any of us.
It's what I am doing.
- I know.
It's just you're talking about me
like I'm not here or something
and that just makes me feel weird.
Alright.
We're all in.
We'll help you.
You finally listened to reason.
- On one condition.
You wanna be on our team,
you gotta be on our team.
Which means the professor over here
is gonna give us all lessons
on how to be better people.
Including you.
Oh, no.
No, I won't be taking any classes.
I'm an immortal being with abilities
you can only dream
Yeah, and we're in Arizona, dirtbag.
A human turtleneck, a narcissistic monster
and literally the dumbest person
I've ever met.
And who am I? Describe me now.
We are all going to take classes.
We are all going to improve.
And the second you betray us
I walk into Vicky's stinky
chowder restaurant and tell her everything.
You agree to those terms,
and you can join us on Team Cockroach.
So what's it gonna be?
You're running out of time.
And we're your only option.
So it's all frozen yogurt places now, huh?
Yeah, yogurt was what we started with.
A lot of us like the first version best
so we went back to 322
perfectly matched human souls,
blended together in a blissful
harmonic balance.
- Well done.
I've only given this opening day tour
to you like, 800 times.
Hey, how's this for my
oh-my-God-I'm-in-Heaven face?
Not bad.
- Right? I'm a pretty good liar.
You really are.
I've always admired that about you.
Thank you, Michael.
Now I wanna introduce someone
that you're gonna get to know very well.
She was the top point getter,
so she'll be helping me out
around the Neighbourhood,
kind of like your mayor.
Vicky Sengupta!
Vicky, would you like to say a few words?
Actually, Michael,
I'd like to sing a few words. Janet.
Hit it!
♪ At first I was afraid, I was petrified ♪
♪ Kept thinking I could never live ♪
♪ Without you by my side ♪
♪ Then I spent so many nights ♪
♪ Thinking how you did me wrong
And I grew strong ♪
♪ And I learned how to get along ♪
♪ And now you're back from outer space ♪
♪ I just walked in to find you here
with that sad look upon your face ♪
♪ I should have changed that stupid lock
should have made you leave your key ♪
♪ If I'd known for just one second ♪
♪ You'd be back to bother me
and so now go! ♪
I don't know
how long I can keep this up.
I nearly cracked about 50 times.
What are you talking about,
so far this reboot is dope.
There's fro-yo, there's fro-yo toppings and—
Oh, spoons!
Alright.
We should have a few hours to ourselves.
Vicky's working on her performance
for the welcome party tonight.
It looks like pretending to enjoy
her singing is gonna be half our job here.
I got her to tell me
how she was gonna torture you
at the party, which is basically
the same way I did.
Eleanor gets drunk, hogs all the shrimp,
insults people, etcetera.
Whatever bad stuff you do
becomes the basis
for the chaos tomorrow morning.
- OK, OK.
So my job is to get drunk and insult people.
I think I can hack that.
Now, Chidi, I'm gonna need you
to act nervous
and embarrassed by Eleanor.
- Way ahead of you.
Tahani, just be your fabulous self.
And Jason, you're good old silent
Jianyu the monk.
So I told Vicky that I would handle
the surveillance on the four of you.
That'll let us meet each day
for Chidi's ethics lessons
which will apparently include me.
Even though that's transparently insane.
Cool. And, um, Janet
you're not gonna rat us out, right?
Well, Jason I've been thinking about this
a lot over the last 1.3 milliseconds
I'm not allowed to lie, but my purpose
is to make humans happy.
And since you're the only
actual humans here
I'm on board for whatever fun little
schemes you guys come up with.
OK, bring it in.
Team huddle.
The Bad Place is about to be
outsmarted by a cowardly traitor
four dum-dums, and a robot.
- Not a robot.
We can do this.
Team Cockroach on three.
One, two, three.
- Team Cockroach!
- Bobcats!
I still think that's better.