Have you guys seen this feature
that lets you talk to Siri
without pressing
any buttons?
No. How does it work?
You just say, uh, “Hey,
Siri, what time is it?”
The time is 6:37 p.m.
Yeah.
So now anyone
can control your phone?
Hey, Siri, show me pictures
of naked grandma butts.
Nice try.
It only recognizes my voice.
Oh. Cool.
Hey, Siri, show me
pictures of naked grandma butts.
I don't sound
like that.
Here are some images
of naked grandma butts.
Hey. Good news,
everybody.
Now that I'm no longer
with Amy,
I have an extra ticket to the
annual Thanksgiving lunch buffet
at the aquarium cafeteria.
Who wants it?
Well, you realize
you won't be going alone—
I'll be there the whole time.
Providing
fish and pilgrim facts.
Can you people hear me?
Well, we're having
everyone over.
Yeah, Leonard and I
are gonna be cooking
all day.
Otherwise we'd love to.
But we can't.
Yeah, poor us.
Mm-hmm.
And Raj and I
are volunteering
at the soup kitchen,
feeding food to the homeless.
Well, Howard,
what about you?
Oh...
I can't. I'm going
to the soup kitchen, too.
You said that sounded like
the worst thing ever.
If you can't support me
when I'm lying,
why are we married?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x09 ♪
The Platonic Permutation
Original Air Date on November 17
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Hi, Sheldon. What's?
Well, I'm calling
because Thanksgiving
is coming up,
and I wanted to offer you
the aquarium tickets.
No one can go with you?
No. They'd rather spend
the holiday with each other
than find out of this is the
year I finally touch a starfish.
Anyway,
I wouldn't want
the tickets to go to waste,
so take whomever you'd like.
Oh.
Okay. Thank you.
And feel free
to tell your guest
that the Myanmar catfish
is also known
as the pilgrim fish.
In case the turkey's dry
and you need something juicy.
Sheldon...
I can tell you want to go,
so if you'd be comfortable
with it,
maybe we could go as friends.
You don't think
that will be awkward?
Well... it is Thanksgiving
in an aquarium cafeteria,
so I'm gonna go out
on a limb here and say yes.
But if you mean between us...
I think it'll be fine.
Very well, then.
I'll see you
on Thanksgiving morning.
See you then.
Oh,
and forget what I said
about the Myanmar catfish.
My list of marine-themed
pilgrim facts is pretty short.
Did you know they served
shellfish and eel
at the very first Thanksgiving?
And there goes my list.
So, how does this work?
The soup kitchen manager
assigns the jobs,
and the shifts
are six hours.
Six hours?
Oh, God, I don't want to
complain for that long.
Do you ever do anything
for anyone else?
I happen to be
a giving and generous lover.
Are you and I close enough
for me to say that's creepy?
We are, and I believe the word
you're looking for is... yech!
Uh, can I help you?
Hi. We'd like to volunteer.
Oh, I appreciate
you guys coming down,
but we already have
enough people.
Any other day,
please, come back.
Oh. Okay.
Wipe that smug smile
off your face.
Maybe I'm happy
that so many people turned up
to help the less fortunate.
Are you and I close
enough for me to say...
That he's an ass?
He beat you to it.
I was wrong.
A large group had to cancel.
Oh, great.
We'd love to help.
Wipe that smug smile
off your face.
I can't!
Look at us!
Our first Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
I know.
I feel so grown up.
Sweetie, you are grown up.
Really?
How many grown-ups do you know
who have Mr. Spock oven mitts?
Hey, the recipes
are on my iPad.
Will you pull 'em up?
Yep.
What's the code?
My birthday.
It's not working.
It's just the four digits—
month and day.
Nope.
Let me see.
Yeah, there.
What number were
you putting in?
Uh...
You don't know my
birthday, do you?
Yes, I do.
Well, what is it?
May.
May what?
I'm not gonna say
your password out loud.
That is not secure.
You don't know your own
husband's birthday.
Well...
you don't know everything
about me.
Your birthday is December 2,
you grew up on
Perkins Street,
the last four digits
of your social are
7-6-2-1,
and the odds of me letting
you forget this are zero.
Oh, look at us.
Our last Thanksgiving
as husband and wife.
Hello.
Hi.
Ready for the
aquarium?
I am. You know, and in an effort
to reduce awkwardness
as we learn how to function as friends,
I printed out a list
of safe topics
for polite conversation.
If that makes you
more comfortable.
If there were a list of things
that make me more comfortable,
lists would be
on the top of that list.
Okay, now... Oh.
"Since last we spoke,
have you acquired any pets?"
No. You?
No.
Um, "Since last we spoke,
have you planned
or gone on any vacations?"
I might go visit my aunt
next week.
Mm. Your aunt
in Modesto?
No, the one in
Bakersfield.
Bakersfield. I see.
Where has this list been
all my life?
We're gonna have you
washing dishes.
Uh, aprons and rubber gloves
are here— just...
scrape, wash and stack.
If you need me, I'll be around.
So we don't even get to be up front
where the action is?
What difference
does it make?
I don't know.
I was hoping some poor kid
would come up to me and say,
Please, sir, I want some more.
You're in a soup kitchen,
not a production
of Oliver!
It's not like
I'm expecting them to sing.
and then the next day
was 73 degrees,
and the day after that
was 72,
and then it was
72 again...
uh, then it was 74,
and that brings us
to today, at—
I'd wear shorts
if I had a pair— 78.
Are we done discussing
the weather?
I don't know if
I'd call it "discussing."
You kind of sat back
and let me do all the work.
Let's see
what's next on the list.
Oh, here.
Uh, "Do you whittle,
"and if so, what kind of knife
do you..."
Sheldon.
We've known each other
a long time.
We are perfectly capable
of having a conversation
without relying on a list
off the Internet.
All right.
Well, what should
we talk about?
I don't know. Just ask me
whatever comes to mind.
Very well.
I know you've been
seeing other men.
Have you had coitus
with any of them?
Man, I walked
right into that one.
Next we need a
teaspoon of pepper,
which, I believe, was also
the name of your childhood dog.
Fine. You think
you know so much.
Who's my favorite
Spice Girl?
Baby.
Who's my favorite member of NSYNC?
Justin.
Who's my favorite Backstreet Boy?
Nice try. NSYNC forever.
Damn it!
Face it,
you can't stump me—
I am the king of husbands.
I know that you
don't like the lingerie
that I got you
on Valentine's Day.
I know you hate the word "moist." I know...
Hang on.
Wait, wait. Why don't I like
the lingerie you got me?
Because it's orange
and you think it makes you
look like a slutty carrot.
Interesting.
I never told you that.
Sure you did.
No.
I never told anyone that.
But I did write it
in my journal.
What?
I didn't know you had a journal.
I also know your voice
gets higher when you're lying.
No, it doesn't.
You know, this reminds me
of high school.
You worked in
a restaurant?
No, I was in India—
it was humid and smelled funny.
All right, I think
I'm getting into a groove here.
This isn't so bad.
Only five hours
and 40 minutes to go.
We've only been
doing this 20 minutes?
You know, I read that
washing dishes can be an
excellent form of meditation.
The key is that while
washing the dishes
one should only be...
washing the dishes.
Just because you
have that accent
doesn't mean what
you say isn't stupid.
No, seriously.
It's about being present
in the moment,
focusing on the feeling
of the warm water,
the smell of
the detergent,
the sound of the dishes squeaking,
and following your own breath.
It's about... it's
about simply being.
Ah.
Okay..I'll try t.
I need three people
out front.
I'll do it!
Me! Right here!
No fair! I was meditating!
Come on,
don't be mad.
It was a long time ago,
and it was an accident.
How can reading my journal
be an accident?
I didn't even
know what it was.
I saw it on your nightstand.
I picked it up.
Well, when you realized what
it was, why didn't you stop?
You know me, I'm a
big ol' bookworm.
All right.
Let's just finish cooking.
Well... Hey. O-Okay.
Let me make this up to you.
Sometimes I keep
an online journal.
I want you to read
something that I write.
Okay, really, I'm fine.
Okay.
Well, then I'll read it to you.
It's from the day we first met.
"Beauty, thy name is Penny."
Oh, God.
Stop.
I don't want you
to read something
you think'll just butter me up.
I want to hear
the most recent thing you wrote.
Fine.
Mmm...
"Penny's beauty,
like our love,
grows more with
each passing day."
Does it really say that?
Why would I lie?
"OMG. OMG.
"We're so close
to the new Star Wars.
"I can't take it.
Gah."
"Gah"?
Well, you didn't
read it right.
The new Star Wars
is coming. Gah!
I'm sensing things
have gotten awkward.
No. It's okay.
If we're friends, we should be
able to talk about anything.
All right.
So, you had some questions
about me seeing other people.
Just a few.
Go ahead.
How many dates have you been on?
Who were they with?
Where'd you go?
Where did you meet them?
Did you sleep with them?
And how much longer
to the aquarium?
I'm getting kind of hungry.
Let's see.
I have been on six dates
with three different people.
It was either for
coffee or dinner.
One I met at a bookstore
and two I met online.
I haven't slept with anyone.
The aquarium is
40 minutes away.
And there's a baggie of Cheerios
for you
in the glove compartment.
Uh, regular or honey nut?
I mixed them.
You mixed them.
No wonder gentleman callers
are pounding down your door.
Do you have any questions
for me?
Just one.
Are you doing okay?
I am.
Good.
I-I want you to be happy.
I believe you.
I'd believe you more if you
threw a few Apple Jacks in here.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You got to be kidding me.
Sorry?
Y-You're Elon Musk.
I am.
Wh-What are you doing here?
I'm washing dishes.
Well,
I was on the turkey line,
but I got demoted
for being too generous
with the gravy.
Oh, man. I...
What an honor to meet you.
I'm-I'm such a fan
of Tesla and SpaceX.
All your companies.
Howard Wolowitz, Caltech.
Nice to meet you, Howard.
Feels great to come down here
and help the less fortunate,
huh?
Oh, yeah.
Nothing better
than helping people.
Which is something I realized
when I was viewing Earth
from the deck of
the International Space Station,
where I spent two months as
a payload specialist, a job
I was qualified for because
I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
And I thought
I ladled the gravy on thick.
Sorry. It's just...
you're you, you know?
And I really want you
to adopt me.
Well, you're here
on Thanksgiving,
so you're probably
a good person.
Oh. I made my wife come down,
too.
You think you might
ever get back out to space?
Is that a job offer? 'Cause
I really want to go to Mars.
Assuming I can
bring my wife.
She hardly takes up any room.
She's basically a carry-on.
Well, we're not quite there yet,
but we're always looking
for engineers.
So let me give you my e-mail.
We can stay in touch.
Thank you.
Oh, look.
Someone hardly touched
their pumpkin pie.
Want to share it with me?
A-a partially eaten piece
of pumpkin pie
from a homeless shelter?
With Elon Musk, you bet I do!
You know, for a
Thanksgiving buffet
in an aquarium cafeteria,
that was really bad.
You're just upset 'cause
they ran out of Pilgrim hats.
They gave one to that baby.
He wasn't even awake.
Well, it wouldn't be a holiday
without you being mad at a baby.
Oh.
Would you care to play
an ocean-themed game I invented?
Sure. What is it?
It's called Food, Friend, Fight.
One of us chooses
three aquatic creatures,
and the other one must decide
which he would eat,
befriend, or battle.
So it's like Kiss, Marry, Kill.
What is that?
It's a game
where you're given three people
and you choose which one
you'd kiss, marry, or kill.
Well, my game is better, 'cause
instead of marrying someone,
you get to eat them.
Let's just play.
I'll start
you off easy.
Electric eel,
pufferfish, shrimp.
Hmm. Well,
I wouldn't fight the eel,
because I know
it can generate enough current
to kill a horse.
So I'd eat
the eel,
fight the shrimp,
and befriend the pufferfish,
because it would be nice
to have company
on those days I feel bloated.
Very well done.
Thank you.
Okay, your turn.
Hmm. Seal,
hagfish...
SpongeBob SquarePants.
Well, I'd befriend SpongeBob
but he's not real,
so I can't do that, can I?
But you can pal around
with a hagfish?
Hey, let's not pull
at that thread.
Okay. I'll
fight SpongeBob,
because he's so friendly we'll
just end up tickling each other.
Um, I'll befriend the seal,
because he's trainable,
which is the problem
I'm having with my
current friends.
Which means I'll have
to eat the hagfish.
Isn't that gross?
I mean, a hagfish can produce
enough mucus to fill a bucket
in a minute.
I know. It makes its own gravy—
it'll slide right down.
I miss this.
How can you miss a game you've
never played before, silly?
I guess sometimes I'm silly.
Hey. Where'd you go? I can't
tell if the turkey's done!
Be right there!
Hi, lover.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry about the journal.
I want to make it up to you.
So I'm gonna let you post
a shame photo of me on Facebook.
I am not putting
that on the Internet!
I don't want
people to see this.
I don't want to see it!
Don't want people
to see what, huh?
A little bit of this?
Oh...
Huh?
Some of this?
And, since it's Thanksgiving,
an extra helping of this?
Happy Thanks... Yikes.
I'm glad you had a
nice time with Amy.
Me, too. It's comforting to know
that she and I are able
to function as friends.
Well, I've never been
friends with any of my exes.
Oh, I'm sure you and Leonard
will be able to pull it off.
Oh. It's my friend Amy.
Hello.
Hi, Sheldon.
I'm just driving home
from my mother's.
Did you have a nice time?
I did. Um...
listen, I really enjoyed
spending this morning with you.
Well, I can't take
all the credit.
It was pretty funny
when that one anchovy
started going the wrong way.
It was.
Uh, listen,
I-I was thinking that, um,
maybe I'm ready
to be your girlfriend again.
Oh.
I thought we were just friends.
We are.
But I was hoping,
maybe...
Amy,
I excel at many things,
but getting over you
wasn't one of them.
I think I need
to just be your friend.
Okay.
I understand.
Good.
Oh, I watched a video
of the hagfish producing mucus,
so I'm gonna change my answer
and eat SpongeBob.
Okay. Sure.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man