Hello.
My name is leslie knope, and I work for
the parks and recreation department.
Can I ask you a few questions?
Would you say that you are
enjoying yourself and having fun,
having a moderate amount of fun and somewhat
enjoying yourself, or having no fun and no enjoyment?
I'm gonna put "a lot of fun.
" Ms. Knope! There's a
drunk stuck in the slide.
Sir, this—this is
a children's slide.
You're not allowed to sleep in here.
You know, when I first tell people that I work
in the government, they say,"oh, the government.
The government stinks. The
lines are too long at the dmv.
" But now things have changed.
People need our help.
And it feels good to be needed.
- Could you put your arms to your side?
- And that might help you slide down a little easier?
Do you want to come this way?
- Okay, we're gonna need you to get out.
- Can you please go away?
Get out of the slide.
- Okay? You're... Here we go!
- Can you please go away?
Okay, wake up.Here we
go. Out of the slide.
You know, government isn't
just a boys' club anymore.
Women are everyw re.
It's a great time to
be a woman in politics.
Hillary clinton. Sarah
palin.Me. Nancy pelosi.
We did it!
You know,I— I like to tell people, you know,"get on
board and buckle up,"bause my ride'sgonna be a big one.
If "andyou get motion sickness,"you
know, put your head between your knees
'cause leslie knope's
stopping for no one.
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí/font>
Parks.and. Recreation.S01E01.
Tonight is our next monthly
community outreach public forum.
And that is tonight.
- That is tonight.
- Right.
Leslie will be running it.
And we need one more.
Who wants in?
Tom.
Fine.
This is a great thing
for you guys to see.
This is where the rubber of government
meets the road of actual human beings.
When I go through these
doors,I need to be on.
Like the white house press secretary.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Here we go.
It's locked.
Okay.
Here we go.
Thank you so much for
coming. What an amazing turnout.
My name is leslie knope.
I am the deputy director of the
parks and recreation department,
and tonight we're gonna be
taking some of your questions as—
hello?
We're having a meeting in here.
Does anybody have any
questions about permits?
So take two.
I'm leslie knope, and with me is
department member tom haverford.
We are here to answer any
and all of your questions.
So fire away.
Well, it's a great day,because,uh, last
month they put me in jail.
That's right.
The,uh, the head of the police
is a ninth-degree mason.
But the music is so loud.
Stop the graffiti,please. Please.
I don't like obscenities ju— just
as much as you don't like them.
No, it drives me crazy.I have kids.
hey, My And the guy's,"you My, You Head.
" These people are members of a
community that care about where they live,
so what I hear when I'm being yelled
at is people caring loudly at me.
Now,I have a few t ngs I want
to say about laura linney.
Thank you so much, barry.
Always great to have you here.
Anyone else who would
like to contribute—
I'm ann perkins.
Uh,I'm a nurse, and frankly,I
don't really care for politics.
uh,but, um,I'm— I'm here to talk about
the abandoned lot on sullivan street.
Excellent. That sounds like a
good idea. Tell us about that.
No, it's a problem.
It almost killed my boyfriend.
Yeah.
There's a lot nearby my house, and a
developer dug out a basement for some condos,
and then they went bankrupt.
So there's just this giant pit, and
it's been there for almost a year.
12 months,yes. Go on.
Yeah,and,um, my boyfriend, who
is a musician— actually,
I support him— but anyway, he
fell in and broke both his legs.
Ann, let me speak with you for a minute.
So your boyfriend fell
down into this pit, right?
Yes.
And,um, this guy— is it pretty
serious? Are you guys living together?
Yes.
Uh,I'm sure this must
be really tough for you.
You know, just— this guy— sounds like he
didn't have a lot going on for him to start with,
and now both legs broken. He's just weak.
You have to take care of him.
- You probably feel like
you need to move on.- Why—
what does this— Just become more adventurous
in relationships with your body, just in—
Are you—are you actually
hitting on me right now?
Oh,oh,god, no.
I'm not— I'm not hitting
on you.I'm actually married.
I'm just an open person, and
I like connecting with people.
I'm, you know, very comfortable
around women, attractive women.
I've spent a lot of time with
them. And I just— I—I don't know.
I feel like we might be taking
up too much of the forum's time.
Maybe we can just exchange numbers.
You know, maybe go away one weekend
and just kind of talk about this.
Look.
I'd love to do it.
The bottom line is I've been trying to get this
thing fixed for months and nobody's done anything,
and it's ugly, and it's dangerous, and it's
government-owned, and you need to do something about it.
Okay.
- I'll do something about it.
- Really?
Yes, we— I
will help you.
Is that a promise?
It's more than a promise.
It's a pinky promise.
I pinky promise all of you that I will
help, and I will go to that location tomorrow
and we will fill in that pit, and then when
that's done, we're gonna put a park on the land.
Okay.
Well,I've worked at the parks department for six
years, and I've handled a lot of things that I'm proud of.
Recently I led a city-wide drive to disinfect the
sandbox sand after we had those problems with the cats.
But this pit— the chance to build
a whole new park from scratch—
this could be my hoover dam.
No, that sounds great.
Um, problem is, anything
over $25 I have to report.
So,um, maybe give my wife a
call and give her the suits,
and then if they don't fit
her, maybe she'll give 'em to me.
Morning.
All right, mr. Mayor.
That sounds good.
I'll see you on saturday for
the,uh, ultimate frisbee game.
Bye.
Leslie, hello.
You were talking to the mayor?
Yep, we was rappin' about some things.
Tom and I work really well together.
We're both outsiders.
I'm a woman, he's A...
oh,I think he's a libyan.
I am from bennettsville, south carolina.
I am what you might call a "redneck.
" Okay, brainstorm.
How do we make this park happen?
Let's go to the city council directly
and ask them to put up the money.
No, parks are not a priority.
I need more firepower.
I need bigger guns.
You know what I need to
do?Form a committee. Right?
Yeah, that could work.
Yeah,'cause committees are power, and
committees make things happen.
Committees are the lifeblood
of our democratic system.
That's really good. Write that down.
Yep.
From time to time, when I think of an eloquent
saying or a phrase,I have tom write it down.
He's collecting them for my memoirs.
Here's leslie's quote from wednesday.
Okay, read it back to me.
"committees cover our
democracy with blood.
" Sounded better when I said it.
It's still good, though.
Okay,I have an idea.
What about bringing mark on board?
- Which mark?
Mark brendanawicz. Which mark?
Well, if you want something done in this
town, you call mark brendanawicz because,
you know, he's a city planner, but he's
more than that. He's kind of like a fixer.
He fixes things. He's
a smart, capable guy.
He just—he knows where
the bodies are buried.
What's up, brendanawicz?
You crazy old polish person.
City hall is like a locker room, and you gotta
get in there and you gotta snap towels at people
and you gotta give 'em the
business, and if you can't take it,
you know, you—you—
then you can't take it.
You—you gotta leave...
the locker room.
Let's get down to brass tacks.
I know you don't have a lot of time and
I want to thank you for meeting me today.
I just work right there.
Well, thank you for
clearing your schedule.
Oh,I didn't clear anything.
You know this lot that
I'm talking about, right?
Uh,yeah, lot 48.
Um, condo developer.
He dug a basement and
then he went bankrupt.
I checked it out like a month ago.
It's pretty gross.
What would you say if I told you that I
was thinking about turning it into a park?
A park, huh?
Okay.
Well, when I think about the logistics, the various
hoops that you're gonna have to jump through
,I would say—
is it likely?
No, it's not likely, you know.
But is it possible?
No.It's not possible.
I would give up on that one.
What? Why?
Why? Uh,I don't know.There's, like,a
million reasons why.
Uh, homeowners' associations, anti-government
nuts,bureaucrats, miles of red tape—
Really? It sounds like you're
telling me to go for it.
There's no way it can happen.
I can do this.
I just need a little help.
Could you do me a favor?
For old times' sake?
Mark and I—
it's complicated.
When you work closely with someone
and you share similar interests
and you have a similar worldview and you're
passionate about the same things, things can happen.
We slept together.
Leslie?
No.
Oh, my god.
You know what?
Yeah, we did, like five years ago.
I'd
sort of—
No, but yeah.Yeah. We did.
Honey, can you straighten
up your area a little bit?
'Cause they're gonna be here soon.
Can—
thanks.
That parks lady is coming over and
we're gonna go take a look at the pit.
I—I think it's probably
just a photo op for her.
I mean,I don't think anybody in
government actually cares about—
Honey, do you mind doing
that somewhere else?
I'm trying to watch tv.
I'm talking about the pit you fell in.
It's ms. Perkins' house.
Doorbell!
Yeah,I heard it.
I heard it.I'm getting it.
I'm here.
Look at that.
Safety.
You remember tom from last night.
- Hey,ann, how are you?
- Yeah,hey. Of course I do.
And this is our college intern, april.
She's going to be documenting
our fact-finding mission.
Hey, april.
Is this fun for you?
Yeah, it's so much fun.
Uh,I'm just gonna grab my phone quickly.
This must be our hero.
The man heard 'round the world.
How you doin', son?
Pretty good.
I'm leslie knope.
And the entire government of pawnee would like to let
you know that we will do everything we can to help you.
Could you pass me my itch stick?
Of course.
So,um, andy jumped over this fence.
He was crossing through to get
home and then he fell right there.
Oh, my god.
How did we let this happen?
Dream with me for a second, ann.
Doesn't this neighborhood
deserve a first-class park?
Imagine a shiny new playground with a
jungle gym and swings,pool, tennis courts,
volleyball courts, racquetball courts, basketball
court, regulation football field.
We could put an amphitheatre over
there with shakespeare in the park.
It's really not that big of a pit.
We could do some of those things.
It's gonna take a little extra work.
But why not try?
I think that would be great.
Me, too.
I'm going in.
- Why?
- 'T w donorry.I have a hard hat on.
- I can see
that, but— Yeah.
- April, document this.
- Okay, why?
The key to any fact-finding mission is to
get right into the battle zone, you know?
It's like george bush when he flew over new orleans or richard
nixon when he went to china to see what the chinese were up to.
No.
Leslie, are you okay?
Leslie!
Hold o april's gonna get
some photos for the website.
Can you just be still?
Don't move around as much.
Okay, squeeze my fingers.
Good.
Does it hurt a lot?
No.
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
Good thing I was wearing that hard hat.
But it—
it fell off.
After my head hit that rod.
I can't believe you fell
in,too. That's awesome.
It's not awesome, andy.
Well, at least my boss will listen
to me now that I broke my clavicle.
It's not broken.
It is.
Do you have one of those
neck foam collar brace things?
Honestly, you're—
you're fine.
Oh,honestly, my clavicle's broken.
Oh,hey,baby, if you're going to the
kitchen, could you make me pancakes real quick?
Uh, sure.
Ooh, are pancakes being made?
Yeah, sure.
I don't know, she's a little doofy.
But she's sweet.
Ron, please.
No.No way.
Come on, ron.
I've been a loyal foot soldier.
Give me my shot.
Let me have lot 48.
Is that a travel
pillow around your neck?
Ron,I don't know how
to explain this to you.
When you've been down in the
pit— have you been in the pit?
No,I haven't gotten down there yet.
- Well,I have.
- When you fell in.
When I visited the bottom of the
pit on a fact-finding mission.
And when you're down there, you get some
perspective about what it all means.
And let me tell you something, ron.
What it means is... I
want this subcommittee.
I've been quite open about
this around the office.
I don't want this parks department to build
any parks because I don't believe in government.
I think that all government
is a waste of taxpayer money.
My dream is to have the park system privatized
and run entirely for profit by corporations.
¾ÍÏñchuck E. Cheese.
(¼¯¿ì²Í ÓÎÏ·ºÍÓéÀÖÓÚÒ»ÌåµÄ´óÐÍÁ¬Ëø¼ÒÍ¥ÓéÀÖÖÐÐÄ)
ËûÃÇÓÐÍêÃÀÎÞȱµÄÉÌҵģʽ
ÎÒÄþÔ¸¸øchuck E. Cheese¹¤×÷
Well,I will definitely think about it.
I like the sound of that "definitely.
" I'm gonna leave before
you change your mind.
Mr. Swanson,I presume.
Lot 48. Thoughts?
Yes?No? Me?
Park? Giving the park to me?
Still mulling.
She's insatiable.
She's like A... little
dog with a— a chew toy.
All right, you guys. All
right, all right.I'll ask him.
Everybody wants to know
what your decision is.
Someone on the phone about the park.
You know,I don't think I even want it.
Oh, man.
The clavicle's still really hurting me.
this is a great shot.
I know.
That's awesome.
I think she's crying in
that one. Look at this one.
Hey, kids.
That's another good one.
Hey, brendanawicz.
You gotta come check this out.
Leslie took us out to that pit
in lot 48 and she fell inside.
And we have some awesome photos.
- Uh, is she okay?
- Yeah, she's fine.
Oh, this is a classic.
That's the best one.
The up-skirt photo.
Awesome.
Hey, man.
Give me the photo back.
What's going on?
Don't worry.I can print more.
Leslie is unique.
Um, government work can beat you down.
I would say that I lost my optimism
about government in about two months.
Leslie's kept hers for six years.
I've got a few rules about how to
survive and prosper in a government job,
and I think I'm about to
break one of those rules.
I want you to give lot 48 to leslie
so she can try to build a park.
Why should I?
You owe me one, remember?
Do you want to cash in for this?
Yeah,I do.
So this was built in 1935.
It's called pioneer hall.
A little trivia— it is one of the first
structures in america to ever have locks.
Oh, yeah.
This is our crown jewel.
It's one of our best murals.
It depicts the very famous
battle at conega creek.
We have a lot of children visit, so often we have
to cover up the more gruesome parts with a poster.
That is horrifying.
Yes, it is.
So what do you want to
see? The dmv? Animal control?
- Or we
could— Leslie.
We did it.
Ron's approved our committee.
- Oh,m D.
- That's great!
- That's so great.
- That's so exciting!
This is huge.
I'm barely 34, and I've already landed a
parks department exploratory subcommittee.
I'm a rocket ship.
Leslie.
I just heard the news.
- Isn't it great?
- Congratulations.
Thank you.I'm so excited.
It's exciting, isn't it?
- It is.
- Yeah.
Should I call a press conference now, or?
- Yeah, call one. Definitely.
- I would.
Every now and then we have these little
gatherings and leslie gets plastered.
One time I convinced her to try
to fax someone a fruit roll-up.
She one time made out with the
water delivery guy in her office.
On halloween, she was
dressed up as batman.
Not batgirl. Batman.
And I convinced her to go stop a
crime that was going on outside.
And it is my favorite
thing in the world.
You know what? America is awesome.
It's so full of hope and small
towns and big cities and real people
and delicious beverages and hot guys.
You just never know when
opportunity is gonna strike.
- Yeah.
- You gotta be ready for it.
- Are you excited?
- Definitely am. Fired up.
- Yeah!
I'm really fired up.
I—you know they say that democracy or
whatever only works when people get involved?
Well,I'm getting involved.
So I am gonna make a vow now that I will do
whatever it takes to get this pit filled in.
Even if it takes two months.
Soul sista, soul sista
- gonna get your phone, sista
- Yeah.
Sweet lady marmalard
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
- =www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí/font>
I've created this office as a symbol
of how I feel about government.
This sawed-off shotgun
belonged to a local bootlegger.
People who come in here to ask me for
things have to stare right down the barrel.
Did you guys get a grant to do this?
This is my basketball court.
I don't want to see any double dribble.
I don't want to see any
three-second violations.
Bobby knight!