'cause I'm drunk,
aren't you?
Yeah, I'm a bad girl.
Lucky for both of
us, I don't judge.
JAKE:
It's not my fault!
ALAN:
Then whose
fault is it?
JAKE:
I told you.
Uncle Charlie.
I thought you lived alone.
I do.
I leave the TV on
to deter criminals.
ALAN:
Charlie,
did you tell Jake
he could use your computer?
(scoffs)
Just take what you want
and don't hurt us.
Go ahead and tell
him, Uncle Charlie.
No one's talking to you.
Can you explain to me
why I caught him watching
a Quicktime movie called
Vanessa Does Van Nuys?
Hey, meet Vanessa.
Why don't you hop upstairs?
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Hey, Dad, can we move
to Van Nuys?
No.
VANESSA:
Hey,
whose skateboard?
Mine.
Wow. It's really rad.
Thanks.
So's your movie.
We're working on a sequel.
Yeah, I'm gonna do
Woodland Hills next.
Hop, hop,
hop, hop.
Can we move to
Woodland Hills?
Forget Woodland Hills.
Excuse me.
We were talking
about the dirty movie
on your computer.
I'm sorry. I forgot
it was on there.
You can't forget things
like that
when you have a child
in the house.
I'm not a child.
And I don't have him.
No one's talking to you,
and that's no excuse.
Look, it's not hardcore.
It's mostly her
and a couple of friends
having a pajama party.
I didn't see pajamas.
Shut up. Go away.
Again, I'm sorry.
Mea culpa.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
mea goin' upstairs.
For a culpa hours.
BERTA:
Hey, Charlie,
who do I work
for— you
or this fastidious
parasite
you call a brother?
I get the feeling
you want me to say me.
Me. Definitely me.
She works for me.
Well, then, tell her
when something
is on the shopping
list, she should in
fact shop for it.
I'm gonna slug him.
Can I slug him?
Why are you making such
a big deal out of this?
Because it is a big deal.
No, it's not.
The hell it isn't.
Hey, what is going on here?
It's very simple.
I have decided to start drinking
acidophilus milk.
It promotes intestinal flora
which aids in healthy digestion.
Anyway, for
three weeks,
I have been writing it
on the shopping list,
yet Berta insists
on bringing home two percent.
Slug him.
This is my life.
Milk and skateboards.
(thudding)
It's a good thing I'm drunk.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Men.
Extra large eggs.
Acidophilus milk.
Two percent milk,
you whiny pinhead.
Morning.
Hey, how you feeling?
Not too bad really.
That was some fall you took.
Yeah, if I hadn't
been plastered,
it might have killed me.
You'd think the liquor industry
would promote that.
It is a selling point.
Right up there with making
ugly people doable.
Two percent—
the king of milk.
He's got to go, Charlie.
What am I going to do, Berta,
he's my brother.
We could make it look
like an accident.
(doorbell ringing)
No, no accidents.
As long as my mother's alive
nothing happens to Fredo.
Hi.
I am sorry to bother you,
I'm just moving in next door.
Really?
You're my new neighbor?
Thank you, God.
Anyway, I just wanted
to stop by and introduce myself.
Danielle Stewart.
Charlie Harper.
Nice to meet you, Danielle.
Come on in.
Oh, thank you.
We'll have a "welcome
to the neighborhood" drink.
It's 9:00 a.m.
You're right, who drinks
at 9:00 a.m.?
I wouldn't mind
a cup of coffee.
Great.
Oh, Berta?
(angrily):
What?
My faithful housekeeper.
Would you be so kind
as to bring a cup of coffee
for our new neighbor?
Sure.
Luckiest S.O.B. on the planet.
Please.
Thank you.
So, Danielle,
what brings you
to our little
stretch of paradise?
Me? Well, I just got tired
of the cold winters in Chicago.
Well, I don't want
to scare you away,
but winters here the mercury
can dip down to the mid-60s.
Oh, how will I stay warm?
I recommend the buddy system.
You're cute.
I know.
So, what did you do in Chicago?
Well, for the last eight years
I've had a full-time career
trying to spend
my divorce settlement.
Oh, a working woman.
Well, buying a Malibu
beach house
ought to take a big chunk
out of that settlement.
Yeah, you'd think.
Whoa.
Anyway, I've had my fun.
I want to settle down,
get serious with my life.
Oh, yeah, me, too.
No kidding.
So, are you married?
Me? Uh... no.
Are you looking to get married?
Uh... no.
Do you like children?
So how do you define getting
serious with your life?
Well, I've stopped
drinking in the morning.
Hey, Berta, where's that coffee?
You men are all alike.
Isn't there anyone left who just
wants to get married
and raise a family?
Yeah, but they're all gay.
Here we go.
Thank you.
Oh, you wouldn't happen to have
any acidophilus milk, would you?
Walk me through
this again.
She's beautiful,
rich, divorced
and you want to hand her off
to Zippy the Chimp?
Follow my reasoning here.
This is a woman looking
to settle down.
If I sleep with her,
I'm happy for one night.
But if I teach my brother
to sleep with her,
he falls in love,
asks her to marry him,
moves out and I'm happy
for the rest of my life.
It's a nice plan,
but it'll never happen.
Don't-don't-don't say that.
(spitting)
Unjinx, unjinx, unjinx.
Charlie, she is way
out of his league.
I know that. Everybody
is out of his league.
He doesn't even
have a league.
He's just a kid with
a bat and a ball and
a football helmet.
But luckily he has me.
Color me dubious.
ALAN:
I'm home.
Come on, I need you
to be with me on this one.
It'll never work.
Voila.
This...
is acidophilus milk.
It's on the shelf below
the two percent
right next to the low-fat
yogurt.
Boy, does your brother have
a girl for you.
What?
She just moved next door.
She's gorgeous,
divorced and loaded.
Mm-hmm. What's wrong with her?
Why does something have
to be wrong with her?
Because there's only two reasons
you ever set me up with a woman.
Either you need somebody to keep
the emotionally disturbed
or cross-eyed or hermaphroditic
best friend busy
while you do
the pretty girl,
or...
okay, I guess there's
just one reason.
There is nothing wrong
with Danielle.
Berta, is she or is
she not gorgeous?
Hey, I'd do her.
If she's so great, why
are you giving her to me?
You want the truth?
It'd be a nice
change of pace.
All right, first of all,
I am sorry about the
hermaphroditic incident.
"I'm sorry" doesn't make up
for leaving me in a hotel room
with a girl who had
a vestigial penis.
I didn't know.
I was as surprised as you were.
Charlie, no one
was as surprised as I was.
But let's move on.
I'm not saying I didn't try
to hit on our new neighbor,
because I did.
And?
I got nowhere.
She saw him for the mindless
meat-seeking missile that he is.
Anyway... I just thought
you two might hit it off.
I'm even making
a little welcome basket
for you to give
to her, see?
So, she's beautiful,
rich and single?
Right.
Why would she want me?
What kind of thing
is that to say?
Why wouldn't she want you?
I'm broke, middle-aged,
twice divorced
sleeping on your
on your hide-a-bed
and sharing custody of a
flatulent, underachieving son.
We're gonna need
a bigger basket.
You're gonna need
chloroform and a rope.
♪ Men...
Just remember, the most
important thing
is to project confidence.
Got it.
How do I look?
Just project confidence.
Here, you give her
the welcome basket.
All right, what do I say?
"Welcome."
Good, that's good.
Oh, hi.
Welcome.
Danielle, this is
my brother Alan.
Alan, Danielle.
Alan just wanted to welcome
you to the neighborhood.
Welcome.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Would you like
to come in?
I don't know, she seems
kind of busy.
Maybe we should
come back...
Go, go, go.
I am sorry that the
place is such a mess.
Don't be silly.
Moving takes time,
right, Alan?
Oh, yes.
I remember the last
time I moved,
it was very time-consuming.
I had to collect boxes
and those packing peanuts,
and boy, those things
get everywhere.
Hey, you know, that's summer
sausage, not salami.
A lot of people
confuse the two.
Interesting.
So, why don't I
open up this wine
and we can toast
to my new home.
Good idea.
None for me. Red wine
makes me gassy.
I'm sorry, I don't have
anything else to offer.
I haven't had time to go
grocery shopping.
Well, then you must
be starving.
Alan, I think we should take
this young lady out to dinner.
But I was planning on warming up
the pot roast from Sunday night.
The pot roast will keep.
I don't know,
it's right on the edge.
Forget the pot roast.
So what do you say?
We could walk up the beach
to Georgio's and grab a bite.
You know, that
sounds wonderful.
Let me just throw on
some clean clothes.
Terrific.
Great. I will be right back.
Huh? Huh?
She's incredible.
Incredible my ass,
she's perfect.
Okay, a couple of pointers.
First off,
you never open with "gassy."
I know that.
It just came out.
It's all right, it's all right.
No, no permanent damage.
Now what's going
to happen here
is I'm going
to bail on dinner
so you two
can be alone.
Really?
'Cause Georgia's
is kind of pricey.
Oh, geez.
Here, tip big.
Don't agonize over the math.
I don't agonize.
I just take the sales
tax and double it
which is roughly 15%.
Unless, of course, the service
is less than impeccable
in which case I leave
a flat five dollars.
Alan, it's my money, go crazy.
Fine, 18% it is.
Now, dinner conversation.
Don't talk about your boring
job, your petty problems
or your stupid hobbies.
What else is there?
Her petty problems,
her stupid hobbies.
No woman ever came home
from a date complaining
that all she did
was talk about herself.
Oh, that's good.
And that way,
I remain an enigma.
Yeah, let's call you an enigma.
All righty, do I look okay?
You look beautiful,
fantastic.
Right, Alan?
Welcome.
Okay, let's go.
Let me just lock up.
Oh, no...
What do you mean
you have to go?
I mean, uh, what's wrong?
I just remembered I have
some work I need to do.
Oh, no!
Oh, what a shame.
Maybe we should
do this another time.
BOTH:
No, no.
You two go ahead,
enjoy yourselves.
Are you sure?
He's sure. Let's go.
Okay.
See you later,
Charlie.
So, Danielle, you got any
hobbies or problems?
Yes, I know she's hot.
But I'm thinking long-term,
so shut up!
♪ Men...
Hey.
Where have you been?
Stuck in traffic.
Danielle's coming over
in a few minutes.
Got to shower and change.
Wow, you two
are going out again?
What can I say, Charlie?
The girl digs my mojo.
When did you get mojo?
Scoff if you like,
but that woman is entranced
by the enigma
that is Alan Jerome Harper.
Unbelievable— your
plan is working.
Told ya.
There must be something wrong
with that girl.
There must be a lot wrong
Well, then it's a match
made in heaven.
There's something wrong with her
and we know there's something
wrong with him.
(doorbell rings)
Yeah, and before you know it,
he'll move out,
they'll get married
and we'll be wondering
what's wrong with their kids.
Hey, Charlie.
Hey, Danielle.
Come on in.
Thank you.
Oh, man.
If the kid
wants to kill me
why doesn't he just cut
my brake line?
Alan's in the shower.
Am I too early?
No, no. No, he's been living
here for three years.
You want a drink?
No, thank you.
I'm trying to cut down.
Really? Why?
Long story.
Alan takes long showers.
Longer when
he's not dating.
Thank you, Berta.
So, tell me your story.
It's a little embarrassing.
Hey, all the good drinking
stories are.
After a night of partying
at the Pomona State Fair,
I once woke up on a tilt-a-whirl
wearing nothing
but a grass skirt
and a tiny sombrero.
No kidding?
I've still got the sombrero.
Okay, your turn.
All right, um...
the reason my marriage
didn't work out...
the reason none of my
relationships work out,
is because I tend to drink
a little too much
and then do things I regret.
And by "things," you mean...?
Men.
Huh.
And the occasional woman.
Well, as stories go,
I'd say this is a good one.
At least yours
doesn't end
with a toothless carnie
offering you a churro.
You know, I had a feeling
you'd understand.
Alan is very sweet,
but the guys I usually go for
are more like... well, you.
Huh.
Anyway, I think I am ready
for a nice normal relationship.
No more getting blitzed
and falling into bed
with the first guy who asks me.
Or a girl.
Or a couple.
Huh.
Huh-huh-huh-huh.
(clears throat)
Excuse me.
Okay, new plan.
I'm going to boink Danielle
and Alan's going
to live here forever.
Quelle surprise.
Hello.
It's not your night, Alan.
What?
Danielle, she's not right
for you.
But you said
she was perfect for me.
I was wrong.
She's sick and twisted.
That makes her perfect for me.
I'm sorry, I'm not following.
I was talking
to her out there
and it turns out she's a
boozehound and a sex freak.
What?
I haven't seen that
in her at all.
I mean, I got a good-night kiss,
but she was perfectly sober
and her tongue
did nothing freaky.
That's because she's trying
to hide who she really is.
Who's that?
Me!
She's me, Alan,
top to bottom,
except, you know,
from here to here.
So what is you want me to do,
step aside
so you can lead her back
to a life of sordid degradation?
If you wouldn't mind.
No! No! No!
You gave her to me.
There's no takebacks.
All right, fine.
We'll just let her make
her own decision.
All right, all right,
may the better man win.
You would be rooting
for the shriveled man.
Oh, now, just a little.
You got it.
That is a
beautiful dress.
Whoops.
Ooh.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Mm...
buttery...
with a slight citrus finish.
Hmm.
Ah!
You know wine.
Okay, Danielle,
we'd better get going
if we're gonna make
that reservation.
You're right. Well, thanks
for the wine, Charlie.
Whoa, whoa, what's the hurry?
I was going to make
a pitcher of margaritas.
Ooh, I love margaritas!
Be right back.
Gee, Danielle, do you really
want to sit here
and drink with Charlie?
Oh, yeah, you're right, Alan.
You're a nice guy.
You're good for me.
Okay, Charlie, we're leaving!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
If you don't have time
for margaritas,
I could mix one up
in your mouth.
Cut it out, Charlie.
I know what you're trying to do?
What are you talking about?
I'm being a good host.
(hushed):
You're taking advantage
of Danielle.
No, no, I respect
Danielle for who she is.
for who she's
pretending to be.
I don't get you—
why did you bother
putting us together
in the first place?
Because I thought
she was dull and
boring like you.
and I had hoped the two
of you would go
and be dull and boring
at her house!
That was really your plan?
That's insane!
It would have worked if she
wasn't a drunken slut!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
There is no need
to fight over me.
Alan, you're a sweet gentle guy.
Charlie, you're a pig.
But I find you very attractive.
There's only one
reasonable solution.
I have to do you both.
No crossing swords.
Are you out of your mind?
You're actually
considering this?
Yeah, you're right.
I don't even like eating
dinner next to you.
Thank you
for your generous offer,
but I'm afraid
we must decline.
But mostly he's afraid.
I should have known.
Not a pair between you.
Well, if either of you
change your mind,
you know where to find me.
(gasps)
Okay, you can have her.
♪ Men...
"One pound salted butter...
"one dozen extra-large eggs...
one acidophilus milk
for the whiny pinhead."
I thought I was
the only one who
drank this stuff.
What? Are you kidding me?
It's all I drink.
You know,
for the intestinal... fauna.
That's all you drink?
Well, I've been known
to add a few fingers of vodka.
Kind of a acidopha-tini.
You're cute.
So I've been told.
I can't. I promised Berta
I'd get the groceries.
You're right. You're always
right.