♪ Joy to the world
♪ I'm getting laid
♪ I'm getting laid tonight
♪ We'll light the Yule log,
deck the halls ♪
♪ And then we'll play
some jingle balls ♪
♪ It's been a real long wait
♪ This is our second date
♪ It's Christmas Eve
and I'm getting laid. ♪
Hey, I'm mixing up
the eggnog.
You want this broad lit up
or just slightly glowing?
Well, let's see, we're
celebrating peace on Earth
and goodwill towards
all mankind,
so let's get her plowed.
Hallelujah.
♪ Glo-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
♪ Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-
oh-ria ♪
♪ Tonight I'm boinking Gloria
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
♪ Two drunk twins...
♪ And a lap dance
in a pear tree. ♪
Merry Christmas,
Uncle Charlie.
Oh, right, the other part
of Christmas.
Go ahead, open it.
Hold on. Let me give you
your gift first.
Don't want you think
I forgot you.
A hundred bucks? Wow!
Picked it out myself.
Now open yours.
Okay.
This is kind
of exciting.
"Fart in a Can"?
You don't have one, do you?
Well, I've got you.
But this is good for travel.
Jake, I just talked
to your mom.
She's going to be
here any minute.
Don't look at
Uncle Charlie's gift.
You're getting the same thing.
Oh, boy, I'm excited.
Don't be.
Speaking of gifts...
Merry Christmas.
I'll leave it up to you.
You can open it tomorrow
morning at your mom's, or...
you can rip it open with your
teeth like a rabid jackal.
You got me the new Nintendo?
It's from Uncle Charlie, too.
You owe me $125.
But I just...
This is so cool!
Thanks, Dad!
Thanks, Uncle Charlie!
Yeah, yeah, merry Christmas.
I'm going to go hook it up.
No, no, no, you're leaving.
Your Uncle Charlie's
hooking up.
You're leaving too, right?
Yes, relax.
I plan on spending
Christmas Eve
at a movie theater
all by myself
just so you can have
sex tonight.
You can have sex, too.
Just pick the right
movie theater.
(doorbell ringing)
Jake, time to go.
Take some paper towels
and don't wear your suede shoes.
Ho, ho, ho.
That's another option.
BOTH:
Merry Christmas.
Come on in.
Hey, merry Christmas,
Charlie.
Yes, swell. I'll go get the kid.
Ooh, eggnog.
Honey, we've got
a long drive ahead of us.
We're spending the holidays
in San Diego with my parents.
That's why I need eggnog.
Hey, I spent Thanksgiving
with your parents.
Oh, really? Your mom's
out of rehab?
Yes, my mom's out
of rehab.
Actually, she kind
of jumped the fence.
Well, the woman's going
to be your mother-in-law—
you might as well
get used to it.
Remember the time she rode out
of Betty Ford on a lawnmower?
On the plus side, she bakes
Toll House cookies
with walnuts and Demerol.
Stuff never goes back in
the box the way it came out.
It's a life lesson, Jake.
Come on, your mom's here.
Vamoose.
Okay, table's set
on the deck
and dinner's in
the oven.
Great.
You might want to keep the
candles away from the eggnog.
Got it.
All right then,
I'm leaving now.
Good-bye and thanks.
Yeah, merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
All the best.
Same to you.
Give me my bonus,
you blockhead.
Oh, right.
Thank you for all
your hard work.
Couldn't get along
without you.
You're one in a million.
Really?
What would Jesus do?
Herb?
Oh, no thanks.
I'm driving.
I'll have some.
No, you won't.
It's for grownups.
I'll have another.
Sweetie, my parents
are waiting.
I know, dear.
Apple doesn't fall far
from the tree, does it?
Okay, merry Christmas to all,
and to all, a good-bye.
Hang on.
I've got a long bus ride,
and I don't want to sober up
halfway home.
KANDI:
Hello?
Kandi?
What are you
doing here?
I didn't want to be alone
on Christmas Eve
and I didn't know
where else to go.
Where's your new boyfriend?
He decided to spend Christmas
with his family.
Why didn't he
bring you along?
He thought it would make
his wife uncomfortable.
Oh. Sweetie,
come on in.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've got company coming,
remember?
I can't just throw
her out, Charlie.
How do you know
if you don't try?
Lighten up,
it's Christmas.
Okay, two minutes, and then I
bring out the Fart in a Can.
ALAN:
You remember Judith.
Hi, Judith.
And this is her
fiancé, Herb.
Hi, Herb.
Hi.
ALAN:
Here, let me
take your coat.
Oh, my golly.
Well, I guess we should
get going.
What's the hurry?
Your parents are
waiting, remember?
What do you care?
They don't like you anyway.
Eggnog?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm a doctor.
A real one or like Alan?
I'm a pediatrician.
Wow, so you're into feet.
No, children.
Isn't that illegal?
Berta, don't you have
a bus to catch?
And miss this show?
Are you nuts?
Feliz Navidad, everyone!
Ooh, I didn't see
that one coming.
Mom, what are
you doing here?
I was on my way to a party,
thought I'd
drop off your gifts
so that I don't have to schlep
back here tomorrow
and mess up my day.
ROSE:
Charlie?
Rose?
How could you have a Christmas
party and not invite me?
This isn't a Christmas party.
Well, what do you call it?
The beginning of a news story
that ends with the phrase,
"He then turned
the gun on himself.
All right, all right,
everybody listen up.
Listen to me.
There is no party.
You all have to leave now
because a beautiful woman
is coming over and I intend
to get her drunk
and have sex with her.
WOMAN:
That's a good plan.
Except I'm already drunk.
Boy, I can't wait
till the second act.
♪ Men...
More fuel for the fire.
You said you were going home.
Well, that was before I knew
you were having a party.
This isn't a party.
It's just a bunch of people
I don't like
standing around drinking
my booze.
Oh, crap, it is a party.
Give me that.
Love to know that those two
are talking about.
I could tell you.
I read lips.
Really?
Yep.
Right now your date
is saying
"The wily ostrich
sank my boat."
I have a little congestion
in my upper chest.
Can you take a look at it?
Oh, well, I could...
Kandi, he's a pediatrician.
He only treats children.
Now hold on.
There's no actual age limit.
I took an oath to ease
suffering wherever I find it.
Alan, a word.
Oh, good... a word.
I don't have
my stethoscope,
so why don't you just
breathe in and out for me.
Make this stop.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Don't screw with me.
Tell your ex-wife to stop
flirting with my fiancé.
Gee, that's funny.
The way I see it,
your peanut butter is
all over my chocolate.
Damn it, Alan, I can
make your life a living hell.
How would I know
the difference?
Cough again.
Once more.
Let's have a little pow-wow.
She might have a touch
of the croup.
Listen, Herb...
So you were married
to her?
Yes, we were married.
Judith is getting
really upset with you.
So you got to see
her naked?
Stay with me, Herb.
Your fiancée is
very angry.
Really? How come?
Oh, I don't know,
maybe it's because
you were trying use
Kandi's nipple as a Q-tip.
It's okay, I'm a doctor.
Just do yourself
a favor—
go pay attention
to Judith.
All right.
Some party, huh?
Yeah, I'm glad I didn't waste
this buzz on the bus.
Here comes your mom.
Act like you didn't
know what they were saying.
Charlie, I must
talk to you.
I know. Why is that?
How serious is your
relationship with Gloria?
Not that it's any
of your business,
but this is our
second date.
What happened on the first date?
They went out to dinner,
he took her home
and they made out
a little bit in the car.
Oh, I'm sorry, did
you want to tell it?
So, you haven't slept together?
Not yet.
Oops. There I go again.
That's good. Uh, darling,
you need to end
this relationship now.
Why?
Do you trust me?
ALL:
No.
Okay, but you know I have
your best interests
at heart, don't you?
ALL:
No.
All right, then,
let me put it this way.
I forbid you to see
this woman any more.
You forbid?
What gives you
the right to forbid?
I'm 39 years old.
I'm your mother. You're 40.
And you must not see
this woman anymore!
Mom, you know that just
makes me want her more.
Charlie, I mean it.
I'm getting hotter.
Look, I know certain things
about Gloria's past
which are, well, unsavory.
Okay, I'm going supernova.
Would you listen to me?
If you continue
to see this woman,
it will hurt me, deeply.
I may have to marry this girl.
Okay. Okay.
You give me no choice.
Who are you calling?
It's probably
about the ostrich in the boat.
Charlie, I'm getting
pretty drunk,
so if you like a girl who moves,
you better do me soon.
Follow me.
Ah... isn't that sweet?
Every time a guy has sex,
an angel gets a stiffy.
Would you look at them?
Oh, I completely forgot
about the subplot.
What do you want me
to do, Judith?
He's your man. You want him?
Fight for him.
How can I
compete with that?
There's no competition.
Herb loves you.
You have a mature,
sophisticated relationship
based on mutual respect.
All Kandi has is...
There'll be other men.
Just get here
as soon as you can.
Where's Charlie?
Damn it!
Oh, I get it.
It's like Tony and
Tina's Wedding.
You gotta follow
them around.
Hey. Mommio. Daddio.
Hi, buddy.
Mommio. Daddio, Daddio.
Mommio, Mommio. Daddio...
Stop!
Mom!
Get out of that bed
this instant!
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Charlie, I'm
warning you.
You can't tell him what
to do— he's 34 years old.
He's what?
She's drunk.
Mom, what are
you doing here?
I'm trying to keep you from
making a horrible mistake.
What do you care?
I make this mistake
on a regular basis.
Some might call it
a lifestyle.
Charlie...
I don't want
to hear it.
I came up here to do a job.
Actually, two jobs
and a chore.
Now, you can stay and watch,
which I don't recommend,
or you can leave.
Either way, Gloria and I
are going to have sex.
Go ahead.
Okay, I'm bluffing.
He sure is.
(playing "Heart and Soul")
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells
♪ Jingle all the way
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride
in a one-horse open sleigh ♪
♪ Jingle bells,
jingle bells... ♪
Have you seen Jake?
Nope.
Huh.
Jake?
HERB:
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Judith! What the hell
are you doing?
You told me to
fight for my man.
I'm fighting
for my man.
HERB:
Alan, would you please
close the door?
Sorry.
12 years of marriage, she never
fought for me from that angle.
(Kandi playing same tune)
♪ Silent night
♪ Holy night...
Kandi?
Yeah?
Take a break.
Okey-doke.
(doorbell rings)
Hello.
Oh, my goodness.
Are you Alan?
Uh, yes.
I haven't seen you in 35 years.
No kidding. I'm sorry,
I don't remember you.
Well, I'm not surprised.
At the time you were busy
learning to use
the big-boy potty.
Ah. Well.
I did it.
Good job.
Uh, listen, Alan, I'm
looking for my daughter.
Drunk blonde?
Well, she isn't
always blonde.
Upstairs.
Thank you.
You know,
you turned out to be
a very attractive man.
Um, thank you.
Coulda gone either way.
Lucky you grew
into those ears.
(playing same tune)
♪ Frosty the Snowman
♪ Was a very jolly soul
♪ With a corncob pipe
and a button nose ♪
♪ And two eyes
made out of coal... ♪
Damn it, Charlie,
you don't know what
you're getting into here.
Oh, I think I have
a pretty good idea.
I mean, what could you possibly
tell me about Gloria
that would get me
to kick her out of bed?
She's married? Clinically
insane? She's a man?
You're not a
man, are you?
Nope.
Then we're good.
Gloria, get out
of that bed.
Mom?
"Mom"?
Well, did you tell them?
I tried, but I couldn't.
Why not?
What do you mean, why
not? Why do you think?
Oh, so, as usual, I have
to do your dirty work.
You can't sleep with him
because he might
be your brother.
There, was that so hard?
It's certainly not hard for
someone who has no shame.
Says the woman who
killed my husband.
I did not kill Sherman.
I made Sherman happy.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Hold on. Hold on.
Can we go back to the part
where I may be her brother?
Oh, dear Lord,
has the blood
not returned
to your brain yet?
It was the '70s.
We were young,
attractive couples
and there was
a gas shortage
so we had to
"entertain" at home.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you saying you
and her husband...?
Yes, and she and
your father.
Blame OPEC.
It started with a
weekly fondue party,
but one night the dipping
didn't stop at cheese.
Unfortunately, some of
us couldn't handle it.
You did unspeakable
things with Sherman
and then he wanted
to do them with me.
Oh, nonsense.
I just raised
the bar a bit.
Raised the bar?
Do you have any idea how
many third-world countries
that man visited trying
to find someone else
who would do those things?
Oh, he didn't
have to go abroad.
He was just looking
for a bargain.
If it weren't for you
he would never have contracted
amoebic dysentery and died.
I hate to interrupt,
but I'm still trying
to process the
"I'm her brother" thing.
Mmm.
Not the shiniest penny
in the roll, is he?
All right.
I guess I better
spell it out for you.
Based on the amount
of time that elapsed
between the last fondue party
and Gloria's birth,
and not to mention
the fact that Sherman
lost interest in
traditional sex with me...
Thank you very much.
There is the very real
possibility
that your father
may be her father.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
So you can see why a
tryst of this nature
is completely
unacceptable.
It's not like we couldn't
have foreseen this,
given that your son has spent
the bulk of his adult life
humping his way through
the greater Los Angeles area.
Oh, and like this booze-addled
tart is an innocent victim.
Hey, I'm drunk, not deaf.
Just get out of bed
and get dressed.
Well, that
was humiliating.
Just be glad we didn't
have to tell them
about our little experiment.
EVELYN:
Don't remind me.
Oh, you loved it.
Oh, a third-act twist.
Wow.
Yeah.
I am so horny right now
I can't believe it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Did you miss what just
went down here... Sis?
Oh, come on. It's not like
we're gonna get married
and have a bunch
of web-footed kids..
You have absolutely no
boundaries, do you?
Well... I don't
like fat guys.
Interesting.
Turns out...
I draw the line at incest.
So you'd do a fat guy?
Do you hear that?
Charlie found
his boundary.
It's a miracle.
A Christmas miracle.
Judith, can I just say that this
was the best Christmas ever.
Yeah, well,
don't get used to it.
"'Twas the night
before Christmas
"And all through the house
Not a creature was stirring..."
(vomiting)
Okay, just so we're clear.
We are only doing this
to piss off my mom?
You have a problem with that?
No, that makes it better.