Previously, on...
I'm asking you
to marry me.
We might as well
just go to Vegas and elope.
If we're gonna have a family,
we'll need to turn the
second bedroom into a nursery.
But that's where
Jake stays.
Yeah, but once Alan moves out,
then Jake won't be
staying there anymore, right?
Alan's moving out?
Of course he is.
Isn't he?
I said the wedding's off.
Can I borrow your wedding ring?
What for?
Well, I thought,
as long as we're in Vegas,
I'd marry Kandi.
(laughing)
MAN:
I now pronounce
you man and wife.
You may kiss
the bride.
I don't freakin' believe it.
Cheer up, Charlie.
You're finally getting
what you always wanted—
I'm moving out of your house!
I don't freakin' believe it!
Do we have time to play
roulette before we go?
Oh, honey,
that is a sucker's game.
The odds are totally
stacked against y...
Ooh, Super
Slots O'Fun Jackpot.
Sure, make the smart bet.
Here, honey.
Kiss it before I put it in.
And the honeymoon begins.
Slots O'Fun— you get it?
It's Slots O'Fun.
I'm ready for a refill.
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
Is that good?
(bells ringing)
I won.
(laughing)
I won a half a
million dollars!
(screaming)
(both laughing)
I don't freakin' believe it.
Alan, you're rich!
We're rich!
We're married now—
what's mine is yours.
Really?
And the honeymoon ends.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men. ♪
Uh, excuse me.
Do you know
where Charlie is?
Who's Charlie?
(knocking at door)
Charlie?
You in here?
(laughing):
Hey, Alan.
Long time, no see.
Say hello to my brother Alan.
Hi, Alan.
Um...
I'm interrupting.
Gee, do you think?
Listen, I really
need to talk to you.
Can you come downstairs?
Sure.
Give me...
an hour and a half.
An hour and a half?
I know it's a little rushed,
but we're on
a tight schedule here.
Tina's got homework,
Cindy's got to meet her fiancé,
and Marie—
well, Marie's on the clock.
You already had two women in bed
Better safe than sorry.
I see.
Well, I guess I'll just
wait downstairs.
Good call.
'Cause, you know,
five's a crowd.
(door closes)
Okay, does everybody
remember their assignment?
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Think so.
Then let's do this thing.
Hour and a half
on the dot.
Can I plan or what?
Hey, come on.
Show a little class.
So, how's the newlywed?
Still living the dream?
Well...
I got to tell you, buddy,
things haven't been the same
around here since you left.
That's nice, but...
Yeah, they've been way better.
I mean, look around.
I don't even know
these people.
Yeah, and I can have sex
in every room in the house now.
I had forgotten
how much fun you can have
on top of a washing machine.
You know— hibbe-dah, hibbe-dah,
hibbe-dah, hibbe-dah.
That does sound like fun, but...
And the best part of all is,
without Jake here,
Mom has no reason to visit.
Heck, I may not have to see
her again till we meet in hell.
I'm happy for you...
Come to think of it,
without Jake here,
there's no reason
for you to visit, either.
I'm your brother.
Yeah, so?
I'm your brother—
I don't visit you.
Charlie, listen to me.
My wife threw me out.
Aw, dude...
that's awful.
Yeah.
Well, thanks
for stopping by.
Aren't you listening to me?
Kandi doesn't love me anymore.
My marriage is over.
My life is in ruins.
Whoa.
What?
Déjà vu.
It's as if I've lived
through this before
and didn't really enjoy it.
Charlie, I...
But wait, there's
a difference.
This time,
you can get your own place
instead of sponging off me,
'cause you have money now,
right?
Uh, well...
Oh, you suck!
It wasn't my fault.
There were taxes and the condo
and Kandi's new car
and Kandi's new clothes
and the shoes.
Oh, God, so many shoes.
How much do you have left?
Eleven dollars.
Okay, okay, let's start
from the beginning.
Well, things were fine
until about a month ago.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll go back upstairs,
you come knock on my door again
and say you want
to talk to me.
Only this time, I'll kill you!
Oh, come on.
You're all I have left
in this world.
I need you, Charlie!
Anybody here know a Charlie?
♪ Men. ♪
Ah, geez.
I'm working for Caligula.
Hi, Berta.
Hey, Zippy.
What are you doing here?
My marriage is over.
Kandi kicked me out.
Damn, that's horrible.
Yeah.
Damn, damn, damn!
Tell me about it.
I had October in the pool.
Pool? What-what-what pool?
Me, your brother, your mom,
a couple of neighbors,
had a pool on how long
before she dumped your ass.
I was so close!
You were betting that
my marriage was going to fail?
No.
We were betting on when.
So Charlie took
you back, huh?
Well, not with open arms
or an open heart
or even an open door.
After he pushed me out, I had
to climb in through the window.
But yeah, I'm back.
Well, I'm glad.
You're kidding.
No.
With you and
the kid around,
I won't have to hose down
the washing machine so often.
(doorbell rings)
I'll get that.
I guess there's no trusting
this butter now.
Or the loose bananas.
Hello, Alan.
Judith.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, buddy.
So is somebody going to explain
to me what the heck is going on?
I thought he should
hear it from you.
(sighs):
Okay.
Jake, listen,
I know you liked Kandi
very much,
but she and I have decided that
we really can't stay married.
Ah, man!
That doesn't mean that you
can't be friends with her.
No. I had December.
Alan, I just want to say
I'm very sorry
things didn't work out
for you and Kandi.
Thanks.
You won the pool,
didn't you?
Yeah.
And just FYI,
I spoke to my lawyer,
and he said that
even if Kandi takes you
for everything you've got, you
still have to pay me alimony.
Here's his bill.
(scoffs)
Six hundred dollars?
He explained it very slowly.
You didn't call.
What?
When Dad moved out,
you said you and me
could still get
together and do stuff.
But you never called.
Ah, geez, Jake, I'm sorry.
I waited.
I'll make it up to you.
When?
Later.
I'm still here.
What do you
want me to do, Jake?
I don't know.
You really let me down,
and it hurt my feelings.
I know. I feel awful.
Fifty bucks and
it goes away.
Ten.
Done.
Love you, Uncle Charlie.
Back at you.
♪ Men. ♪
How long is he going
to sit out there?
I don't know, Jake.
He's pretty depressed.
Yeah, well,
that's the price you pay
when you think
with your penis.
Did you hear that
from your mother?
No, your mother.
And how are you feeling
about all this?
I'm okay.
You sure?
Uncle Charlie,
this is not my first divorce.
Got it.
Tell you one thing, though—
I am never getting married.
That's a sweet dream
to have, Jake.
But sooner
or later,
you're going to meet a girl
who's smart, beautiful,
and has a real grudge
against your parents.
What are you going
to do then?
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
Really?
Yeah. If a girl falls
in love with me,
I'll tell her I can't marry her
until I have enough money,
even though
I'll be secretly rich.
How do you plan
to get secretly rich?
I'm going to marry a movie star.
You're going
to marry a movie star
to avoid getting married?
Guess I haven't worked out
all the bugs.
Well, keep me posted.
Hey.
Jake sure changed
in the last few months.
Starting to see a
real little man there.
Mm-hmm.
Not a real bright little man.
What you doing?
Making plans.
Do they involve
marrying a movie star?
What?
Nothing, nothing.
What's your plan?
Well, I figured
I'd have a nice big lunch,
get real drunk,
stroll down to the beach,
and try to swim to Japan.
Huh.
Why the lunch?
I want to cramp up and drown
before the sharks rip me
to shreds.
Well, keep me posted.
I'm a failure, Charlie.
Everything I've tried to do
in my life has ended
in complete abject failure.
Oh, buddy, you're looking
at this the wrong way.
See?
I've failed again.
Will you shut up
and listen to me?
Failure is nothing
to be ashamed of.
It's a part of life,
it's how we learn.
Well, you know what?
I've failed
for almost 40 years.
And what have I learned?
Oh, that wasn't a
rhetorical question?
Come on, Alan.
You got to have a sense
of humor about this.
A broke-ass,
middle-aged guy
marries a 22-year-old
knucklehead
just before he wins a
half a million dollars.
And then she takes him
for everything he's got.
(chuckles)
That's hilarious.
Okay, okay.
Okay, maybe you're
too close to it now,
but trust me,
it's funny.
(inhales deeply)
Hmm.
Where are you going?
The ocean's that way.
♪ Men. ♪
(knock at door)
Hey, the kid and I are
going to the movies.
You want to come?
No, thanks.
Can I get you
something to eat?
No.
Something to drink?
How about a bottle
of Scotch and a hooker?
I just want to be alone.
Well, you don't need my help
for that.
That's your home run swing.
Just close the door
on the way out.
Fine, I'll close it.
Then I'll nail it shut
and plaster it over
and hang a picture of something
a little more cheerful,
like a plane crash.
Okay.
I am through feeling sorry
for myself.
Maybe not.
(knock at door)
Alan?
Oh, terrific.
Charlie told me
about you and Candy.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, thanks.
Did he also tell you
I want to be alone?
Yes, he did, so...
want some company?
No.
How about a hug?
Is it a good-bye hug?
Alan, I know what it's
like to lose at love.
Rose?
Yes, baby?
You're a stalker.
I prefer to be called
boundary-challenged.
Just go away.
Go away?
(laughs)
Alan, I'm a stalker.
Trust me.
This pain will pass.
The aching emptiness
that's swallowing up your heart
will be transformed
into something beautiful.
What's that?
Resentment.
A burning,
white hot resentment
that empowers you to commit
unspeakable acts of revenge.
You're going
to want a scrapbook.
♪ Men. ♪
Dad?
Yeah.
Uncle Charlie's going
to take me back to Mom's now.
Well, come in here
and say good-bye.
Bye.
That's it? Come here
and give your old dad a hug.
That's better.
You still depressed?
Oh, no, no, I'm fine.
Just taking a little nap.
You've been napping
for two days.
I'm getting old, Jake.
Old people nap a lot.
It's kind of a dry run
for death.
Okay.
Well, see you.
See you.
Hey, Dad?
Yeah?
Even though
Mom stopped loving you
and Kandi stopped loving you,
you don't have to worry
about me.
Thanks, pal.
You're my dad.
I pretty much got to love you.
So?
Is he still curled up
like a cocktail shrimp?
Yep.
This is a real fun weekend.
Wait in the car, Jake,
and I'll be right there.
Okay. I am running out
of patience with this guy.
I've had relationships end,
and I don't go crawling
into bed over it.
(clears throat)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what I mean.
It may not be just
the relationship.
What are you talking about?
Charlie, I've studied
psychology for eight years
and been a
patient for 20.
Your brother is exhibiting
all the classic signs
of clinical depression.
What are you saying? You think
he might try to hurt himself?
The important question is,
do we stop him?
Oh, like I'm the only one
here thinking that.
All right, I didn't
want to have to do this,
but desperate times call
for desperate measures.
What are you going to do?
Something I hoped
I'd never have to.
You don't mean...?
I'm afraid so.
Hello?
Mom?
(knock at door)
Oh, God, what plague
have you set upon me now?
Alan, it's Mommy.
Good one.
Oh, my poor
darling.
How are you holding up?
How do you think?
I blew another marriage.
I wasted all my money.
I'm a complete
and utter failure.
Oh, sweetie,
you just can't see
the big picture,
can you?
What big picture?
Every foolish choice
you've made,
every wasted opportunity,
every hapless misstep in your
sad, misbegotten life...
I know, I know...
It's an opportunity
to learn and grow.
Well, perhaps,
but more importantly,
it's a reflection on me.
Always good to see you, Mom.
I'm not finished.
Of course not.
There is a silver lining
in this dark cloud.
I can't wait to
hear about it.
(clears throat)
You're all alone,
you're penniless,
and you have no prospects.
Are we at the silver lining
part yet?
Yes. Short of contracting
a flesh-eating disease,
things couldn't possibly
get any worse.
You've hit rock bottom.
You have nowhere to go but up.
You know what?
You're right.
You're self-obsessed,
insensitive and soul-sucking,
but you're right.
I have stared into the abyss,
and I'm still here.
I-I've had my heart shattered,
and then...
and then shattered again,
and I'm still here.
I've taken every piece of crap
that life could throw at me,
and I'm still here.
Well, we don't have to turn this
into an evening
with Liza Minnelli.
Now, get washed,
get dressed,
get on with your life.
Okay.
And remember, no matter what,
I'll always love you.
I know. Thanks.
Oh, don't thank me,
sweetheart.
I'm your mother.
I have to love you.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Thanks for taking Jake back
to Judith's.
No problem.
Sorry I had to send Mom
in there.
No, no, you, uh...
you did the right thing.
I needed a good slap
in the face.
Although, with Mom,
it's more like a nail
gun to the testicles.
That was my thinking.
Well, uh...
I'm really grateful.
Don't mention it.
So, look at us, huh?
Just like old times.
(laughs)
Yep.
The Harper brothers,
together again.
(laughs)
Uh-huh.
The chicks
will come and go,
but you and I will always
be there for each other.
Sure.
Forever.
Well, you know, not...
not literally
till the end of time,
but, you know,
till one of us dies.
It'll probably be you,
'cause you don't take
very good care of yourself.
Gotcha.
Fist me.
You want me to fist you?
You know, like the,
the bros in the hood.
We're the bros,
and this is our hood.
(laughs)
Pow! Right on.
Tell you what.
I will grab us
a couple of brewskis
so that Team Harper
can kick back and chill.
Terrific.
Uh,
but I'll get you a beer.
Okay.
Oh, uh, maybe I'll make
a nice little plate
of cheese
and crackers.
Hmm, nothing fancy.
Good.
Ooh. Uh, I don't suppose
you have any brie?
I don't know.
Not important.
You relax.
I got you covered. Pow!
♪ Men. ♪