"Help me out
here, Doc.
I need a time of death."
"Sorry, Lieutenant,
but I can't give you
"an official T.O.D. until
I get her on the slab.
"But based on
hypostatic lividity
"and degree of rigor,
I'd say our cheerleader
got her pom-poms pierced
right around halftime."
Real?
Real.
"Anything else?"
"Left-handed assailant,
used a single-edged blade,
multiple entry wounds
and defensive trauma."
"So how are we gonna
find this psychopath?"
"Well,
like our killer,
we'll just have to...
take a stab at it."
That's it.
(light applauding)
So, you think I'll get the part?
Uh, well, I for one
totally buy you
as a brilliant forensic
investigator.
Thanks, but I believe
it's pronounced "fornesic."
What do you think, Charlie?
Unbelievable.
Aw...
I mean... beyond belief.
That's sweet.
I mean...
I just don't believe it.
You made your point, Charlie.
Do you like what I did
with the glasses?
On, smart...
off, hot.
My mind is just
completely blown.
So when are you
gonna be on TV?
I have to pass
the audition first.
Let's not put the cart
before the whores.
Horse.
(clears throat):
Maybe a little.
I've been rehearsing all day.
(makes exploding noise)
What's the name
of the show?
Stiffs.
Stiffs?
You know,
like dead bodies.
Oh, right. Sure.
I know what
you were thinking.
Well, I better go.
The audition's at 4:00
and I still have to get
my tan sprayed on.
Best of luck.
It has nothing to do
with luck, Alan.
You just have to stand still
and keep your eyes
and mouth closed.
No, I meant...
Never mind.
Knock 'em dead
at the audition.
Thanks.
And thanks for lending me
your chiropractor coat.
It makes me feel
like a real doctor.
Now you know why Alan wears it.
Okay, well, uh,
tell me how it goes.
I will.
Oh, and by the way.
Did you get the divorce papers?
Not really, but my lawyer
explained them to me. Bye.
The-They need to be signed.
Kandi?
(engine starts)
(vehicle departs)
Hey, what's
your hurry?
If she becomes a big TV star
while you're still married,
she'll have to pay you alimony.
Yeah, and if pigs start
flying out of my rear end,
we'll have free bacon
for the rest of our lives.
I don't know that
I'd eat that bacon.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
(knocking)
(knocking continues)
Isn't anybody
gonna get that?
Jake?
Yeah?
(knocking)
What are you doing?
Hanging posters.
Did you consider
using scotch tape?
It doesn't hold as well.
Especially her.
Who is that?
Raven.
She's the North American
ladies' wrestling champ.
Aha.
All oiled up and
ready to... wrestle.
(knocking)
Damn it! This isn't funny!
Quick little bastards.
What happened to your
Harry Potter posters?
I'm not a kid
anymore, Dad.
You don't have to be a kid
to like Harry Potter.
You want it, take it.
Aw, Harry.
You crumpled Harry.
You remember when we got this?
No.
Oh, come on, we stood on line
outside that bookstore
at midnight
to get one of
the first copies?
You were dressed as Harry and
I was dressed as Dumbledore.
I don't remember, Dad.
Sure you do.
You made fun of that
other kid 'cause he had
a flying mop instead
of a broom, and, uh,
he started crying and his father
punched me in the chest?
No.
Yeah, well, you weren't
the one with the cracked rib.
Anyway, what, uh, what
prompted you to...
redecorate like this?
I don't know, I like
cars and wrestling.
And wet T-shirts, apparently.
Oh, there is a wet T-shirt
on that— I hadn't noticed.
(knocking)
Ha!
Jake's redecorating.
Yeah, I can see that.
Oh, Raven.
Those are fake,
by the way.
Charlie!
What? He has
a right to know.
I'm just glad the little
guy's got me to...
Wait a minute.
Are those nails in my wall?
Are you out
of your freakin' mind?
No.
No? That's your answer? No?
Yeah.
Charlie...
Charlie, come on.
For God's sake!
These are railroad spikes!
I'll putty over it.
That's not plaster
board, that's stucco.
You can't
just putty stucco.
I know, I'll fix it.
Let's just give
him some privacy.
Wait, wait, wait.
At least I can take one
hammer out of his hand.
♪ Men... ♪
ALAN (on TV):
Jake, look at Daddy.
Look at Daddy.
Ah, that's my boy.
Where's Daddy?
Daddy's over here.
Wasn't he adorable?
Yeah.
Hey, could you rewind
to Judith breast-feeding him?
That was
really adorable.
Especially the part
where she does
the old switcheroo.
(baby Jake babbling)
I miss that little boy.
Seems like only yesterday
I could hold him in one arm.
He didn't weigh more
than eight or nine pounds.
He craps more than that now.
Where did the time go?
His childhood is almost over
and there's still so much stuff
I want to do with him.
Like what?
You know,
father-son stuff.
Pretty soon, there'll be
no more playing catch
or riding bikes.
Do you realize
I've never even taken him
fishing or camping
or hunting?
Do you know how to fish
or camp or hunt?
That's not the point.
I-I-I thought
we would learn together.
Oh, that sounds good.
You and knucklehead
out in the woods
taking turns shooting
each other in the ass.
Okay, it's not so much
about hunting, per se.
"Per se."
There's an outdoorsy phrase.
It's about bonding.
Before you know it,
he'll have no interest in
spending time with me at all.
Not unless you grow boobs
and straddle a Harley.
All right, look.
It doesn't help
to whine about it.
If you want
to get lost in the woods
with Jerky Gherkinheimer,
go do it.
My life is just
one big joke to you, isn't it?
Actually,
it's more of a limerick.
There once was a moron named Al,
who wanted to camp
with his pal...
Any chance you can go
camping in Nantucket?
So, Charlie,
where's the wife and kid?
They went camping to do
some father-son bonding.
(thunder booms)
(all laughing)
(wind whistling)
(thunder rumbling)
ALAN:
And when they looked at
the door handle of the car,
there was nothing there...
but a hook.
A hook?
That makes no sense.
Oh, I left out a part.
Um, uh, okay,
the guy who escaped
from the insane asylum
had lost his hand
in some kind of
an industrial accident.
Anyway, they replaced it
with a sharp metal hook.
And it was said hook
that was stuck
on the aforementioned
door handle.
(creepy voice):
Ooh...
Dad, over the past
three birthdays
I've gotten $175 in
bookstore gift cards.
They're yours
if we can just go home.
No, no, we're having fun.
Hey, I know—
we'll sing a song.
♪ On top of spaghetti
♪ All covered with cheese
Come on, you used
to love this one.
♪ I lost my poor meatball
♪ When somebody sneezed
(thunder booms)
♪ It rolled off the table
♪ And... onto the floor
Come on!
♪ And then my poor meatball
♪ Rolled right out the door.
♪ Men... ♪
Dad...
Yeah, buddy?
Bite me.
You'll see.
Someday you and and I will look
back on this weekend
and laugh and laugh...
I didn't say someday soon.
Hey, come on.
I thought you liked
wet T-shirts.
Hey.
Shut up.
Oh, come on, Alan.
We both know
I can't do that.
What do you want
me to say,
that it was a bad idea?
Okay, it was a bad idea.
And the only thing we bonded
over was our mutual discomfort
with pooping into a coffee can.
It wasn't Chock Full O' Nuts,
was it?
Sorry, sorry. Where's Jake?
He went back to his friends
in Hooterville.
Well, I can't blame him.
It never rains
in Hooterville.
Look, Alan, seriously,
I'm, I'm sorry
it didn't work out.
I know your heart
was in the right place.
Thank you.
Now, I finished the limerick.
You want to hear it?
Too soon?
You don't get it.
You don't understand
what it's like
to be a little boy's
best friend,
to be someone he looks up to,
and then one day you turn around
and the only person he looks up
to is covered with baby oil
and nailed to the ceiling.
Count your blessings.
There's all kinds of pictures
that could have been up there.
Yeah, I guess.
It could have been
the Moscow Ballet.
I got it. Still,
I can't help but feel
a little empty inside,
like, like a chapter
of my life is over.
So? You've still got plenty
to look forward to.
You mean, besides work,
loneliness and death?
Absolutely.
There's memory loss...
impotence, adult diapers.
I'm all you've got, pal.
That's true.
My wives are gone,
my son is grown,
but I'll always have you...
my brother.
Forever.
Okay, now, I was just having
fun, but that was mean.
♪ Men.
Well, when will he be back?
All right,
tell him I called again.
Boy, some agent.
He never calls,
he never returns my calls.
I'm almost sorry
I let him feel me up.
I guess that's showbiz.
That's what he said.
Uh, listen, Kandi...
I really thought they liked me
at that audition.
They had me read three times,
and then all the jumping jacks.
Jumping jacks?
It's an action series, Alan.
They need to know that I'm fit.
Ah. Uh, listen, Kandi,
there's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
If it's about
the divorce papers
I haven't signed
them yet.
No, no, that's not
why I'm here.
Um, sweetie, do you remember
why we split up?
The big reason or all
the little reasons?
The big one.
'Cause there were
a lot of little
reasons, Alan.
I know.
Like the way your toenails
grow all crazy.
Right.
And your ear hair
and your nose hair.
Got it.
And that one long hair
on your back, yuck!
Wait, forget
the little reasons.
Just, just the big one.
Yeah, you didn't want
to have a baby, and I did.
Right. Well, what would you say
if I were to tell you that
I've changed my mind about that?
Really?
Yeah, I've just been thinking
that Jake is almost grown
and there's still a lot of daddy
left in me.
So you want to have a baby?
Yes, I do.
A fresh start,
a-a-a new chapter.
Wow, that's a big step.
Yeah, I know.
I know it is.
So if you want
to think about it...
No, that's okay.
Let's make a baby.
Just like that?
Don't you want to talk
about it some more?
Alan, it's practically
all we talked about
our entire marriage.
Baby, baby, toenails,
baby, ear hair, baby,
how clocks work, baby.
(chuckles)
So... so you really
want to do this?
Do what?
You see, if you use tape,
it's much easier
to rotate in new posters
when these ones
stop working for you.
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
Trust me. After a while,
these beautiful eyes
are gonna be filled
with judgment and condemnation.
What are you talking about?
Okay, maybe that was just me.
Anyway, you're lucky
your dad lets you hang
posters like this.
I guess.
Does your mother let you?
No way.
So what do you got
at her house,
a secret stash
of magazines?
Just one. Playboy 1998,
the Christmas issue.
God bless Hugh Hefner, huh?
God bless Kimberly Macadoo
from Portland, Oregon
born March 4, 1979.
Turn-ons:
sunshine and goatees.
Turn-offs:
judgmental people and war.
Gotta love a chick
who doesn't like war.
Tape me.
Hey, Uncle Charlie,
could you do me a favor?
If it's the favor I'm thinking
of, not until you're 18
and not in my house.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
What do you need?
Could you get my dad
to lay off the father-son stuff?
It's kinda lame.
Lame? You think it's lame
your father cares
so much about you
he wants nothing more
than to be part of your life?
Yeah.
Look, you gotta understand
what your father's going
through.
What do you mean?
Okay, here's the deal.
Your father has reached
a very difficult age.
It's confusing
and a little bit
scary for him.
Scary how?
Well, first of all,
his body's changing.
Really?
Oh, yeah. Hair is growing
where it's never grown before.
That is scary.
And then there's
the hormones.
Hormones?
Yep, your father
is running out of them.
Sounds bad.
No, no, it's just a
perfectly natural part
of growing old, Jake.
Is it happening to you?
No, no, no.
My point is that your father
is going through this phase
and you have to be patient
and understanding.
So he's gonna want
to go camping again?
Probably not in this lifetime.
But you might have to play
catch with him or something.
Guess I could do that.
Atta boy.
All right, well, I'm glad
we had this little talk.
Now I'm gonna go get hammered.
(English accent):
Hello, ladies, I'm Harry Potter.
♪ Men.
Is there anything special
we have to do?
Oh, no, no.
It's just like
regular sex,
but without all the
last-minute fumbling
for a condom.
Oh, okay, but I still
get all the rest
of the fumbling, right?
I prefer to call
that "foreplay."
(phone rings)
Hold on.
Hello.
This is she.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Hold on a sec.
Here, we're divorced.
Okay, I'm back.
You were saying?
Really?
I got the part?
Thank you so much.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Alan, I got the part.
Oh, that's terrific.
Congratulations.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Put that thing away.
But I-I thought...
Oh, please, nobody wants
to see a pregnant
fornesic investigator.
Hey, can we still do it
with a condom?
♪ Men.
(sportscast playing)
It's dark out.
Okay.
I tried.
Help me out here, Doc.
I need a time of death
for our little cheerleader.
I can't give you
an official T.O.D.
until I get her on the slab.
But based on hypostatic
lividity and degree of rigor,
I'd say our cheerleader
got her pom-poms pierced
right around halftime.
Anything else?
Left-handed assailant,
used a single-edge blade,
multiple entry wounds
and defensive trauma.
So how are we gonna find
this psychopath?
Well, like our killer, we'll
just have to take a stab at it.
♪ Mama's got a squeezebox,
Daddy never sleeps at night ♪
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
They're real, you know.
I know, I was married to her.
Oh, yeah.
Dawg!
You know what?
I'll be in my room.
When are you guys
going fishing?