So you understand
the situation?
I think so.
Now that we're not
married anymore,
you want to sell
my condo.
No, no, it's, it's our condo.
I got it for us.
Not the smartest thing
I ever did,
but my real estate adviser
was my penis.
Is that what they mean
when they say
the market's gone soft?
I don't think so.
Look, my point is
I can't afford
to carry the mortgage
on this place,
but if we sell it,
then we can split the profit.
Or I could
buy you out.
Do you have money?
I will after we sell.
I am at the end of my rope.
If can't get out
from under these bills,
I may well have
to declare bankruptcy.
Wow,
that sounds
really serious.
It is deadly serious.
Well, in that case...
Want to have sex?
What?
I'm horny, you're stressed,
seems like we both benefit.
Well, I am really stressed.
No, that's not going
to solve anything!
Okay.
Well, I'm gonna go
take a shower.
Let me know
if you change your mind.
I changed my mind.
(snorts)
(groans)
I either drank too much...
or got hit by a train.
Oh, God... train.
Charlie.
Oh, look,
it's my sweet angel
come to take me to heaven.
Don't touch me.
I hope you're proud
of yourself.
Well, I didn't wake up
in my own vomit,
so, yeah, kinda.
You are such
a child.
Many people find that
to be an endearing
quality.
I'm not one of them.
It would appear not.
We had fun last night,
though, right?
Oh, terrific.
What woman doesn't enjoy
pleasing a man
who falls asleep while he's
in the middle of reciprocating?
That explains why I dreamt
I was kissing Abe Lincoln.
Okay, some underwear,
no need to panic.
And a little bit of makeup,
no biggie.
Running shoes, reading glasses,
flannel nightgown
and the latest issue
of Modern Bride magazine.
Red alert.
Lydia?
What?
I couldn't help but notice
that you put some of your stuff
in one of my drawers.
Yeah. Hey, you want
to come in here
and make up
for last night?
Well, yeah, but I think
we should talk
about this drawer thing.
Okay,
talk.
Four score and
seven years ago
our fathers brought forth
a upon this continent
a new nation...
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Morning.
That was a great job.
Yeah, you know it's good
when you feel dirtier
coming out than you did
going in.
So what are you doing?
Just practicing.
For what?
Nothing in particular.
Just keeping sharp
for my work.
Oh, yeah, your
little jingle thing.
Hard to believe
that takes practice.
Berta, I'd like
some scrambled egg whites,
dry wheat toast
and Earl Grey tea.
Oh, yeah? well, I'd
like some new shoes
a jet pack
and a waistline.
You really thought
she was going
to make you breakfast?
Yo, bro.
Hey.
How'd it go with Kandi?
(chuckling):
Great, just great.
Turns out we can be friends
with benefits.
Ooh, nice. Did she agree
to sell the condo?
What?
Isn't that why
you went over there
in the first place?
Oh, yeah.
Son of a bitch!
Charlie,
you need to talk
to your maid.
Shh-shh-shh-shh!
Keep your voice down.
Yeah, we don't use
the "M" word around here.
Why not?
Because it's
disrespectful.
And demeaning.
And wildly inaccurate.
The point is, Berta's the one
who keeps this house running,
and more important,
she's kinda like family.
She's rude, offensive
and vulgar.
Okay, exactly like family.
Fine.
See if she'll do that thing
with the ice cubes
and the silk handkerchief
you like so much.
Come on, sweetie,
don't be like that.
Ice cubes
and a silk handkerchief?
You can also use
a Popsicle and a necktie.
But I do owe you
a silk handkerchief.
And your Water Pik's
kinda iffy.
And whatever you do,
don't lick your hairbrush.
♪ Men.
I'm sorry to come over here
and bother you again,
but we never finished talking
about selling the condo.
But I don't want
to sell the condo.
I can see boats from here.
I understand, but I can't
afford the payments.
I like boats.
All right, well,
if you won't...
you won't cooperate,
I'll just have
to call my lawyer.
What are you doing?
Chester lost his bone.
I'm looking for it.
Now? Can't it wait?
No, when Chester wakes up
from his nap,
he's gonna want his bone.
You can keep talking.
Okay, well, as I said,
if you won't be reasonable,
I'll just have to...
to..
Have to what, Alan?
Son of a bitch!
♪ Men.
(gasps)
What the...?
We need to talk.
Okay.
I don't mind your girlfriends
throwing the occasional thong
or panties into the hamper.
I just boil 'em
and sell 'em at the swap meet,
but this broad
is taking advantage
of my easygoing nature.
Now, to be fair,
Lydia does have her positive
attributes.
Yeah, well, I ain't hitting
any of them attributes
so I don't give
a rat's ass.
All right, all right.
You know what
she said to me, Charlie?
She said I need to learn
my place around here.
Oh, she didn't.
Ah, but she did.
Is that true, Charlie?
Do I need to learn
my place around here?
No, Berta,
we all know our place.
And where is that
place, Charlie?
Wherever you want
it to be.
There's only room
for one alpha dog
in this house.
I know.
And who is that
alpha dog, Charlie?
You are.
Say it.
You're the alpha dog.
Aw, you sweet talker you.
We'll just pretend
that's morning wood.
♪ Men.
Hi, how's it going?
Well, look who's finally up.
I need some lotion on my back.
Oh, sure.
Listen, I have to talk
to you about Berta.
For God's sake, Charlie,
grow a pair.
Is this your house or hers?
Well, my name's on the deed,
but she was here first.
Thing is,
over the years
Berta and I have developed
a really nice working
relationship.
Do my thighs.
Right.
And the key to a happy
home, I find,
is to not rock the boat.
Not tamper
with that balance.
So you really need
to make the effort...
Where is she now?
Huh? Oh, she went shopping.
Anybody else around?
No. Anyway,
the thing with Berta...
Why don't you put some sunscreen
on your cute little bottom?
What for?
'Cause I wouldn't want you
to get a nasty burn.
Why would I get a nasty...?
Oh, we have sex.
Good thing you're pretty
'cause you're very slow.
♪ Men
(mimics Lydia):
Grow a pair, Charlie.
Hey, Alan, come here.
What's going on?
I'm doing Lydia's laundry.
Can I throw in
my handkerchief?
It wouldn't help.
You'll probably have to burn it.
Okay. And why are you
doing Lydia's laundry?
'Cause Berta won't.
Then why doesn't Lydia
do it herself?
'Cause I told her
I'd get Berta to do it.
Aha. And do you have
any idea how to do laundry?
Oh, come on. You wash 'em,
you dry 'em.
How tough could it be?
So what do you need me for?
Which one's the washer?
That one.
Thanks.
Just kidding.
It's that one.
Sorry.
It was the first one.
Look, it says "Wash"
on the dial.
Okay, okay, I can do this.
I just turn it on
and stick 'em in.
It's a washing machine,
not a cocktail waitress.
Let's start by
separating the delicates.
How is that not like
a cocktail waitress?
The reason you need
to do these separately
is they're
mostly synthetic.
Add a beat-up Civic
and an ex-husband
and we're back to
cocktail waitress.
Charming. Hand me
the detergent.
This stuff here?
No, no, that's
fabric softener.
You put that in after
the first rinse cycle.
You know what? Maybe I'll just
buy her some new clothes.
Don't be such a baby.
Detergent.
See?
Here we go.
Cold wash.
Cold rinse.
Gentle cycle.
Done.
(water running)
What's that?
That would be water
entering the washing machine.
Amazing.
Mmm.
Yeah, it's pretty
cutting edge.
(water flow stops)
Did I break it?
Close the lid.
(water running)
Well, son of a gun.
(water flow stops)
(water running)
(water stops)
what will they think of next?
Yeah, I hear scientists
are working on a machine
that can cook two pieces
of bread at the same time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
very funny.
Now what?
We wait.
How will we know
when they're done?
Don't worry, the machine'll
call you on your cell phone.
Really?
I don't know what Berta
is always complaining about.
This is kinda fun.
Yeah, well, you're dealing
with pretty-girl underwear.
Berta has gotta handle
Jake's skivvies
after P.E. and
pudding pops.
Good point.
What are you doing?
Pouring a glass of vodka.
Is that part of
"doing the laundry"?
'Cause I could really
get into this.
No, I'm just mad at myself.
Well, in that case,
pour me one.
I'm mad at you, too.
So what's the problem?
I went over to
Kandi's again.
And how'd that go?
Not only are we not
selling the condo,
I may have promised to
buy her a new fridge.
Oh, Alan.
She likes getting ice without
having to open the door.
You poor, whipped sap.
Me? What about you?
What about me?
Charlie, you're
doing a woman's laundry.
No, no, no. No. See,
that's just me
trying to pitch in.
Oh, just face it.
Lydia's got you
wrapped around
her little finger.
She does not.
She uses this one.
And it's not so much wrapped
as... skewered.
Who's using my washing machine?
Excuse me, but it's my
washing machine,
and I'm using it
to wash Lydia's clothes.
You're doing laundry?
Hey, it's not rocket science.
Cold wash, cold rinse,
gentle cycle,
but first,
you separate the delicates.
Is that so?
Yeah, that's so.
(phone rings)
That's probably them now.
Hello.
Oh, hey, Mom.
I thought you were
my washing machine.
♪ Men.
Rodney Cerman's
the lone setback.
Fox straight back again.
He's got...
Oh, come on—
throw the ball.
Throw the ball!
Or... fall down.
Charlie, I'm leaving.
Bye.
I'd like a kiss.
She's still there,
isn't she?
Yep.
Just kidding, sweetie.
That's better.
Good-bye, Jake.
I'm not kissing you.
Oh, Charlie,
I almost forgot.
I'm serving hors d'oeuvres
at an open house tomorrow,
so I'll need to borrow
Berta for a couple of hours.
Say what?
I'm talking to Charlie.
You don't mind,
do you?
Mind? Well, I, uh...
You want to borrow me?
What am I,
a carpet steamer?
I'm not saying
I won't pay you.
Plus, you can take home
all the leftovers.
Oh, gee, why don't you just
toss them all in a big bowl,
and I'll eat them
out in the yard?
Well, that's a little
uncalled for.
I thought I was
doing you a favor.
You want to do me a favor,
you take the money
that you were going
to pay me,
convert it into
rolls of nickels,
then bend
over and...
Berta!
Berta! Berta.
Well, I don't have to stand
here and listen to this.
Charlie, you have
to make a decision.
It's her... or me.
The skank's
right, Charlie.
It's her or me.
Great.
That's just great.
Did somebody say there
was a big bowl of food?
♪ Men.
You got an offer on the condo?
Oh. Oh, Mom, you're a lifesaver.
I don't care. I fully expect
to take a loss.
At least I don't have
to pay you a commission.
Oh, come on, you're my mother.
Wait, wait, hang on, Mom,
I've got another call coming in.
Hello.
Oh, oh, Kandi, Kandi, hello.
Yeah, listen. Um,
about the condo.
My mom just got a very
reasonable offer and...
I give up. What are you wearing?
Hang on.
Mom, I gotta go.
Kandi, I'll be right there.
(whispers):
Hey.
Is Berta here?
I haven't seen her.
Great.
I have to admit, Charlie,
I never thought you'd have
the cojones to fire Berta.
Are you kidding?
I've got huge cojones.
Why do you think I'm
wearing these baggy shorts?
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, you fired Berta?
Yes, Alan.
She didn't know her place
and she had to go.
But we can't live
without Berta.
I'll be right there, sweetie.
Hurry.
You know what?
We need to work on our
communication skills.
You know, I always thought
that, but I didn't think
you'd be open to...
No, no, no, you jackass.
God, you play along like
a monkey with a mandolin.
You mean you didn't fire Berta?
That's it. Give me the mandolin.
But you promised Berta
you'd get rid of Lydia.
Alan, do you know
what this is?
No.
Then shut your stupid mouth.
And don't tell
Berta she was here.
Fine. Just give me a heads up
when you're lying.
I'm always lying.
I'll give you
a heads up when I'm not.
Yeah, you're the smart one.
Know how I know?
The washing machine
called and told me.
Ooh! High heels and Cool Whip.
(toilet flushing)
Oh, Charlie, how could you?
Berta, this is not
what it looks like.
Charlie, you lied to me.
Lydia, this is not
what it looks like.
That's it. I'm outta here.
Me, too.
Berta. Lydia.
Oh, come on, wait!
This is not what
it looks like!
(doors slam)
Say it a few
more times, Charlie.
Maybe somebody will believe you.
Berta. Berta,
Berta, Berta.
Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
You can't quit.
Why not?
Because we're family.
We love each other.
We forgive each other
our shortcomings.
Oh, bite me.
Don't go, don't go.
I promise I'll break
it off with her.
No, you won't. And you
want to know why?
'Cause you are
addicted to this broad.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
I can stop anytime I want.
No, you can't.
You're a nookie junkie,
and I just can't
trust you anymore.
No, no, no,
no, no, wait.
Wait! Wait, wait,
wait, wait.
You're right.
I am addicted.
I've got a vagina on my back,
but I know I can get it off.
I mean... you've got to help me.
I can't help you, pal.
You've got to help yourself.
Good-bye, Charlie.
Oh, come on, Berta, don't go.
I'll do anything!
I'm leaving now.
You don't have to!
I just fired her.
Good-bye, Charlie.
Oh, come on, Lydia,
don't go.
I'll do anything!
You know what?
I don't need either one of you.
I can do my own laundry
and I've got my own finger.
♪ Men.
I don't like it here.
Well, tough.
This is the only way
I can get Berta to come back.
But why do I
have to be here?
'Cause it's the only
way you're ever gonna
sell your condo.
Okay, let's get started.
Welcome to our regular
Monday night meeting.
Do we have any newcomers?
My name is Charlie and, uh...
my maid says I'm a sex addict.
GROUP:
Hi, Charlie.
Uh, hi.
Uh, I'm Alan and...
I have a lovely condo for sale.
And I'm a sex addict.
GROUP:
Hi, Alan.
It's priced to move.
Hi, my name is Pam...
and I'm a sex addict.
GROUP:
Hi, Pam.