(car door closes, footsteps)
Charlie:
thank you for
transporting me home.
You're a terrific cab driver
And i hope someday
to visit your country.
Damn, where
is that key?
Here, key-Key-Key-Key-
Key-Key-Key-Key.
Aha!
Hello, key.
(key rattling in lock)
Oh, no...
Wrong house.
I'm lost!
Hello?
Hi, alan. Come on in.
Um, why don't you come in here?
I can't. I lost my key.
Dah!
Had a few cocktails,
did we?
Me, too.
Listen, i need
to ask you a favor.
Your needs, your needs.
What about my needs?
Are you capable
of having a conversation?
Capable?
I just spent 20 minutes
discussing open-Toed shoes
With a fat man from rangoon.
He's a rangooni.
We'll talk in the morning.
I wouldn't
count on it.
Go ahead.
You talk, i'll cook.
It's 11:30.
What are you cooking?
Good question.
And i can give you
the answer in two words:
My famous homemade chili.
Since when do you make chili?
There's a lot you don't know
about me, alan.
I am man of many layers.
Strata, if you will.
I see.
A thin crust, magma
And a chewy
nougat center.
Okay, uh, anyway, tomorrow
i have to go to the dmv
To get my license renewed.
Ah, cars.
Where would we be
without cars?
And how do we get there?
Run, run, you're free!
Well, listen, the thing
is i can't take jake
Because he's got
a book report to do.
I love jake.
Well, that's good, but will you
help him with his report?
I would like nothing better.
You want chili?
Uh, no, no, i'm good.
But just so we're clear,
you'll help jake?
I love jake.
Charlie, it's very
important that...
Relax, i'll take jake to
the dmv to get his license.
Book report.
Beans.
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Reencoded by dr. Xj | psa
www.Psarips.Com
Oh, no!
Charlie's blackout chili.
It's delicious.
No argument there.
Why is it called
"blackout chili"?
Well, sweetheart,
Sometimes when
people drink,
The do things they
wouldn't normally do.
Me, i like to walk into
a biker bar and take a swing
At the biggest chick there.
Your uncle charlie, on the
other hand, makes chili.
But what's the blackout part?
Ah, geez, jake,
how many times
Have i told you not
to crap up my kitchen?
I'm not the one who...
Oh.
Still, it beats waking up
To find pool chalk
between your fanny cheeks.
Where's your father?
He went to the dmv.
He said you promised to help me
with my book report.
Really?
That doesn't sound like me.
I didn't think so either,
but that's what he said.
When's it due?
Monday.
Okay. Today's saturday?
Yeah.
We got plenty of time.
Yeah, but my dad always says
if i do my work early,
Then i have the rest
of the weekend to have fun.
That makes no sense whatsoever.
That's what i said.
Let me ask you
something.
Do you want
to do it now?
No.
Then trust your instincts.
Here's what you do.
You go out and have a good time,
Let the report percolate
in your subconscious.
Then,
As the deadline approaches
and that flop-Sweat panic hits,
Those pages will come
shooting out of you
Like a lunch from a supermodel.
Well, i do like to percolate.
That a boy.
What are you
doing today?
Well, i've got to write
a new jingle
For a big credit card company
And they're expecting it
on monday, so...
I'm going to the track.
♪ Men.
Woman (over p.A.):
now serving number 38
at window "d."
I got 42.
I made an appointment.
Good for you.
What's your number?
I'm 97.
Ooh. Ouch.
You're gonna
be here forever.
Yeah.
Oh, hey,
you know what?
I'm probably not even going
to need this power bar.
You want it?
Thanks.
You're very kind.
Next time,
plan ahead.
Will do.
Got to know how
to work the system.
Again...
Thanks.
Okay, i'm leaving.
Bye.
If you need anything,
ask berta.
Okay.
She won't give it to you,
but she enjoys being asked.
Turn that off.
You're coming with me.
Really? To the track?
It's got to be better
for you than tv.
Are we gonna gamble?
No, suckers gamble.
We're gonna analyze
statistics
With proven
scientific principles
And make wagers based
on the result of data.
I think i'd rather watch tv.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Woman (over p.A.):
now serving number 39
at window "a."
It appears my time on your
planet is almost over.
(laughs)
(mocks laugh)
Excuse me. Are you
done with your paper?
Oh, sure. Here.
Thank you.
I didn't even have
a chance to finish the jumble.
Well, i'll have time.
Ooh.
Hey, 97, that ought
to lift your spirits.
I'm ebullient.
I feel like such
an idiot.
I didn't even know you
could make an appointment.
Well, most people don't.
Am i right?
Lena.
Oh, uh, i'm-I'm alan.
Ooh, you have a firm
handshake, alan.
I like that
in a man.
Well, i'm a, i'm a chiropractor
and my hands are my instruments.
And i also carry a little
squishy ball in my pocket
To head off carpal tunnel.
Ooh.
How much can i bet?
How much did you bring?
I have to use my own money?
Boy, you really are
your father's son, aren't you?
Okay.
I have $14.
That's not gonna
get you very far.
Um, oh, and i have a $50 gift
certificate to pizza hut.
Want to buy it?
Sure. I'll give you 25 bucks.
But it's worth $50.
To who?
To pizza hut.
Well, so let the good folks
at pizza hut
Place a bet for you.
You're just trying
to rip me off.
Yeah. I've been
staying up nights
Trying to figure
out how
Now, listen and learn.
In any financial
transaction
There is one question
Both parties have
to ask themselves.
We're going to a party?
Will you shut up and listen?
I thought we were going
to the track?
I swear to god,
I'm going to throw
you out of this car.
Now, as i was saying,
The question is what leverage
do i have in this transaction?
The answer for you is "none."
What's leverage?
Oh, boy.
All right, a lever
is how you move things.
Leverage is how you move people.
Now, if we were going
to pizza hut
And they didn't take real money
and i was starving to death,
Your gift certificate
would give you leverage over me.
But alas, this
is not the case.
Okay, i guess i'll take $40.
Now you're catching on.
But no.
Woman (over p.A.):
number at 40 at window "e."
I'm sorry, baby,
mama's got to stay here
Till she gets
her license.
I'm hungry, too.
I don't know
how much longer.
You want to come in here
and wait with me?
All right,
you stay in the car
And play your
video game.
Mommy loves you, too.
I get such little time
with him.
Where's his dad?
Damned if i know.
Woman (over p.A.):
now serving number 41
at window "b."
Oh, he is gonna miss
his piano lesson.
Listen, um, why don't you
take my number?
Oh, i couldn't.
No, no, no, i insist—
i've got somebody
Taking care of my little
boy, so i can wait.
That is so sweet.
Woman (over p.A.):
now serving number 42
at window "b."
Oh, you're up.
Thank you so much.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
Hey, listen, maybe,
Do you think sometime
we could maybe go out...?
Hey, mama.
Baby, i thought you were
waiting in the car.
Batteries are dead.
That's okay.
We're out of here.
You lied to me.
No, i didn't.
Baby, you got
a piano lesson today?
Yep. Gershwin.
See?
Hey, i thought you had her
at "squishy ball."
♪ Men.
So how much do i get
if my horse wins?
If you bet $14 at
two to one, you win $28.
That doesn't sound like a lot.
Why can't i bet
the 80-To-One horse?
You can, but there's dogs
with forks and napkins
Waiting at the
finish line for him.
What does that mean?
It means the greater the odds,
The lousier the horse.
But he could still win, right?
Yeah, and you could still be
class valedictorian.
But that's not where
the smart money goes.
You can make your point
without being mean.
If you want me to bet
The 80-To-One horse
for you, i will.
Okay, fine.
It'll be a good lesson for you.
You won't be such
a know-It-All when...
Four times eight's 32,
one times is zero is zero—
$120,000.
All right, two lessons.
It's not as much as i thought,
but i'm still rich.
You're not rich...
You lucky little peckerhead.
There's no reason
for name-Calling.
Mr. Smart money.
You want to walk home?
I don't have to walk home.
I could take a taxi
or a limo.
Or a hearse.
♪ Men
Mm. You were so
smart to bring this.
Woman:
now serving
number 97 at window a.
Hey, that's me.
You hang in there.
Thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
I was being facetious.
Ooh, 99.
Lucky you.
I'm 138.
Been here all day.
With my kid waiting
in the car.
Nice try.
♪ Men
Hey, dad, guess what?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
he doesn't need to know.
Why not?
Think about it.
What's your father going to do
When he finds out
you've got $1,120?
Don't worry, i'm not going
to lend him any.
No, you clod.
He's going to make you
put it in the bank.
Oh, yeah.
Plus he's going to give me grief
for taking you to the track.
Oh, so i guess that means
i've got leverage on you.
Hey, i can live
with the grief.
Can you live
without the money?
No, i love the money.
Okay, so here's what you do.
Hide it in your room someplace
no one will look.
Oh, i saw this movie once
where they put the money
In a plastic bag
and hung it in the toilet.
Bad idea. Your toilet sees
way too much action.
Okay, i'll buy a big safe.
Oh, brilliant— that won't
raise any questions.
Just stick it in a shoe.
But what if i want to wear it?
Then put it in a different shoe.
But not the same pair, right?
Correct.
Now, you have to be careful
spending it.
You don't want to call
attention to yourself.
Okay, i'll just get
a plasma tv.
No, no, no, no,
No plasma tvs, not computers,
no expensive video games.
Buy small stuff
that no one will notice.
Like donuts?
Perfect.
What about a donut machine?
Okay, you're not hearing me.
I could hide it in the safe.
Get out of here.
Hey, where have
you been?
I told you— the dmv.
All day? You should have
made an appointment.
Yeah, next time i'll know.
So what did you
guys do today?
Oh, not much.
We just hung out,
ran a few errands.
Oh, did you help him
with his book report?
Yes, i did.
Really?
No.
Charlie, you said
you'd help him.
Yeah, well, you said
You'd only be living
here for a couple weeks.
And you weren't drunk when
you said it.
Fair enough.
So you guys just ran
errands all day?
Yes, errands.
Where is he, in his room?
Yes, his room.
Thanks for keeping
an eye on him.
No problem.
Oh, i have a bad feeling.
Hey, jake, i'm back.
I was thinking...
Charlie made me go to the track.
(sighs)
What a day.
Just sitting and sitting
and sitting.
Huh.
It was like jury duty,
Without the fun of sending
someone to jail.
Sounds awful.
Yeah, yeah.
So...
You guys ran errands today.
The little rat bastard
sold me out, didn't he?
Almost immediately.
Why would you take
a 13-Year-Old boy
to the track?
Hey, i thought it
would be better
Than him hanging around
the house all day doing nothing.
He was supposed to be
doing his book report.
Oh, yeah.
And come to think of it,
Weren't you supposed
to be working on
Some big credit card jingle?
I'm percolating.
Boy, you are
some role model.
Well, one of us has to be.
So, uh, exactly how much
did he win?
$1,100.
Wow.
Forget it. He's not
going to loan you any.
All right, all right,
we'll put it in the bank.
It'll be a nice addition
to his college fund.
What college fund?
The one with $1,100 in it.
Come on, alan.
He won the money
fair and stupid.
So you think i ought
to let him keep it?
What's the worst
that could happen?
So he blows it.
It's a life lesson
and we get a donut machine.
What?
It's just money, alan.
I don't want him
to think like that.
Oh, much better he think
like you?
Squirreling away
every dime he makes
So he'll haven it handy
for alimony payments
And phone sex?
For the last time,
i misdialed.
Yeah, every wednesday night
for 20 minutes.
Okay, okay, we are not
talking about the phone bills.
We are talking about teaching
jake sound financial principles.
And i am entitled
to a date night.
Fine. Take the money
away from him.
No, no, i'm not going
to be the bad guy.
I'm not going to be
the bad guy either.
Why not? It's your fault.
Hey, if you want to point
the finger,
Look for the horse trainer
Who put crystal meth
in mr. Mcglue's feed bag.
I'll bet that clydesdale
is still running.
Okay, okay, you think
you know best?
We'll let him keep the money.
But mark my words, no good can
come from a boy like jake
Having that kind of cash
to throw around.
Oh come on, the kid might
surprise you.
Here's a hundred bucks.
What's that for?
I broke a lamp.
♪ Men
(playing "call to post")
♪ It's the card that's accepted
all over the globe ♪
♪ Something, something...
♪ Terrycloth robe.
That's enough for today.
Have you see jake?
Oh, little lord fartleroy?
Well, he wasn't pleased with
grilled cheese for lunch,
So he walked down
to the red lobster
For their all-You-Can-Eat
popcorn shrimp.
Wonderful.
He lined his pockets with
foil before he left.
You think this is funny?
The kid gets to throw
some money around.
What's wrong with that?
Hey, richie rich back
with my crab legs yet?
No.
You don't understand.
Money gives him choices
and freedom.
Yeah, so?
I don't have choices and
freedom, why should he?
Dad, uncle charlie,
Come out and see
what i just bought.
Oh, i have another
bad feeling.
Oh, jake, where
did you get that?
A guy had it in the back of his
pickup truck at the gas station
And it had a "for sale" sign.
Oh, no.
I asked him how much it was
and he said,
"how much you got?"
And i told him $1,106,
And he said,
"it's your lucky day."
Can you
believe that?
That's two lucky days in a row.
Okay, i am sorry.
You did not ride
that thing here?
Oh, no, i pushed it.
I figured i can
ride it on the beach.
Well, you figured wrong—
it's too dangerous.
Don't worry, i got a helmet.
I traded him for a bag
of crab legs.
Can you help me take it
down to the beach now?
No, you are not
riding that thing.
Yeah, well, i bought it
with my own money,
So you can't tell me
what to do.
Really, i am as sorry
as i can possibly be.
Let me just show you
how cool it is.
Look, the guy told me
how to start it.
He said it might
need a tune-Up.
So where are
my crab legs?
♪ Men
Go ahead— say it.
I'm stupid and i got
ripped off.
No, nobody thinks that.
I wouldn't say nobody.
Charlie.
Oh, come on, it's not
the end of the world.
Look, jake, sooner or later
every guy gets hustled.
Even you?
Even me.
I remember once when i
wasn't much older than you,
I spend a hundred bucks
on a bag of oregano.
Oregano?
Your uncle was making
spaghetti sauce.
Yeah, in a parked car
Before i went to the
pink floyd lasarium show.
Thank you.
The important think is
that you learned something
That will serve you
for the rest of your life.
What's that?
Always buy motorbikes and
oregano from authorized dealers.
No, no, that
is not the lesson.
A fool and his money
are soon parted?
No.
Don't run with scissors?
Do you mind?
Go ahead, i'm down to
Don't eat the yellow snow.
That's not it, is it?
No, the lesson here
Is that when a little extra
money comes our way,
We do the smart thing—
we put it in the bank
Where it makes reasonable
interest at minimal risk.
And then we have it
for a rainy day.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Attaboy.
Trust me, there is
no better feeling
Than knowing you have
a little nest egg
To fall back on.
There are at least
eight better feelings.
Charlie!
Coming.