So, tell me about your day—
how's it going
with the particle detector?
Wow! You remember that?
Yeah, I listen
to what you say.
You're building
a particle detector
using superfluid helium.
You know, when you
talk like that,
I want to take you
right here on this table.
And you know
from past experience
this table cannot support
both our weight.
So, how's
the detector going?
Well, it's tricky working
with superfluids.
Whatever container
you put them in,
they kind of
creep up the sides
and crawl out
all on their own.
Kind of like
Sheldon's ant farm.
Exactly, except you don't have
a lunatic running around,
yelling, "I fed you sugar water,
why are you biting me?"
Come on, this is boring— you
really want to talk about this?
No, I do.
I-I didn't write
"superfluid helium"
on this napkin for nothing.
Okay, well...
This is cool.
Uh, there's a thing called
"superfluid vacuum theory",
where empty space is
imagined as a superfluid
with all of
its qualities—
viscosity, density,
surface tension...
Hey, if you're pausing
for dramatic effect,
I'd keep it moving.
No, no.
People don't talk
about surface tension.
If you imagine our
three-space as the surface
of an N-dimensional
superfluid bubble...
This... is exciting.
This is really exciting.
I have to go
find Sheldon.
Okay, well,
if you find him,
use the kitchen island—
that coffee table will not
support both of you.
Which means a spherical
multidimensional superfluid
shows the same negative-energy
density as space-time.
So what do you think? What do
you think? So what do you think?
Hmm...
What? Is it wrong?
Have you seen it somewhere else?
Hmm...
I know this isn't my area,
and I could never
do the math like you can,
but could this be something...?
Well...
You could have set Newton's
gravitational constant to one.
And, ugh, the whole thing reeks
of blueberry.
You know I can't stand
these scented markers.
No one told you to taste them.
Come on, is-is this
good or not?
It's good.
Really?
I like it.
I think you're on to something.
You do? You're not
messing with me?
Not at all.
In fact,
I have got something
for just such
an occasion.
I was starting to think
I might never get a chance
to give it to you.
Good job.
You're giving me a sticker?
Not just a sticker.
That is a sticker of a kitty
saying, "Me-wow!"
I'm not a preschooler.
Fine, I'll take it back.
I earned this!
Back off!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x14 ♪
The Troll Manifestation
Original Air Date on February 5,
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You're still awake?
For a man whose
last observation was
our universe may be the surface
of a multidimensional
supercooled liquid,
"you're still awake" seems
like quite the sophomore slump.
You worked out
all the math.
Oh, I did more
than work out all the math.
I wrote a paper.
You wrote a paper
on my idea?
I wrote a paper
on our idea.
When did my idea
become our idea?
When I mixed it with
Sheldony goodness
and cooked it in the
Easy-Bake Oven of my mind.
This is good.
Our idea is really good.
Well, the lightbulb in this
oven is ridiculously bright.
You know, if no one's
thought of this, yet,
this could be a big deal.
Only way we'll
know for sure is
if we post it online to
the pre-print server.
I have it ready to go, but I
wasn't gonna do it without you.
Wow, it's all
happening so fast.
Should we just sleep on it?
We could, but we
always run the risk
of someone else beating
us to the punch.
You're sure it's good?
My name is right on
there with yours.
That is a surefire
mark of quality.
That might as well say
"Directed by Joss Whedon".
Okay, partner, let's do it.
Come on.
Click the
mouse with me.
One...
two...
three...
Click.
Well, we did it.
Yes, we did,
my friend.
Is your tongue blue?
I don't want to
talk about it.
Okay, movie night—
what do you want to watch?
Whatever happened
to that ape movie you were in?
Oh, God.
Probably nothing.
I think I saw the director
twirling a sign
outside the Verizon store.
Search for it.
Wha... no.
No! Why?
'Cause it would be
fun to watch.
It would be humiliating.
Well, now we have
two reasons.
They have it.
Please,
can we watch it?
Please?
Fine, but I'm telling you—
it's terrible.
Have you even seen it?
No.
Well, maybe it turned out
better than you think.
Bananas,
get your fresh bananas.
It really didn't.
Sheldon, this is
superfluid helium.
Put this in
your mouth,
your tongue will
freeze and break off.
Does it smell like blueberries?
No.
Then we're probably okay.
Hey, your paper
got mentioned
on the Quantum Diaries
physics blog.
Really?
Wh-What'd they say?
Uh, it's basically
a summary of the theory,
but there's a bunch of positive
comments on the message board.
Let me see,
let me see.
One calls it "insightful
and innovative".
We're insightful
and innovative.
Ooh, nice to meet you,
Mr. Insightful.
Oh, the pleasure is mine,
Mr. Innovative.
Uh, another one says,
"The concept shows
some real out-of-the-box
thinking".
Do you hear that,
Mr. Out-Of-The?
I do, indeed,
Mr. Box-Thinking.
How are you today,
Mr. Can-You-Believe-
These-Jack-Asses?
Just dandy, Mr...
I-Wish-I-Was-
Better-At-Improv.
Read another one.
Okay, okay. Uh...
"The analogy
between space-time
and a supercooled fluid is
either meaningless or... false".
"I wish this blog would
devote itself to real science
"instead of wasting
our time with crackpot,
wannabe theoreticians
in a rush to publish".
Who wrote that?
It's anonymous,
and user name
"General Relativity."
Well... I'm responding to it.
Uh, don't lower yourself
to their level.
Look, I am simply
going to defend our work,
scientist to scientist.
And failing that,
suggest that his mother enjoys
a string
of both human
and non-human lovers.
Sheldon, my name's
on that paper, too.
There's no upside to doing this.
He just left another comment.
What does it say?
"Upon review, I've
changed my mind about
"the Cooper-Hofstadter
hypothesis
"that space-time is like
a superfluid. In fact,
"it's inspired me to come up
with my own theory.
"Maybe space-time is like
two clowns
"with their heads in a bucket,
much like Cooper
and Hofstadter."
Can I respond now?
Do it.
You mess with the bull,
you get the horns.
I'm about to show this guy
just how horny I can be.
Somebody else do it.
Doctor, please help me.
I think I might be turning
into a killer gorilla.
Why do you think you're turning
into a killer gorilla
and not just a regular gorilla?
Because regular gorillas
are vegetarians,
and I just bit the fingers
off your receptionist!
Okay, we've seen plenty.
No!
Give me the remote.
Careful. She'll bite
your fingers off.
Okay, well, I've been
poking around the internet,
and I think I found something
we'll enjoy watching even more.
What is it?
Oh, just a video
of Bernadette
in a beauty pageant.
What?
Okay, I learned my lesson.
Making fun of people is wrong!
I haven't learned
my lesson.
Play it! Play it!
Hi. I'm Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski
from Yorba Linda, California.
You look like
a talking cupcake!
And you should pick me
for Miss California Quiznos
1999, because I want to...
Tell you what I want,
what I really really want
I'll tell you what I want,
I wanna, I wanna,
I wanna, I wanna
Really, really, really be
Miss California Quiznos 1999!
Play it again!
Did he respond yet?
Hmm. No, not yet.
Well,
maybe we shouldn't have sunk
to his level.
It wasn't that bad.
Read it back one more time.
"My good sir, we are neither
crackpots nor wannabes.
"In fact, we are
experts in our fields.
"And while you hide
behind your anonymity,
"we stand behind our paper.
And later tonight, your mother".
And you don't think
that's too rough?
We're just standing behind her.
It's not like we're gonna say
"boo" and scare her.
How could you not tell us
you were in beauty pageants?
'Cause it's
embarrassing.
It is; it truly is.
Yeah, well...
Amy writes Little House
on the Prairie fan fiction
about herself
and posts it on the Internet.
No!
Why? What did I do?
Sorry, I had to get
the spotlight off me,
and tearing down other women
is part of my pageant training.
Okay. We are
reading that right now.
No, please don't.
We got embarrassed
tonight. Come on.
But it's personal.
Why? Is it about you
and Sheldon?
No.
Oh, my God, it's
about her and Sheldon.
It's not about me and Sheldon.
It's about a young woman
in the 1800s named Amelia...
and the time-traveling physicist
named Cooper
she falls in love with.
Please show us?
Please?
No.
You know I'm gonna read it either way.
Good luck finding it.
Amelia and...
the time-trav...
Found it!
"It was just past dawn
on the prairie,
"and like every morning,
"Amelia prepared
to do her chores.
Except something about
this morning felt different."
Why?
Why did it
feel different?
"Maybe it was the first whisper
of winter in the air,
"or maybe it was
the unconscious handsome man
"with porcelain skin
and curious clothing
"she was about to discover
lying in the field.
"A man who would
open her mind
"to new possibilities
and her body to new feelings."
You know, there was a time when
I was alone and had no friends.
I'm starting to miss that.
He still hasn't responded.
What's taking him so long?
Do you really want
him to write back?
Yeah, I do.
No matter how he responds,
I am going to destroy him
with a picture of a bored cat
saying, "Oh, really?"
Me-wow.
What are you doing?
I've, uh, created some
other user accounts
so I can post positive
comments about their paper.
"This wee li'l bairn
of a theory
nearly blew my kilt off"?
No. You have to read it
how Dr. Angus McDoogal
of the University
of Edinburgh would.
"This wee li'l bairn of a theory
nearly blew me kilt off."
He wrote back!
"Cooper and Hofstadter resorting
to juvenile attempts at humor
"is proof they have nothing to
back up their ridiculous paper.
"It should come
as no surprise
"given they work at Cal Tech,
essentially a technical school,
where even the physicists
are basically engineers."
"Engineers"!
Do you know
how insulting that is?
Yes.
Guys, this person's
just going out of their way
to get a rise out of you.
Yeah, but it's still so aggravating.
Yeah, well,
all the other comments
said really nice things.
Focus on those.
Yeah.
Dr. Dmitri Plancovik
of Moscow
University said,
"Dis paper great.
I love it more
than 'wodka.".
See? Better
with the accent.
And...
send.
What did you write?
I'm done hiding from bullies.
I'm taking this
into the real world.
What does that mean?
I told him we'll meet him
face-to-face anytime, anywhere.
Are you crazy?
You don't know who this person is.
Delete that!
Come on, Sheldon!
Oh, okay,
okay, calm down.
It's him!
He's trying to video chat.
Perhaps I shouldn't have
taken this into the real world.
Oh, really?
"'Time travel?
I don't understand,'
"said Amelia.
Cooper stared at her.
'Which rd don't you
understand, time or travel?'"
Wow, even in your fantasies
Sheldon's kind of exhausting.
He's like that
in the beginning,
so she can change him.
It's called good writing.
And wishful thinking.
"It stung Amelia
"when he spoke to her this way.
"In her little
one-room schoolhouse,
"she was always
the smartest student,
"regularly besting the boys
in her class,
"but this was no boy
in front of her—
"this was a man.
Here we go.
"Cooper told Amelia
"about all the strange
and incredible things
"the future would hold,
like computers
"and living past 30.
"He asked her
if she had any questions.
"All she longed to ask was
"if his heart was beating
as fast as hers,
"but she was too afraid
to hear the answer."
Oh, Amelia.
"So instead she asked if,
in the future,
Montana ever became a state."
In the 1800s
that was considered flirting.
I'm so sick of people
being mean on the Internet.
Well, I think the anonymity
makes everyone feel like
they can say things
they'd never say to your face.
Interesting.
I can't think of a single thing
I wouldn't say
to someone's face.
Never noticed that about you.
You know what? A-At least
you guys did something.
You know, you-you had a theory,
you wrote a paper,
you made
an actual contribution.
All guys like this do is just
stand on other people's work.
He's right.
I say we call this person back.
We've got no reason to hide.
All right, do it.
Call him.
Let's find out what this loser's
ever accomplished.
Click it with me.
One, two, three...
Click.
click.
Well, hello there.
Professor Hawking?
Oh, brother, you should see
the look on your faces.
You really
didn't like our paper?
I like your paper very much.
The premise is intriguing.
Then why are you
attacking us?
If you were sitting in a chair
for 40 years,
you'd get bored, too.
Anyway,
got to go.
I promised to help the neighbor
kid with his math homework.
Ciao.
Stephen Hawking
liked our paper.
Said the premise
is intriguing.
Good to see you again,
Mr. Stephen-Hawking-
Liked-Our-Paper.
And you as well,
Mr. Our-Premise-Is-Intriguing.
How do you do, Mr. I'll-
Admit-That's-Pretty-Cool?
Yeah, you keep
setting me up for failure.
"With a heavy heart,
"Amelia stood before
the newly repaired time machine.
She regretted giving Cooper
the part he needed."
Because she wanted him
to give her the part she needed.
Okay, that's enough.
What?
No! I really want to know
what happens— and Bernadette
really, really, really wants
to know what happens.
You're just making fun of me.
I was just kidding.
I'm sorry.
And the story's
really good!
No, it is!
Does he stay?
Do they kiss?
Does she find out about Montana?
Please?
Fine.
"As Cooper prepared to depart,
"tears filled Amelia's eyes.
"He took her hand in his
and said, 'I can't stay,
"but I will never forget you.'
"He brushed his fingers
against her cheek,
"then quickly stepped
into the machine.
"'Please don't go,'
she whispered.
"But it was too late.
"The engine hummed to life.
But they didn't even kiss.
"She turned away,
"wiping her eyes.
"She couldn't bear to watch
"her one chance at true love
disappear forever.
"Then... she felt a strong
hand on her shoulder
"spin her around.
"It was Cooper.
Yes!
"'What about the future?'
asked Amelia.
"He looked deeply into her eyes
and whispered,
"'There is no future
without you.'
"He pulled her in close.
"She began to
tremble all over.
She felt his warm breath..."
You will not believe
what Stephen Hawking just said.
- Get out!
- Not now!
Is the water warm enough?
Given the fact that you took
the time to build a wood fire,
draw the water from
the well and heat it,
it would be rude
to complain.
But since you asked,
it's a little nippy.
I can fix that.
I couldn't help but notice
your unusual undergarments.
They're not undergarments.
They're Underoos.
Where I come from,
they're known as
"underwear that's fun to wear."
And what's the significance
of the spider?
Oh, that represents
Spider-Man.
He does whatever
a spider can.
There's a lot of rhyming
in the future, isn't there?
You're right.
This is even weirder
than I thought.
You want me to
stop reading?
Are you kidding?
No, no.
"As he stood for
Amelia to dry him..."
So, tell me, Cooper...
are the ways of physical love
different in the future?
Yeah, okay, I'm good.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man