- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Say, Rachel,
I was wondering if you'd like to go
to a movie with me sometime,
as my lover.
Too out there.
Maybe you'd just like to get
something to eat with me sometime,
as my lover.
- Hi.
- Hi!
All right.
Let's go shopping.
You know, before we go, uh,
there's something I need to say.
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
I've kind of had
this crush on you.
But since you were with Ross,
I didn't do anything about it.
But now that you're not, I'd really
like to ask you out sometime.
So that's what I'm doing now.
I dropped a cup.
So that's why within a few years,
that voice recognition
is going to be pretty much standard
on any computer you buy.
You know, so you can be, like,
"Wash my car," "clean my room."
It's not going to be able
to do any of those things
but it will understand
what you're saying.
- Oh, this was so great.
- Yeah, it was.
All right, then.
Bye.
Hello, people who
do not live here.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I gave you a key
for emergencies.
We were out of Doritos.
Hey, how'd the date
go with Mr. Millionaire?
"Mr. Millionaire, new,
from Snooty Playthings.
Third wife sold separately."
He's great. I mean, we have
such a good time together.
He's so funny and so sweet,
and I'm not attracted to him at all.
- Still?
- No!
It's driving me crazy. In every other
way, he's like the perfect guy.
He has everything.
Plus, he actually has everything.
Life-sized Imperial Storm Troopers
from Sharper Image?
Two.
Can Joey and I
put them on and fight?
Oh, Mommy! Oh, Daddy!
I am a big old baddy!
I guess he must have gotten
the part in that play.
Either that,
or Gloria Estefan was right.
Eventually, the rhythm
is going to get you.
- Joe, how's it going?
- Good.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So you're playing Adrienne, huh?
Yes. Are you one
of the retarded cousins?
No, no. I'm playing your husband,
Victor. I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Kate Miller.
So, play's pretty great, huh?
Oh, yeah. I love
Jennifer Banberry's work.
She's so brilliantly incisive
when it comes to deconstructing
the psyche of the middle class.
Oh, forget about it.
She rocks.
Where do I know you from?
Dr. Drake Ramoray?
"Days of our Lives"?
Voted most datable neurosurgeon
by "Teen Beat"?
No, that's not it.
So you're a soap actor.
Well, this must be exciting for you,
being in a real play.
Hey, I've done plays before.
I'm a serious actor.
That infomercial…
for the milk carton
spout thing.
You're the guy who doesn't
know how to pour milk.
I actually can pour milk. But I got
you believing that I couldn't.
Now, see, that's acting.
Right, and at the end,
you choked on a cookie.
Yeah, that was real.
- I cannot believe Mark asked you out.
- I know.
Well, so, what are
you going to tell him?
I told him I would think about it,
but I'm going to tell him no.
I mean, I think I'd say no
to anybody right now.
Oh, but it was so strange.
I mean, I'm standing there
with this charming, cute guy
who's asking me to go out with him,
which I am
allowed to do
and I felt guilty, you know, like
I'd be cheating on Ross or something.
So, okay, maybe that means
that you're not over Ross yet
and you have issues with your father.
I don't have any issues
with my father.
Okay, so it's probably
just the Ross thing then.
I hate this woman.
I hate her!
She told everyone in the company
about that infomercial,
and now they all keep asking
me to open their drinks.
Okay? And whenever I can't do it,
they're all, like, laughing at me.
- Hello.
- Hey!
So Rachel called.
Wants to see me.
Going over in a minute.
What do you think she wants?
Maybe the crazy fog
has lifted,
and she realizes that life
without me sucks.
It's possible. You are very lovable.
I'd miss you if I broke up with you.
I'm just trying
to be supportive.
Well, be supportive
like a guy.
If I broke up with you,
I'd miss you.
- Hi.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Here's a box of your stuff.
What?
It's just, like, hats
and a shirt and CD's.
Just sort of stuff
that you've left here.
What are you doing? Are you trying
to hurt me or something?
No.
Ross, it…
It just seems that, you know,
it's time we, you know, move on.
I mean, don't you think?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
- Yes, I do.
- Good.
Yeah, I really do.
Hey!
This was a gift.
Ross, you got that for free
from the museum gift shop.
It's still a gift.
I got it from the gift shop.
Okay. All right. Give me the mug.
I'll keep the mug.
No! You know, don't do me
any favors. In fact, where…
Where's the rest of my stuff?
Like, like…
This book is mine!
And that T-shirt you sleep in.
I'd like that back, too.
Yes, I do.
You know how much
I love that T-shirt.
You never even wear
that T-shirt.
I'm just trying to help
you move on.
Oh, you are a petty man.
You are a petty, petty…
- Petty…
- Petty, petty…
- Small…
- Petty, small…
You are so just doing
this out of spite.
No, no, no.
I'm going to wear this all
the time. I love this shirt.
You have not worn that since
you were 15.
It doesn't even fit you anymore.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Now, if you don't mind, I'm going
to take the rest of my stuff,
and relax…
in my favorite shirt.
You have a pleasant evening.
So, you're, like, a zillionaire.
And you're our age.
You're our age.
You know what?
You should, like, buy a state,
and then just name
it after yourself.
What, like, "Pete Dakota"?
Or "Mississi-Pete."
I got it.
"Pete Chicago."
That's not a state, Joe.
Oh, and "Mississi-Pete" is?
I got to go.
So I'll see you guys later.
- Okay. You're our age.
- Okay.
So, are we on
for tomorrow?
Absolutely.
Now get out
of here, you.
Okay, I'm running out of
places I can touch him.
I mean, is there
something wrong with me?
I mean, why am I only attracted
to guys where there's no future?
Either they're too old
or they're too young.
And then there's Pete,
he's crazy about me,
and he's absolutely perfect,
and there's, like, zip going on.
Seriously. Does it sound like
there's something wrong with me?
Yeah. Kind of.
Happy? Is that what
I'm supposed to be, Vic?
Happy?
Well, why don't you tell me
what you're supposed to be, huh?
Because I sure as hell
can't figure it out.
I talk to you,
and nothing.
You look at me,
and it's nothing.
Nothing.
Tasty.
I'm really starting to feel like
you guys have a history. It's nice.
- I have a question about this scene.
- Yes.
Well, I don't understand why
Adrienne's attracted to Victor.
Peel the onion.
First of all,
he's good-looking.
Yeah.
I think my character's going to need
a bit more of a reason than that.
Oh, hey, how about this one…
It says so in the script!
You know, I don't know why
my character likes you either.
I mean, it says in the script
here that you're a bitch.
- It doesn't say that in the script.
- It does in mine.
I can blow dry it. I can put
gel on it. It doesn't matter.
I still wind up with this
little cowlicky thing
on the middle part of my head.
It's so annoying.
- Does it bug you?
- You bug me.
Is there any chance
you didn't see that?
Ross, you got
to stop, okay?
Ross, you can't just stare through
the peephole for three hours.
You're going to
get peep eye.
I knew it. I knew it.
I always knew she liked him.
She'd say no, but
here we are, right?
We just broke up,
first thing she does…
You didn't just break up.
Hey, it's been,
like, three weeks.
You slept with somebody three hours
after you thought you broke up.
I mean, bullets have
left guns slower.
Here they come.
If she kisses him good night,
I'm going to kill myself, I swear.
I can't watch…
Come on. Date over.
Date over.
- Oh, oh. Here we go. She's going in.
- Okay.
She's going in.
Wait. He's going in.
He's going in.
The door's closed. I can't see
anything with the door closed.
And the inventor of the door
rests happily in his grave.
Okay, I have to do something.
I mean, I have to stop it.
- Stop what?
- I don't know.
But I have a feeling
that my being there will do it.
I'll go over and
I will borrow something.
- Juice. I need juice.
- No.
- You can't.
- A little help.
- Look, they must be stopped.
- I am your friend.
And I am not going
to let you do this.
You are surprisingly strong.
- I need juice. People need juice!
- Look, man…
- People need juice! Juice!
- Listen to me.
She's moving on. If it's not this
guy, it's going to be somebody else.
And unless you're thinking about
subletting my peephole,
you are going to have to get
used to the fact
that the relationship is over.
Okay, man? It's over.
- Yeah, okay.
- Okay.
It's just I miss her so much.
I know.
Why do all your coffee mugs
have numbers on the bottom?
Oh, that's so Monica
can keep track.
That way, if one of them is missing,
she can be,
like, "Where's number 27?"
You know what?
No, and I don't think
I'm going to want to.
I can't do this.
Yep. Yep, that's what
I didn't want to know.
Yeah. Mark, I'm just doing this
for the wrong reasons, you know?
I'm just doing it
to get back at Ross.
I'm sorry.
It's not very fair to you.
Fair, shmair,
you know?
Look, you want to get back at Ross,
I am here for you.
Really.
No, no. I say we get back at him
right here on this couch. Right here.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry about this.
That's okay.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I can just go home and
get back at him by myself.
…poised to become
the penicillin of the 21st century.
And so today, this hospital
is about to take major steps
toward leading that revolution.
- It is truly ironic…
- Hey. Can I ask you something?
Where are we?
Well, with all these
doctors and nurses,
I'm going to say,
Midget Rodeo.
Just tell me the truth.
Okay.
I don't think I told you this,
but I just recently got out
of a really serious relationship.
Oh, right.
Wasn't that like a year ago?
So I did tell you.
Okay. Well, you know,
that's not really the thing.
The thing is, is that right now
I'm just in a place in my life
where I just need to focus on me.
- Do you know what I mean?
- Oh, yeah. I know.
- I so want to be attracted to you…
- But you're not. Okay. Good.
I'm sorry.
You know what? Don't be.
This is not…
Don't be,
'cause it's not so bad.
- It's not?
- Yeah. I know I'm no Jon Bon Jovi.
Or someone you find attractive.
I'm just
think, you know,
that you might end up
feeling differently.
Well, look, I don't want
this to come out wrong,
but you seem awfully
confident for a guy
I just told I wasn't
attracted to.
Yeah. Stupidly
charming, isn't it?
Listen, you want to get
something to eat?
'Cause this place is
kind of dee-pressing.
And now the man who made all
this possible… Mr. Peter Becker.
One sec.
I don't think this town is big enough
for the both of us to relax in.
Draw.
I wasn't doing anything.
What did she do now?
Just because she went
to Yale Drama,
she thinks she's, like,
the greatest actress
since sliced bread.
Sliced Bread,
a wonderful Lady Macbeth.
God, I hate her. I hate her
with her, "Oh, I'm so talented"
and "Oh, I'm so pretty,"
and "Oh, I smell so good."
I think somebody has
a crush on somebody.
Hey, Chandler, can we please try and
stay focused on my problem here?
I'm talking about you,
you big, big freak.
You're out of your mind.
Hey, you have done nothing but
talk about her for the last 48 hours.
If you were in school yard,
you'd be pulling her pigtails
and pushing her down now.
Oh, yeah? Then how come
I keep thinking about her
in all these sexual scenarios
and stuff, huh?
Happy? Is that what I'm
supposed to be, Vic? Happy?
Well, why don't you tell me what
you're supposed to be, huh?
Because I sure as hell
can't figure it out.
I talk to you,
and it's nothing.
You look at me,
and nothing.
Nothing.
You guys make me fly…
high.
Okay. We're going to
pick it up here tomorrow.
- Well, that was…
- Better?
Yeah, yeah. It was definitely
an improvement,
- Good night.
- Kate.
Yeah?
You forgot your shoes.
I'm probably going
to need those, huh?
- Okay.
- Hey, listen.
You feel like getting
a cup of coffee?
- Kate.
- Yeah.
- You ready to go?
Very nice. Very nice.
- See you tomorrow, huh?
- Yeah, yeah. Sure.
- Right.
- Good night.
Hey.
Why isn't it "Spiderman"?
You know, like
Goldman, Silverman?
'Cause it's not his last name.
- It isn't?
- No, it's not, like…
Like Phil Spiderman.
He's a spider… man.
You know, like
like Goldman is a last name.
But there's no gold-man.
Oh, okay.
There should be a Gold Man.
- Hey.
- Hey, Rach.
- How was work?
- Oh, great.
Although I did sit down
where there wasn't a chair.
By the way, Ross dropped by
a box of your stuff.
Well, I guess
I had that one coming.
I'm going to throw it out. It's
probably a bunch of shampoo and…
Something wrong?
No, nothing.
So, what kind of powers
would Gold Man have?
Okay. Well, he would
turn things to gold.
What about things that are
already gold?
His work is done.
Okay. Let's play
my game now.
Okay.
Why, you yellow-bellied,
lily-livered… draw!
Yeah, it's fun.