Okay, everybody,
time for the hummingbird lottery.
You know how it works.
Write your name down on a paper.
No, they don't win a hummingbird.
I installed hummingbird feeders
in all of the parks.
So the winner
gets to refill those feeders.
Scientifically,
hummingbirds
are the world's cutest animals.
They're so small,
they have tiny beaks.
And they only eat sugar water.
I mean, what beats that?
Come on.
Baby monkeys in diapers?
They do.
Baby monkeys in diapers are the cutest.
- Okay, who's it gonna be?
- Not me. Not me.
You can stop by tomorrow morning,
before work.
This is my 3rd time in a row.
It's just a bad luck streak. Next time,
I'm sure it'll definitely be one of us.
But it won't be me
because I always write...
No. I always write my own name.
But,
just to be safe, I do add
20 extra Jerrys.
La Fabrique ::.
- Feygnasse Team -
Episode 219
Park safety
mpm
lestat
Finally, we're going to kick off
the children's concert series
this weekend
with a performance
by Freddy Spaghetti.
- I thought Freddy Spaghetti O.D.'d.
- No. That's Mr. Funny Noodle.
He didn't O.D.
His drummer shot him.
Where's Jerry, by the way?
Why isn't he back? How long does it take
to fill bird feeders?
Maybe he fell into the toilet.
Remember when he fell into the toilet?
"Sorry, guys. I'm late.
"I got confused and took a shower
after I got dressed 'cause I'm Jerry."
David Meyers,
the Jewish guy who works at city hall,
once told me something.
A schlemiel, is the guy
who spills soup at a fancy party.
A schlimazel,
is the guy he spills it on.
Jerry is both the schlemiel and
the schlimazel of our office.
"And then I put my underwear on my head
instead of my butt."
Okay, guys, that's enough.
Unless somebody has another one.
Jerry, are you okay? Ann, is Jerry okay?
What's wrong with your arm?
What's wrong with his arm.
Jerry, talk to me.
- Ann, get Jerry to talk to me.
- He's okay.
He's got a couple of scrapes
and a dislocated shoulder.
What happened?
- You guys are just gonna laugh.
- Why?
Did you throw it out trying to swing
a honey pot off your hand?
I was mugged.
My God.
I'm so sorry, Jerry.
I was on my way
to the hummingbird feeders,
and I was walking Lord Sheldon.
Is that code
for some kind of weird sex act?
Lord Sheldon is my dog.
My wife named him.
These kids came out of nowhere.
They pinned my arm back,
grabbed my wallet,
and knocked me to the ground.
How did you counterattack?
Fist to the throat?
Hit in the beanbag?
There's no shame
in attacking a criminal's beanbag.
No, I just curled up
and laid still till they left.
Well, that's another way to play it.
Did any of them have weird tattoos
or scars or anything?
If even one of them had a unique scar,
we got 'em.
- I didn't get a good look.
- Damn it, Jerry.
You're the victim.
Sorry.
I feel we're responsible for this.
Why?
We didn't mug Jerry.
Why was he in the park?
'Cause we tricked him.
I don't see the link.
This is on us. It's karma.
Wouldn't it be karma
if we got mugged?
That's how pathetic Jerry is.
He can't even get karma right.
That's not funny.
Our friend got mugged this morning.
And we will not let that happen in vain.
He doesn't have a black eye.
The whole department
has a black eye.
This is our wakeup call, guys.
Jerry's face
is the symbol of failure.
Our failure.
To keep the parks safe.
I have some folders.
Inside are some assignments.
And some homemade taffy.
April, check in
with our police liaison.
Donna, go to Ramsett park.
- Tom, you're with me.
- So when you say,
check in with the police liaison,
you mean hook up with him, right?
Just check in with him.
Everybody dismissed.
Wait. I want to help.
I'm gonna teach everybody self-defense,
so you can defend yourselves.
We need it 'cause we certainly
are a bunch of weaklings.
- Especially Tom.
- I am not a weakling.
- Arm-wrestle me right now.
- Okay.
I think I'm more
than holding my own here.///
- Hey. How you doing?
- Not too bad.
I was dropping off Jerry.
He was mugged in the park.
No. Jerry?
The black guy
with the looney tunes ties? I love him.
Jerry who works with Leslie.
That Jerry?
He got mugged?
That's kind of a bummer too.
While you here,
what do you think of this?
Scrotation Marks.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but my gut says no.
New band name.
'Cause, Mouse Rat, it's a great name,
but, at the same time,
it sucks.
So we have to change it
one more time.
Dude, you've got to stop doing that.
How are people gonna become fans
if they don't know
the name of the band
they're listening to?
Good point.
I always had fun with Andy.
But, when you're his girlfriend,
you're also his mother,
and his maid, and his nurse.
He's completely helpless.
He's like a baby in a straightjacket.
Baby in a straightjacket.
That's a good band name.
I should tell him that.
- Really funny. Where's the real banner?
- We only had an hour.
So did I.
Look what I did.
Welcome back.
Really. You shouldn't have gone
to all this trouble.
It's no trouble for our buddy.
Here you go.
Today is Jerry day.
We'll do whatever you want to do.
Honestly, what I would like to do
is have everything go back to normal.
That sounds good to me.
I believe you were going
to do a presentation?
Yes, sir, I was.
I will go set up.
Remember, you guys,
no jokes, no comments,
nothing but support.
He needs a lot of support.
I'm talking about a bra for a man.
Seriously, that was the last one.
So as we know,
spring hunting season is upon us.
Anyway, here's the info
about the new licensing system.
I don't think
your computer's plugged in.
Sorry.
Just gotta power up.
First thing we should have
is my graph about the season.
What? Wait a minute.
No.
That's not the graph. That's a picture
from my vacation in Muncie.
You went on a vacation,
and you chose Muncie, Indiana?
My wife and I have a timeshare.
In Muncie?
Muncie is a lovely city.
Anyway, hunting and fishing season
is winding down.
And we all know that it's already
closed season on twout.
So...
I said "twout",
instead of "trout".
It happens to everyone.
My marbles are full of mouth today.
You know what,
has anybody seen my glasses?
I don't even think I can...
It says here 1:00 meeting.
Who are we meeting with?
- Don't worry about it.
- Please no.
It's important to meet
with the park rangers.
They are the first line of defense.
What's up, pencil pushers?
Good to see you, man.
Is it hot in here? I feel hot.
Are you guys hot?
How you guys doing? I'm good.
You guys got any snacks?
Carl is the head
of all outdoor security.
Why was he transferred
from his indoor desk job, you ask.
- Listen.
- It's so sweet.
Hey, Leslie, have you seen Avatar?
I never saw Avatar.
I wanted to read the book first,
but then I realized
there's no book version of Avatar.
What'd you guys do
for St. Patty's day?
I was wearing this t-shirt that said :
"Kiss me. I'm Irish."
But no one would kiss me.
So...
you're too important for me
until one of your own gets attacked.
I just feel like there's more we can do
to keep the parks safe.
You think you know how to do my job?
You might not be so confident
once you've walked a mile
in my size sevens.
Kind of small feet.
Seven is the worldwide average.
Welcome to the emergency
self-defense class.
I'll be showing you how to escape
from a variety of situations
while inflicting maximum damage
on your attackers.
Do you think that maybe
I should put Mark in a headlock?
That way I can show everyone
how to escape a pervert.
In the scenario you just laid out,
you're the pervert.
You understand that, right?
- You wish.
- Enough.
I'm gonna start off simple
and demonstrate how to extract
oneself from a wrist grab.
Andy, Ann, step up here.
I watch a lot of lifetime movies.
There was this one,
How far is too far enough:
the Teri Palliber Lonergan story.
This woman had agoraphobia,
and her therapist was obsessed with her.
And he hid in her house,
and then he attacked her
and tried to eat her toes.
Also, her daughter
was having sex way too young.
So yeah, free
self-defense class, I'm there.
And just twist your weight.
Very good.
Very good. Well done.
What's up now, mugger?
That was awesome.
That was really good.
I don't know, Leslie.
I'd rather be back at the office.
I know this is painful for you, Jerry,
but you have to be strong.
You guys ready?
Oh, boy, yeah.
Okay, we're ready.
I'm gonna show you guys
all the problems we've been facing.
I'm gonna show you
we've been doing everything we can.
I'm looking forward
to working together, Carl.
And after that, I'm gonna
show you this log I found.
It's got, like, 50 worms on it.
I call it worm log.
Yeah, I've always been
a bit of an outdoorsman.
When I was a kid,
my parents used to make me hang out
in the backyard a lot
and just run around till I got tired.
But if there's any criminals
out there watching, I never get tired.
And ladies too.
- This thing is a mess.
- We used to have three carts actually.
The first one got pushed into the creek
by some kids.
The second one raccoons got onto.
There was urine everywhere.
And the third one
was recently stolen.
- What's this one?
- This is the second one.
The raccoon piss one.
All right, so we're gonna
just head out.
I think we got too much weight.
That's Tom probably.
- Are you serious?
- Tom, can you get off please?
Just run alongside the cart, okay?
Okay, here we go.
So let me tell you
a little bit about the park.
Up here on the left
is one of our most beautiful
grass fields.
It's primarily grass.
I'm gonna make a hard left here.
Stick with us, Tom.
Okay.
Lesson learned.
Next, Andy.
Impressive.
I'm gonna engage Andy in an attack hold,
and he's gonna try and break free.
Cool.
Now I don't want to hurt you, Ron.
Don't worry about that.
Just try to escape my attack.
Now when I get out,
am I allowed to counterstrike?
Sure.
When you get out,
you may counterattack.
But just promise me you'll be ready
because, I mean,
I don't want to destroy you.
I see where we're going with this.
Now when your arms
are pinned to your sides,
use your legs to break free
instead of your neck,
which is what Andy's trying to do.
Okay, hold on.
Let him go.
Any of this looking familiar?
Yeah, it happened right over there.
I'm not surprised.
Take a look at this path.
With budget cuts,
we can't afford a single safety light.
There's been ten assaults
already this year.
Really?
- Can't you station a park ranger?
- We have.
Who do you think they're assaulting?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to yell.
One way or another, I'm gonna get money
so you can protect Jerry
and all the other helpless,
pathetic people in this town.
You guys got to slow down.
- Can I just take a rest for a minute?
- Sorry. No can do.
Sun's going down.
It's dangerous.
- Let's roll, Carl.
- Okay, going fast.
What day is it today?
- I don't know.
- Okay, but to be fair, you never know.
That's kind of true.
I'm super bad at days.
But honestly I'm fine.
Sorry I squeezed
your lights out there, son.
No worries. Will you show me
how to do that move, though?
Sure. I can teach you right now.
You shouldtake it easy, I think.
Do you want some more water
or maybe some pancakes?
No, no, no.
I'm fine.
- What's the first move in any fight?
- Punch to the balls.
We've all heard the old saying,
"Parks are supposed to be fun,"
but sometimes muggers
have their own ideas.
Leslie Knope is with us again
from the parks department.
Tell us your story.
This is my coworker Jerry Gergich,
diabetic,
sloppily out of shape,
friend.
He was mugged this morning
in Ramsett park.
Who's next?
Your frumpy uncle?
Your simple neighbor?
Your unpopular coworker?
Head of security Carl Lorthner
is doing his best
to keep the parks safe,
but he's failing.
So what is the solution to fix this?
To make it right
and not bad?
We need money from city hall,
and it's not coming through.
And, Pawnee, I am sorry to say this
but your government is failing you.
Up next, ten objects
you didn't know you can eat.
What possessed you to do that?
I'm sorry, Paul, but one of my guys
got mugged in the park.
I don't care how upset you are,
you do not badmouth
your own government on TV.
I'm sure you'll be happy to know
your little stunt worked.
The mayor's going to divert $2,500
to the parks for security upgrades.
There'll be an announcement tomorrow
at 10:00 in the press room,
so make sure you bring the doofus
that got his ass kicked.
I don't know who you're referring to.
We treat everyone with respect.
Good morning.
As many of you know,
there was an incident
involving a government employee
in Ramsett park.
Jerry, are you nervous?
Just talk about how hard it was for you.
Speak from the heart.
You'll be fine.
I wasn't mugged.
- Jerry, why don't you step on up here?
- No, no, I will get up here.
I'm gonna speak for Jerry.
He can't talk right now
because he has hysterical muteness.
- From trauma.
- Correct.
What about this?
Is this fake?
This is real.
I really dislocated my shoulder.
Were you even in the park yesterday?
Look, I was on my way
to feed the hummingbirds,
and I stopped
for a breakfast burrito.
The farting.
And, lord Sheldon,
he lunged at a bird,
I dropped the burrito, and it
lands on a log in the creek.
So I go to reach for it,
I lose my balance,
and I fall on my shoulder
really weird.
Why didn't you
just tell everybody the truth?
Are you kidding me?
Imagine what Tom would have said.
Damn, Jerry,
you jumped in a creek for a burrito?
What would you do for a Klondike bar?
Kill your wife?
Block the opponent's punch
and counterpunch to the jaw.
Shoeshine?
Ann Perkins in the shoe shouse.
I wanted to check in.
I brought some stuff from the hospital.
Water, compress,
aspirin, some lollipops.
- I know you love those.
- You know, thank you,
but I'm really... I'm feeling great.
I took a couple of aspirin
and slept right through the night and...
Hold on a second.
Ludgate!
What the hell?
I got you
those muffins that you're always eating.
Score.
- Tastes like a rug.
- Shut up.
- Good, I'm glad you're feeling better.
- I am. Thank you for that.
That's so cool.
Since when did he start doing stuff
for other people?
Now I actually am worried
that something happened to his brain.
People change, I guess.
Wouldn't you rather the money
go to keeping the parks safe?
Yes, but now we have the money
under false pretences.
I actually think
that you have a bigger problem.
What?
There is someone in your department
who is willing to lie
about being mugged because
he's afraid of his coworkers.
Carl, what are you doing here?
Well, since you decided
to drag my name through the mud on TV,
I figured why not return the favor?
Carl, could you quietly quiet down
for a second and please tell me
what's going on quietly?
In a quiet voice.
A citizen handed in
a very interesting home video
that I think the people of Pawnee
will find very interesting.
Take a peek at this.
Keep your eyes on the creek.
There he is.
This is my favorite part.
Not willing to share with a dog.
So it would appear that park security
was not to blame after all.
Okay, look,
I have a proposition for you.
Fine. I'll have sex with you
in exchange for the tape.
That's not what I'm saying!
Okay?
Just listen to what I have to say.
The Ramsett park mugging story
continues
with a shiny new twist.
Ranger Carl Lorthner is here today.
Now I understand
that you have a bombshell
to drop
that you are just sitting on.
Yes, that's correct.
I came on today because I have
some important information to share.
I finally saw Avatar,
and I thought it lived up
to the hype.
I'm not sure
what that has to do with the mugging.
Leslie, counterpoint.
I disagree with Carl.
I have seen avatar as well.
And I think it exceeded the hype.
What?
Oh, boy.
- We...
- Disagreement.
Well, things are
really heating up in here. Aren't they?
We should probably take some calls.
That segment was a disaster!
Don't you ever **** me like that again.
This is Pawnee ***** today.
Do you know that for you I bumped a cat
that can stand up on its hinders?
You disgust me, Knope.
Get out of my sight.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Go.
Don't make me chase you.
You want to go eat something.
I am part of a great team.
And sometimes the best way
to maintain a strong team
is just by letting someone know
that he is still a part of it.
This is the only copy.
And I am going to destroy it.
Right after I watch it
one more time.
I'm sorry, but it is so good.
- I got you a peppermint latte.
- Seriously?
- My goodness. I love a pepp...
- I know.
Jeez.
Go ahead.
We should just directly
apply the food to your clothes.
Making fun of Jerry's back.
They can laugh at me all they want.
Because two more years until I retire
with full benefits and pension.
And my wife and I, we have bought
a little cottage on a lake.
And I'm gonna make myself
a stack of mystery novels,
a box of cigars and I could sit back
and enjoy my life.
April was double-checked the lunch order
you want the salmon or the twout?
Twout! Twout! Twout!