That's me.
I'm George MacFayden.
I wanted to talk to you
about the amount of snow
in the parks.
I've been getting a lot
of visitors recently,
thanks to...
a stupid, worthless, new push
to make government officials
more accessible
to the public.
There is a disturbing
lack of benches in Ramsett park!
I want to sit more!
And another thing I like
is the layout of the hiking trails.
I made this in one
of your pottery classes.
It's terrible!
This is my hell.
- Feygnasse Team -
La Fabrique ::.
Ann's friend, Justin.
Of course. Hi.
Thank you. Thank you for coming in.
- My pleasure. Not a problem.
- Have a seat.
I should warn you, land seizure
isn't my specialty,
- Any friend of Ann's...
- Is a friend of mine.
That's my motto too.
So, what is your specialty?
Is it locking up the bad guys,
or keeping them on the streets?
Neither.
It's civil litigation, mostly.
- That's interesting.
- Can be... I've got this crazy case.
Have you ever heard of this product,
fire in a can?
I love those commercials!
If you wanna start a fire
but you have to do it fast, then...
You shouldn't buy it. It'll literally
burn your hand clean off.
It is an aerosol can
with an igniter and a trigger.
It's essentially a blow torch.
And, if you can believe it,
it was invented
to warm up baby bottles.
This is my colleague, Tom Haverford.
How are you?
You are wearing the hell
out of that suit, sir.
- Banana 2-button.
- Let's go into the conference room.
- I got everything laid out.
- We should talk later.
12:15.
You're early today.
April, there's no paper
in the printer.
So?
So that's the one thing you do.
Attention.
April, stop doing that.
Jerry told me to,
so it's super-crucial.
More important than that,
and more important than anything
in this God-forsaken world
is finding me an assistant.
You get an assistant now?
I've always been able,
but I've turned it down
cause it's a waste of money.
In the 8 years I've been at the job,
I've saved the taxpayers of this city
more than 150 grand.
But now, I need the taxpayers' money
to save me from the taxpayers.
Post this at your college.
This looks like an ad for nothing.
Please be careful with it.
It's my only copy.
You are very organized, Leslie.
Yeah, I am.
Thank you.
I love that.
You got the coolest job.
Let me guess.
This is our park.
I want to know
everything about this.
These green things represent trees.
I come in, like, two hours late
because I had to finish
watching Swimfan
because it was... on.
And everyone, like,
jumped down my throat.
Oh, man.
Can't wait till my internship is over,
so I can get the hell out of here.
You're all set.
Free of charge, of course.
Why don't you
sell your band's CDs here?
That is a brilliant idea.
I cannot believe
I didn't think of that.
I have been
writing a lot of songs
about shining shoes lately.
I tend to write about
what I'm doing.
Talkin' 'bout
Writin' about what I'm doin'
Now I'm singin' about
talkin' about
Writin' about what I'm doin'
Companies make bogus claims
all the time.
You're gonna be just fine.
Thank you so much.
I know you're really busy.
Please, it's my pleasure.
Least this stuff is interesting.
It actually reminds me...
Two years ago I was in Borneo,
officiating a wedding,
and this enormous
medicine man showed up,
and he was there
to basically tell...
Hey, kiddo.
How you doin'?
- Good. I haven't seen you in forever.
- So good to see you.
You too.
Do you want to grab some dinner?
I would love to.
I cannot. I am swamped.
You're always so busy.
Next week, I promise.
Hey, I'm Mark.
Sorry.
Justin, this is Mark.
- This is the city planner.
- Oh, my God.
- It's such a pleasure to meet you.
- Pleasure.
Anyway, Leslie, I have to go.
It has been a super pleasure
meeting you.
I am gonna get into this,
and I'll get back
on Monday about it.
Great.
- See you, Justin.
- Tom, good seeing you.
I've been thinking.
It has been a while since Dave left.
And I think I might be ready
to start dating again.
That's great!
Oh, my God.
I have so many ideas.
I was only with Mark for one night,
and then I was hung up on him
for six years.
I dated dave for three months.
So if I continue that pattern,
I won't be over him for...
500 years.
What is your ideal man?
He has the brains of George Clooney
in the body of Joe Biden.
Interesting.
Okay, just off the bat,
there is a couple of doctors
I think you would love.
What about Justin?
I feel like
we kind of hit it off in there.
Yeah, I don't...
I have to think about that.
I'm not sure that would work.
- Is there something wrong with him?
- No, he's really, really, really great.
And you're so great, obviously.
I just do...
I don't know.
But I will find you someone.
I promise. And he'll be awesome.
- I'm gonna go do it right now.
- Good, great. Yes!
Go, Ann, go!
Just one rule.
I don't want to date a twin.
'cause I've been tricked before.
Yes, I understand your complaint.
I have to go now.
Please. Thank you.
Ron Solo.
I want to help you
with your search.
- Why?
- 'Cause I wan to do my boy Ron a solid.
I know exactly what you're looking for,
and I will find you a reliable person.
Now, get out there
and find me an assistant.
- Did you get my messages?
- No, I been running around all day.
- What's up?
- I found the perfect guy.
But he's going out of town,
so he can only do tonight.
So I came over here
right after work.
- Is that his blood?
- What?
- Damn. Now I have to go back.
- Who is he?
His name is Chris,
and he's an MRI technician.
And he's really cute and he's
very passionate about his job.
And I told him all about you
and he's really interested.
So dinner tonight,
and here's the info.
Thanks.
Wait!
How is he gonna know it's me?
I'll wear a red rose in my hair.
No, I'll wear a giant, red hat.
I don't have one of those.
What should I wear? It's gotta be red.
I'll tell him what you look like.
Good call.
I'm Leslie.
Are you Chris?
- Sorry I'm late.
- Don't worry about it.
You look beautiful.
- Let me take your coat.
- Thanks.
Sure.
Well done, Ann.
- I actually heard that.
- What?
I went to Wisconsin for both undergrad
and grad school.
- Go, Badgers.
- Indiana Hoosiers.
No, Badgers.
It's not important.
I'm just...
glad that we could make this happen.
Ann told me
how wonderful you are,
and I just had to see for myself.
She's my number one best friend.
Kind of wish she'd told me
that you went to Indiana, but whatever.
So you're in charge
of amusement parks, right?
- God, that's exciting.
- Actually, it's regular parks.
Like swings and slides and stuff.
Strike two.
Isn't it funny
how these setups
are always just so awkward?
Hey, watch this.
I will now extinguish this candle
with my bare hands.
- That really hurts.
- Are you okay?
God, it looks so much easier
on the Internet.
God, I gotta borrow
some of your ice.
German?
All right, later.
Was that... Justin?
We are going to lunch tomorrow.
Great.
Did you guys ever date?
No, we never did.
He's just like...
a really amazing person.
Awesome.
Let's do this!
Marley & me.
- Puppies! Puppies, puppies.
- I know.
Let's... watch marley & me.
Brian.
Technically, you'd be assisting Ron.
But Ron really doesn't
do much government work,
so you'd really be working for me.
I'm interested
in real world expertise.
I got a nightclub opening to go to.
Which tie do I wear?
I like the one on the left.
That was a trick question.
The answer is this one.
Tell me about you.
Tell me about your friends.
Be as superficial as possible.
I meet a girl at a bar.
She seems kind.
Could go either way.
I get her number. It's two days later.
What do I text her?
- It was nice meeting you?
- No, zack!
I don't text her,
"it was nice meeting you."
I wait eight weeks,
and I text her, "what's crackin'?"
So do you enjoy it?
Being an MRI technician?
Great question.
Someone steps into the room.
Imagine a mother of three.
Maybe she's a teacher.
She knows something's wrong,
but she doesn't know what it is.
She's scared.
In less than an hour,
I know what it is.
- What's wrong with her?
- I don't know.
But the best part
about being an MRI technician is...
I can see inside everything.
See that guy over there?
Imagine being able
to look inside his head.
I know.
Could look inside the steak
or this butter or this bread.
You can look inside...
anything.
If you look inside this bread,
all you're gonna find is more bread.
I don't know.
I'd have to do an MRI.
Anyway, it's good
that you found your calling.
I've never even had an MRI before.
What?
I don't know about this.
I'm offering you a free scan.
Usually costs up to $2,000.
I'm kind of spoiling you here.
I am a little curious.
Good.
'Cause, frankly,
I don't want to invest in someone
who has 3 months to live.
I'm trying to think of this
as an adventure.
Just getting right back
on that horse.
Even if that horse is crazy
and want to peer inside my body.
- How does that feel?
- Weird.
Perfect.
You're not on your period?
No.
Does that matter?
Not for this.
It's gonna be a little cramped.
Don't worry, I'll be right
on the other side of that glass.
Just your basic assistant stuff.
Taking messages, wakeup calls.
Muscle milk runs,
condom runs,
bottle service to the Snakehole Lounge.
- That kind of stuff.
- What do I get out of this?
Connections.
Plus 19 grand a year.
Minus my 10% headhunter's fee.
I have to pay you two grand
if I get hired?
I have a job to offer.
In the immortal words
of Rob Blagojevich,
it's a *** valuable thing.
You just don't give it away for nothing.
You never told me where you're from.
- I'm from Pawnee.
- Keep still, please.
- What kind of music do you like?
- Can I answer that?
Sure. Keep still.
All kinds.
It's very important
that you keep still at this moment.
I've told you that a 1,000 times.
Did you ever break your arm?
You can answer that.
Here, I'll turn it off.
I was on my bike,
and some boys were making fun of me.
I chased them and I lost control.
I'm surprised you can see that.
It was like three years ago.
I turned the machine off for that.
You never had any kids?
You've got a great oven.
- Time to go.
- You've got ample room in there.
Honestly, if you wanted to,
you could go triplets
right off the bat.
You got a big,
industrial-sized oven.
So we're done?
How's the date going?
Good.
We just finished the MRI.
I said that I wanted
to get back out there,
but this guy is nuts.
Sorry, Les.
I'll find you somebody else.
Don't let this sour you on dating.
No cell phones!
What was that about?
I set Leslie up on a date.
I don't think it's going that well.
With Justin?
No, this guy I know
from the hospital.
Why not Justin?
I don't really see them together.
Leslie got out of a relationship,
so I didn't want Justin
to be like her rebound guy
or anything.
That makes sense.
Leslie is a notoriously cruel
and thoughtless person.
- Why are we talking about this?
- We're not.
You got a large brain.
Thank you.
No, it looks pretty.
Hang on.
That's weird.
- What? What's weird?
- Your brain.
- You see that shadow right there?
- Is that bad?
I don't know, I'd have a doctor
look at that immediately, if I were you.
Are you serious?
Wait.
It was like a smudge or something.
Crazy.
Thank God I was here.
Mark, I've never gone out with him!
I swear!
There's something weird
about the way you talk about him.
I don't know
there was definitely times
when we thought
we would go out someday, but...
That's why you didn't set Leslie up,
because you're saving him.
- No, I'm not.
- You are.
You don't have someone in your life
that you think,
"I don't know, if things were different,
maybe someday... "
You know what?
You can't save somebody for the future
while you're in a relationship.
Even I know that.
- Come on, don't go.
- I'll talk to you later.
And, by the way,
the dog dies at the end.
- Did you want to go back to your place?
- Actually,
it was nice to meet you, but I think
this is gonna be our last date.
I get it.
You get your MRI and get out?
- This was your idea.
- Clever lady.
Guess I'm not as good a tech
as I thought I was.
Should have noticed
that you're missing a heart.
Good-bye, Leslie.
Right.
I drove us here.
- Goody.
- Do you mind if we pick up my son
at his basketball game
on the way back?
This is really good.
"Cease and desist, burden of proof"?
Check out paragraph two,
where I dropped the F-bomb.
"Frivolous."
Definitely have
the city attorney look at that.
But that should be enough
to do the trick.
- Justin. I can't thank you enough.
- It's my pleasure.
Maybe I'll see you around.
I would lo...
I'll see you.
Damn, he is all right.
Why don't you hit that?
Well, frankly,
I would like to hit that.
But Ann's being
a little weird about it.
When you were dating Ann,
did you know this guy Justin?
I hate Justin.
Ann was obviously into him.
It was so annoying.
I would say, in terms of guys
that she's in love with, he's up here.
I'm up here,
and then you're down here.
I just wanted to make sure
that I wasn't crazy.
So naturally,
I came to you for reassurance.
Do me a favor. Don't tell Ann
that we talked about this.
Will do.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
What you're doing to mark is not cool.
Why are you talking to each other?
You know what? Forget it.
I'm not getting into this with you.
- You did something wrong?
- No! I didn't do anything wrong!
Come here.
This isn't your business. You don't know
what you're talking about.
Actually,
I do know what I'm talking about.
Every time I sit around all afternoon,
playing video games,
wearing my slippers,
all of a sudden, I would start
to feel bad about myself.
- And do you know why?
- Didn't you explain why?
I would feel bad about myself
because I would start
to think about this perfect guy.
Any time
you would talk about Justin,
I didn't feel very important.
That was rough.
I didn't know that.
If you had, I wouldn't have left.
But you do know now,
so you have to choose.
- It's either me or Justin.
- I'm not gonna choose.
- Wait, I'm dating mark!
- Are you, though?
That close.
I've done it.
I found your assistant,
and he's dope.
His name is Jean-Ralphio.
Big-T.
Mr. Swanson, two things.
One :
It is an absolute honor to meet you.
Two :
Who is that hot intern chick out there?
Because, honestly,
daaaamn!
- Take a seat.
- Right. Here we go.
So, Jean-Ralphio...
You got him right here.
Leave a message after the beep.
Why do I want you as my assistant?
For starters, access to the illest club.
And that's just for starters.
I will work for you.
I will be on you, 24/7.
I'll be like your family.
I'm here when you get here,
tucking you into bed at night.
It's not gay.
Do we have questions?
I think our only question is
when can you start?
Right now. Let's do it.
Thank you for coming in.
We will talk.
Cool.
I feel good about this.
You can hit me up on Facebook any time,
day or night. You know that?
- Take care, buddy.
- Boom.
What do you think
of your new assistant?
I wanna punch you in the face
so bad right now.
What?
- Message received. I'll keep looking.
- Thank you.
Bring me the opposite of him.
- What kind of music is this?
- Rock and roll.
Fast, smooth,
handsome rock.
That band is blowing up right now.
They're number one on itunes.
I'll take one.
Your change.
You are amazing.
I like when you hang out here.
- I want to be your assistant.
- Really?
- You hate it here.
- So do you.
I'll make sure you don't have to go
to any meetings.
If anyone comes to see you,
I'll scare them away.
Wait, April.
If you had to choose
between these two ties...
You're hired.
I just figured
I might as well get paid
for being here.
I was just calling you.
Here.
This is a prescription
for Denise Dogan.
My God, I'm sorry.
I'm so out of sorts.
Here.
Porter's grill at 7:00.
Justin's gonna meet you there.
I'm sorry Chris was such a jerk.
You deserve way better than that.
If this situation is weird,
or if you feel weird...
It's not weird.
You guys will really like each other.
- Thanks.
- I gotta run. I have another stop
on the pride-swallowing tour
of city hall.
Go get 'em.
That's where I never find things.
Hi, Ann.
So I just set up Justin and Leslie.
And I'm sorry.
I rented district 9
if you maybe wanted
to spoil that for me tonight.
My God!
Dark ending, right.
I'm back on the horse.
And this horse is a lawyer,
so I'm looking forward
to riding him.
No, wait.
Ten months ago, she was an intern
who could give a c-r-a-p
about local government.
Now, she's our newest employee.
To April.
Cheers!
Jerry, come and celebrate.
No, thanks.
Everybody, let's get back to work.
Where are you going?
I want to talk to Ron
about the size of my desk.
You have to schedule an appointment.
How about now?
- Ron's not here.
- He's right there. I can see him.
I'll let you know
when he's available.
Atta girl.