It's quiet in here.
Where is everyone?
The government has shut down.
It's in every newspaper.
How long?
If we're lucky, this building
will be empty for months.
That is really bad timing.
I just got this super-sweet-ass
rad crotch rocket.
I've always wanted one of these!
But due to, you know,
never having a job,
I couldn't afford it until now.
Got a really good deal on my lease.
Paying like 12% interest.
That's one of the highest
you can get.
I've been trying
to get a hold of April.
If you see her,
tell her I really need to talk to her?
- You got it.
- All right, thanks.
Nailed it.
- Feygnasse Team -
La Fabrique ::.
Episode 224
Freddy Spaghetti
mpm - Collioure
valpi - Gérard
Yeko - lestat
All I can tell you
is that all the parks
are closed until further notice.
No one is more upset about this
than I am.
Not like it's a competition
or anything,
cause, I would win.
But that's neither here nor there.
- Point is, I would win.
- How long?
Could be forever.
With the government shut down,
who's gonna stop Al Qaeda?
One thing at a time.
School is out in two weeks.
What am I going to do
with my kids all day,
keep them in my house?
- Where I live?
- I don't know what to tell you.
What about the kids concert
tomorrow at Ramsett park?
The Freddy Spaghetti concert.
Freddy Spaghetti
has been canceled.
What? Jeez.
Sit down and tell me exactly
what's happened.
Every year we kick off summer
with a children's concert series,
and this year, the concert
is canceled due to the shutdown.
That's terrible.
And we need to fix it.
All right.
Great!
Very glad that you agree,
but I worked hard on my argument.
Is there any way I can still...
- I'd love to hear it.
- Good, thank you.
"You're wrong.
Are you crazy?
"Can you put a price tag
on a child's smile?"
What a surprise.
The government
has been shut down for two days.
And one city employee
has tried to schedule
14 meetings with me.
Can you guess who?
Ben, there was a big concert?
Now there's not?
Isn't there anything we can do?
- No, there isn't.
- It's too bad.
Sorry, Leslie.
Damn!
I have to go run ten miles.
I have run ten miles a day,
everyday, for 18 years.
That's 65000 miles
a third of the way to the moon.
My goal is to run to the moon.
Ben, let's talk solutions.
Pawnee is broke.
There's no money
for a concert. Okay?
Idaho
cut their parks department by 80%,
and Idaho
is basically one giant park.
I'll say it again...
Pawnee is better than Idaho.
Pawnee is not special, okay?
Your department...
all the way down here,
is not a priority.
Frankly, you're not supposed
to be in the building.
- You're non-essential.
- That is not your call.
I know.
It's on your badge.
This?
This isn't me.
Ann Perkins!
Chris... Something.
I was just doing my daily
lunchtime ten miles,
I ran by the hospital,
I thought I'd pop up and say hi.
- Did you just start your run?
- I'm already at mile nine.
- But you're not sweating at all.
- I know.
I have a resting heart rate
of 28 bpm.
The scientist said that my heart
could pump fuel up into an airplane.
I'd love to go out on a date with you.
I think you might find me attractive,
cause you got drunk
and kissed me when we first met.
No pressure, but tonight is open.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really busy right now.
I will try again soon, Ann Perkins.
That's the guy who likes you
that you're not into.
Which part of him
are you not looking?
Traditionally,
when I end a long-term relationship,
I'm fragile.
And I have a tendency
to do some reckless things.
So I need to stay away from Chris.
Can't stand this government shutdown!
Can't stand this budget crisis.
But what I can't stand
is they're canceling Freddy Spaghetti.
You know everything.
What should I do?
I don't know.
Why don't you see a movie
or go shopping or...
What are you doing?
What's happening?
They offered me a buyout,
and I took it.
And so now I work
for Norton construction.
Sorry, I shouldn't have done that.
- That's OK.
- How could you quit?
You know, not everyone
has your enthusiasm for this work.
I guess I've been
mispronouncing your name
all these years.
Mark brendana-quits.
Recently, I had been
thinking about maybe,
leaving this job.
But I felt like I needed a sign.
And then Ann broke up with me
the week that I was gonna propose.
The government got shut down,
and yesterday...
one of those pigeons
took a *** on me.
And I was indoors, so...
Why are you here?
I need your help.
Is this a bad time?
Lucy's here, I'm in my sexy pajamas,
I just took four Benadryls
to dull my sensitivity.
- Yes! It is a bad time.
- You're about to have sex.
Why else would Boys 2 Men's
On Bended Knee be playing right now?
I just wanna give you a little advice,
don't make it last really long.
- Ladies don't like that.
- Okay, great.
Wait, just one more thing.
Are you using protection?
I'm just gonna stay away
from all guys right now.
Less man time, more Ann time.
The only guy
that I care about right now
is six feet tall
with wild, crazy hair
and a ukulele
that doubles as a water gun.
Children's concerts
aren't a priority.
What is?
Sewage.
Pawnee's kids
are less important than poop tubes.
I don't know, what are you gonna do?
- That's the way it is...
- Wait, wait...
If all parks are closed,
why not just have the concert
in the lot behind my house?
Ann, you devious bastard.
Well, the cow goes moo
And the pig goes oink
I've spent the last 3 hours
coming up with the plan.
And I sent up the bat signal
for all the department to join us.
I told them to be here by 8:00.
- You think anybody's gonna show up?
- "A", yes.
"B", even if they don't,
we'll put the concert on ourselves.
But, "C", yes,
they're definitely gonna show up.
Although, "D", maybe not.
You need to prepare
for the eventuality that no one...
God bless you, Jerry Gergich!
Never thought I'd hear
those words from you.
April's here.
Move.
I didn't think you were gonna help.
I still might not.
Jerry, how do you feel
about lifting heavy things?
- My doctor said I should avoid...
- Being a wuss? I agree.
So go out there
and get the equipment out of the truck.
With current and projected deficits,
we need to cut expenditures by 32%.
Let's make it an even 40.
That's not necessary.
Slash it! Slash it!
I am an official member
of a task force
dedicated
to slashing the city budget.
Just saying that gave me a semi.
Right off the bat,
we sell City Hall.
Let somebody turn it into
a large gas station or a T.J. Maxx.
That is a very creative idea.
But we don't wanna sell
any major assets,
we don't wanna lose
future revenue streams.
I hear that.
Don't worry, I have tons more ideas.
So sorry.
New ringtone.
Don't cut anything without me.
I don't care if you hate what we do.
I love it enough for both of us.
We're gonna put on the concert,
today, 5:00, on lot 48.
- You can't do that.
- Watch me.
We're gonna do this.
With or without you.
Hammering away!
Crank it, hit it.
Needs 16 minutes for premium bounce.
After this,
can you go pick up Freddy Spaghetti
in your Mercedes?
We need to give him star treatment.
Sorry we're late.
I had to wait on my girlfriend
- to finish eating breakfast.
- Hi. I'm Lucy.
We had dinner last night.
And... breakfast this morning.
What were doing in between?
Sex stuff.
You guys know Tom really well,
so I don't have to apologize?
Craziest thing is it's like super loud.
You know what I mean?
Was on it 5 min, can't hear a thing.
Am I talking loud?
Hey!
Excuse me.
I called a gajillion times.
Why didn't you call back?
I'm so sorry.
I was busy not wanting to talk to you.
- Jerry, what are you doing?
- Leslie asked me to post these.
- I'll do it.
- Really?
You want some help?
Okay, let's talk
about parks and rec.
This one's complicated.
I know what'll loosen up our brains.
A massage train.
I know what you think.
It's not that I want a massage.
I'll be the caboose.
And Ron Swanson is the locomotive.
Thanks to Ron, the services budget
has already been cut significantly.
So seems like
the best option is job cuts.
Starting with Leslie Knope.
If you fire Leslie,
you might as well
get rid of the department.
I know how valuable she is.
But we've run out of options.
There are plenty of other options.
For example...
sell the zoo animals.
Okay, to whom?
Cosmetics labs.
Weird restaurants.
- I'm just spit-balling here.
- Let's switch it up.
She makes the 2nd highest salary
in the department.
That will go a long way.
I'm telling you,
it's just not an option.
- Come on, focus up, buddy!
- Give me a sec.
Will you stop and listen to me?
Fine, I don't wanna talk to you.
Reverse psychiatry.
Fine.
What?
I like you.
In a...
romantical kind of way.
You do?
Do you...
- Like me?
- Yes.
So then...
perhaps...
shall we go out this evening?
Don't think
we should see each other.
Damn it.
Because you're 21 and I'm 29?
Don't care about that.
It's because
whenever I see you talk to Ann or...
talk about Ann,
I feel like
you still have feelings for her.
No, I don't!
But I don't!
Really.
I don't.
Well, I think do.
So...
That's a problem for me.
Because of my libertarian beliefs,
Leslie does 95% of the work.
So you should lay me off.
I'd be proud to be a casualty
in this righteous war.
It's because of your beliefs
that we need to keep you.
You would maintain fiscal responsibility
after we're gone.
- I strenuously object.
- Well, Ron, we're moving on.
Every department
is losing a Leslie Knope.
No, they are not. No other department
has one to begin with.
Right now, she's single-handedly
putting up some lousy concert
for the city's kids.
What?
Could someone else
massage my shoulders?
Looking good.
I wish we'd
built one of those elevators
that comes up from under the stage.
? kind of thing?
They're coming.
- Who, the Russians?
- No, the state auditors.
I accidentally told what you were doing
in an attempt to save some jobs.
It's been a very strange day for me.
Everybody be cool.
Just be cool.
All right!
Everybody!
Everybody, everybody.
Everyone...
You are all super amazing.
You are what makes Pawnee great,
and I just want to tell you
that I'm totally supportive
- of your inspiring efforts here today!
- That, we'll take.
My partner Ben
wants to say something.
- We're shutting this down.
- Damn!
That's terrible news.
Surely there has to be a solution, Ben.
Ben says no.
Sorry, everyone.
The concert is canceled, everybody.
Here's the thing.
It's not canceled, we're putting it on.
Because the stage is already built.
Everything was donated for free
by local vendors.
Everyone here believes
that what we're doing is essential.
Freddy spaghetti will sing.
Actually, I just found out...
Freddy Spaghetti ain't comin'.
Freddy Spaghetti may not sing.
But something much cooler
is going to happen.
I think.
Good job.
You should hydrate.
When we canceled on him,
he took another gig in Eagleton.
At a library.
That's the worst place
I could imagine.
We're not giving up.
He's not the only musician in town.
I don't feel like playing right now.
Andy, please.
I don't even have children's songs.
My last song was called sex hair.
Well, just take the word "sex"
and change it to "pickle".
Pickle?
You've got pickle hair, baby
And you got it from me
- Still sounds it's about sex.
- I'm in.
I gotta grab my guitar from my house.
I'll be back shortly.
See, guys?
We have a solution.
And the good news is,
there's always a solution
if your motives are pure
and your cause is just.
There's nothing...
My arm!
You have two broken bones
in your right arm and four in your hand.
That's the side that hurts.
- How soon until he's better?
- We'll set the fractures.
I'd like to keep him
for observation.
Can you fix me
in the next ten minutes?
Sure. I'll just advance
medical science 30 years.
- Great.
- Can Mouse Rat play without you?
They tried once.
They're called Rat Mouse.
And they're awful.
But you have got to find somebody.
There's an old saying in show business:
"The show must go wrong".
Everything always goes wrong,
and you just have to deal with it.
Hello, Pawnee.
I'm Renata Ricotta.
Freddy Spaghetti
couldn't make it today.
He bumped his noodle.
There was sauce everywhere.
It was just streaming
out of his face.
It was really scary.
If you're happy and you know it
Clap your hands
Hey, kids, it's me,
Freddy Spaghetti!
I thought you were playing Eagleton.
All I know is this guy showed up,
made me a much better offer.
I am all about the money, baby.
Thank you very much.
Ron Corleone.
This really attractive woman
is my girlfriend Lucy.
- Impressive handshake.
- Thanks.
My father told me that a limp handshake
was for weak men and communists.
- He hated both.
- Well done, Tommy.
Is that bacon on your turkey leg?
They call it a "Swanson".
I brought you your favorite.
Every color of jell-o.
The jell-o rainbow.
Injured Andy.
It's kind of like old times?
I almost expect you
to call me A-cakes.
"A-cakes."
I'm glad you're okay.
My God, I'm...
I'm so sorry.
I should not...
I'm sorry.
That was... not...
Spaghetti
Fuseli
Egg noodles
Why did you do this?
Well, I'm not a monster.
I want the kids to have their concert.
Mean Ben has a soft spot.
Is that what you guys call me?
"Mean Ben"?
Look, this is really great today.
But...
There's gonna be a lot of pain ahead.
We have to cut 32% of the...
Can you just stop it?
Just for one moment,
enjoy the fact
that you provided a service for people,
not a cut.
A service.
And they love it.
Biggest service
was getting you to stop singing.
I just heard.
Are you okay?
Listen,
what I said this afternoon was...
stupid.
I totally want to go out with you.
Good.
I want to be with you.
- That was nice.
- That... Yeah.
Here's one thing, real quick.
I want to be totally honest with you,
because I like you so much.
But two minutes ago,
me and Ann did kiss.
- What?
- But here's...
No, no, no.
It was crazy.
She kissed me.
- Okay, bye.
- Wait, where are you going?
Dude, don't even think
about kissing me.
What was your favorite song,
Chelsea?
Penne and the jets.
Me too!
Thank you all so much.
With all the parks closed,
we've been going crazy.
It's our pleasure.
You guys are the best,
most important people,
and government
- in the best city in the world.
- Suck it, Paris, France.
Well, I would say
see you tomorrow, but...
- Great job.
- Good work, Leslie.
See you soon, I hope.
I liked this a lot better
when it was a pit.
Is that weird?
I'm sorry I called you
Mark Brendana-quits.
Don't ever apologize to me.
I'm serious. If everyone in government
were like you,
then I would probably
still work there.
- I got you a going away present.
- You did?
Here.
Red tape.
So you'll never forget your roots.
That's really nice of you.
Well, I have something for you too.
You do?
I sort of threw together some plans
for a future park.
I couldn't fit in all you wanted,
like the roller coaster
or the shark tank,
but I think
it's a pretty good start.
You're really welcome.
But, you know, Pawnee's bankrupt.
I doubt I'll get to build a park
anytime soon.
I wouldn't bet against you.
See you around.
Morning.
What are you doing here?
Ron made me the official Parks and Rec
representative for budget discussions.
- That's only supposed to be...
- Essential personnel?
So shall we get started?
I have so many ideas.
Is this an autographe of Jaime Foxx?
There it is.
How long is this shut-down
gonna last?
No idea.
I might have to get a temp job.
Maybe I should start working
on my cologne line.
Check it out.
Whenever Ron has sex,
the next morning,
he comes in dressed like tiger woods.
You all set?
God.
What?
Who is that?
That is my ex-wife.
www.sous-titres.eu