Ann Perkins,
what's happening, sweetheart?
Just waiting for April.
She's taking care of my house.
That's great.
Happy belated valentine's day.
Valentine's day was a month ago.
Why are you giving it to me now?
Whatever. Happy early valentine's day.
I saw this and I thought of you.
Hope you keep that
somewhere special.
Okay, this is one of those nanny cam
teddy bears, isn't it?
What?
No!
It's a regular
camera-less teddy bear.
Just put it in your bedroom,
don't even think about it.
It's a robot bear.
It's programmed to snuggle.
- I'll take it.
- Donna, there's a camera in it.
I know.
- Feygnasse Team -
La Fabrique ::.
All right, that's basically it.
Water the plants, get the mail...
- Can I read your mail?
- No, please don't.
- Fine.
- And...
Here are the keys, and remember...
I know, don't let Tom make a copy.
That's right, good.
I'm paying April 50 bucks
to watch my house while I'm away.
I would have asked Leslie,
but I've seen the way
she takes care of her house.
Plus, there's always been
a little distance between me and April.
And I thought this would maybe,
give us a chance...
to get a little closer,
maybe even...
I don't like Ann.
Become friends.
Who knows?
Leslie, this is Evelyn Rowshlind
from the mayor's office.
Hello, I've always dreamed of you.
- Excuse me?
- Meeting you.
- What can I do for you? Have a seat.
- I prefer to stand.
I have kind of an odd favor to ask.
Mayor Gunderson was playing golf
at Pawnee municipal,
and he brought his dog...
Rufus. We all know Rufus.
Everybody loves Rufus.
He's a great dog.
Continue.
They were out on the sixth hole
when suddenly, out of nowhere...
Rufus was bitten by a possum?
Yes, how did you know that?
It was Fairway Frank.
Fairway Frank is this awful possum
who lives near the sixth hole
of the public golf course.
He's number 3 on the parks department's
most wanted pests list.
Right behind the bats
who like to poop on the bell tower,
and poopy, the raccoon who poops
all over the high school cafeteria.
Shouldn't you take this
up with animal control?
Let's be honest,
it's not the most effective
branch of our government.
A bunch of burned-out morons.
You have the reputation
as a person who gets things done.
So we'd like
you to form a little task force,
find the animal, and put it down.
- Task force?
- Needless to say,
the mayor will be very grateful
for your help.
Ma'am, the next time we speak,
we shall be dancing
on the grave of a possum.
Great.
Ron will show you around.
Right this way is the exit.
Yo, police.
No, you're not.
Coffee?
You always know what to bring me.
I only ever bring you coffee.
And it is my very favorite
non-alcoholic hot drink,
except for hot tea.
And hot orange juice,
weirdly delicious.
Anyways, thank you so much.
I needed it.
I got a really bad case
of shoe shine head today.
Andy recently diagnosed himself
with what he calls
"shoe shine head".
It's when you shine too many shoes
and the fumes create
a thunderstorm in your brain.
Cures include coffee,
cheeseburgers,
and napping on the floor.
- Hey, Ron. What's up?
- I...
have a wood shop
and I'm planning a little expansion.
Need my buddy Mark, the city planner,
to sign off on the plans.
Sure, I just need
to schedule an inspection.
- That's not really necessary.
- Yes, it is, but you'll be fine
as long as you
don't have any code violations.
You don't have
any code violations, do you?
Nope.
Eugene!
Boy, we have
a really important job for you.
- We'll get to it first thing Monday.
- Today's Wednesday.
- Look, this is not a request.
- We're acting under direct orders
- from mayor Gunderson's dog.
- Office.
I need your two best guys to join me
and be part of my task force.
That would be Harris and Brett.
But they're not here.
- Isn't that them there?
- Nope.
Dude!
That stupid possum
is on the golf course again.
Would you rather I capture it myself
and then you can come and pick it up?
Cool!
You want your ball back?
Want your ball back?
Come with me.
How you know my name, homie?
- Stop.
- Stop hanging yourself.
- I'm gonna hang yourself.
- Quite a crack team you've assembled.
- There's 5 of us and only one possum.
How hard can it be?
Excuse us,
task force coming through.
Task force clear, resume golfing.
I used to love Tiger Woods
because he was a great champion.
But after that sex scandal,
the man is a God.
Welcome to my haven.
You're the first non-me to set foot
in this building in ten years.
- None of this is up to code.
- Sure it is.
It's up to the Swanson code.
There's no drainage,
doesn't seem to be any ventilation,
you've got hazardous chemicals
over here.
Yeah, which only I am breathing.
It's the same liberty that gives me
the right to fart in my own car.
Are you gonna tell a man
that he can't fart in his own car?
There is a basket of oil-soaked rags
above a wood burning stove.
Good thing
I've got a fire extinguisher.
Which, I can assure you,
is totally up to your precious code.
This says it should be recharged
June of 1996.
Those dates are arbitrary.
They're like those expiration
dates that the government
forces companies to put
on yogurt and medicine.
Observe.
Watch yourself.
I'll replace this.
Happy?
How long
it would take me to learn golf?
I could teach you.
I have a 16 handicap.
But it takes a lot of practice.
You have to get up early, hit the range,
- practice reading greens.
- See, I don't wanna do all that.
I just want
some of those dope pants.
It's Fairway Frank!
All right, Tom?
I want you to very slowly...
25, 26, 27, 28...
- violations.
- Come on, Brendanawicz. Relax.
Let me make you a canoe.
I don't need a canoe, Ron.
I need you to fix this place up.
I'll give you 24 hours.
We may only get
one chance to catch this thing,
so we have to play it smart.
You two flank the left,
I'll flank the right,
Andy will come in through...
I got it.
- I got him.
- Task force! Engage!
- He's got it.
- He's good.
Come on, you cowards!
Lemme see his face.
It's him, we got him!
It's okay.
He's on my neck.
- He's on my neck.
- It's all right.
All right, it's okay.
You're next, poopy.
Very impressive, Leslie.
Thank you.
I had a great task force.
I was just the simple mastermind
who planned the whole operation
and executed it to perfection.
This is Andy Dwyer.
He actually caught the thing.
- Mr. Dwyer...
- Please...
My friends call me Andy radical.
No, we don't.
By day, Andy Dwyer, shoeshine-ist.
By different time of day,
Andy radical, possum tackler.
And by night...
I do whatever I want, no job.
We think that this
is a great P.R. opportunity
so we've arranged for a reporter
from The Journal
to stop by to interview,
get some pictures of the team.
Task force.
Great.
And next time you need a special favor
from the mayor's office, give me a call.
Oh, my God, I will.
I need so many special favors.
- Which one should I choose?
- You don't have...
How about an extra recycling can?
Laminated bus pass?
What time do yougo to bed?
'cause my best ideas come at night.
Let's stick
to business hours, shall we?
See you in hell, buddy.
Am I sure the possum
we caught is Fairway Frank?
Am I quite sure?
No.
Am I sure enough?
Maybe.
If it wasn't Fairway Frank,
would I feel badly? Of course.
- Could I live with myself?
- That depends.
As a city official it's important
that I ask myself a lot of questions.
Does doing so
help me make decisions?
- Hey, Shauna.
- Hi, Leslie.
Andy, you remember Shauna Malwae-Tweep
from The Pawnee Journal.
How could I forget?
You wrote the article when I fell.
And then afterwards
had sex with Mark,
and everyone talked about it.
So you're on the golf course,
and you see Fairway Frank.
Well, we see a possum
that we believe to be Fairway Frank.
So for right now,
let's just refer to it as a possum.
Let me explain something, Tweep.
When you're in a situation,
you don't have time to think.
So I thought to myself,
"Don't think, Andy. Act."
So you weren't thinking.
Not at all.
I cannot emphasize enough
how little I was thinking.
Were you scared?
No, no, I wasn't.
Well, I lived in the pit
for the better part of last year
and made some vermin friends.
You know what?
Friends sounds stupid.
Colleagues.
They are bad at sharing,
but they are good at tag.
Well, your family
must be very proud.
What does your girlfriend think?
The nurse?
I broke up with Ann.
Shortly after she kicked me out and told
we wouldn't be together anymore.
Maybe this article
will change her mind.
What now?
I hadn't even thought of that.
Of all the things I thought
would bring us back together,
catching a possum
was never on that list.
Let's go take some pictures
of Fairway Frank.
Of the possum.
Seriously, man,
when you wear these clothes,
you just feel better than everyone else.
You know?
Busy?
- No, what's up?
- Just wanted to tell you,
I understand that city codes exist
and I know why they exist.
And I understand
that you enforce them.
Okay, good talk.
Can you sign off on my plans now?
Did you get everything up to code?
- Yup.
- No, you didn't.
- You clearly didn't.
- It's my property,
my land,
my shop!
Tummy needs a banana, you guys good?
Ron, you're asking me
to do a bad job,
at my job,
and I'm just not gonna do that.
So if you don't mind,
would you please get out of my office?
Silly me, there was this little pom-pom
on my glove
and it fell off. You've seen it?
Could you help me look for it?
It should be on the ground somewhere
where I was puttin' it up.
Let's see.
- So how's your hole?
- Excuse me?
The pit. Lot 48?
We're making progress on the park.
In fact, there may be some big news
on that front coming soon.
All because of this very important
business card.
So this isn't really a big story, right?
Nobody cares about this very much.
Fairway Frank did bite the mayor's dog,
so this could be on the front page.
Fairway Frank you're gonna die
You're gonna fry
You guilty son of a bitch
when they flip that switch
Can I talk to you about the possum?
Hypothetically, if you were going
on a mission to say
catch a guilty whale.
And while you were catching the whale,
you saw something else
that may also be another whale,
you were like "what?", you thought :
"Maybe it's not a whale? But a big fish,
a submarine with a face painted on it?"
The point is, if I kill the first whale,
am I technically a murderer?
- What you're talking about?
- I saw a second possum.
There was another possum.
Andy's in there talking to a reporter,
literally kissing his own biceps.
You're telling me
he might not be a hero,
but just some jerk that goes around
tackling random possums?
I've gotta help Leslie find the truth.
Not because I'm pissed at Andy,
which I'm not.
Because I care so deeply
about possums.
'Cause they're so adorable.
April, did you see my photo shoot?
I nailed it.
I fell off the stool when I was trying
to look serious. But I'm okay.
That's cool,
I'm really happy for you.
You are?
Our happy reactions
are super different.
So, he said he's gonna email me
the photos in, like, six hours.
- You wanna wait with me?
- That sounds good,
but I can't because I have to go
do something that actually matters.
Fairway Frank's been haunting
the 6th hole for a while.
You must know him well.
I sure do.
I've chased that little sucker off
more times than I can count.
Can you just take a look
at these photos
and make sure
that it's Fairway Frank?
That's him.
Mr. Campopiano, those are photos
of three different possums.
You want something to drink?
Boss, there's a possum
wandering around on the 14th green.
Should I call animal control again?
My God,
they're here from animal control.
They're gonna take it away.
We need a little bit more time
to figure out the truth. I have an idea.
I'm gonna distract everybody,
then you get that possum out of here.
Can you do that, April?
Get the possum out of here?
Sneak it out?
Can you do it?
Tell me you can do this.
Yes, I can do it. God.
I can't kill the possum
because it might be innocent.
I can't let the possum go
because it might be guilty.
Can't make a good soup,
can't do a handstand in a pool,
can't spell the word "lieutenant."
There's a lot of "can'ts"
in my life right now.
Let's make it happen, captain.
Help, my arm is bleeding.
Holy cow... Leslie!
Look how much it's bleeding.
Look at it.
Everybody look over here.
- I need everyone's full attention...
- There's a lot of blood.
It is so...
- It's ketchup.
- Is it?
It's ketchup.
Do you know them?
What do you mean,
that Fairway Frank is not here?
Here's the thing, Evelyn.
We're not sure that the possum
we caught is, in fact, Fairway Frank.
Whoever it is, it's a possum.
And the sooner it's dead,
the sooner the mayor
can do what he wants with it.
Does he want to have sex
with a dead possum?
He's not a monster.
He wants
to stuff it and hang it above the urinal
in his office bathroom
so that little flecks of pee
can get on it forever.
You did a great job.
And the mayor knows
that you did a great job.
Now where is the possum?
I'm sorry but he's somewhere.
You'll never find it.
And he's gonna stay there
until the truth comes out.
And I will not reveal his location,
no matter how much you ask me.
I'm gonna stop talking now, I'm afraid
to say where it is. So please go.
Interesting.
They put down a raccoon
that bit a jogger in a park
in Staten Island.
And in Walnut Creek, California,
they put down a duck
that bit a kid.
But security footage later revealed
that it was actually a goose.
Great.
No, it's awful, Tom. How would you feel
if you killed an innocent duck
and let a vicious goose waddle free?
- Tom Haverford.
- Tom, it's April.
I'm at Ann's house
and the possum's loose.
I need your help.
It's chewing on everything!
- Don't tell Leslie!
- You got it.
Possum got loose at Ann's house.
My God.
April, it's Leslie Knope
from the Parks department!
Stop ringing the doorbell.
It's making him mad!
My God, how did this happen?
I let it out of its cage
because it needed water
and I thought it would drink out
of the toilet, but it ran off
and I couldn't get it back in.
He did that too.
Then I opened all the doors,
I thought it would go outside,
but it won't leave the house.
It must love tacky pictures of flowers.
I'm gonna fix this.
Let me just think for a second.
- What?
- Where is it? I can't see it!
Where did it go?
Here's what we do.
We just go outside.
Let's go outside...
Get in here!
- I haven't even started yet.
- I know.
You could use some help.
Those city planning guys
can be real pains in the ass.
I just want you to know
that I still don't think city codes...
Ron, shut up, would you please?
I'm taking a half day off
to come and help you out
because you're my friend.
So just...
shut up.
I'm bringing my workshop up
to the Swanson code.
And if the Swanson code
happens to overlap
with the city government code...
Shut up!
I know there's a door there,
but I kind of feel like
it's gonna chew through the door
and jump on my face and bite me.
- What if it's in here?
- What if it laid eggs in the bed?
There are no eggs.
We should have killed it,
it's so huge.
I'm gonna call Andy.
He tackled it once before.
He can do it again.
No, please don't, okay?
He's gonna be pissed at me.
I already ruined his big day,
it's my fault that it's in Ann's house,
who he's still in love with.
I just...
I don't...
want him to be mad at me, okay?
He'll forgive you.
You think?
We don't call Andy.
We can just call animal control.
Anytime you want to talk
about boys...
My God, stop.
So you were mad at me yesterday,
and I don't know why.
So I made a list of everything I did
and I'll try not to do
any of them again.
Also,
I got you this coffee.
And then there's this.
Fourth paragraph down.
"But Dwyer had some help
catching the possum.
"I couldn't do it
without an early morning caffeine boost
"from the amazing April Ludgate.
"She gave me the liquid courage
to wrestle that beast to the ground."
I have to say I'm very disappointed.
You didn't have to say that.
You'd have just thought it.
What'd you do with the possum?
I'm proud to say
that it's somewhere
the mayor can never pee on it.
It's okay.
I mean, look,
when I retire,
and I'm attending some gala
honoring the first three female
presidents in history,
myself, and two other women
I've inspired,
I wanna be looking back
at my distinguished legacy,
and not thinking that I owe my career
to some possum.
And I wanna be wearing a huge,
beautiful blue hat.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
It made me feel so happy that I knew
you were here, taking care of my house.
Cool.
Did the neighbors
give you any problems?
- Anything in...
- Possum. There was a possum.
We captured a possum,
we brought it here,
- it might have laid eggs in your bed.
- What?
It went into your laundry, your kitchen,
and it touched all your bras.
And I'm so sorry, it's our fault,
we captured it, it got out, ran around
and it was a possum.
Run, April!
Sorry, Ann! I love you!
- I'm gonna go.
- I think that would be best.