- I was here first. Get lost.
- We were here first.
But we're scheduled for this time.
This is no way for adults
to act in front of children.
You're not only coaches,
you're role models.
I would hardly call
what he does coaching.
Excellent role modeling.
The girls' team does not have a field
assigned to them for practice,
but the boys' team does.
Not on my watch.
Every child has the right to play,
no matter how boring the sport.
Could you just share the field
with the girls today, please?
I'm the girls' coach.
She's the boys' coach.
- Sorry.
- That's sexist.
- No, it's not.
- Yeah, it kind of is.
Why don't the boys
take the field today
and then I will make sure
that the girls
get a place to practice
by the end of the week?
And that, little lady,
- is a Leslie Knope promise.
- I'm a boy.
Good, 'cause I was talking to you.
You're a girl, right?
She.
- Feygnasse Team -
La Fabrique ::.
Episode 217
Woman of the year
mpm
lestat78
Mail's here.
You got soup all over our mail.
You jerk.
My God. It's an envelope
from the I.O.W. awards office.
Nobody freak out.
Do you know what this means?
I am Pawnee's woman of the year.
The I.O.W.
is the Indiana Organization of Women.
I have been a dues-paying member
since I was nine.
And every year,
they choose one woman to win
the Dorothy Everton Smythe
female empowerment award.
Winning is every girl's dream.
But it's my destiny.
And my dream.
Can you read it, please?
Where my ladies at?
Here we go.
The I.O.W. is proud to announce
this year's Dorothy Everton Smythe
female empowerment award winner:
Ronald Swanson.
- Pretty funny.
- It says Ronald Swanson.
What?
No, it doesn't.
I... That... No.
They only honor women,
and Ron's the opposite of a woman.
What's going on?
You're Pawnee's woman of the year,
it looks like.
Well, it's about time.
They've obviously made a mistake.
Bully for me.
Congratulations, Ron.
- It's very exciting.
- It's awesome.
Awards are stupid.
Which is why I fully intend
to decline this nonsense
and recommend it go to Leslie.
Because she works really hard
and I don't.
However,
she cares way too much
about crap like this,
which is why I can't pass up
this opportunity to tease her about it.
We can't stand around all day
congratulating me
on receiving an award
from some lousy
women's organization.
Back to work, everyone.
Hey, Freddy.
Good news.
Your liquor license renewal got go.
What do you mean by that?
I got you temporary approval
from the liquor board
pending full-board authorization
and council review.
Got got.
Thank you so much.
No worries. You know the Snakehole's
my favorite Pawnee hot spot.
I wanna open up my own club one day.
Maybe call it like Club-a-dub-dub
or the Clubmarine,
sort of a submarine-themed club.
Or Tom's bistro.
The word bistro is classy as ***.
We are looking for
a few top quality guys like yourself
to become part owners.
With your political connections,
I think you'd make a great asset.
I agree. That's why I got
into public service, to help me.
All right.
$10,000 a share.
Need the money by Friday.
$10,000.
That's chump change.
I will see you Friday with...
- $10,000.
- All right, partner.
I just don't get why the I.O.W.
would give that award to Ron.
- That's a bummer.
- One, he's not a woman.
And two,
they mention the Camp Athena project
in that letter.
That's my project. I started that.
It was my brainchild.
Why would Ron
start a camp for troubled girls?
- He wouldn't.
- Exactly.
I deserve that award.
That award is mine, not his.
It's mine.
- You should do...
- I know, I started a list.
"Write an email to Barack Obama.
"Lock myself in my office
and scream until I lose my voice."
That's all I have.
I was gonna suggest,
you go and talk to him.
You're only gonna get more resentful
if you don't.
I have so much
I need to tell you right now.
Leslie would like to talk to you
for a moment, is that all right?
Good.
Jean-Ralphio.
Big T, what it do, nephew?
I have a hot investment opportunity
that you are gonna wanna jump all over.
Hit me with it.
- The Snakehole lounge...
- Heard of it.
- Is looking for investors.
- No way.
Yesterday I would have said no,
but thank God my grandfather died
so I am Fluh-ush with cah-ash
Awesome.
I have 4,000 bucks.
All I need you to do is kick in 6gs
and then you and I are part owners
of the hottest nightclub in Pawnee.
Also, sorry about your grandpa.
No worries, he was a dick.
Here's the thing.
I can kick in 5gs.
That should be enough, right?
No, it's not enough.
I just said I need 6gs.
- Your trust fund?
- My parents had it amended.
Nothing 'til I'm 50,
which is a waste, 'cause I'll be
a billionaire in Costa Rica by then,
eating dolphins and hanging out
with lady singers.
It's not a huge deal.
Sit tight.
- I'll take care of it.
- You wanna come home with me?
Don't you work at Lady Foot Locker?
Look, if you're not gonna pay rent,
at least clean up your dishes.
Is that all?
Also, the bag of smells was fun,
but it has to stop.
Come on. Now... No, we're finally
starting to get serious results.
Andy, dude, I love you.
But shape up or move out.
- What's going on?
- My guitarist is driving me crazy.
He's such a control freak.
That's not a working fireplace.
Stop writing phone messages
on the wall, Andy.
Dude, seriously, I love you, but stop
digging that weird hole in the backyard.
Is Mouse Rat gonna break up?
We're not Mouse Rat anymore.
We changed it to Tackleshaft.
- I should just get my own place.
- You should.
- I'll help you.
- You could help me?
Yeah, that'd be fun.
You're like an angel with no wings.
So like a person.
- What's in the envelope?
- Nothing.
- You wanted to see me?
- I think the Pawnee chapter of the IOW
has a made a little mistake.
Really?
You're saying a women's organization
made a mistake?
I was as surprised as you were.
But the fact is,
they only give that award to women.
Well, it definitely said
Ron Swanson in the letter.
Yeah, but it also mentioned
my camp project.
Ah, yes, camp Xena.
Athena. Camp athena.
- You don't even know the name.
- I almost got it. It was pretty close.
Look, Leslie.
Your job, which you're great at,
is making me look good.
Which you've clearly done well
because I'm getting an award.
Right?
Be proud of yourself.
I mean, you deserve an award.
Not this one, obviously.
This one belongs to me.
But some other one.
Some other lesser award.
And if the shoe were on the other foot
and you won,
I would have congratulated you.
Congratulations.
- What's that?
- You heard me.
You promised the girls a field
by the end of this week.
Well, it's a man's world,
winston, get used to it.
I'm a man.
You know who you should talk to?
Ron Swanson.
He's an award winning public servant.
He's the guy that's gonna help you out.
Go on in there.
'Scuse me.
Ron, someone's coming in.
Leslie said I should come over here.
If you don't get credit for your work,
why bother doing it?
Because I love it.
But I'm gonna make a point.
This VIP card gives you
exclusive access
to the investment opportunity
of a lifetime.
Where?
Multipurpose room F.
When?
3:00 p.m.
Dress code?
Black tie optional.
Just like life.
Hey, you want to see me?
Yes, yes, just hang on one second.
I'm doing my official portrait
for the I.U.D. awards dinner program.
I.O.W.
No, this portrait
is not official in any way.
I'm paying for it myself.
Did you need me?
Because some of us
actually do work around here.
Work that often goes unrewarded.
I need your opinion.
Which of these objects
most represents women for this portrait?
A pot?
Or this deputy director Barbie?
Isn't it adorable? She's got
a little briefcase, her cell phone...
I'm going to help my boss
win an award.
How's the scheduling conflict
with the soccer teams going?
- Take care of that, did you?
- Nope. Passed the buck to Donna.
That's not really the attitude
I expect from an award winner.
Everything I do is the attitude
of an award winner
because I've won an award.
So what kind of place
are you looking for?
I can afford, like,
300 bucks a month.
I've always wanted
a doorman named Ernie.
That would be awesome. Or Kipp.
I'm pretty flexible on that.
Here's a great one.
It's a Tudor mansion,
it's got seven rooms,
four bathrooms,
it's got a tennis court,
a pool, and a three-car garage.
What?
And it's only $20,000 a month.
And it's in Chicago.
That close.
It was almost perfect.
Actually, there are
a couple cool places in here.
- Let's go look at them.
- Now?
- Let's roll.
- Okay.
Thank you all so much
for joining me today.
I have two questions for you.
One: are you ready for the investment
opportunity of a lifetime?
Two: do any of you have pacemakers
or a history of epilepsy?
Yes, both.
- Anybody, no? Right.
- Both.
Ladies.
Jay-z. Rihanna.
Audrina Patridge.
Jon Gosselin. Lady Gaga.
Snooki.
Are these real people?
Cash Warren.
And Dennis Rodman.
These are few the celebrities
that wish they could invest
in Pawnee's hottest club.
But they can't!
And you can for the small price
of only $1,000.
The only question is,
who's gonna be my partner?
Mark, I'm talking to you.
Donna, I'm talking to you.
Jerry, I'm talking to you.
Mark, I'm talking to you.
26 certificates, plaques,
ribbons, trophies,
medals, and miscellany
certifying that I deserve recognition
for my achievements.
What do you have, Ron?
I have the Dorothy everytime
smurf girl trophy
for excellence in female stuff.
Dorothy Everton Smythe.
I swear to God...
Before you continue,
please read this.
Another organization giving you credit
for something you didn't do?
"I, Ron Swanson, recognize that...
"Leslie Knope should have received
the I.O.W. Award
"for all the hard work she has done,
especially for the camp Athena project.
"However, in my opinion,
"she is far too concerned
with institutional gratification."
No, I'm not.
"So I'm gonna let her dangle
"in order to show her
that awards are bull..."
Come on, Leslie,
you know I'm not sexist.
I love powerful women.
Well, you do attend
a shocking number of WNBA games.
I'm just saying
that awards are political.
And everybody has an agenda.
If you spend your life chasing them,
you'll drive yourself nuts.
Yeah, all right.
But Dorothy Everton Smythe
was a trailblazing feminist.
She was the first woman in Pawnee
to wear pants on a Sunday.
She spent 4 years in jail for that.
I know I'm not supposed to care
about these things,
but this one means a lot.
I know you've been changing
The acoustics in the bathroom
are insane.
So, how much is this one again?
This one is $425 a month
plus utilities.
I like it.
It seems to have...
a lot of potential and...
a lot of advantages, per se.
Could definitely picture myself
doing something over there.
You hear that?
What is that?
- It's still on.
- Light a match to get rid of the smell.
I feel really good about this.
- Really?
- It screams Andy Dwyer.
And I live nearby, so we could, like,
carpool to work or something.
Are you serious?
The scream just got louder.
- So what do you think?
- I don't know, make me an offer.
Okay.
First come, first served.
Who's in? Jerry.
Geez, Tom.
If I spend any more than 25 bucks,
I gotta ask my wife.
Jerry, get out.
Mark, what are we doing tonight?
I don't know, Ann.
We could do the usual boring stuff
like eat some chicken salad
with some crackers
or watch the pay-per-view.
Or...
We could go to my nightclub
and do some dancin'.
I don't think so, man.
You'd never have to beg
for sex again.
I don't wanna get into this, really,
but I don't beg for sex now.
Forget about that.
Are you in or out?
Just not really my thing.
Bye, Mark.
Cindy.
Maybe. I like the Snakehole.
Plus, I would look good pulling into
my owner's parking space in my Mercedes.
To be clear,
you wouldn't be an owner per se.
You, me, and my boy Jean-Ralphio
would each own part of a share.
- Will that be cash or check?
- Not so fast.
I need to know who I'm in business with.
I wanna meet your boy.
Come here.
This lady's here.
Hi. I'm Elise Yarktin.
I'm with the I.O.W.
I'm... woman of the year,
Ron Swanson.
Yes, I know.
We are very excited to be presenting you
with the Smythe award.
That's what I want to talk about.
I don't know if I can take
all the excitement.
So I think the award
should go to Miss Knope here.
She's the one
who really deserves it.
Camp Athena was her idea,
she did all the work.
You made a mistake.
We didn't make a mistake.
We made a very conscious
decision this year to choose a man.
Why?
Every year we give it to a woman,
and frankly nobody cares.
The media has all but written us off
as a niche interest group.
But if you give a woman's award
to a mustachioed,
masculine man such as yourself,
well, then,
eventually people take notice.
- I don't want the damn thing.
- Well, we're giving it to you.
So you're gonna take it.
Like a man.
So congratulations.
The I.O.W. is
a bunch of sexist jerks
who need to get back
in the kitchen where they belong
and leave the real feminist
work to actual feminists
like Ron Swanson!
Oh, my God, what is happening?
Now do you see
how silly these things are?
- Unbelievable.
- Obviously, I'm just gonna decline it.
No, accept it.
I want you to go to the podium
and talk about how stupid awards are.
And how they're superficial
and meaningless.
I want you to rip awards
a new a-hole.
Now we're talking.
I'll tell you what.
You write the speech,
don't pull your punches.
I won't. I'm gonna push my punches.
As far as my fist can extend.
Atta girl.
Kind of.
What up, big T?
Stop.
This must be the lovely Donna.
Enchanté.
Listen, beautiful,
let's cut the bull. Right?
Right? You want this.
I definitely want this.
T.H. wants this.
Let's seal this devil's threeway
right here, right now.
Step one: we buy into this club.
Step 2: we roll over to the club,
either in your Mercedes-Benz
or my pre-owned Acura legend.
Step 3: I dagger you
on the dance floor,
just bounce, bounce, bounce.
And now all the ladies say
Bounce, bounce, bounce, bounce
- What do you say, sexy?
- I'm out.
- Why?
- I hate that guy.
Hi, welcome to the I.O.W. Awards,
and congratulations on winning.
Well, here is your awards packet,
and if you will just follow me,
we're gonna have
a little meet and greet.
No, I'm sorry,
this area is for award winners only.
Get over yourself, Elise.
Work on the speech.
Let's nail these women.
You know what I mean.
I don't know. What's it all about?
What's the secret?
Why is it so hard to become a mogul?
All I want in life is to own a nightclub
on every continent.
Have my own line of upscale sweat suits
and a cologne called Tommy fresh.
And I fell $1,000 short.
Seriously?
That's all you needed?
I have $1,000. You can have it.
- Thanks, but I can't take your money.
- I'm a singer-songwriter.
The two lines I put
into every song I've ever sang,
"Spread your wings and fly"
and "You deserve to be a champion".
You're telling me that all you need
is $1,000 to do your dreams?
Then I want you to have it.
Are you sure about this?
- Maybe.
- You know how happy you just made me?
He's the director of the Pawnee
Parks and Recreation department.
He is also the recipient
of this year's Dorothy Everton Smythe
female empowerment award.
Please put your hands together
for Mr. Ron Swanson.
Every award from the smallest trophy
to the Nobel prize
is nothing more than...
Is nothing more than a great way
to honor someone.
So I would like to present
this year's
Dottie English whatever award
to the person
who actually deserves it.
Leslie Knope.
Come on up here, Leslie.
I don't know what to say.
Honestly, I'm just very honored
to work for someone
as insightful and kind as my boss.
So I would like to present
this year's
Dorothy Everton Smythe award
to Ron Swanson.
I don't want it.
Just take the damn thing.
- You deserve it.
- No.
- Really, but I don't want it.
- But you won it, and you should win it.
- After that whole conversation...
- Could someone please just take it?
- Okay, I'll take it.
Who do I speak to
about getting this changed?
Get off the stage.
I still think awards are stupid.
But they'd be less stupid
if they went to the right people.
- You gave Tom all your money?
- Yeah. Well, I'm investing.
I'm like Warren "Buffay".
I feel like it would have been
good for you to have your own place.
Yeah, I know.
But I feel like Tom
really needed the money.
And small sacrifice to see one
of your best friend's dreams come true.
- They cropped you out.
- Figures.
So where are you gonna put it?
I have an idea.
What's up?
Hey, guys.
How long did you wait in line?
I didn't wait. I'm a part owner.
Freddy. I'm back.
Tom Haverford, part owner.
Let me know if you need anything.
Keep this booth warm for me
every night.
I'm gonna live in this booth.
Yes, sir.
- What are you doing here?
- I bought three shares.
Thanks for the tip.
www.sous-titres.eu