♪ Men...
I'm gonna hate this movie.
How can you be so sure?
It's got subtitles.
The only good subtitles
are for Nazis,
Colombian drug lords,
and space aliens.
Oh, and Kung Fu.
Excuse me, but NPR called
Hiroshima la Poubelle
an "enchanting journey
of self-discovery."
Well, they're not
gonna call it
a "two-hour French snooze-fest
for pompous douche-buckets."
Hey, you agreed that
if I paid for the tickets,
we could see what
I want to see.
That's because I
didn't actually think
you could scrape
together 18 bucks
without stopping
at a blood bank.
Well, it is
a small price to pay
to finally get you
out of the house.
It's been three weeks since
you and Chelsea broke up,
and you need to move on.
Says the guy who still
carries around
a naked picture
of his ex-wife.
Hey, I bought those boobs.
I have a right to look
at them once in a while.
Damn. I don't
believe it.
What?
She's here.
My ex-wife?
No! It's Chelsea.
She's with that Brad guy.
So wh-what do we do?
Do we say hello?
No. We get the hell
out of here.
CHELSEA:
Charlie?
Hey.
Look who's here.
Alan, Chelsea's here.
Oh, hey, Chelsea.
Hi, Alan.
You guys
remember Brad.
How's it going?
Good. Great.
Looking forward
to the movie.
I'm surprised
to see you here.
This doesn't strike me
as your cup of tea.
Are you kidding?
NPR called it
an "enchanting journey
of self-discovery."
You know I live
for that crap.
Right.
Okay, well, it was
good seeing you.
You, too.
Wow.
That was awkward.
Tell me about it.
Had to be tough for you.
Your ex-fianceé
out with another guy?
Uh-huh.
Good-looking guy.
Yeah.
You're here
with your brother.
I know.
That'll tighten
the old sphincter.
Oh, God.
You still want to go?
No. No, I'm not gonna give
her the satisfaction.
I can suck it up
for two hours.
Three hours
and 20 minutes.
What?
It covers four generations
of transsexual Kabuki dancers.
Let's go.
All right, but I think
you should pay me back
for the tickets.
Well, not now.
When it's convenient.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Men...
I can't believe
she's already dating.
You're kidding, right?
The day after she moved out,
you ran off to Vegas
and married a stripper.
People grieve in
different ways, Alan.
Mm.
Besides, the stripper
was already married,
so no harm, no foul.
(sighs)
Everybody's got
somebody but me.
Hello? I'm not
with anyone, either.
Hello? You're a big loser
that says "Hello?"
I wonder if she's
slept with him yet.
Oh, don't go there, Charlie.
Don't punish yourself.
Well, if she hasn't already,
I'll bet you she does tonight.
Okay, punish yourself.
I mean, what kind of man's
gonna sit through
a three-hour gay French
flick unless he figures
he's got a good shot at
getting laid afterwards?
You didn't even give
that movie a chance.
I'll bet you right now he's
driving her back to his place.
They're talking
about the movie.
He'll make up some crap
about how it made him cry.
Then he'll ask her in
for a cup of coffee,
which he'll turn
into a glass of wine.
One thing leads to another,
and before you know it,
he's got her in the bathtub
running like a jet ski.
At least that's
how I'd play it.
Come on.
Where we going?
Chelsea's. I got to see
if she comes home tonight.
Okay. Why am I going?
Hello? I'm hammered.
How's it gonna look
if I get a DUI
on the way to spy
on my ex-girlfriend?
He's very responsible
about drinking and stalking.
♪ Men...
(sighs):
How long are we
gonna sit here?
Till she comes home.
What if she spends
all night with Brad?
Well, then we'll be here
all night.
(groaning sigh)
No, no. No, don't...
Hey, I can (groaning sigh)
if I want to.
I'm tired.
Then go to sleep.
Without my melatonin
and mouth guard?
I don't think so.
Car, car, car.
Oh, it's them.
It's them.
Get down. Get down.
Okay.
Quick, put this on.
What the hell is it?
Mustache.
What are you doing
with a mustache
in your glove compartment?
Don't worry. It's fake.
That doesn't answer my question.
You think you're the first guy
who's ever checked up
on a woman who's dumped you?
Put it on!
(sighs)
There is a whole side to you
I don't want to know
anything about.
Hey, that's a good
look for you.
It's kind of '70s porn star.
I'm guessing.
Look at that thing
he's driving.
What? It's a Prius.
Of course
it's a Prius.
(mocking):
I'm saving the planet.
Could I play with your boobies?
Hey, do not put down
the green lifestyle.
I have worked
very hard
to reduce the size of
my carbon footprint.
You're a mooch and a miser.
Don't try to make it sound hip.
All right, they're
getting out of the car.
Oh, don't you just
love how he dresses?
I mean, youthful, but
not trying too hard.
Unlike some people.
Oh, great.
They're kissing.
Good thing he doesn't know
where her mouth has been.
Wait a minute.
He's getting
back in his car.
And there he goes.
Well, denied,
Mr. Greenpeace Sissy Pants!
There. You feel better?
Can we please
go home now?
Wait, just a minute.
I want to make sure
she gets inside okay.
You know, there's a soft side
to you that I just applaud.
You don't let it
out very often,
but when you do, it just
lights up the world.
Wait a minute.
Why is she getting in her car?
Where is she going
at this hour?
Maybe there's a third guy,
and she's cheating on Brad.
What?
Isn't that how
you'd play it?
Follow her.
♪ Men...
CHARLIE:
Catch up.
Catch up. You're
gonna lose her.
Relax.
This is not the first woman
I've surreptitiously followed
while honoring the letter
of a restraining order.
Oh. Looks like she's
heading for Malibu.
Who does she know
in Malibu?
No idea.
(engine sputtering)
What the hell is that?
Oh, damn.
I'm out of gas.
How could you be
out of gas?
I don't know.
I just put three dollars
in the other day.
Three dollars?
Actually $2.50.
I bought a Milky Way.
Oh, crap!
All right, we'll just
have to call Triple-A.
Um...
You don't have Triple-A?
It costs, like, $49 a year.
Charlie, I gas up
three dollars at a time!
Great! Just great!
Do you have Triple-A?
I have Mercedes
Gold Platinum Valet
something or other.
So? Won't they come
and help us?
Let's see.
Will Mercedes come out
to put gas in an '89 Volvo?
I'll call them to ask.
You're actually waiting
for me to call, aren't you?
No.
(sighs) Come on.
We'll just have
to hoof it.
What, I'm supposed to
leave my car abandoned
on the side of the road?
What if somebody
tries to steal it?
Good thinking.
Leave the keys, gas money,
and a thank-you note.
Spoken like
someone with insurance!
♪ Men...
(sighs)
(groans):
Oh...
My feet... are killing me.
Well, that's
what you get
for wearing those
expensive Italian loafers.
They're just not
made for walking.
You're right.
Hi, Charlie.
Chels?
Hey, Uncle Charlie,
you look like a '70s porn star.
I'm guessing.
♪ Men...
What are you doing here?
I needed to talk to you.
Okay. What's up?
Um...
Oh, uh, come on, Jake.
Let's give them some privacy.
Why? Do you think they're
gonna do it on the couch?
Okay, here it is.
Seeing you tonight
made me realize
how much I miss you.
Really?
Do you miss me?
Oh, yeah, he's been crying
like a little girl.
Will you go away!
What? I'm on your side.
Well, I can see nothing's
changed around here.
Well, just that
you're gone.
And-and yes,
I do miss you,
and I have been crying
like a little girl.
Good.
So, what have you been up to?
Not much. How do
you like living
with your dad
and his boyfriend?
It's a little weird.
I can imagine.
Two old Navy guys
shacking up.
The walls are pretty thin.
Every night I'm hearing:
(deep voice):
"Up periscope,
down periscope."
"Launch the torpedo."
Enough idle chitchat.
What's the deal
with you and Brad?
He's great, but...
it's just not the same.
Have you two, uh...?
No.
Oh.
(chuckles quietly)
Wipe that smile
off your face.
You wipe it off.
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
One question.
Yeah?
What was with the mustache?
When I'm out with Alan,
I don't like people
to recognize me.
Hey, they are doing it
on the couch.
♪ Men.
So what's the deal with
Uncle Charlie and Chelsea?
Are they back together,
or was that just
a booty call?
What do you know
about booty calls?
In theory, everything.
Aw, crap.
What?
Just a little disappointed.
I saw Chelsea's car outside.
I didn't see yours.
She spent the night,
but we don't know
if they're back together
or if they were just
scratching the old itch.
What do you know
about the old itch?
It's intercourse, Dad.
Why do we play these games?
Good morning, all.
Morning.
What?
Come on. Give.
There's nothing to give.
She came by, said she misses me,
spent the night.
Yay.
So is she
moving back in?
Is the wedding back on?
Or was it just making
the beast with two backs?
What is wrong with you?
I'm at an awkward age.
Morning, everyone.
Morning.
Hey, you want coffee?
Actually, I have to get home
and change for work.
Oh, okay.
Can we talk?
Sure.
Oh, that's never good.
How do you know?
That's what Mom
said to you.
So I'm thinking,
you grab some things
from your dad's for tonight,
and then we move all of your
stuff back this weekend.
Charlie, I'm not
coming back tonight.
Why not?
Last night was good, right?
It was great, but it
doesn't solve our problems.
Sure solved mine.
It's not that
I don't love you,
but I'm still not sure that
we have a future together.
Chelsea, you're really
freaking me out here.
I've got to go.
Come on. Wait.
Oh, I found your mustache.
Where was it?
Where do you think it was?
It was stuck to my ass.
♪ Men.
Hey.
Feel like talking?
No, I do not.
Understandable.
You got to admit you're
in a better place now
than you were
this time last night.
I mean, 24 hours ago,
the woman you love was
on a date with another man.
But presto-change-o,
she wound up
spending the night with you.
Of course, come the morning,
once again, she dropped you
like a lead turd.
Sorry.
You didn't
want to talk.
Me, I'm just the opposite.
When I get my heart broken,
I have to talk.
You cannot shut me up.
Yakkity-yak-yak-yak-yak.
Sorry.
I've tried to be
the strong, silent type,
but... it's just not
who I am.
I mean, not to mention
there's physical manifestations
to bottling up
your feelings.
I mean, constipation,
migraines.
Or it goes the other way:
gas, diarrhea.
You just cannot predict it.
It's kind of an
emotional crapshoot.
(snickers)
Crapshoot.
That just came to me,
right off the top of my head.
(snorting laugh)
Got it.
But you are lucky.
You've got your music
to express your feelings.
I mean, you could play
the blues, for instance.
(scatting blues riff)
♪ My baby done left me
♪ She ain't coming back
(scatting blues riff)
What's going on?
♪ I'm smothering your daddy.
(scatting blues riff)
♪ Men.
(elevator bell dings)
I'm just saying it
seems like every time
it's my turn to pick up
the crap, he's got the runs.
Well, stop feeding
him chili.
Oh, hey, Charlie.
Hey, Charlie.
Hey, Tom, Ed.
Are you looking
for Chelsea?
No, he came to see
two old queens
walking a dog.
Who are you calling
a queen, Elizabeth?
TOM:
She's not here, Charlie.
She went to dinner
with that Brad guy.
Oh.
You want to come in,
have a beer?
Nah, I don't want
to bother you guys.
Don't be silly.
Come on.
Okay, thanks.
You had to tell him
she's with Brad?
What, I'm
supposed to lie?
No, but you can dummy up.
I mean, look at
the poor bastard.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
"I wasn't thinking."
That should be
your middle name.
Don't be getting in my face
when I'm holding a bag of poop.
I'll grab some brews.
Chelsea told me
about last night.
I don't understand it, Tom.
I thought we were
back together.
Yeah, well, you can't
make sense out of a woman.
They're like beautiful puzzles
with missing pieces,
or a great book
with no ending,
or like my old man
used to say,
"They're all friggin' nuts."
I don't know what to do.
Should I leave her alone?
Should I pursue her?
If I might chime in.
I would say that
stopping by unannounced,
with some liquor store flowers,
sends up a rather
desperate flare.
I know, I know.
I just couldn't sit home
and do nothing.
I keep turning it over
in my mind.
What did I do wrong?
What could I have
done differently?
Man, how many times
did I ask myself that question
when I was married?
Me, too.
What have we got
between the two of us—
something like 80
years of marriage?
Let's see—
I was with Beth for 38,
and you were with Martha
for 40, 41...
I didn't need you to
actually do the math.
Don't bark at me.
I'll beat the snot out of you.
Bring it on, mister.
Maybe I should go.
No, no, no,
sit down.
Finish your beer.
We're just sparring.
I love this broken-down
son of a bitch.
Oh, for God's sake,
don't gay it up
in front of company.
Now you listen
to me, young man,
in the final analysis,
it doesn't matter what
you did or didn't do.
You want Chelsea back?
You've got to make her miss you
like you did last night.
And she's not going
to miss you
if you're squatting
in her living room
with those sad-ass petunias.
So, what, I'm supposed to just
go about my business
hoping that one day
she shows up
and says, "I'm back"?
Or you can do
like me and Ed did.
Change teams.
A lot easier living
with a man than a woman.
Tom and I watch
the same TV shows.
We like the same food.
You don't have to leave
the room to fart.
You don't have to, but it sure
would be a nice idea.
Okay, well, thanks, fellas.
This was real helpful.
We're always here
for you, Charlie.
Thank you.
And don't tell Chelsea
I stopped by.
I wouldn't dream of it.
And remember
what we told you:
lay low for a while.
Run silent, run deep.
There you go.
Well, what do you think?
Watch Sports Center
and then fool around a little?
You, uh, you need
to take a Viagra?
You're my Viagra, baby.
Ah, that's so sweet.
Just for that, you
can hold the remote.
♪ Men.
Hey.
Sorry. Didn't mean
to disturb you.
Just grabbing a water.
No, no, no, it's fine.
Come on. Join me.
Really?
Yeah, sit down.
Okay.
(sighs)
Listen, uh,
I want to apologize
for... you know...
Trying to kill me
with a pillow?
It was horseplay.
Don't make a big
thing about it.
What I'm saying is that I know
you were trying to cheer me up,
and I appreciate it.
Thank you.
I realize that I give you
a hard time about living here,
but frankly,
it's probably a
good thing to...
have you around.
Wow, Charlie.
That means so much
to hear you say that.
Well...
I do... I do love you, buddy.
(voice breaking):
And I love you, too.
I know, I know.
I don't want this moment
to ever end.
Okay.
I mean it.
I am not letting go.
Well, you're gonna have to,
'cause it's starting
to get a little weird.
We don't need women.
We've got each other.
All right, you brought
this on yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll wait for you
on the other side.