♪ Men.
Yes, Judith, I did deduct $30
from your child support
check this month.
Because I paid
for Jake's haircut.
Yes, it is usually nine dollars,
but he wanted to go someplace
without hobbyhorses.
I know he's never gonna win
any beauty contests,
but he is our son.
Look, I've got a patient.
I got to go.
Sorry you had to hear that.
That's, uh, that's my ex-wife.
Bee-yatch.
Hello, Mrs. Honeycutt.
I'm Dr. Harper.
Doctor.
Okay, so you are having
spasms in your lower back?
Yeah, it's awful.
Some days I can't
even get out of bed.
Oh, I know how that is.
You have back problems, too?
No.
Anyway, why don't
you lie face down,
and we'll see if we
can locate the problem.
I've tried everything.
Acupuncture,
yoga, shiatsu.
Nothing seems to work.
Not surprised.
Those Eastern practices
are mostly hooey.
Modern chiropractic,
on the other hand,
is built on over 50 years
of solid science.
Okay, let's take a look
at what we've got here.
Okay, now is this
too much pressure?
No.
Okay, how about this?
Okay, now is this
where the spasms occur?
A little lower.
Okay.
Here?
(moans) Lower.
(loud moan)
Am I hurting you?
No! God, no!
(erotic moaning)
Nobody's touched me like this
since my husband died.
Oh, um, I'm so sorry.
Um, how long has
it been since...?
(loud moan)
That long, huh?
(loud moaning)
Oh, my, it's, uh, pretty...
pretty sensitive here.
Harder!
Oh, okay, no problem. Um...
So, just out of curiosity,
how did you find me?
Uh, referral?
Uh, my Web site?
Or the fliers
on the counter
of the Mongolian barbecue
across the street?
Shut up and rub!
Uh, I'm not technically rubbing.
(loud moaning)
ALAN: Whoa!
Whoa, Nellie. Whoa!
MRS. HONEYCUTT:
Don't stop!
I'm not stopping.
Oh, spank me!
ALAN:
I'm-I'm sorry?
MRS. HONEYCUTT:
Spank my lonely ass!
ALAN:
What?
Do it, bitch!
(slap)
Yes, Doctor, harder!
(loud slap)
Yes!
(slapping continues)
Oh, God, yes!
(slapping stops)
Okay, let's take a look
at the schedule.
See what the, uh, rest of
the afternoon looks like.
Oh, that's not too bad.
So, how are you liking
your first day at work here?
(door opening)
Thank you, Dr. Harper.
Uh, you are most welcome.
A-And remember, alternating
an ice pack with a heating pad
is, uh, very helpful
for spasming.
I'd like to make
another appointment.
Oh, sure, sure. Uh...
What were you thinking?
Maybe next week, or...?
Tonight.
Uh, tonight?
Oh, oh, gloriosky.
Uh, uh... well, we, uh...
we close up at 5:00, so...
So I can expect you
at my place at 9:00.
Oh, gee. Uh, I-I don't
do house calls.
Per se.
See you at 9:00.
(door opens and closes)
Uh, some patients pay in cash.
Uh, uh, their insurance, uh,
won't cover chiropractic.
Uh, part of our ongoing
health care crisis.
Tragic, really.
Uh, by the way, you are doing
one heck of a job.
In fact, here's a little
something for you.
Just 'cause your smile
lights up the place.
You know what?
Let's sweeten the pot.
Um, can you give me ten back?
Not a problem.
Can't put a price on a smile.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
I like the new look.
Thanks.
It's fashion forward.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
It's what the guy
who cut my hair said.
He also said
it was "fun and fabulous."
Really?
Yeah, and he invited Dad
to a party.
I didn't go.
It's just nice to be asked.
So, why'd you decide to abandon
your classic cereal bowl coif?
What's a "coif"?
You can't glean it
from the context?
What's "glean"?
Why'd you change
your freakin' hair?
My new girlfriend
wanted me to.
If your new girlfriend
wanted you
to jump off a bridge,
would you do that?
If she put her tongue in my
mouth when she asked me, yeah.
Well, I can't blame you.
I once bought a woman a car
for the same reason.
She put her tongue
in your mouth?
Sure, let's say mouth.
Can we get
the check, please?
Hey, why don't you let
me get this one?
Really? You're not going
to go for the world record?
What are you talking about?
1,647 meals in a row
where you haven't taken out
your stupid Velcro wallet.
You were counting?
Am I close?
Nevertheless, I'm paying.
(sniffs)
You smell that, Jake?
The air coming out
of your father's wallet
has been in there since
before you were born.
Very funny.
Thank you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Nobody is going to believe this.
For God's sake.
Hey, isn't that
Chelsea's friend, Gail?
CHARLIE:
Oh, yeah.
I wonder if I should
say hello.
I wouldn't mind
saying hello.
Finish paying the
check, you weasel.
Hey, Dad, as long as you
got your wallet out,
I could use
some new sneaks.
Hmm. Oh...
Sure.
Are you dying?
Charlie.
Oh, hi, Gail.
Great to see you.
How've you been?
Pretty good. You?
Well, you know...
Yeah, I'm sorry to hear
about you and Chelsea.
The way it goes.
Win some, lose some.
Start having liquor delivered
straight to your house—
you don't have
to put on pants.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I know how you feel.
I'm still not over
my breakup.
But I'm not much
of a drinker, so...
Cheers.
Have you, uh...
have you seen Chelsea?
Yeah, actually I had
dinner with her, and...
We had dinner
just the other night.
Her and Brad?
Yeah, come to think
of it, he was there.
Looks like they're
an item now.
I guess.
You guess?
What do you want
from me, Charlie?
They're in Mexico
for the weekend.
Mexico. Nice.
I went there with
her once.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, it's fine.
We had a great time.
In fact, when we got
back, I bought her a car.
Yeah, she told me.
Ooh...
Listen, I got to go, but...
if you ever want to talk.
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
For the last time, I am not
dying and I'm not sick.
Everything's fine.
Okay, I got it.
But you can understand
my skepticism, right?
♪ Men.
I really don't see why
I shouldn't ask her out.
Seriously? The woman is
Chelsea's best friend.
So?
She's single, I'm single.
She's lonely, I'm lonely.
She's gorgeous,
I'm well above average.
I'm just saying it's a bad idea.
I never said
it wasn't a bad idea.
I said I don't know why
I shouldn't do it.
What's that?
That's a portable massage table.
So, what, you're givin'
rub-and-tugs on the pier now?
No.
No, I am a licensed
professional,
and-and I will not stand here
and be accused
of unethical behavior.
I mean, just because you have
no moral compass
doesn't mean I don't.
And while, yes,
that's a triple negative,
it nevertheless defines me
as the man for whom
I am aiming to be!
What the hell
are you talking about?
I am just trying
to augment my income
by seeing clients
in their homes,
thus alleviating them of the
added stress of commuting,
not to mention speed bumps
and potholes, of which,
as you know,
can jostle the spine!
Wow, guy picks up one $30 check
and he has a brain aneurysm.
♪ Men.
(phone rings)
(TV broadcast stops)
Yeah?
Chelsea?
Hey! How are ya?
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa,
slow down, slow down.
Why are you crying?
Wait a minute.
You're in Mexico?
Why on Earth are you in Mexico?
Oh, sure, Brad.
Oh, sweetie, I'm sorry
it's not working out.
Well, I love you
and I miss you, too.
When are you gonna be back?
Okay, okay,
I'll-I'll see you tomorrow.
I... can't wait.
All right, bye-bye, sweetie.
(chuckles ruefully)
I hope that smile's
for me.
Uh, who else
would it be for?
♪ Men.
You ready for round two?
Well, um...
yes and no.
Something wrong?
Yeah.
While you were in
the bathroom,
uh, Chelsea called.
Really?
Apparently, things didn't
go well in Mexico,
and she's coming home.
Well, that's a shame.
Yeah.
Anyway, she wants
to see me.
Said she loves me
and misses me.
So, one call and you're just
gonna go running back?
Um, yeah.
Well... this is awkward.
Come on. You know how
I feel about her.
I do.
So, we should probably keep
what happened tonight
just between us, right?
Mum's the word?
Zip the lip?
Ixnay on the oggie day
aisle stay?
Of course.
You know,
we could just pretend
that you didn't get
the phone call
for, like, another hour.
We could, couldn't we?
But wouldn't that
be... wrong?
I won't tell
if you don't.
Uh, I'm sorry, Gail.
I can't, I can't
justify it to myself.
Okay.
Well, can I at least kiss
you good night?
Sure.
On the other hand,
there's no arguing
with a boner.
♪ Men.
Let's see.
When Gail came over,
it was 11:00 here
and midnight in Cabo.
When Chelsea called,
it was midnight here
and 1:00 in Cabo.
So when I did Gail at 12:10,
Chelsea technically
hadn't called yet.
Not my best work,
but I can live with it.
Hey.
Tough night, Bunky?
I'm a whore, Charlie.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Jake needed a haircut,
and you had no money.
What? No, no!
I took money
to give a woman pleasure.
Wait a minute.
You... gave a woman pleasure?
Oh, you have no idea what
powerful orgasms
these hands are capable
of delivering.
No, no, no.
I've always known that.
I just find it hard to believe
they could give them
to other people.
Yeah, well, maybe this'll
convince you.
A woman gave you this?
Uh-huh, right before she told me
she was done with me and I could
show myself out.
Sounds like a dream date to me.
So what's the problem?
How do I live with myself?
How did you live with yourself
before?
By thinking I was better
than you.
Now after all these years, I've
finally descended to your level.
Oh, no-no-no, no, no.
I may have done some
questionable things in my life,
but I have never taken money
for it.
That's not to say
it wasn't offered.
Deservedly so.
Fine, I'm worse than you.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, I am going
to take a shower
and try to wash
the cheapness off me.
Better take some steel wool
and a cheese grater.
Hey, Alan.
Oh, Gail...
Hi.
Don't judge me, Pretty Woman.
Charlie, I better
get going.
Right, right.
So, uh, you and I are okay?
Yeah. I'm just sorry
it has to end.
Yeah, me, too.
Chelsea's a lucky girl.
You think so?
You should tell her.
I mean, don't tell her.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, Charlie.
For what?
(door closes)
Proving once again that
I am better than you.
Hey, hey, I'm just a rascal!
You are a male prostitute!
That is a terribly hurtful thing
to say.
♪ Men.
So there we are in this
beautiful hotel room
overlooking the ocean,
and he's on the phone
with his mother trying
to help her download music
to her iPod.
You're kidding!
And I just sat there thinking,
"Charlie would never do this.
Charlie hates his mother
with a blind passion!"
Remember when you used to think
that was a bad thing?
And when Brad's not on the phone
with his mother,
he's telling me how much
I remind him of his mother.
I hope not while
you were in bed,
'cause that would reflect badly
on everybody.
You don't wanna know.
There's nothing to know.
You went to Mexico
with another man,
he talked about his mother
in bed,
and you didn't have sex
with him.
Charlie...
Nope! That's what happened.
End of story.
(laughs)
I should never have let you go.
Well, sometimes you can't
appreciate what you've got
until you go to Mexico and don't
have sex with a mama's boy.
I'm sorry about Brad.
I know that hurt you.
Ah, it's water under the bridge.
What you did, what I did,
doesn't matter.
What did you do?
Doesn't matter.
Charlie, no secrets.
Please, can't I just have one?
Whatever it is,
it doesn't matter.
We were separated.
All right, here goes.
I was having pizza with Alan
and Jake the other day.
By the way,
Jake got a new haircut.
It's just fabulous.
Okay, well, you'll never guess
who was there getting takeout.
Your old buddy Gail.
Oh, my God, you didn't.
I didn't say I did,
but good guess.
I don't believe you!
What? We were separated.
You were in Mexico
with another man.
But she's my best friend!
Yeah, well, I'd have to say
the jury's still out on that.
You are such a pig!
A-A-A pig who hates his mother.
Go to hell!
Oh, come on!
It was 1:00 in Cabo!
♪ Men.
Oh! Lower.
How about here?
(low, loud moaning)
Oh, yeah...
that's how
Mommy likes it.
Okay, you know what?
I'm sorry.
I-I can't do this.
What's wrong?
I am a professional.
I studied chiropractic
for three years
in Guadalajara.
And that was with almost no
Spanish language skills
and a family of parasites
living in my colon.
And I did not go through
all of that
to become some sort
of G-spot Johnny.
Is that what you think you are?
Well, you're giving me money,
and I'm giving you...
what I'm giving you.
It just, it makes me feel cheap.
So it's too much
like a business transaction.
Exactly.
Well, how about
we forget the money,
and I'll show you something
I learned in Guadalajara?
What?
ALAN:
♪ Ai, yi, yi, yi!
♪ Canta y no llores...
♪ Men.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, hey, hi.
I'm sorry.
I overreacted.
Yeah, you kinda did.
You're both single,
you're both adults,
and you and I were separated.
Plus you were honest with me, so
I'm willing to put it behind us.
Oh, thank you. Thank you!
I love you so much.
I love you, too.
Why don't I take you out
for a nice lunch
and we'll catch up?
You wanna go out?
I'm a little hungry.
Aren't you a little hungry?
Gail's upstairs, isn't she?
Once again, we were separated
and I was vulnerable!
Just so we're on the same page,
are we still together or am I
allowed to go back upstairs?
Oh, damn!
(sighs)
Oh, how much madder
could she get?
♪ Men.
with the back spasms.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll see you on Wednesday.
Looking forward to it.
Uh, and Mrs. Honeycutt?
Yes?
(lowers voice): Uh, if
it's okay with you,
I think I'd like to go back
to our original arrangement.
But you said
it made you feel cheap.
What can I say?
Turns out I am cheap.
Your call. Bye-bye.
Bye.
Have I told you lately that you
are doin' a great job?
(chuckling nervously)
'Cause you are doin'
a great job!
(chuckling nervously)
In fact, I am going to make you
employee of the month.
I want an adjustment.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Are-Are you having
back problems?
No, I want an adjustment
like you give her.
Oh, gee, I-I don't think
that would be appropriate.
All right, then I want a raise
and dental insurance.
Hop on the table.
♪ Men.