♪ Men.
CHELSEA:
First box goes in my car,
the other in the truck.
Guess that's it.
You got everything?
I think so.
I, uh, left the house keys
and the garage clicker
by the nightstand.
Thanks.
So you still planning
to move in with your dad?
Just for a while.
You gonna be okay?
Me? Oh, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I am gonna
miss the cat.
You hate Sir Lancelot.
I did at first, but over
time I came to find...
Yeah, you're right.
I hate that thing.
I put in a change of address
at the post office,
but here's my dad's address
just in case.
I might be open
to a trade.
I'll keep the cat,
you take Alan.
Still got his carrier.
Take care of yourself, Charlie.
You do the same.
I'm sorry it didn't work out.
Me, too.
(door closes)
Well, she's gone.
You handled that very maturely.
What are you
gonna do?
We tried.
Didn't work.
Life goes on.
Mmm.
You want a drink?
Nah. Drinking isn't
gonna solve anything.
What-what are you doing?
Nothing.
Really?
Doesn't look like nothing.
Where you going?
Out for a swim.
You never go in the water.
That's 'cause
I'm not a good swimmer.
You don't think he's gonna...
I don't know.
Charlie? Charlie,
stop this!
Charlie, come back!
It's not that bad!
Come on, Charlie, you
still got your family!
Very smart;
now he's sprinting.
Damn it, Charlie,
get out of that water!
We need to go
after him.
Well, don't look at me.
I just ate; I got to wait
a half an hour.
Well, I just took a shower
and washed my hair.
And this is leave-in
conditioner.
Well, what about Jake?
Jake's at
his mother's.
Maybe we should
give him a call.
There's no time!
Water's really cold.
Just so you know,
we were about
to come get you!
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men... ♪
♪ Men.
(knocking)
ALAN:
Charlie?
You awake?
Come on, man.
It's time to get up.
Charlie?
What?
(shrieks)
I-I didn't see you there.
She was the best thing
that ever happened to me, Alan.
I understand.
But you've been up here
for two days.
It's time to move
on with your life.
There's no life to move on with.
Oh, sure there is.
You've got money, a beautiful
home, good looks, all your hair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have all the things you don't.
That wasn't really the point
I was trying to make, but, uh...
Come on.
Where are we going?
We are going to
get you cleaned up.
No.
No, I can't
go in there.
Reminds me too
much of Chelsea.
The bathroom?
That's where she used to brush
her hair and floss her teeth
and tinkle like
a princess.
Okay.
Well, where have you
been tinkling?
I may need
a new ficus.
♪ Men.
I'm glad you came with me.
You needed to get
out of the house.
No, what I need
is to be loved again.
Uh, well,
I think a good first step
is to stop urinating
in the potted plants.
Jake, your dad's here!
Charlie, I was so sorry
to hear about you and Chelsea.
Thank you.
I know that
breakups can be
very difficult.
Unless you're kicking out
your husband of 12 years.
That seemed remarkably easy.
It was.
You know the part
that I don't understand, Judith,
is how somebody can tell you
that they love you one day,
then turn around
and break your heart the next.
Well, relationships
are complicated.
People drift apart.
Nobody's to blame.
You blamed me.
It was your fault.
I tried to change,
tried to become the man
she wanted me to be,
but it wasn't enough.
Oh, I'm sure
there's a part of her
that still loves you very much.
Is there a part of you
that still loves me very much?
No.
What's wrong with him?
Your uncle's very upset
about his breakup.
Oh, yeah, that sucks.
Can I drive?
Sure.
Cool.
Let's go, crybaby.
♪ Men.
(Jake and girl talking quietly)
(chuckles)
Hey.
Yeah, hey, kind of busy here.
I can see that.
Hi, I'm Jake's Uncle Charlie.
Nicole.
So what's the deal, Nicole?
Are you tutoring
our little genius here?
No, we're dating.
Oh. Dating?
Uncle Charlie?
Hang on.
Listen, Nicole,
I love this kid,
and I don't want
to see him get hurt.
I'm not gonna
hurt him.
Oh, really? So you like him
just the way he is?
You don't want
to change him at all?
Uncle Charlie...
I got your back here, buddy.
'Cause let me
tell you something.
This here is a lump of clay.
And you know what it's gonna be
five, ten, 20 years from now?
A larger, more bitter
lump of clay.
Come on, let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm not done.
So if you're gonna
dump him, dump him now.
Don't wait till he
falls in love with you
and asks you to marry him
and have his children!
Okay, enjoy yourselves!
Are you out of your mind?
I mean well.
You think maybe it's time
to go back to your shrink?
Why? She's just another woman
that wants to change me.
Well, you have
to do something.
No, no.
If I can't have Chelsea,
I don't want to live.
W-Where you going?
Strip club.
Ah, yes.
Death by lap dance.
♪ Men.
Hey, Lord.
It's Charlie.
I know it seems like I only call
on you when my ass is on fire,
but, well, let's face it,
that's how you made me.
Anyway, I'm just hurting
real bad since Chelsea left,
and I was kind of hoping
that maybe you could
take away some of that pain.
Even with the help
of your blessed wine,
I can't get through the day.
Even your blessed vodka's
stopped working.
So, anything you can do
would be much appreciated.
WOMAN:
Hey.
You got a light?
I like a little
buzz before I pray.
Gets me closer to God.
(whispers):
Thanks.
♪ Men.
Come on, Charlie,
answer the phone.
Ugh, damn it.
Voice mail.
Uh, Charlie, it's me again.
It has been three days.
Please call
and let us know you're okay.
I think we should
call the police.
Nah, he'll turn up.
May be broke
and riddled with gonorrhea,
but he'll find
his way home.
No, I-I don't think
this is a typical bender.
He really cared for Chelsea.
You know, he put
her in his will.
Anything happens to him,
she gets everything.
Really?
So, like if he swam out in the
ocean and drowned, for instance,
she gets the house?
The house, the Mercedes,
the bank accounts,
music royalties.
Man, I just can't catch a break.
Hey, look what
someone threw away.
Uh, put that back outside.
And wash your hands.
Welcome to your
new home, baby.
Hey, everybody.
I want you to meet
the love of my life,
Mrs. Charlie Harper.
Better put me down.
I'm not wearing panties.
I told you he'd come home
with gonorrhea.
All right, who's who?
Well, this is my brother Alan.
Alan, Betsy.
Hello, brother.
C-Call me Alan.
Okay.
He doesn't look like
such a mooch.
Okay, well,
this is my mom Evelyn,
and she doesn't
look like such an Antichrist.
Hi, Mom.
(both chuckle)
Call me Mrs. Harper.
This is my housekeeper Berta.
Don't call me at all.
And lastly, this is Jake.
(gasps)
Oh, are you my son?
I'll be whatever
you want me to be.
Um, actually,
he's my son.
Butt out, Dad.
Well, you've met
everybody.
Why don't we go upstairs
and continue the honeymoon.
(gasps)
We have an upstairs?
CHARLIE:
Yep.
Are there people
up here, too?
I like her.
♪ Men.
Hey, Dad.
Mm-hmm?
Do I call Uncle Charlie's
new wife Betsy or Aunt Betsy?
I guess either one's okay.
I'm gonna go
with Aunt Betsy.
Fine.
Aunt Betsy made a lot of noise
last night.
Uh, yeah, yeah, she did.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm not complaining.
Good morning, family.
Morning.
How we doing today?
Good.
Will Aunt Betsy be joining us
or is she taking
a hot, soapy shower?
She'll be right down.
So, based on this
latest turn of events,
would it be fair to say
you're over Chelsea?
Oh, absolutely.
Betsy and I are soul mates.
Soul mates. Uh-huh.
So, where'd you meet
your soul mate?
Guess.
Strip club?
Wrong.
Massage parlor?
Okay, I give up.
Betsy and I met in church.
So what, she's a nun?
No, she's a stripper
and part-time masseuse.
See, I drove to the strip club,
but the parking lot was full
so I circled the block
looking for a spot
and found one right in front
of this little church.
And for some reason—
I don't know why—
I got out of my car,
walked into the church
and started praying.
Are you saying
God sent you Betsy?
I think he did.
Oh, Dad,
we gotta get our asses
to church.
Then when I'm done,
I get up to leave
and she appears in front of me
like some kind of
vanilla-scented angel.
Mmm, vanilla.
So, we got to talking.
Turns out she's going through
a difficult time as well.
Next thing I know,
we're cleaning out
her locker at the strip club
and driving to Vegas.
Where you got married.
I understand your skepticism,
but I'm telling you
this girl is special.
She's really sweet
and spiritual.
BETSY:
Charlie?
In here, baby.
Good news, bad news.
I got my period.
Oh, that's okay.
We can take a break.
We don't have to.
There's more than one way
to skin a cat.
Oh, you are so wonderful.
What are the other ways?
Shh! Uh...
Charlie, uh, can I talk to
you in private for a minute?
Sure.
Bets, coffee's right there.
You just make yourself at home.
Okay.
Morning, son.
Morning, Mom.
So, I was gonna do a little
topless sunbathing later.
You're welcome to join me.
Okay, not to put too
fine a point on it,
but you're out of your mind.
You need to call a lawyer
and get this marriage annulled
immediately.
I knew you wouldn't understand.
Oh, I understand, I understand.
You're still reeling
from losing Chelsea
and you're trying
to fill the void
with a menstruating pole dancer.
Hey, hey, hey, that's
my wife you're talking about.
Oh, damn it, Charlie, you
don't know anything about her.
I know I love her and she
loves me for exactly who I am.
She doesn't want to change me.
Oh, stop it.
Okay, you get one of those.
Next time, that hand
comes back a bloody stump.
Charlie, please,
I'm begging you.
No, I'm doing the right thing.
You're lucky
you're not a girl.
Having a hoochie
is like owning a vintage car.
A lot of maintenance
and once a month
you gotta put down
an oil pan.
Okay, I may have
made a mistake.
♪ Men.
Chelsea?
Hey, Charlie.
What are you doing here?
I need to see
your daughter.
I'm sorry, she's not here.
Hi, Charlie,
what's going on?
Ed.
You know when
she'll be back?
I'm not sure.
She just took
Skipper for a walk.
You're welcome
to come in and wait.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to be polite.
Did you ever consider that maybe
she doesn't want to see him?
Watch your tone, mister.
Sit, please.
Sorry the place is a mess,
we're still decorating.
I'm decorating, he's critiquing.
What, I can have opinions.
He wants me to just shut up
and be pretty.
So, listen,
I'm sorry things didn't
pan out with you and Chels.
Me, too.
Relationships can be
a lot of work.
Even if you've known
someone for 40 years.
That's right.
People get set
in their pigheaded ways.
You want to get something
off your chest, hmm,
I'm right here.
You really want to open
this kettle of fish now?
Oh, yeah, let's open it up,
open it up.
Okay.
I'm just saying that two grown
men should be able to pick out
a club chair without it
turning into Iwo freakin' Jima!
Well, I'm not the one
that thinks that everything
he sits his ass on
has to be made out of leather.
Lucky for you!
CHELSEA:
Come on, Skipper.
Charlie?
I'm sorry to drop in like this.
I just really needed to see you.
Okay, what's going on?
Uh, well...
Uh, why don't we go
in the other room
and leave these
two alone?
Fine, fine.
There's no law that says we
can't order the area rug later
and get two club chairs.
You see, right there.
That's why I love you.
What are you doing here?
Okay, well,
I don't know
how to say this
except just to say it.
I still love you very much,
and I miss you like crazy.
I miss you too, Charlie.
Then what are we doing?
Taking some time to figure out
if we're meant to be together.
And how the hell
are we supposed to do that?
I don't know.
I guess we should start
dating other people.
What?
I'm not ready
to see other people.
I don't know that I am either,
but I think we have to try.
Chelsea, I can't even
think about dating right now.
Can I tell you something
I've learned about myself
since we split up?
Sure, but first, marry me.
No.
Okay, just checking.
Probably some legal
complications, anyway.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
Go ahead.
I've learned that
I shouldn't have
tried to change you.
What you need is someone
who loves you for you.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I need to be changed.
There's something
seriously wrong with me.
Please, Chelsea, take me back
and turn me into someone else.
That wasn't a very good
argument, was it?
Nope.
Well, that's the best I got.
Okay, I guess
I should get going.
I'm really sorry.
That's all right.
Say good-bye to your dad
and Ed for me.
I will.
They're a really cute couple.
I guess.
It's a little weird for me.
Well sure, you're probably
used to seeing your dad
with your mom and not
a big, handsome black guy.
He is handsome.
Hey, Chels...
I just want you to know
that if by chance you should
do something crazy and stupid
like running off
and marrying some stranger,
I would forgive you and
take you back with open arms.
Good to know.
Seriously, I wouldn't
hold it against you at all.
Thank you.
All right then.
Good-bye.
Bye.
TOM (giggling):
Stop it, Ed!
Your beard tickles!
Come on, Skipper,
time for another walk.
♪ Men.
Uh, Charlie,
we've got a little problem.
What's up?
This is Betsy's husband.
Hello.
Want to catch me up?
Really?
Calling him Betsy's husband
didn't do the trick?
I don't understand.
She never said anything
about being married.
She never does.
This has happened before?
Oh, yes.
Any time I find her wedding ring
inside her empty diaphragm case,
I know she's off
on one of her little adventures.
I don't believe this.
Why do you put up with it?
Hey, look at me.
I'd rather share
a girl like Betsy
than have an
exclusive relationship
with a box of old
porn magazines.
I hear you.
That would be sad.
BETSY:
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Charlie,
I'm really sorry.
I was less than honest with you.
Sure, let's call it
less than honest.
I did enjoy our honeymoon.
Me, too.
We stayed at Bellagio.
Nice!
We should go.
Bye.
I'll make it up to you
in the car.
Oh, Betsy, I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
How about that.
I guess I'm not married.
I guess not.
You know what that means.
Going back to church?
That means I just got
three days of unbelievable sex
with no obligations
and no commitment.
Please don't make me
slap you again.
Nah, go ahead.
I think I got one more coming.
That's all right.
I'm happy that things
worked out for you.
Again.
Thanks.
Oh, hey, did I tell you
I won 18 grand in Vegas?
(loud smacking)
CHARLIE:
Ouch!
♪ Men.