So, do either of you guys
urinate with abnormal frequency?
No.
I mean,
you gotta define abnormal.
And keep in
mind the body
doesn't process
alcohol efficiently.
Which is why your
Uncle Charlie
is a perpetual
urine machine.
Also keep in mind
that your father
has the bladder control
of a frightened
nine-year-old girl.
Which is why he needs to wear
two pairs of undies
and a panty liner.
Only on long drives.
Oh, really?
How many times a night
do you get up to pee?
Just once.
I can hear
your toilet flush, Alan.
Okay, four times.
But at least
I get out of bed to pee.
Hey, hey.
That was an isolated incident.
I was dreaming my shoes
were on fire.
Does that answer your
question, buddy?
Yeah.
And remind me
to never ask another one.
Charlie?
Yeah?
Why aren't you ready?
Ready for...?
You've got to be kidding me.
I've told you
at least three times
we're having dinner with
my girlfriend Gail tonight.
Excuse me, gotta pee.
I swear to God,
you never listen
when I'm talking
to you.
It's like you just tune me out.
You look like
you're paying attention,
but your mind
is a million miles away.
CHARLIE:
Do I need to pee?
Nah.
I mean, I could.
Might be traffic.
Probably should pee.
Yeah, better pee.
Now we're going to be late,
and I'm going
to be embarrassed
all because you don't listen.
Boy, she's got great boobies.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Men. ♪
So, Charlie, I've heard
so many nice things about you.
Really? From who?
Hello.
Oh, right.
Thanks.
I guess I only hear
the complaints.
You don't hear anything.
That's not true.
You're right. It's not.
He hears what
he wants to hear.
So I'm right.
Well, you still make
a great couple.
Thank you.
And I'm really looking forward
to your wedding.
(choking up): I'm sure it's
going to be beautiful.
(whispering):
What'd I do?
Nothing. I told you she's going
through a bad breakup.
When did you tell me that?
In the car,
on the way here.
God.
It's going to be okay.
I know. It's just hard.
I thought I knew him.
I thought we were going
to be together forever,
like you and Charlie.
(sobs)
CHARLIE:
Hard to believe somebody
got tired of doing her.
Ooh, French fries look good.
Why did I order
the baked potato?
Isn't that right,
Charlie?
Absolutely.
Now, is this the one
who's the old college roommate?
I should really listen more.
I mean, I knew he
was insensitive...
Boy, I bet,
if they were roommates,
they did some experimenting.
Why is it that girls
can experiment with other girls
and not be gay, but if a guy
so as much kisses another guy—
woop, bad memory.
Drink... drink, drink, drink.
So you're just all alone
in that big apartment?
He even took the dog.
Bastard.
What? It's my first drink.
Not you.
Brian took Rufus.
Oh.
Who's Rufus?
For that matter, who's Brian?
Life of Brian—
that was pretty funny.
Brian's Song, not so much.
James Caan
was great in it, though.
That's 'cause he's
a great actor.
The Godfather, Rollerball...
Yeah, I can so see these two
kissing in a dorm room.
That's really sweet,
but I couldn't impose.
We insist.
Right, Charlie?
Absolutely.
CHELSEA:
There.
You'll come stay with us
for a few days and heal.
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.
Um... yes.
Good.
After dinner, we can
go back to her apartment
so she can pack a bag.
Absolutely.
You'll love
Charlie's place.
It's right on the sand.
Very quiet, restful.
Dear Penthouse Forum...
I always thought your letters
were made up,
until my fiancée's
college roommate
came to stay with us
for a few days.
Right, Charlie?
Absolutely.
♪ Men. ♪
(electric razor buzzing)
Hey, Alan?
Alan?
(razor turns off)
ALAN:
Be right there.
What's up?
(clears throat)
What were you doing?
Um, shaving.
At night?
Well, not so much shaving
as... trimming.
So, uh, how was dinner?
Forget dinner.
Please tell me you
weren't using my razor.
Mine doesn't have
the floating heads.
I don't believe you.
I put that thing on my face.
I was going to clean it
before I gave it back.
I-I don't want it back!
Really?
Yeah. Yeah, it's yours.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
But this is just
a stocking stuffer, right?
I mean, you are going
to get me a real present, too.
A real present?
Well, you obviously didn't put
much thought into this one.
Good night, Alan.
Good night.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Pack up your stuff
and get out.
Okay, okay, the razor
can be my Christmas present.
No, no, no, Chelsea's girlfriend
is staying here for a few days,
so you're going to sleep
on the couch.
Why don't you put her
in Jake's room
and have Jake sleep
on the couch?
Fair question.
Why don't you trim
your ball hair
with a steak knife?
♪ Men. ♪
I feel bad kicking your brother
out of his room.
Well, that's only because
you don't know him.
A little chamomile tea,
help you sleep.
Chelsea, I can't
thank you enough.
Don't be silly.
I know what it feels like
to have my heart broken.
Me, too.
You know, theoretically.
Well, I'm grateful
to you both.
And we're grateful to you.
You know, theoretically.
Anyway, tomorrow,
you can sleep in,
take a nice, long walk
on the beach...
CHARLIE:
I've been a really good
boyfriend tonight.
Chelsea should do
something nice for me.
Like make out with Gail.
Okay, I put fresh sheets
on the bed.
Alan, this is my
friend Gail.
Gail, this is Alan.
I'm so sorry
to put you out like this,
(fading out):
but your brother said...
ALAN:
Gorp. Fnark. Schmegle.
Oh, God, I've been waiting
for you all my life.
(no audio)
Marry me. Have my children.
It's really very generous
of you.
Gorp.
Fnark.
Schmegle.
Come on,
I'll show you the room.
(humming "Here Comes the Bride"
in head)
(humming funky guitar line
Chelsea?
(woman crying)
(crying continues)
Chels, you in there?
CHELSEA:
It's okay, Charlie.
Come on in.
(crying)
Everything all right?
She's pretty upset.
I'm sorry I'm such
a basket case.
Oh, please.
We're here for you, baby.
Right, Charlie?
Absolutely.
I guess I'll... leave
you two alone.
You don't have to go.
I don't?
Not unless you want to.
CHARLIE:
Gorp.
Fnark. Schmegle.
Come on, Charlie.
We all know what
you really want to do.
We do?
We do.
Come here. Join us.
Uh, okay.
So... what now?
Do I really need
to tell you?
We'd probably be better off
if you did.
Okay.
I want you
to make Gail happy.
And you're on board?
It was my idea.
Don't worry— she and I
have done this before.
In college.
I knew it.
Okay, let's turn that frown
upside down.
That's a good boy.
Hey, Chels?
Yeah, babe?
This is a dream, right?
Of course it's a dream.
You think I'm really gonna let
you sleep with my best friend?
Well, in that case, hang on.
'Cause I'm gonna do some
real freaky stuff here.
♪ Men. ♪
Yowza.
Excuse me.
I brought you some
fresh towels, Gail.
Oh, aren't you sweet.
Sure, sweet.
Go smell his room.
Morning.
Good, you're up.
I made you some toast.
Here's your orange
juice.
Oh, thank you, honey.
I'll see you later.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, you're leaving?
I told you I have to go
in to work today.
But what about Gail?
She can take care of herself.
I think she's already
made a new friend.
Yeah, I saw.
You don't think he's got a shot,
do you?
Charlie, you're horrible.
I was joking.
So how long are you
going to be gone?
I'll be home for dinner—
I thought maybe
I'd pick up
some Chinese food,
and we could stay in
and...
Is she nuts?
I can't be trusted alone
with that chick.
Wait, maybe this is a test.
A trap.
The two of them are in cahoots
to find out
if I'll make a move.
Cahoots, that's a funny word.
Sounds like an owl sneezing.
Ca-ca-ca-cahoots!
So, I'll call you later.
Absolutely.
Morning, Alan.
Oh, uh, morning.
Thank you again for letting
Gail have your room.
Oh, don't be silly.
Happy to do it.
Uh, mi casa, her casa.
It's actually his casa,
but the dehumidifier and
the night-light belong to me.
Still very nice of you.
See ya later.
What you got going on today?
Going to play a little tennis
in 1958?
This old thing?
This is just my
knock-around clothes.
So, what's the story on Gail?
Bad breakup?
Something like that.
So, she's on the rebound.
Where you going with this, Alan?
Oh, nowhere,
I'm just curious about her.
And, you know,
when we met last night,
I-I sensed a little spark
between us.
If there was a spark,
it's only 'cause she was
warming up her Taser.
Ha-ha, very funny.
Alan, trust me, the only way
you're gonna
hook up with someone like Gail
is in your dreams.
Already did.
Really? Was Chelsea there?
No! Good Lord!
How creepy would that be?
Well, regardless,
forget about Gail.
Potato head out there has
a better shot than you do.
You know, I've got a nephew
about your age.
You should meet him.
He plays guitar, too.
Maybe you guys
could jam sometime.
Oh... boobies.
(no audio)
Hey, for your information,
there is a very good chance
that a woman like that
is tired of rich, handsome,
successful guys
who have their own homes
and recently built cars.
You really believe that?
I have to.
Woof!
Who's that?
Chelsea's friend.
She's going through
a bad breakup
so she's going to stay here
for a few days...
Hmph! Too bad
I prefer the fellas.
Then again, I can always
draw a moustache on her.
♪ Men. ♪
(crying)
Alan?
Jake?
Berta?
(crying continues)
Oh, boy.
Although, maybe this
is another dream.
(sniffling)
Gail, you okay?
(crying):
I'm fine.
Good. Good.
I'm going to run some errands.
Can I get you anything
while I'm out?
A reason to live.
All righty.
(crying continues)
Coming in.
Sorry.
I just got some bad news.
What happened?
My boyfriend...
Rufus?
That's my dog.
Oh, yeah.
He's okay, right?
He's fine.
I just found out Brian is
already seeing someone else.
No.
I mean, we just broke up
and he's already sleeping
with another woman?
The pig!
I thought we had something.
(sniffling)
He always said
I was his soul mate
and that he wanted
to spend the rest
of his life
with me...
This can't be a dream.
She's still got her clothes on.
And she's talking.
Why can't I find a
nice guy like you?
Absolutely.
Maybe Chelsea would
let me borrow you.
(wry chuckle)
Excuse me, gotta pee.
Oh, crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap, crap.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I don't know how much longer
I can hold out.
I hear you.
What?
Nothing.
I gotta get Gail out of here
before I do something
I'm going to regret.
You know, after
I thoroughly enjoy it.
Just tell her to leave.
I can't do that.
She's Chelsea's best friend.
They were college roommates.
Really?
You think they experimented?
Oh, yeah.
(both chuckle)
I gotta figure out a way to get
Gail to leave on her own.
You got the perfect tool
for the job.
What are you talking about?
The one tool that's guaranteed
to drive any woman
out of your house.
Hello.
Oh, look,
it's an Allen wrench.
What was that about?
Nothing. Nothing.
I was just telling Berta
that maybe I was wrong
about you not having
a shot with Gail.
Why?
Did she say something?
Did she ask about me?
How would you feel
about a double wedding?
I mean, as long
as you're paying for one.
Slow down, slow down.
Nobody said anything.
I just realized
I might've been jealous
'cause she's so beautiful
and if I can't have her,
I didn't want you
to have her either.
Yeah, I was thinking
it might be that.
Anyway, it's not fair for me
to stand in the way
of your happiness.
Really?
I always thought that was one
of your favorite things.
Do you want to pick nits
or do you want to go talk
to a beautiful woman
who's extremely vulnerable
and may very well be looking
for revenge sex?
I don't want revenge sex,
I want a loving relationship
that has depth and meaning
and that will withstand
the test of time.
Oh, that's good.
I'd lead with that.
You think?
Oh, yeah, go get her.
All right.
All right. Wish me luck.
You don't need luck.
You've got the exact skills
needed to get this job done.
Thanks, Charlie.
You're a good brother.
If he actually gets laid,
I'm going to hang myself.
(knocking on door)
Come in.
Hey, there.
Hi, Alan.
You, uh, up
for a little company?
I guess.
You know, it does
get easier.
The wound does heal.
I know. Thank you.
I mean, it may not
feel like it now,
but before too long, you'll
forget all about that fella
who hurt you, because another
fella will be in your heart.
A fella who'll
never hurt you.
Who'll never leave
your side.
A fella who wants
nothing more
than to love you...
GAIL:
Oh, dear God, no.
Thanks for
your hospitality, Charlie,
but I should get back home.
Anytime.
So where'd we leave it?
Uh, I'll call you,
you'll call me?
I'll call you.
So...
how'd it go?
You heard her.
She's gonna call me.
♪ Men. ♪
You knew very well that
Gail was going through
a difficult time.
So what do you do?
You try to take
advantage,
to-to exploit her
vulnerability...
What is it about an angry woman
that I find so hot?
(no audio)
Even when that fat cashier
at the supermarket
was yelling at me,
I got a little engorged.
(no audio)
Boy, if I could just find
somebody like Chelsea.
I mean, look at her go.
She's a real fireball.
Speaking of fireballs,
next time I manscape I should
probably skip the aftershave.