Previously on:
So, how's Charlie doing?
Oh, he's fine.
Uh, actually, he's engaged.
You told her I was engaged?
Why the hell would you do that?
Charlie, there's a woman
named Mia on the phone.
(toilet flushes)
I'll take it.
MIA:
Hi, Charlie.
Mia.
♪ Men.
So, how are you?
Great. How are you?
Fine, fine.
Still engaged.
Come, sit, join us.
Are you sure
I'm not interrupting?
No, no, of
course not.
Yeah, his fiancée just left.
Oh, I'm sorry I missed her.
Oh, I bet she's still out
in the parking lot.
I'll go get her.
So...
what's going on with you
these days? You still dancing?
Not so much.
I'm a little old for ballet now.
Oh, that can't be right.
You look great.
Young and vibrant and... taut.
You know who else
has a great body?
Charlie's fiancée.
In fact,
Charlie calls her boobalicious.
I'm really happy
you found somebody, Charlie.
Thank you. She's great.
Really, really great.
Boobalicious.
So if you're not dancing,
what are you up to?
Well, believe it or not,
I'm trying for a singing career.
No kidding. That's terrific.
You know
who's a wonderful singer?
Charlie's fiancée?
Uh, actually, I was gonna
say Ms. Celine Dion.
I have no idea
about Chelsea.
Although she does have
a set of lungs on her.
Right.
So listen, I'm putting together
a demo of some songs.
Any chance you could
help me with the arrangements,
maybe play piano?
Oh, wow.
That sounds like fun.
It's just, you know, kind of
awkward 'cause, you know...
He's getting married.
Maybe I can find you
somebody else.
That'd be terrific.
Let me give you my number.
Are you still at
696-336-725?
Yeah, I can't believe
you remember it.
Well, I have a little
memory trick.
If you change
the numbers to letters,
it spells out "oxofempal."
Oh, good trick.
I should get going.
Wonderful to see you again.
Same here.
You too, Alan.
Bye-bye.
Charlie?
Yeah?
I've missed you.
Oxofempal?
Hot, hot, hot! Ow!
You have to dial one first.
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
and VOLKSWAGEN.
It's what the people want.
♪ Men...
Hey, Berta, what do you
know about Percocet?
I know three of them
with a Mickey's big mouth
can make you run buck naked
through a Taco Bell.
Why do you ask?
Well, my mom says Grandma Lenore
can't hold the new baby
until she stops popping them.
That's probably a good idea.
You drop one kid, you gain
a reputation as a kid dropper.
So how do you like having
a new baby sister?
Well, she eats,
she sleeps, she poops.
So far I'm not impressed.
Give her a bad haircut
and she'd be you.
Excuse me, but I paid
nine bucks for this haircut.
Sorry.
Besides, the baby doesn't look
anything like me.
In fact, she doesn't look like
my mom or my stepdad either.
Who does she look like?
Kind of like
a girl version of my dad.
I thought your dad was the
girl version of your dad.
I'm telling you, Charlie,
it's a bad idea.
What's the big deal?
I'm just gonna
find her a piano player.
Oh, come on, I saw
the way you looked at her.
You say "piano player,"
but you mean organist.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
I'm engaged to Chelsea.
I'm living with Chelsea.
I'm in love with Chelsea.
What's Chelsea's phone number?
What?
What does it spell?
You know,
your little memory trick.
Oh, uh...
it's... jklpuzo.
Really?
Let's, uh, let's
test it out.
Uh, is that,
uh, 818-jklpuzo
or, uh, 310-jklpuzo?
All right, all right,
I-I made it up.
But I don't have to call
Chelsea; she lives here.
You don't have to
call Mia either.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what about
you and Melissa?
What does that have
to do with anything?
Nothing!
I'm changing the subject
to your peccadilloes.
You were banging Melissa
in the hospital storage closet
while your ex-wife was
giving birth to your daughter!
We don't know
she's my daughter.
Who's your
daughter?
You're my daughter,
I'm your daughter!
This whole court
is out of daughter!
Al Pacino?
Great movie.
Hoo-ah!
See that one?
That was close.
Good thing he's slow.
Yeah, well, Judith's mom
dropped him when he was a baby.
♪ Men.
(both panting)
Wow.
Yeah.
What brought that on?
You're the one who
started talking dirty.
All I said is,
"What'd you do today?"
There you go again,
you nasty girl.
Okay, seriously,
what did you do today?
Nothing.
Just a regular day.
Had coffee with you, hung
out with Alan a little bit,
then came home, had a drink,
took a nap,
next thing I know
you're walking in
the front door with
your whore talk.
All right, whatever.
Oh, yeah, there was
one other thing.
Really?
Yeah, I ran into an old buddy.
What's her name?
Her?
Why do you assume it's a her?
When you've seen
one of your old guy friends,
you don't try
to hump me into a coma.
Fair point.
It was Mia.
Mia, the old buddy
you almost married?
Yeah.
And?
And nothing.
Well, she did ask me if
I'd help her out with
this music thing she's doing.
But I said no.
How come?
I thought it'd be inappropriate.
Why? You still have
feelings for her?
(chuckles)
No, no, of course not.
Then why wouldn't
you help her out?
What?
I mean, if she's just a friend,
then why would it
be inappropriate?
Okay.
Uh, no reason.
So you're saying
I should help her out?
Unless you still have
feelings for her.
I guess I'll help her.
Good.
Or bad.
Probably bad.
I'm gonna go with bad.
♪ Men.
Hi, Charlie!
We were just having a little
moonlight skinny dip
in the ocean.
Good thinking.
Nothing more romantic
than seaweed
hanging from a cold,
shriveled penis.
There's no seaweed—
Oh, my...
Don't put it on the table!
Sorry.
Alan, what do you say
we take a hot shower
and un-shrink the
Snuffleupagus?
(chuckles)
He'll be fine.
It's Bert and Ernie
I'm worried about.
I think Bert has ascended
to my rib cage.
You go ahead.
I'll be right there.
Okey-doke.
Okay.
Hey, uh, can I
ask you something?
I am not gonna help you
find your missing testicle.
No, no, it's about Melissa.
What about her?
Well, now that we're
seeing each other again,
the fact that she still
lives with her mom
presents kind of a problem.
Why?
'Cause you tickled mom's Elmo?
It was just light necking.
I never touched her Elmo.
Anyway,
since you set the precedent
of having girlfriends
move in here,
uh, I was wondering
if maybe...
No.
Why not?
You let Chelsea move in.
It's my house.
You are a guest.
And by "guest," I mean leech I
tolerate until our mother dies
and she can't lay
a guilt trip on me
for kicking your
ass to the curb.
You're gonna kick me out
when Mom dies?
You're planning on being
here until Mom dies?
Okay, okay,
we're getting off subject.
What about Jake?
You let Jake move in.
You're not helping
your case here, Alan.
But I'm just saying...
I said no!
Hmm. Hey, Bert, welcome back.
♪ Men.
(playing "You'll Never Find")
♪ You'll never find ♪
♪ As long as
you live ♪
♪ Someone who
loves you ♪
♪ Tender like I do
♪ You'll never find ♪
♪ No matter where
you search ♪
(voice cracks):
♪ Someone who
cares about you ♪
♪ The way I do
♪ Whoa, I'm not bragging
on myself, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the one
who loves you ♪
(off-key):
♪ And there's
no one else ♪
♪ No... one else.
That's a pretty mouth, but
it ain't made for singing.
What's it made for?
Eating.
Oh.
I thought maybe
she meant oral sex.
(off-key):
♪ You're gonna
miss my lovin' ♪
♪ You're gonna miss,
miss, miss my love. ♪
(piano stops)
So?
Wow.
You want to run it again?
I don't.
I mean, there's a danger
of over-rehearsing it.
Yeah. Plus I kind of
nailed it, right?
I don't see it
getting any better.
That is so sweet, Charlie.
Thank you.
I don't know how
I'd do this without you.
Hey, I don't deserve
any credit.
God gave you
that voice.
I had nothing
to do with it.
Oh, hello.
Oh, hey, hi!
There she is!
Chelsea, this is Mia.
Mia, this is Chelsea.
Hi.
Hi!
We were just rehearsing.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt.
What? No-no, no,
there's nothing to interrupt.
She's singing,
I'm playing piano,
Alan, Berta and Jake
are right there in the kitchen.
Guys, Chelsea's home.
ALL (flatly):
Yay.
I should get going.
Good.
I mean, you don't
have to, but good.
Rehearsal was good.
You've got yourself
a terrific guy here.
I know. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
I'll see you Saturday
at the studio?
You bet.
♪ You'll never find... ♪
No, no, save your voice.
Yikes.
So, how'd it go?
Well, uh, how
can I put this?
She's the picture
you stick on the cover
of an album by a fat girl
who can actually sing.
That's not what
I mean.
Were there any,
you know, sparks?
No, no sparks.
Why would there be sparks?
I'm with you.
We're engaged.
We're gonna be married.
You and me,
that's the sparks...
baby.
Relax, Charlie,
I trust you.
Okay, lady, you're really
starting to piss me off.
♪ Men.
No problem, Charlie,
as long as you're willing
to pay my weekend rates.
You've got weekend rates?
Yep, and you probably don't want
to waste time haggling.
Now, what's the big emergency?
Well, you might not think
it's a big emergency,
but trust me, it is.
Okay.
I'm really constipated.
You do realize which end
of the body I specialize in?
I know, I know, I'm not here
for an enema.
Good, because that couch
isn't Scotchguarded.
I'm thinking it's psychosomatic
'cause I've tried coffee,
fiber, laxatives and something
my housekeeper said was
a suppository, but I now suspect
was a practical joke.
All right,
so psychosomatic constipation.
Good name for rock band, huh?
Weekend rates, Charlie.
Tell me what's going on
in your life.
How are things with you
and your fiancé?
Great, great!
She lives with me now.
We're planning the wedding.
Couldn't be better.
Good. And how's work?
Well, it's been pretty slow,
but thankfully,
the house is paid off,
my pension is funded,
and I've given up prostitutes.
So, really, all I need is
drinking money,
and what's that,
a couple grand a month?
That sounds about right.
Hey, do you remember Mia?
Your ex-fiancé the dancer.
Wow, you remember.
I'm not sitting here
sketching ponies, Charlie.
Anyway, I ran into her.
Really? And how'd that go?
Fine, fine. She looks great,
she's single again,
told me she missed me.
Uh-huh.
I always dig that.
Then she asked me
if I could help her out
with this music project,
and I said no.
But then Chelsea said
if I didn't still have feelings
for her, why not do it?
So I did it.
Interesting.
When did all this happen?
Three of four days ago.
And how long have you
been constipated?
I don't know.
Three, four days.
Hey, you think
there's a connection?
I'm leaning that way.
Look, Charlie,
you obviously still have
feelings for Mia,
and yet you're committed
to Chelsea.
It's an emotional conflict,
and until you resolve
that conflict,
you're going
to be physically blocked.
English, please?
As soon as you pick one,
you can go two.
What happens if I can't pick?
I don't know. C-section?
♪ Men.
Anyway, she said I have
to resolve the conflict
because my emotions
are strongly connected
to my lower intestine.
That makes a certain amount
of sense.
You think with your penis,
and your head's up your ass.
(gasps) The baby just came!
Baby?
Well, it's not technically
a baby,
but we know it's gonna
look like you.
Hey, Charlie
Hey.
What's she still doing here?
Not still. She went away,
she came back.
She's not moving in, Alan.
Of course not.
You said no, it's no.
We're out of
milk, sweetie.
I'm gonna run
to the market.
Okay.
She likes milk.
So how are you gonna resolve
your conflict?
I'm not sure.
I may have to sleep with Mia.
What?
Okay, here's the deal.
(groans)
If I back out of the recording
session with Mia,
Chelsea will think I still have
feelings for her.
All right.
However, if I spend
any more time with Mia
without sleeping with her,
I'm gonna split open
like a roasted pistachio.
Nobody wants that!
Charlie, cheating
on Chelsea makes
absolutely no sense whatsoever.
That's what I thought,
but my shrink was
pretty adamant.
Just promise if anything
happens to me,
you'll raise it as your own.
♪ Men.
(funky R&B playing)
(off-key):
♪ Down in Louisiana
♪ Where the alligators
grow so mean ♪
♪ Lived a girl that I swear
to the world ♪
♪ Made the alligators
look tame ♪
♪ Poke salad Annie
I know, I know
it's hard to believe
I'm not banging her.
Then why are we here?
She's an old friend.
I'm helping her out.
You really want to help her out?
Sneak up behind her
with a big rock.
(groaning)
Detox?
No, constipated.
'Cause you're detoxing?
Can we just do this?
Fine.
(volume increases)
♪ 'Cause your mama was working
on the chain gang ♪
♪ Poke
♪ Salad.
(song ends)
(sighs)
That one felt really good.
Okay, help me
understand something.
You're hoping
to bang her, right?
Can I hear a little?
Sure. Play it back.
♪ Down in Louisiana
That's me?
That's you.
♪ Where the alligators grow
so mean ♪
Wow. I had no idea
I was so good.
Oh, Charlie,
I'm so happy!
Oh, well, if you're happy,
I'm happy.
Why did I ever
let you go?
If I recall,
you had a list of reasons.
Well, I was wrong.
How can I make
it up to you?
Um, how do you want
to make it up to me?
Wow.
There it is.
Let's do this last track, and
then we can go back to my place.
(door closes)
Maybe we can sweeten
her vocals with some reverb,
a little echo,
lay a little guitar over it?
We can lay car horns
and barking dogs over it.
It won't help.
I'm ready.
Just relax and feel
the groove, okay?
I got it.
Okay, this is
"Boogie-woogie Bugle Boy."
Take one.
(trumpets play intro)
(off-key):
♪ He was a famous
trumpet man ♪
♪ From out Chicago way
♪ He had a boogie style that
no one else could play, whoo! ♪
♪ He was the top man
at his craft ♪
♪ And then his number came up,
and he was going to the draft ♪
♪ He's in the army now,
blowing reveille ♪
♪ He's the boogie-woogie
bugle boy of Company B ♪
Okay, Mia, hold it,
hold it a sec.
Is something wrong?
Yeah, kind of.
You can't sing.
What?
You got no talent.
I'm sorry, but we're
both wasting our time here.
I love Chelsea.
I'm gonna marry her,
and I can't see you anymore.
Are you kidding?
You can't just walk out
on me! You...
Where's the bathroom?
Down the hall.
Thanks.
No, thank you.
I should have known
this would happen,
you lowlife
son of a bitch!
Uh, the lowlife son of a bitch
is gone,
but I think
you have a real gift,
and we should work together.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
You might want
to give it a minute.
You were in there
with your guitar?
You never know when
inspiration might strike.
That's called "Two Burritos
and a Root Beer Float."
♪ Men.
Hey, how's
the intestines?
Clean as a whistle.
It's the city's problem now.
(laughs)
Yeah, ha-ha, very funny.
What was in that so-called
suppository you gave me, anyway?
Half a tab of Alka-Seltzer
crushed up in a gel cap.
Oh. Well, that explains
the foam.
Well, I'm off
to work.
Oh, have a good day,
sweetie.
I'll be home
around 6:30.
Okay.
Alan?
She's not living here.
Just checking.
And he calls me stupid.