ANNOUNCER:
Call now. Operators
are standing by.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
What are you doing?
I'm calling them.
Don't you want to be able
to scramble an egg
while it's still
in the shell?
Okay...
new rule— you can't drink
while we watch cable television.
You won't say that when you get
a blanket with sleeves
for Christmas.
Hi, Jake.
Hmm.
Can I offer you
some fruit and cheese?
You can, but I won't eat it.
Okay.
So what's new?
How's your girlfriend?
That's kind of personal,
isn't it?
Sorry. I'm just curious.
Why, you writing a book?
Yeah, it's called The Day
Jake's Uncle Kicked His Ass.
Whatever.
Oh, no, don't go.
We so enjoy your company.
Did I do something wrong?
Yeah, you
anthropomorphized him.
What?
It means
treating something
that's not human
as if it is.
You know, like you
do with your cat.
Which frankly,
makes more sense.
I'm starting to think
Jake resents me.
See? You're still doing it.
Look, you can't
take it personal.
He's a teenager.
You know, that awkward stage
between junior high
and methadone clinic.
I just want to get
to know him better.
I already know him.
Trust me, you're
not missing anything.
Come on, there's got
to be something
underneath that
sullen exterior.
Yeah, a "D" student
with a perpetual boner.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Ginzu knives.
♪ Men.
Kind of like
high school, huh?
I never did this in high school.
Really? Sex in a car?
You're kind of
built for it.
Oh, what the
heck is this?
Oh, Jake's retainer.
He lost this years ago.
This cost me like, $500.
Anyway...
No, this is not
working for me.
Want another
wine cooler?
No, I want to be
in a real bed.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
You won't stay
at Charlie's.
How can I go back there
after his fiancee
called me a tramp?
Oh, come on, she
didn't mean it.
That was just
heat of the moment
when she found out
you'd slept with Charlie.
It doesn't bother you,
does it?
Well, yeah, yeah,
a bit, you know,
but beggars can't be choosers.
And I love you.
No, not here.
Well, then where?
I'd be more than happy
to go back to your place
if you could just get past
that little incident
with your mother.
Little incident?
I caught you
in bed with her!
Boy, you are just going
to keep harping on
that, aren't you?
Why don't we just
got to a hotel?
Uh, well, we could, but wouldn't
that feel kind of cheap?
I'll tell you what
feels kind of cheap— you.
What are you doing?
I'm getting out of here.
What-what, you're
gonna walk home?
Well, it's not
far, Alan.
You didn't want to waste
the gas, remember?
Pardon me for being green.
Good-bye.
Oh, come on, Melissa!
Let's not ruin
a beautiful evening!
I already broke the seal
on the condom!
All right, all right.
All right, you win,
you win.
I'll take you to a cheap motel.
(siren blaring)
Oh, great.
POLICE OFFICER:
Stand up
and put your
hands behind your head.
Uh, I can explain this.
Hands behind
your head!
This is not what it looks like.
I-I-I was just chasing
this girl
who jumped out of my car.
Oh...
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
(playing "Smoke on the Water")
(knocking at door)
You got a minute?
I'm practicing.
Yeah, well, take a pause
for the cause.
What?
Take five.
Five what?
Just shut up
and listen to me!
You have a problem
with Chelsea?
No.
So what's with the attitude?
What attitude?
I just don't consider fruit and
cheese an acceptable snack.
I don't care. You were rude.
Kettle corn— that's a snack.
That's not the point.
Nachos— that's a proper
use of cheese.
All right, all right,
listen to me.
You're hurting Chelsea's
feelings
and I need you to make an effort
to be nicer to her.
Hey, it's not my problem
if your girlfriend's
oversensitive.
Yeah, it kind of is.
If you guys can't get along,
then one of you has got to go.
And guess who
that's going to be?
Why? Just 'cause
you sleep with her?
Good for you. Why do people
think you're stupid?
'Cause of my grades.
Actually, I'm an underachiever.
Just be nice to Chelsea,
all right?
Fine.
(playing hard rock riff)
(door closes)
Well, that was uncalled for.
Just F.Y.I., your
son's a moron.
No, he's an underachiever.
Where have you been?
Had a date with Melissa.
How'd it go?
She broke up with me
and I may have to register
as a sex offender.
Well, as long as
you had fun.
Charlie, do you have any idea
how difficult it is
to maintain a relationship
when you don't have
a place of your own?
Alan, if I didn't have
a place of my own,
I'd be worried about more
important things than
a relationship.
Like, you know,
getting a place of my own.
So, you're saying I'm not
entitled to a relationship?
No, I'm saying if you
can't afford dog food
you don't get a dog.
Oh, great, so I'm just
supposed to be
alone for the rest of my life?
No, you're supposed to get
your own freakin' place!
Just 'cause you keep saying it,
doesn't mean it's gonna happen.
♪ Men.
How's the French toast,
Jake?
It's bread dipped in eggs.
You can't really
screw it up.
It's fine.
It's the best damn French toast
I've ever had in my whole
freakin' life.
Now stop kicking me.
Okay, guys,
I'll see you later.
Oh, you're working
on a Sunday?
Well, kind of.
Since my brother and I are
both extremely anxious
for me to get my own place—
me, because I'd like
a sense of autonomy,
and him, because he's
a spiteful turd—
um...
I have found a way
to earn some extra money.
Great. Put me down for three
boxes of Thin Mints
and some Peanut Butter Sandies.
Ah, Girl Scout cookies?
I like those Samoas.
I'm not selling cookies, Jake.
Oh...
Then what are you selling?
It better not be your liver—
I got dibs.
EVELYN:
Hello.
Where is my
new assistant?
Oh, you didn't.
Morning, all.
Here, darling,
put this on.
Ooh, snazzy. Do
I get to keep it?
No, but if this works out,
I'll sell it to you at cost.
You're going to work for Mom?
What else am I
supposed to do?
I don't know, some job that lets
you keep your self-respect.
Like, you know, man whore...
Dog de-wormer...
Outhouse inspector.
Morning, Charlie.
Hey, Mom. How are you?
Laxative tester,
horse inseminator.
I'm going to work weekends
with Mom selling real estate,
and she's going to give me
a piece of the action.
No, I said having an assistant
would give me a little peace
so I could get some action.
Well, whatever.
It's a start.
Let's go.
No, dear.
I say, "Let's go."
Oh, oh, okay.
Let's go.
Stop.
Take my bag.
Now let's go.
This is going to be fun.
Okay, I'm done.
He didn't say thank you.
He's leaving the room.
We should thank him.
Jake, come back
in here and say
thank you to Chelsea.
Jake, I'm warning you.
Jake!
(muffled):
Thank you, Chelsea.
Now was that so hard?
♪ Men.
Oh, welcome, welcome.
Please sign in. Take a flyer.
There's juice and cookies
in the kitchen.
Thank you.
I know, you think you'd never
use a bidet,
but trust me, once you do,
you'll never go back
to just wiping.
Anyway, if you're
not ready to buy,
the owners are
willing to lease.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Thanks for coming.
Oh, the rat bastards live
right across the street.
They probably just came
for the free cookies.
Um, Mom, I have to go
to the bathroom.
Number one or number two?
What difference
does it make?
Alan, I'm trying
to sell a house here.
Warm cookie smell, good—
hot poop smell, bad.
I'll wait.
You're damn right you'll wait.
So the people who own this
live mostly in New York?
Oh, they have homes
all over the place.
Probably don't even remember
they have this one.
Hardly seems fair.
Want fair? Go live
on a kibbutz.
Funny.
How's that work, exactly?
Do you have to be Jewish?
Oh, welcome, welcome.
Please sign in.
Uh, there's juice and cookies
in the kitchen.
(muffled flatulence)
Loose floorboard.
♪ Men.
Okay, we need to talk
about your kid and my fiancée.
I already talked to him,
and he promised to stay out
of her underwear drawer.
What?
Not that he ever went into it.
It's just a precaution.
Alan, I don't think
you realize...
Look, look, look, I would love
to have this conversation,
but I've got to get to work.
It's 9:00 at night.
Tell that to our mother.
People want to see a house
at night and she's got a date,
guess who has to show the house?
Well, fine, at least take
the rhesus monkey with you.
Oh yeah, nothing sells
a multi-million dollar home
more than a 15-year-old boy
with greasy hair and BO.
Okay, let him stand
on the lawn
in a jockey costume,
holding a lantern.
Look, you're the one who said
I needed to get my own place.
This is what I got to do.
You don't fool me.
You're never leaving.
Never!
That's it.
I'm done trying with that kid.
(sighs)
When did my life turn
into Leave it to Beaver?
It was more fun when it was
Leave it to Beaver.
Okay, numb nuts, what
did you say to Chelsea?
Nothing.
Then why is she so upset?
I don't know.
Maybe it's her period.
She says it wasn't,
but I don't believe her.
♪ Men.
(doorbell rings)
Ah...
Welcome to our love nest,
my tiny sparrow.
♪ Men.
This is unbelievable.
How can you afford it?
Well, I didn't buy it,
of course. I'm renting.
I don't get it.
Just the other day we were going
to do it in your car
because you didn't
want to shell out $59
for a hotel room.
It was $69, but, uh...
But this is
different. I, uh...
I get a tax break on it.
You know, the home office.
So, you've moved out
of your brother's house?
Uh, well, not quite yet.
This is just a pied-a-terre.
Besides, I might flip it
and move up to something
a little bigger.
But you said you're renting.
Yes, yes, I'm renting...
with-with an
option to flip.
But let's not
talk money.
Let's talk love.
Shall we go try out the bed?
The bed? With the—
with the sheets?
Um...
Beds are so bourgeois,
don't you think?
Ooh, Alan.
The couch?
Uh, actually I was
thinking right here
in front of the fireplace...
on this beach towel.
Come on. I was
trying to be nice.
By asking her
if she was on her period?
I was taking an interest.
You're an idiot.
Why are you making it personal?
I'm not making it personal.
Okay, here's the deal.
You two are going to stay in
here and work this thing out
until you're
either getting along
or one of you is dead.
FYI, she can kick your ass.
Have fun.
(door closes)
Hey.
So...
I guess you owe me an apology.
♪ Men.
Wow.
(both chuckling)
I've never seen you
so forceful and virile.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
You were wonderful, too.
You're-You're still
on the towel, right?
You know what I think?
I think finally making love
in a place of our own
has given you more confidence.
Well, truth be told, I
do feel kind of cocky.
No pun intended.
Oh, it is so intended.
Ah. You got me.
(laughing)
Yes, I do.
(moans)
I want to make love to you
in every room in this house.
I don't see any
reason why not.
As long as we
bring the towel.
Of course, we're going to have
to wait about a half hour,
give my erectile
medication a chance
to overcome my
anti-depressants.
Complicated man,
Alan Harper.
And I've got the medicine
chest to prove it.
(laughing)
Whoopsie.
Oh, damn it!
Sorry.
Sorry doesn't get
out the stain.
Do you have any club soda?
How the hell would
I know? Don't rub!
Blot, blot, blot!
Stop yelling at me!
Just get out of the way.
What is wrong with you?
Nothing. I just...
(screams):
Oh, no!
That's your whoopsie.
Oh, my mother's
going to kill me!
What does your mother
have to do with it?
Are you kidding? She doesn't
even let me poop here!
♪ Men.
Hey, so, how did
everything work out?
Sit down, Charlie.
Why?
Just sit.
Okay.
What's going on?
We figured out what
the problem is between us.
Well, great. What is it?
You.
Well, this ought to be good.
You told Jake
that he should be nice to me
because I was oversensitive?
Well, I don't know
that I said those actual words.
And you called me a "D" student
with a perpetual...
you know what.
Boner.
Yeah,
those were my actual words.
Charlie, don't you see
how you're the one
who's been driving a wedge
between us?
No, not really.
I told you he
wouldn't get it.
Well, hang on a second. Hang on.
You're blaming me
because you two
can't get along and now...
You're right. You're right.
I'm the problem.
I am so sorry.
It won't ever happen again.
Thank you.
Thanks.
"Perpetual" means
"pointy," right?
♪ Men.
Okay, I think
I got it all out.
You didn't have to yell.
I know. I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't know
what got into me.
It was just an accident.
I know.
You hurt my feelings.
Again, I am so sorry.
Come here.
(clicking tongue)
(door opening)
Now, wait till you see
the panoramic city to
ocean views at night.
Why are we running?
Well, remember when I told
you I rented this house?
Yeah?
I lied.
(police siren wails)
Oh, no. Not again.
Okay. Okay.
Just let me do the talking.
Melissa?
POLICE OFFICER:
Get down on your knees,
and put your hands
behind your head.
Uh, okay. Okay.
First of all,
let me explain the erection.
♪ Men.
What's going on?
Not much.
Where's Jake and Chelsea?
They went
to the movies together.
Oh, how nice.
Yep.
Life is good.
Hmm.
So, did you sell that house?
Uh, no.
Actually, I'm not working
for Mom anymore.
You quit?
Yeah, let's say that.
And while we're at it,
let's say I dumped Melissa
and decided she never
wants to see me again
as long as she lives.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, uh, hey, you
know how they say
if you take one
of those pills
and your erection lasts
for more than four hours,
you should call a doctor?
Yeah.
What time is it?