♪ Men.
Mmm, oh, and here's
another money saver:
If you buy a big bag
of irregular socks,
you can pair up the good ones
and use the cash you save
for underwear.
Good to know.
And you can use the leftover
misfit socks
for dusting gloves, golf club
cozies, even a hand puppet.
A hand puppet?
Oh, sure, couple of buttons for
eyes, and you're ready to go.
Hello, pretty lady.
That's funny.
So, you done the Internet dating
thing before?
All the time.
Oh, and if you're interested,
I know a couple of tricks
to weed out the losers.
I'm very interested.
Hey, how are ya?
Hi.
Oh, you know him?
No.
Oh, talking to
strange women.
Must be drunk.
Anyway, my profile says
that I am a chiropractor,
but I also do a lot of
holistic work, you know
acupressure, deep
tissue massage,
both of which promote a
general sense of well being
and also a heightened
sexual sensitivity.
(chuckles)
Assuming, of course,
your sexual sensitivity
requires heightening.
I have absolutely no intention
of sleeping with you, Alan.
Whoa, whoa, where'd that
come from? (chuckles)
I'm just talking about my job.
Making conversation.
And when you say
"absolutely no intention,"
you just mean tonight, right?
Um, you look like you could use
another one of these.
You're a mind reader.
Uh, excuse me,
but, uh, I'm
with this lady,
and if she would like
another drink,
I am more than capable
of providing one.
But the dinner's still dutch.
What's your name?
Uh, Louanne.
Hi, Louanne, I'm Marcus.
All right, all right,
fun time's over.
Look, Marcus,
the lady is on
a date with me, and
you are intruding.
Why don't we ask the lady
what she wants?
Not necessary. I can tell you
what she wants and it's not me.
But there is a
principle involved
and that is one
of poaching
another man's gal.
Is that so?
Yes, that's so. Now take a hike.
Why don't you just sit down
and finish your peanuts?
Don't you touch me!
Hey, hey, calm down.
You're right, you're right.
We should just, uh,
take a deep breath
and calm down.
That's a good idea.
So, what are you doing after
Potsie here drops you off?
Hey, Marcus?
How's that, bitch?
♪ Men.
What are you doing in there?
Be patient.
I got you a surprise.
You hear that?
She got us a surprise.
(phone rings)
You gonna grab that?
You'll have to be more specific.
Answer the phone,
Charlie.
Right, right.
Hello?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
slow down, slow down.
Who is this?
Oh, hi, Alan.
Not a good time right now.
Really?
What the hell
are you doing in jail?
You're kidding me.
That's hilarious!
(laughs)
All right, all right,
I'm on my way.
What do you think?
Doing-oing-oing-oing!
I was gonna save it
for our wedding night,
but I couldn't wait.
Oh, baby, by the time
we get married,
that thing's gonna be
half-eaten.
Who was on the phone?
Alan.
Everything all right?
Yeah, he was just callin' to say
he wouldn't be home tonight.
Oh, did he get lucky?
Not yet, but the night
is still young.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Ten hours!
Ten hours I sat in that
urine-soaked jail cell!
You shouldn't have
peed yourself.
You said you'd be right there!
Look, look,
I understand your anger,
but you gotta see it
from my side.
What's your side?
I get really sleepy after sex!
What's going on?
Oh, your gallant fiancé
let his baby brother rot
in a prison cell all night.
What?
I've been there
plenty of times.
You slip
the booking officer a $20,
he'll send out for Starbucks.
You know I don't carry
that kind of cash.
Regardless, it was
just one night.
Nobody took your man cherry,
did they?
Was that why
Alan called last night?
Uh... I assume so.
Oh, Charlie.
Hey, hey, you had that sexy
lingerie on
and you were so beautiful,
plus you know how
I hate to waste an erection.
I can't believe you abandoned
your brother when he needed you.
It's horrible.
How did I become the bad guy
in all this?
He's the felon!
Why were you in jail, Alan?
I was forced to use my hands
to defend a lady's honor.
Ask him what happened
to the lady.
She drove the guy I punched
to the emergency room.
I don't understand.
Why would she go with him
if you were defending her honor?
Who knows?
I would've asked her,
but I was busy being handcuffed
and dragged off to jail!
Where I spent the night covering
my behind with a food tray.
Shame on you,
Charlie Harper.
Now she's mad at me.
Happy?
Oh, yeah, I'm thrilled!
If my transsexual biker
cell mate had only been
a little more affectionate,
my life would now be perfect!
♪ Men.
I don't know.
I just snapped and hit him.
It's the first time in my life
that's ever happened.
You mean it's the first time
you've ever won.
The important thing now
is for you to know
that your family is a hundred
percent behind you.
Thanks, Mom.
Now, before we waste money
on some expensive lawyer,
how much jail time
are we talking about
if you just roll over?
I don't want to go to jail!
And if he does, he certainly
doesn't want to roll over.
Charles, that is crude
and uncalled for.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Nobody wants to go to jail,
sweetie, but let's face it,
if all we're talking about
is 60 days alone in a room
with no friends, how is that
different from two months
squatting in
your brother's house?
You're kidding, right?
I guess.
You know what?
Don't worry yourself.
I'll just get a public defender
and take care of this myself.
There you go, problem solved.
Charlie?
What? Some kid out
of law school
hungry to make his bones.
What's wrong with that?
He gets his hair cut by trainees
at the barber college.
Alan, I'd be happy
to help you hire a lawyer.
Oh, no, Chelsea,
I couldn't take money from you.
That's an honor
he reserves for family.
So, what, you guys really aren't
gonna help him?
Well, of course we are.
But if we didn't torture him
a little bit,
he wouldn't feel comfortable
accepting our help.
You don't know that. Try me!
I'll tell you what.
I'll find the lawyer,
and we'll split the fee.
Not fifty-fifty, 'cause I'm out
six years of room,
board and incidentals.
And by incidentals, I mean
mostly Kleenex and hand lotion.
Oh, please, I paid
for four years of college
and chiropractor school,
and he still gives me handmade
tchotchkes for Christmas.
You said you loved
the pot holders I made you.
I said they made me cry.
Okay, okay, okay, fifty-fifty.
But we'll put it on my card
so I get the miles.
I can't believe you two.
That's okay, Chelsea, I'm used
to being treated this way.
The mocking, the insults,
the humiliation.
It's all part of the festering
ugliness of this family.
See? He's fine with this.
♪ Men.
Thanks for coming, you guys.
Your support
means a lot.
Thank her.
If it was up to me,
you'd be in San Quentin wearing
lipstick and a mop wig.
Okay, Mom,
I gotta go.
No, I love you.
Okay. What?
No, you're not bothering me.
I'm happy
to take care of it. Okay.
Okay, bye-bye.
Sorry. I just bought my mom
a new computer,
and it's opened up
quite a can of worms.
Ironic. I just bought my mom
a can of worms.
Brad Harlow.
Are you Alan?
No, no, no,
I'm his brother Charlie.
This is my fiancée Chelsea.
And this pasty-faced jughead
is the family Rottweiler.
I just want it
on record
that I am not by nature
a violent man.
My fuse is long,
but it is attached
to dynamite.
Shut up.
I'm payin' by the hour.
Would you two
just stop it.
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
I have siblings, too.
We tease each other constantly.
You know, sometimes I think
it's just easier
than saying "I love you."
Okay, well, I got some good news
for you, Alan.
Hey, when's the last time
you heard that?
I made some calls,
and the fella you punched has
quite a few
alcohol-related priors,
and is definitely not looking
to press charges.
So I don't have
to go back to jail?
You won't even see the inside
of a courtroom.
Oh, thank God!
I can't go back to
the joint again.
All right, great,
we're off the clock.
What do I owe you?
Eh, relax,
you don't owe me anything.
Even better.
Thank you.
Charlie. We... we have
to pay you for your time.
Oh, you hippie.
Well, uh,
well, you can always make
a donation to my charity.
What's that, Lawyers
Without Yachts?
(laughs)
No...
no, it's for inner city kids.
They come out to my ranch
once a month,
you know, learn to ride horses,
get out in the fresh air.
Oh, that's wonderful.
I love horses.
I used to ride
all the time.
Shall I write you a check?
No, no, no, no, I got it.
Who do I make it out to?
Danielle's Darlings.
Who's Danielle?
My late wife.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
I started the charity
to keep her memory alive.
She loved horses.
Crap. That's another zero.
There you go.
Wow.
This is incredibly generous.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
You know, we're having
a nature ride and barbecue
for the kids this Saturday.
You should come.
Really? That sounds wonderful.
Doesn't it, Charlie?
Do the kids race
the horses?
What?
No.
There's no action?
No action.
I don't see the point.
He's just joking.
No, I'm not.
I really don't
see the point.
Well, if you change your mind,
here's the info.
We'd love
to see you.
Thank you. Maybe we will.
Great.
Yeah, maybe.
Thanks very much, Brad.
Always nice to bring
good news to a client.
And the best news is,
I think having a criminal record
is really spice up
my online dating profile.
I might even post
the mug shot.
♪ Men.
Wasn't Brad terrific?
Who's Brad?
Alan's lawyer.
Uh, he's okay, I guess.
You guess?
Not only does he have
a successful law practice,
he's doing so much
to help poor kids.
What, by sticking
them on horses?
How's that
going to help?
Get them a high paying job
with the pony express?
It's not about jobs.
It's about getting
them out of the city
and into the fresh air.
Fresh air?
Have you ever
smelled a horse?
You know what I mean.
And did you hear the way
he talked about family?
They obviously mean
a lot to him.
Family also meant a
lot to Charles Manson.
That's a terrible
thing to say.
Sorry.
Hey, speaking of
horseback riding—
why don't you hop on
and I'll race you
to the finish.
You know what, I'm not
really in the mood.
That's okay. I've got enough
mood for both of us.
Good night, Charlie.
But Charlie's a
frustrated pony.
Go to sleep.
I was pretty
charitable today.
Mm-hmm.
I guess the spirit of giving
doesn't extend
to the bedroom, huh?
Good night, Charlie.
(nickering)
♪ Men.
Hey.
Can't sleep?
Nope.
Me neither.
Even though I dodged
the legal bullet,
I've got all this stuff
building up inside me.
I'm afraid I'm going to explode.
I'm afraid I won't.
The other night in that bar,
I just snapped.
It was like I became
a different person.
Well, that had to be
a nice break for you.
I'm scared, Charlie.
I mean, there was a part
of me that really enjoyed
driving my fist into
that jerk's stupid face
and watching him crumble
to the floor in agony.
So what are you scared of?
What if this is
just the beginning?
What if I've awakened
some long-dormant monster
inside of me
who revels in violence?
What if I can't
control the monster?
What if the monster
takes over?
Ouchy!
You're fine. Go
to bed, monster.
Okay, good night.
♪ Men.
What happened
to your hand?
Oh, well...
I won't lie to you.
I got into a bar fight
and punched a guy
in the face.
Yeah, right.
No, I'm serious.
I spent the night in jail.
Fine, don't tell me.
I was just trying
to make conversation.
Hey, I am warning you.
There is a monster
inside of me
and you don't want
to wake him up.
Oh! Oh! Hot, hot.
Did the monster burn
his mouth with his
chamomile tea?
It's oolong.
Where's Chelsea?
She went to that
charity thing
for inner city horses.
You let her go
without you?
Why the hell would I want to go?
I hate kids
and I'm scared of horses.
Maybe you didn't notice
the way my lawyer
was looking at your fiancée.
What are you
talking about?
Or the way she was
looking back at him.
That's ridiculous.
I'm telling you, there
were definitely sparks
between the two of them.
You think?
Charlie, that guy
is everything you're not.
Well, what's that mean?
He likes people,
he loves his mother,
he works with children
and he doesn't stumble
through life
stinking of whiskey
and KY Jelly.
Hey, hey, hey,
KY Jelly is odorless.
Not where you put it.
I'm just saying that
if Chelsea were my fiancée,
I wouldn't leave her
alone with this guy.
If Chelsea were
your fiancée,
you'd have bigger problems.
Like what?
Like being the
last man on Earth.
♪ Men.
I don't understand why
I have to go to this thing.
Because your uncle
wants to use you
to camouflage
his growing fear
that his girlfriend might
be interested in another guy.
Hey, hey, hey.
I have no fear.
Of course not.
You just got
a sudden craving
for barbecue
and horses.
Whoa, there's gonna be
barbecued horses?
Cool.
Where the hell is this
lawyer's stupid ranch?
You must have passed
the turnoff.
Maybe we should put
the GPS back on.
I don't need
the GPS.
GPS:
Take the next
legal U-turn.
Then proceed 22 miles
to main road.
Okay, turn around.
There's no room.
Well, then back up.
22 miles?
Just till you find
a place to turn.
I'm hungry.
We're almost there.
I don't think so.
I'd smell the barbecue.
Jake, would you pipe down
so I can concen...?
Oh, damn.
You have reached
your destination.
(sniffs)
I don't think so.
♪ Men.
Un-freakin'-believable.
Still no signal.
Well, of course,
there's no signal.
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
I'm starving.
What do you want from me?
Go catch a squirrel.
This is why
I always tell you
to keep an emergency kit
in your car.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No matter what happens,
I know that in my trunk
is a thermal blanket,
flashlight, batteries,
bottled water and
assorted protein bars.
You hear that, Jake?
You have an inheritance.
I already ate
the protein bars.
You were right, Alan.
The more time Chelsea
spends with this Brad guy,
the more time she's going to
have to contrast and compare.
And I'm not going to come
out of that looking so good.
If you're really worried
about her being attracted
to a better man than you,
why don't you become
a better man?
(mocking tone):
Why don't you become
a better man?
Yeah, like that.
♪ Men.
You guys think there are
mountain lions up here?
Hadn't given it
much thought.
Till just now.
Relax. There's no
mountain lions here.
You know, this is where
it normally goes bad
in slasher movies.
One guy falls back a little bit,
usually to smoke pot
or have sex,
and he gets his head
hacked off.
Let that be a lesson to you
about drugs and premarital sex.
Good parenting, Alan.
Thank you.
(growling)
ALAN:
Mountain lion!
Mountain lion! Run! Run!
Oh, crap! Hey, guys wait up!
(screaming)
Psych.
♪ Men.
I can't believe you really
thought I was a mountain lion.
Go to your room.
You're punishing me just because
you're gullible?
Yeah, pretty much.
(Jake growling)
Still not funny!
Chelsea's not home.
How could she not
be home yet?
That thing was
over hours ago.
Are you worried she might be
cheating on you with Brad?
No, I was thinking car trouble,
but thanks for that.
Sorry.
Look, Chelsea and I have been
together for over a year now.
We're engaged to be married.
What are the odds she's going
to leave me for some lawyer
just because he's kind,
rich, handsome, generous,
loves his family and named
a charity after his dead wife?
I don't know, even money?
At least.
So ten bucks just
to make it interesting?
(slap)
ALAN: Ouchy!