♪ Men.
(doorbell rings)
JUDITH:
I said, "No!"
JAKE:
And I said, "Why not?"
No!
Why not?
but Mom won't let
me drive her car.
Just because they give
15-year-olds learner's permits,
doesn't mean
they're ready to drive.
Oh, please, I've been
driving for years.
Grand Theft Auto One,
Grand Theft Auto Two.
And I never ran over anybody
but pimps and crack whores.
Jake.
Sorry. Crack
prostitutes.
Go get started on your homework.
Afterward, will you
take me driving?
We'll talk about it later.
When?
Just go to your room.
I'm available now.
Go!
Man, if I knew how to hot-wire
a real car,
I'd so be outta here.
Well, thanks for bringing him
by, I guess.
Yeah. Uh, if you need
to reach me,
Herb and I are going to Laguna
Beach for a weekend getaway.
Oh, how nice.
Taking the baby?
Are you insane?
I said "getaway."
Herb's lucky I'm taking him.
I see.
So, uh, so, who's watching
little Millie?
My mother.
Ooh. Are we sure
that's a good idea?
Okay, first of all,
there is no "we" here.
And what are you implying?
I'm implying that there might be
better choices for a babysitter
than a woman who has a sandwich
named after her
at the Betty Ford Clinic.
She's three years clean
and sober,
all the charges were dropped
and she's great with Millie.
All right. All right.
I hope you don't mind,
but I gave her your number
in case there's an emergency.
I don't mind.
So, uh, how is the baby, anyway?
Fine.
Good, good.
Jake showed me some pictures.
I gotta say, she doesn't look
much like you,
and she certainly doesn't look
like Herb.
Don't go there, Alan.
Go where? I'm not implying
that someone other than Herb
could be the father.
Even though that someone did
have unprotected sex with you
approximately nine months
before the birth of a child
that looks suspiciously
like that someone.
You get that I'm talking
about me, right?
Honey, if we want
to beat the traffic,
we really should get going.
Oh, hey, Alan.
Hey, Herb.
Did you hear?
Judith and I are spending a
romantic weekend in Laguna.
I said "weekend," Herb.
That's all.
Okay, fine,
no romance.
But sex is still
on the table, right?
Just get in the car.
Oh, can I drive?
No.
Why not?
Is she gone?
(cat screeching)
Damn it!
Chelsea, your cat's
trying to kill me!
CHELSEA:
Is he okay?
The cat's fine!
Probably off plotting
his next move... Whoa!
(thudding)
Whoa!
Are you okay?
No.
What happened?
Uncle Charlie fell.
Oh.
Can I drive you to
the hospital?
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
CHELSEA: Sir Lancelot!
Here, kitty, kitty!
He's probably hiding
because he thinks
you're mad at him.
For God's sake, Chelsea,
the cat doesn't think
anything except maybe,
"Mmm, fish, I'll eat it."
Or "Ooh, sand, I'll crap in it."
You're wrong.
He's very intelligent
and very intuitive.
He knows you resent him
living here.
Thank you, Chelsea,
but I can defend myself.
I was talking
about my cat.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
Mmm, fish. Yum.
Okay, I'm going
to work.
Feel better.
Thanks.
How's the shoulder?
The shoulder's fine.
I'm just hopin' to get a little
"Oh, poor Charlie" tonight.
"Oh, poor Charlie"?
Yeah. You know,
"Oh, poor Charlie.
"I feel bad about your shoulder,
so you just lie still
while I provide you with a
series of intense orgasms."
Wow.
I don't know what to say,
other than "oink."
(engine starting)
Is that a car?
Can I drive?
Relax, it's just Chelsea
going to work.
Oh.
Uncle Charlie,
you need to go anywhere?
Yeah, away from you.
All right. I'll drive you.
You want to drive
my $80,000 Mercedes?
Yes, please.
It's good that he's polite.
It's a necessary quality
in a doorman.
Was that a "yes"
or a "no"?
That was a "no."
So the doorman thing
was an insult?
Yes.
Oh.
And a prophecy.
(phone rings)
(alarm blaring)
Hello?
No, it's Charlie.
Who's this?
I can't hear you. What?
Alan, it's for you.
Oh.
Hello?
Oh, oh, hi, Lenore.
It's, uh, Judith's mother.
Uh, is that the house alarm?
Uh, is-is the baby okay?
All right, open the little panel
by the front door
and enter pound,
star and the code.
Pound is the little
tic-tac-toe board.
Yeah, like on Hollywood Squares.
She still poppin'
the pain pills?
No.
Good. See if she's
got any leftovers.
Okay, the code is
Jake's birthday.
Your grandson.
Anyway, it's oh-three-one-four—
Oh, no, no, Le-Lenore, don't
punch it into the phone.
No, Lenore! Lenore! Lenore!
Okay, okay, okay,
calm down, calm down.
I-I'll be right there.
I-I will turn it off for you.
Oh, okay, okay. Bye.
(grunting): I gotta go.
You couldn't be more of a sucker
if you were on the end
of a stick.
Why?
Because I'll take any excuse
to spend some time
with my baby daughter?
You don't know
you're the father, Alan.
Oh, come on.
She's got my jawline,
my eyes, my ears.
You left out thinning hair
and poopy pants.
That was one time
and I begged you to stop
at a gas station.
(alarm blaring)
♪ Men.
(baby crying)
Oh, Alan, thank God
you're here.
I pushed all the buttons,
but I can't get it to stop.
Well, that might be
because you were adjusting
the thermostat.
(alarm stops)
Ah, there we go.
Oh, thank God.
(crying continues)
Oh, here, let me see
if I can turn this
alarm off.
Come here, Millie.
Come to Papa...
♪ ... was a rolling stone
♪ Wherever he laid his
hat was his home... ♪
Always sang this to Jake.
Worked like a charm.
(crying continues)
(high-pitched):
♪ And when he died
♪ All he left us
was alone. ♪
(crying stops)
Huh, look at that.
Well, you're a miracle
worker, Alan.
Oh, no.
I just have a knack
for babies.
And, uh, and animals.
It's only English-speaking
adults that don't like me.
Well, I think you're
a wonderful fella.
And if you don't
mind my saying,
I think Judith was a
fool to let you go.
Well, she didn't so much
let me go
as drop me from an airplane
with an anvil necklace.
Okay, honey, time
to get your beauty rest.
I'm afraid that's gonna
have to be a long nap.
I mean, I hate to say it about
my own granddaughter,
but let's face it—
with those big ears
she looks a little
like a fruit bat.
I think her ears are
the perfect size.
You would.
How about some wine?
Uh, uh, well, thank you, but
I-I really should get going.
Oh, no, come on, join me.
Just one. We'll catch up.
Uh... Lenore, it's really
none of my business,
but do you think you should
really be drinking?
What? You mean,
because I've been to Betty Ford?
Oh, no, no, uh,
because you got kicked out
of Betty Ford.
Hey, Britney bit me first.
Anyway, I was there
for pills.
I've never had a problem
with alcohol.
Oh.
See?
No problem.
Okay, now,
where did I hide
those muscle relaxers
I picked up in Mexico?
That's right.
Between my buttcheeks.
Turn around.
♪ Men.
Uncle Charlie?
What?
You hungry?
'Cause if you are, we could go
get something to eat.
And I'll even drive.
Jake, I'm sleeping.
Okay.
You know, you could nap
in the car.
I just gotta have an adult
with me.
They don't have to be conscious.
I'm not hungry.
Okay, fine.
Hey, want to go see a movie?
'Cause if you do...
(grunting)
Maybe after your nap.
Oh, crap, now I'm awake.
Great.
You hungry?
♪ Men.
You're lucky you're
single, Alan.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, no, trust me.
I've been married
for 39 years!
Really?
But Judith's 40.
Shh.
Do you know what it's like
to wake up every morning,
year after year,
and see the same stupid face
lying next to you?
Uh, well, all I can tell you
is what I told your daughter.
If you don't like it, roll over.
Fred hasn't touched me
in 14 years.
Uh, well, uh, in his defense,
he did have that stroke.
Do you know what happens
to a woman's body
when it goes unloved
for that long?
Oh, gee, Lenore,
I don't really
feel comfortable
talking about this...
Oh, now, Alan, come on,
we're both grown-ups.
Think about what I'm saying.
All right, well...
I'm getting an image of a...
a cave
from an Indiana Jones movie.
What?
Well, you know— cobwebs,
dust, human skulls.
This is my vagina
we're talking about.
Oh, I am well aware
of what we're talking about.
(voice breaking):
I've been so lonely.
Oh, oh, I'm...
I'm sorry, Lenore.
Mmm.
A stroke's starting
to look pretty good.
♪ Men.
Can't I at least
back it out?
No.
Come on, nothing's
gonna happen.
Look, you wanna eat or not?
Fine.
What if we went to
an empty parking lot?
Could I drive it then?
Dammit, Jake, how many times
I gotta tell...
(cat screeching)
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
Sounds like you
ran over a cat.
♪ Men.
Told you you should've
let me drive.
You know, Chelsea's gonna
completely freak out.
No, she will not be happy.
Doesn't even look
like a cat anymore.
Nope.
More like a cat pancake.
Catcake.
Sorry.
What am I gonna tell her?
She doesn't have to know.
You're right.
She thinks Sir Lancelot's
missing, so he stays missing.
Sir Squished-a-lot.
Okay, okay, let's just
think what we gotta do.
We have to get
rid of the body,
clean up the mess then act
like nothing's happened.
Good plan, except...
Except what?
Say, "cheese!"
What are you doing?
Making sure I get to drive
your car whenever I want to.
What? Give me that!
Too late, I already
emailed it to myself.
You're bluffing.
Perhaps.
But can you really afford
to take that chance?
♪ Men.
♪ Hush, little baby,
don't say a word ♪
♪ Daddy's gonna buy you
a mockingbird ♪
♪ If that mockingbird
don't sing ♪
Forget it, I'm not sleepy.
Let's go in the hot tub!
Uh, but I don't
have a bathing suit.
Me neither.
Come on, stroke.
(phone ringing)
Judith, ugh.
Oh, this just keeps
getting better and better.
(baby crying)
Oh, hey, look who's up.
Hi, sweetie.
You need a little change?
(sniffs)
Oh, yeah.
I'll let you in
on a little secret.
Before this day is over,
I might need to change
my undies, too.
(cell phone ringtone)
Uh-oh, it's your mommy again.
Shh.
Hello?
Oh, hey, Judith, what's up?
So, how's Laguna?
Laguna's fine.
Um, listen, my mother's
not answering the phone
so I need you to go check
on her and the baby.
Me?
You, uh, you want me to drive
all the way to Sherman Oaks
to check on your mother who you
assured me was clean and sober?
(baby crying)
What's that?
Uh, uh, that is the...
is the TV that I am watching.
The... Baby Channel.
A... uh, uh... documentary
about obese babies.
Tragic.
Okay, listen, I-I will check up
on your mother for you
but, uh, you owe me one.
(sing-song):
Oh, Alan...
Ta-da!
Not bad.
What's not bad?
Uh, I mean, it's not a bad idea
for me to check up on her.
Thank you. Call me
when you get there.
(sing-song)
Oh, Judith...
Look who mowed
the front lawn.
♪ Men.
So, we're agreed.
We will never speak
of this again.
Well, that kind of
depends on you, doesn't it?
I've already got
the shovel, Jake.
I can dig another hole.
CHELSEA:
Charlie, I'm home!
Hi, sweetie,
how was work?
Okay.
I was a little worried
about Sir Lancelot.
Have you seen him?
No, haven't seen
him, not a trace.
What about you, Jake?
No, but if I was a cat I'd
probably be on the beach.
'Cause, you know, the beach
is one big litter box
and the ocean is
a giant fish bowl.
Kind of like having
a sushi bar in your bathroom.
Wow, how great
would that be?
I guess.
I'll still feel better
when he comes back.
We all will.
You're quite the little
liar, aren't you?
I'm 15. My life depends on it.
Chelsea, Uncle Charlie's
gonna take me driving.
Can we bring you
back anything?
♪ Men.
That woman just cut you off!
Learn how to drive, you whore!
Yeah, I'm talking to you!
Lenore, ooh, Lenore...
Lenore, Lenore, we should
probably keep it down.
We don't want to
wake the baby.
What baby?
Oh, right.
Woof.
(cell phone ringtone)
Ugh.
Hello, Judith.
Yeah, I was just
about to call you.
Uh, the baby's fine,
nothing to worry about.
Hey, Judy, Judy, Judy!
Uh... yeah,
yeah, that's her.
Uh-huh, blotto.
Uh, no, no.
No, no need to rush home,
everything's under control.
We're in the car, Millie's
sleeping in the back seat
and we're heading for Malibu.
Ehab-ray.
Ehab-ray?
You said you were taking me
for crabcakes at Gladstone's.
Well, I'm sorry, but you
just don't have a choice here.
The hell I don't.
Lenore? Lenore? Lenore!
Red light.
Slow down, slow down, stop!
(brakes screeching)
You're making me really
nervous, you know that?
♪ Men.
(TV playing)
Hey, you mind getting me
another grape soda?
Yeah, I mind.
Get it yourself.
Fine. I just have to send this
jpeg to Chelsea real fast.
(sighing)
Okay, okay.
Look who finally came home!
Who?
Sir Lancelot.
You've been a bad kitty cat.
I've been so
worried about you.
Okay, I'm confused.
If that's Sir Lancelot,
then what did we squash?
Your hope of ever getting behind
the wheel of my car again.
Oh, man.
Leverage is a fickle bitch,
my friend.
(doorbell ringing)
CHELSEA:
I got it!
Can I help you?
Sorry to bother you.
I live down the beach
and I'm looking for my cat.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I haven't seen it.
In fact, I just found
my little guy.
I'm really worried.
He's black and white,
about yay big.
Answers to Puss-Puss.
CHELSEA: I'll keep
an eye out for him.
Looks like the
fickle bitch is back.