I was forced to use my hands
to defend a lady's honor.
So I don't have
to go back to jail?
You won't even see
the inside of a courtroom.
You know, we're having
a nature ride
and barbecue
for the kids
this Saturday.
You should come.
That sounds wonderful,
doesn't it, Charlie?
You let her go
without you?
Why the hell
would I want to go?
Maybe you didn't notice the way
my lawyer was looking
at your fiancée.
What are you talking about?
Or the way she was
looking back at him.
Charlie, that guy is
everything you're not.
♪ Men. ♪
Where the hell is she, Alan?
Calm down; don't work
yourself into a tizzy.
A tizzy?
I don't have tizzies.
Women have tizzies.
You have tizzies.
Me, I am outraged,
I am furious, I am, I am...
Miffed?
Do not complete my sentences
if you don't grasp the concept.
Sorry.
She should've been home
hours ago.
I'm sure there's a perfectly
good explanation.
Oh, really?
And what would that be?
Okay, well, after
the barbecue ended,
Chelsea stayed behind
to help clean up.
And then she and Brad
got to talking
about all the things
they have in common.
You know, their love
of horses, children...
Probably just
lost track of time.
Because, you know,
he's so easy to talk to.
Not to mention how...
good-looking he is.
Or she got diarrhea.
Oh, maybe she called.
Oh, look, there's
two messages.
WOMAN: Hi. I'm calling
for Alan Harper.
This is Jenny from
Malibu Day Spa.
I just wanted to confirm
your Saturday appointment
for a bikini wax.
Bikini wax?
Uh, I wear a European-cut
bathing suit.
I like to keep it
tidy down there.
Anyway, I'm sure the
next one is Chelsea.
Hi, Mr. Harper.
This is Jenny again.
Just a reminder—
we can no longer accept
a personal check from you...
I should've just gone with her
to that stupid charity thing.
True. If you'd made
a little effort,
you wouldn't be in
this situation.
But I bet she knew
I wouldn't go
when she asked me.
In fact, I bet she was
counting on me not going,
so she could be alone
with this Brad guy.
Do you really think Chelsea
would do something like that?
Why not? That's what I'd do.
I mean, hypothetically.
If I were ever
in that situation.
Again.
Right.
The point is, I've been honest
through this whole thing.
She's the one who's
been deceitful.
She's nothing but
a manipulative,
calculating,
two-faced...
Hey, honey.
(sweetly):
Oh, hi, baby.
How was the party?
It was great.
There was, like, 80 kids
taking turns riding a horse
for the first time
in their lives.
So, what, there was
just one horse?
No.
Good, 'cause that
would've been
a tough day for the horse.
Sorry I'm late, but after we
got the kids back on the busses,
a bunch of us hung out
to chat and help clean up.
Yeah, yeah, that's
what I figured.
Anyway, I'm beat.
I just want to jump in
the shower and go to bed.
Okay, I'll be right up.
Night, Alan.
Night.
Glad you had a good time.
Well done.
You sublimated your anger and
came from a place of love.
You took the high road.
Really?
Is that what you call it?
'Cause I call it a
complete and total betrayal
of my testicles.
If you'd done it
as much as I had,
you'd call it the high road.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Chels?
So, when you say a bunch
of you stayed to clean up,
how many are you
talking about?
I don't know;
a couple.
Uh-huh.
You know, technically,
a couple is two.
So are you saying
there were two people
in addition to you and Brad
or just you and Brad?
What are you getting at?
Nothing. Just trying to get
an accurate head count.
You could've come with me,
you know.
I know.
It'd be nice for us
to do some things together
once in a while.
We do plenty of
things together.
Besides sex.
Oh...
When Brad's wife was alive,
they played tennis every day.
Probably what killed her.
She was hit by a car.
Maybe she was chasing
a tennis ball.
You know, like a dog.
You throw it,
they run after it,
even if there's traffic...
Goofy dogs.
♪ Men. ♪
(crowd cheering)
What the hell is that?
Two guys in a cage beating
the snot out of each other.
I can't believe I wasted
so many years watching cartoons.
Turn it down.
Aye, aye, Captain Douche.
What did you say?
Aye, aye, Captain.
I'll do that.
Why are you on the couch?
You and Chelsea have a fight?
No, we didn't have a fight.
Were you farting in your sleep?
No.
Did you screw up the sex?
What the hell are
you talking about?
You know, there's more
than one way to satisfy a woman.
Oh, really? Like what?
I'm not sure.
But I have some theories.
Get out!
Fine.
We wouldn't have these problems
if you just put a TV in my room.
if I just put
a python in your room.
Touché, douché.
What?
I said touché, douché.
BERTA:
♪ I really can't stay
(in deep voice):
♪ Baby, it's cold outside
(normal voice):
♪ I've got to go away
(deep voice):
♪ Baby, it's cold outside...
You mind?
I'm trying to sleep.
Hey, I didn't see you there.
What'd you do?
I don't want to talk about it.
Fine. I'm not one to pry.
Money?
No.
Old girlfriend?
She find those Polaroids?
No.
How did you know
about the Polaroids?
You just told me, you dirtbag.
So, what did you do,
try to sneak in at 2:00 a.m.
smellin' of booze
and pole dancer?
For your information, Chelsea's
the one who came home late.
And she was smelling of horse.
Oh, good Lord, Charlie,
you can't compete with a horse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Seriously.
I've seen your tallywacker,
and you're blessed, but
you ain't no Seabiscuit.
When have you seen my...
tallywacker?
I don't know, maybe the nine or
ten times I found you passed out
in your bathtub, holding onto it
like it was a flotation device.
Sorry about that.
Don't be.
Mmm, boy!
Breakfast,
the most important meal
of the day.
Three scrambled egg whites,
two slices of "I can't believe
it's not buttered" rye toast
and to flush it through me,
a piping hot cup
of freshly ground coffee.
(coffee grinder whirring)
Shut that thing off!
(whirring resumes)
(crashing)
So... decaf?
Don't push me.
I'm not in the mood.
Did you sleep
on the couch last night?
What's it to ya?
Oh, Charlie, what'd you do?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I may have compared Brad's
recently deceased wife
to a ball-chasing dog.
Whose balls?
Tennis balls.
Get your mind out of the gutter.
All right, look— while this is
admittedly a bump in the road,
you do have an opportunity here
to really improve your
relationship with Chelsea.
How do you figure?
Well, think about it—
the reason you're
threatened by Brad
is because he's a much
better man than you.
No, he's not.
I would never come on
to another guy's fiancée.
Okay, first of all,
we don't know
that he's come on to Chelsea.
And secondly, I've seen you
hit on a bride
while she was walking down
the aisle.
That was a joke.
I asked her what
she was doing later.
Everybody laughed.
My point is, if Chelsea is
looking around for a better guy,
why not make that guy you?
Because I'm not
a better guy than me.
Not yet.
But you do have something
going for you that Brad doesn't.
What's that?
Room to improve.
Lots and lots of
room to improve.
Thanks. You've filled
me with optimism.
And keep in mind, you're
the underdog here,
and everybody loves an underdog.
Then how come
nobody loves you?
The principle is still sound.
Just go up there and
tell Chelsea you know
that you're a
flawed human being,
but that you will spend the rest
of your life trying to be better
because she deserves the best.
So, lie.
You don't have to lie.
Don't you think
you're a flawed human being?
Of course I do.
But I know me.
I'm not gonna spend the rest
of my life doing anything,
let alone try to be
a better human being.
Oh, come on, Charlie.
Look at every New Year's
resolution I've ever made.
I've got the best of intentions,
but by January third or fourth,
there I am broke, hung over, and
coughing up stripper glitter.
Okay, lie.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey Chels... I brought
you some orange juice.
Thank you.
Is there any coffee?
No, no, my stupid brother
broke the grinder.
There's vodka
in this orange juice.
Whoopsie, that's mine.
It's 8:00 in the morning.
Hence the orange juice.
So, listen, I wanted
to apologize again
about my unfortunate
remarks last night.
And tell you I love you and
I'll spend the rest of my life
trying to be a better man
because you deserve the best.
Well, I appreciate
you saying that.
So... we're good?
Yeah.
Great.
So what do you want
to do today?
Your choice— whatever
makes you happy.
Really?
I'll go anywhere,
I'll do anything.
Of course, you'll
have to drive.
Well, I was thinking
of going to Beverly Hills
for this charity blood drive.
Great.
We'll give blood together.
than tapping a vein
for a good cause.
Terrific.
Brad will be happy to see us.
Brad?
It's his charity.
He's got another charity?
What the hell's
this guy's problem?
It's not a problem, Charlie.
He's a very caring
and compassionate man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
he's a freakin' saint.
And you were already
planning on seeing him again.
Well, yeah. He told me
about the blood drive
last night.
Right, right, while you were
"cleaning up."
What's "this"?
Oh, I think you know
what "this" is.
Just go to hell!
Hey, hey-hey,
I'm not the one sneakin' around
seeing somebody
behind my fiancé's back!
I am not sneaking around!
I asked you
to go with me!
Figuring that I wouldn't.
Very sneaky!
Drop dead!
(grinder whirrs, revving up)
Fixed it.
♪ Men. ♪
So...
when are you gonna call Chelsea
and tell her you're sorry?
Okay, first of all, I have
nothing to be sorry about.
And second, I am not gonna
discuss my personal life
with someone whose current
girlfriend is a gym sock.
Wow, no wonder she left.
You just lash out for no reason.
EVELYN:
Hello?
Out here!
That's my reason.
Boo-hoo.
When you gonna stop
blaming your problems
on your mommy?
Hey, boys.
Charlie, where's your
bride-to-be?
We were gonna finalize
the guest list.
She's not here.
She told him to go to hell.
Will you please shut up?
Oh, Charles, what did you do?
I didn't do anything!
He slept on the couch
last night.
Nobody's talking to you!
And this is what
we've been living with.
Stop heating your socks in the
microwave, you little freak!
Charlie, please don't
let this girl get away.
Don't worry, I won't.
Good, 'cause she's
one in a million
and you're a dime
a dozen.
Yeah, but I'm the underdog, and
everybody loves the underdog.
Oh, God, now you sound
like your brother.
How do you plan
on getting her back?
I'm gonna become a better man.
Great, so no
plan at all.
♪ Men. ♪
REPORTER:
like Santee, California,
maybe Long Beach, California,
could actually top out around 90
before it's all said
and done.
What's the forecast?
(slurring):
High tonight, low tomorrow.
A hundred-percent chance
of hangover.
Heard from Chelsea?
She's staying with her
father for a few days.
At least that's what
she e-mailed me.
You don't think
she could be with...
Go ahead, say it.
Braa-ad!
You know what?
If she is, fine.
Good riddance.
I was never meant to be tied
down to one woman, anyway.
Well, you are by nature
a free spirit.
(sobbing):
I miss her, Alan!
I can't live without her!
And you don't have to.
Remember our talk?
Becoming a better man?
Screw it!
I'm as good
as I'm ever gonna be!
If she doesn't like it,
the hell with her!
That is true.
In a healthy relationship,
your partner needs to
accept you for who you are.
(sobbing): Oh, she deserves
better than me, Alan!
She's such a wonderful gal!
I know, I know.
She's-she's
like an angel!
She... She sure is.
Then why is she running off
with Braa-ad?
We don't know that she's
running off with anyone.
This is not
angel behavior, Alan.
You know what
kind of behavior this is?
Charlie behavior.
(wailing): I took an angel
and I turned her into me!
♪ Men. ♪
Charlie...?
I can't sleep in my bed.
It smells like Chelsea.
O-Okay. Well...
why don't you stay here
and I'll go sleep in your room.
No, no, no, don't go.
I don't wanna be alone.
All right.
You're wearing
pajama bottoms, right?
Shh...
Exactly how drunk are you?
Both questions...
asked and answered.
♪ Men. ♪
(phone rings)
(curtly):
What?
Oh, hi, Chelsea.
No... no, he's up.
Or not.
Hang on. I'll find him.
Charlie?
Found him. Hold on.
Hey, Charlie?
What?
You got a phone call.
I'll call back.
It's your fiancée.
(brightly):
Oh, hey, baby.
No, no, I've been up
for a while.
So how are ya?
Uh-huh.
What's going on?
Man, you'll do anything
not to kick in a little rent,
won't ya?
Are you coming home?
I really miss you.
Uh, sure, I can meet you
for coffee, no problem.
Half hour?
No problem. See ya.
(groans)
Problem?
What the hell
are you doing here?
♪ Men. ♪
Hi, sweetie.
Sorry I'm late.
I got you some coffee.
Thank you.
(gulping)
Isn't that awfully hot?
Scalding!
(raspy cough)
Whew...
So, what's new?
We need to talk about Brad.
No, no, we don't.
I'm sorry.
I trust you, and I was totally
and completely wrong
to think there might be
something going on
between you two.
Thank you for that.
You're welcome.
Okay, let's go home.
Hold on. I do have
a confession to make.
Oh, this is never good.
The reason I got so upset
by the things you said
was because,
well, you kind of
touched a nerve.
Yeah, I do that.
I'm a nerve toucher.
Runs in the family.
Okay, well, confession's over.
And you forgive me,
I forgive you.
Let's go home.
I'm not done.
Aw, crap.
The thing is, I was kind
of attracted to Brad.
He's a great guy and we have
a lot in common.
He loves his family
and he really cares
about his friends
and his community.
I'm taking from your tone
that stuff's important to you.
Yes, Charlie,
it's important to me.
Okay.
Did you and Brad do anything
other than talk?
Of course not.
Nothing's happened.
Oh, thank God.
But while I do love you,
I need to know
you care as much as I do.
I do.
You say that,
but are you willing
to really work
on our relationship?
Of course I am.
We can start doing things
together; community things.
You know, with the-the-the...
the kids that are poor
and the old people that fall
and can't get up.
What about your family?
I'll get a new family.
Look, I'm telling you,
I can change.
(gagging): I can be a better
man; the man you want me to be.
(gagging intensifies):
And I promise you...
Excuse me.
(vomits)
Oh, my God!
I am so, so sorry.
You threw up on my baby!
(baby crying)
Anyway, to be fair, I don't
think the carrots were mine.
Get away from him,
you pig!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cute kid.
(baby crying)
Chels?
(sighs)
Damn.
♪ Men. ♪
I just got a call
from Chelsea.
Oh, yeah?
She said she wants
to postpone the wedding.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Believe it or not,
I do love you,
and I hate to see you hurt.
Yeah, well... I guess
I kinda had it coming.
But you tried.
I did.
I just have
one question.
What's that?
Did you really vomit
on a baby?
Don't beat yourself up
too much.
We've all done that.
You're kidding.
Of course... most of us do it
on our own babies.