And the same thing goes for quarterly
reports. They are unreadable.
They're just numbers
and boring and...
Blech!
So what I was thinking is that maybe
we should have some sort of graphic,
like if we have a bad quarter,
put in a storm cloud.
And when we have
a good quarter,
fireworks or a racecar.
Doesn't have to be a racecar.
Use your imagination.
There's this cube on the screen,
and it bounces around all day,
and sometimes it looks like it's heading
right into the corner of the screen,
and then at the last minute, it
hits a wall and bounces away.
We are all just dying to see
it go right into the corner.
Pam claims that she saw it one day when
she was alone in the conference room.
Okay. I believe she
thinks she saw it.
I saw it. I saw it,
and it was amazing.
Who said I didn't see it? Did
Jim say that I didn't see it?
I saw it.
We have a lot
of colored paper here.
Why, oh, why do we keep
printing this on white?
No! Come on!
Yeah! I know.
I know.
It's bland.
It's never going
to happen.
Dude, you gotta believe.
Maybe we could have
some sort of riddle?
Wait for it.
Like something that you have to
look for, sort of a Where's Waldo?
All right. All right.
Let's quit while we're ahead.
That was so awesome.
That was awesome.
Thank you.
Some days I am just on fire.
What can I say?
Hey. There he is.
Hey, Meredith.
How are you feeling?
I never thanked you
for coming to the hospital.
Oh, please. It was my pleasure.
Well, we all came, so...
Well, I really appreciate
you coming.
I'm singling you out.
Anyway, I have
this Sharpie,
and I was wondering
if you could sign my cast.
Mmm-hmm.
Can you write
where I can read it?
Oh, yeah.
I'll read this
when I get home.
All right.
Michael, this is the press
release I was telling you about.
Ryan wants you to
share it with everyone.
Does he?
He does.
Okay. Attention.
Earthlings,
I have some news.
Beep, beep, beep.
Beep, beep, beep. Okay.
Today is the big day that I'm heading
to New York to attend a party
with sushi and
important people.
On an unrelated note, if anybody
has an interesting anecdote
that is not boring
and easy to memorize,
please drop by my office before I leave.
Thank you.
Is that really what Ryan
wanted you to tell us?
And today, the Dunder Mifflin
Infinity website officially launches.
Well, the website is the
brainchild of my brainchild, Ryan.
It is my brain-grandchild.
And to celebrate its birth,
all of the different branches are
going to have satellite parties,
which will be connected,
via webcams and fibers,
to the real party, which is
going on in New York City
at a very
exclusive nightclub.
That is where
all of the VIPs,
including yours truly, will be
partying with New York City's finest.
And I do not
mean policemen.
The company is projecting
record high sales,
and that by 6:00, the website will be
the new best salesman in the company.
Wow. Watch out, Dwight.
That's ridiculous. I'm not
gonna be beaten by a website.
Actually it sounds
like you are.
Really?
'Cause Ryan says so?
That's from Ryan? Does it
mention if he's seeing anybody?
No, it doesn't.
I'll find out tonight.
Yes, please let us know.
I can make more
sales than a computer.
In fact, I challenge that website
to make more sales than me today.
Waste of time.
What's that, pipsqueak?
Waste of time. The
website's going to win.
You believe a computer
can beat me?
I don't care,
but yes.
Well, I will
prove you wrong.
I don't care, and you won't.
You'll see.
I won't be watching,
and I won't.
Dwight mercy-killed
Angela's cat.
It's very complicated.
It's caused a lot of unpleasantness
between Dwight and Angela,
who were both already
prone to unpleasantness.
Stanley,
you're dancing.
No, I'm not.
Yeah, I created a website.
Look, at the end of the day, Apple's
apple is flying at 30,000 feet.
This is a paper company,
and I don't want us to get lost in
the weeds or into a beauty contest.
I told you I don't want you
doing these things in here.
You can use your own office
or do it in the hall.
Convergence, viral marketing,
we're going guerilla,
we're taking it
the streets,
while keeping an eye on
the street, Wall Street.
I don't want to reinvent
the wheel here.
In other words,
it is what it is.
Buying paper
just became fun.
And this is where
I will record your sales.
Very nice, very nice.
And then I will say something
positive like, "Kudos,"
or, "Job well done."
Or, "Zip-a-dee-doo-dah!"
I can't tell
if he's mocking me.
Just ignore him.
I can't do that. It's really
hard for me to let things go.
I was mocking.
Thank you.
I just feel like we need something more
to acknowledge when I make a sale.
Yes! Like a chime
or a bell.
Or a gong.
Go to my car, open the trunk,
inside you will see many pelts.
Under the smallest one is a case.
Inside that case is a bear horn.
Bring it to me.
Yes!
Isn't 7:00 p.m. A little
late for a lunch party?
Lunch party? It's supposed
to say "Launch Party."
What is wrong with you?
Angela is worse than usual lately,
and we have a party to throw,
so I googled, "How to deal
with difficult people."
And I got all of this.
So we're gonna try out
some new things today.
So, how do you feel about the fact
that the banner says "Lunch"?
I feel angry. Angry at you. Angry
at you for doing something stupid.
Angry at me for believing you
could do something not stupid.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
That must be awful.
It is awful. You've
made this day awful.
Maybe you could just
change the U into an A.
Then it would say
"Lanch Party," Kevin.
Would it really be better
if it said "Lanch Party"?
Lunch party.
It's supposed
to say "Launch."
Okay, wow, easy,
booster seat.
Nobody cares about
this party anyway.
I care.
"Plan a party, Angela. Oh, and
the entire world will see it.
"Oh, and here's $65
for your budget.
"Oh, and here are four idiots who
will do nothing but weigh you down.
"Oh, and your
cat's still dead."
Twenty seconds
to go-time.
Got it. Carb up.
Really? Power Gel?
Hey, if you want to win,
you got to fuel like a winner.
Okay, we start.
As soon as
I make this shot.
Hey! Go!
Yeah!
Hello, Susan.
Dwight Schrute.
What would you say if I told you
we could pull a prank on Dwight,
at the same time,
not be working?
What? He's going
through a breakup.
Yeah. I'm aware of that, but
he's also being super-annoying,
and I'm not
a perfect person.
Yeah! Yeah!
Got one!
Three reams! In your
face, machines!
What kind of prank
are you thinking?
What if I told you
I could offer free shipping?
Sure, I'll hold.
Not sure.
Just became self-aware.
So much to figure out.
I think I am programmed
to be your enemy.
I think it is my job to destroy you
when it comes to selling paper.
It appears that the
website has become alive.
This happens to computers
and robots sometimes.
Am I scared of a
stupid computer?
Please, that computer
should be scared of me.
I have been salesman of the month
for 13 out of the last 12 months.
You heard me right.
I did so well last F'ebruary,
that corporate gave me two
plaques in lieu of a pay raise.
Okay.
Yes, it's too tight.
Way too tight.
Really?
This is why
I'm here?
Why is it so tight?
It's a European cut.
It just looks bad.
Um...
Hey, what's hanging?
Setting up the webcam
for the party.
Good, okay, cool.
How many pounds do you
think I can lose by 7:00?
Depends. How much have
you eaten already today?
I had one of those big...
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Pam.
Just one second. We're in a meeting.
I'll see if he's available.
It's Jan.
Why don't you want
to go tonight? What...
All your friends are going to be there...
My friends?
It'll be fun. Michael,
I was terminated.
Just...
Is it really that
important to you?
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you.
Go by yourself.
No. No.
No. If I go by myself, everybody
will think I'm a big loser.
Well... Do I have your
permission to invite Carole?
What? Jeez, Michael!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It's just the first
girl that popped into my head.
I'll find somebody
that I haven't slept with.
Nice.
Website check, please.
305.
305. You, my friend,
are winning handsomely.
It just made
another sale. 380.
You, my friend, are in
a very close second.
402.
Okay, why don't you
just lay off, lady?
What do you want me to do?
Not announce it? 412.
So, this is the dealio.
God has smiled upon me
and given me two tickets to the
big party in New York, tonight.
What are you doing
this evening?
Look at that.
They have their own little
language now, like twins.
Sure, we'll go.
All right. Well, fight it
out amongst yourselves.
I was thinking Pammy,
but boys' night out
is also good.
I'm sorry. What?
One of the tickets
is for him.
Just let me know
who the winner is.
Not it.
Not it. No!
I won.
Definitely not.
If anything it was a tie.
Tie goes
to the girlfriend.
No, I realize you normally reorder in
November, but what I'm suggesting...
You did what?
No. That's exactly what you're
not supposed to do, damn it!
Why would you reorder
from a computer
when you could have the
personal touch of a salesman?
How's it going?
F'ine. Good.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You look
a little worried.
I do not look worried.
"Here's a suggestion,
computer.
"I assume you read binary, so
why don't you zero, one, one,
"one, one, one, zero, one,
one, zero, one, one?"
Okay.
While you were typing that, I
searched every database in existence
and learned every fact about
everything and mastered the violin.
And sold more paper.
I asked for assorted cutlery,
and I got back spoons.
These are worthless.
I want to understand
what you're saying,
but it's difficult for me
when you use that tone.
Phyllis, these are spoons.
Spoons have rounded tops
and are used to scoop things.
What we need are forks,
which have prongs
or tiny spears on top.
And we need knives,
which have blades.
Do you understand me now?
Yes.
Goodie.
Hey, man.
What's up, man?
What's going on?
Paper delivery.
Oh, yeah?
Kelly ordered this online.
What are you doing?
I am in the fight of my
life against this computer,
and every sale counts.
But you get to put the paper in this
little shopping cart and then it says,
"Thanks for shopping
with Dunder Mifflin."
Damn it, Kelly! It knows!
It knows what you did!
Who knows?
Return it!
Return it now!
Hey.
How about instead of yelling at
our sweet little Miss Kapour
over 500 sheets of paper,
you get back to your desk
and start selling multiple
reams like a man.
You don't understand.
Okay, if this makes
the difference,
I'm going to tell it
that you were responsible.
Who's "it"?
There you go.
Thanks.
So, you still
missing Ryan?
Not so much anymore.
I am not a bad person.
When I left Staples, I took
some of their leads with me,
but I never intended
to use them.
What did I intend
to do with them?
Who knows? Maybe keep
them as a souvenir,
maybe use them.
Yes, Mr. Galioto, how would you
like to pay 10%% less for paper
than you're
paying right now?
It's not important how I
got your information.
What is important
is that you say yes. Good.
All right, I'm ready to go,
and I'm calling shotgun.
I'm driving?
Yes.
Thank you.
All right. Let me just
say goodbye to Pam.
Oh, yeah. You better say goodbye to Pam.
Say goodbye to Pam.
Bye.
I love you.
I love you. Okay.
I'm leaving
inside Jim's car
I don't know
when I'll be back again
Yes, I do,
tomorrow I'll be back
I'll be back tomorrow.
Yeah, so you know what? Why don't you
guys take off a little bit early tonight?
Because there's a party.
A party for the website I've
been planning for two weeks.
If you are not this tall, you
may not ride the rollercoaster.
See you guys tomorrow.
Perfect. So let me just get some
basic information from you.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. Yes.
Could you repeat that?
Yes! Ten reams for the
U.S. District Court!
Did I happen to mention the 40 reams
for the Battered Women's Shelter?
No!
Stop it. Give me that. Give it.
Did you see the board?
There's still an hour.
You ever read this?
Yeah. A long time
ago, but I liked it.
I got it for Ryan.
I wanted to get him
Oh, the Places You'll Go!
But they were sold out.
I figured it's the same
sort of stuff in here.
It's not. It's different.
It's a good book.
What was that?
Leaving Pennsylvania.
Two kisses.
One for me.
One for Jan.
Gotcha.
You guys should come over
for dinner, you and Pam.
That would be fun. F'riday?
That would be fun.
Want to come over F'riday?
Can't.
After work, you...
Oh, no, 'cause...
You're gonna let me know
when we're close, right?
Yes. Actually, I will
tell you right now.
It's a club called Chat Room, and
there's a password to get in,
which is actually
"Password," so...
Okay.
What are you doing?
That is an invitation
to an online party.
No. No.
I'm sure that's not.
Are there three "W's" at the
beginning of the address?
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, the invitation says VIPs only.
Is this how you treat your VIPs, Ryan?
We're already
in the city.
The main part, with the buildings.
What am I supposed to do?
What do you want me
to do tonight?
And if you tell me
that I have to drive back to
Scranton to the satellite party,
I am going to throw up.
Okay, I am going
to throw up.
I'm throwing up. You're
making me throw up, Ryan.
You know what this is like? I'll
tell you what this is like.
This is like when the
freshmen would throw a party
and wouldn't let
any of the seniors go.
Doesn't it just piss you off sometimes that
little twerp got the promotion over us?
Actually, I withdrew
from consideration.
Yeah. I withdrew too.
F'our, three, two, one!
Yes!
After numerous projections
that the computer
would crush all
salesmen in its path,
I am very happy to report that
our very own Dwight Schrute
has crushed his electronic
nemesis, if you will,
by a whopping 52 reams.
Reams.
- Wait, say it again.
- Announce it again.
F'ifty-two reams!
No, no.
No, the first part.
Dwight has
defeated the computer.
Hey, so,
what do you think?
I did it for you.
I didn't ask you
to do it for me.
You didn't have to.
How do you tell
someone it's over?
You send them a notarized letter, right?
Well, what if the recipient is your notary?
Hello, Pam.
Hello.
Hey,
do you have any men that
you can fix me up with?
I would like to have
a relationship with a man.
I'll get back to you.
Let me know.
All right,
who wants to party?
Why aren't you
in New York?
What?
I think I faked
Oscar out.
You said you weren't coming
back and we could leave early.
I think I faked
Stanley out, too.
Who else thought that I was leaving
and that you could all go home early?
Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
Well, who needs New York?
Right? We can have a killer
party right here in Scranton.
Thank you.
No, no, no. This is going to be nothing
like the party you've been planning.
This is going to be good,
and everybody's gonna come.
What's wrong with Dwight?
He beat the computer.
Hey, good for you. Good for you!
Scranton power.
All right, you know what?
Angela, I'd like you to come
into my office in 10 minutes.
Bring something to write with
and something to write on.
Good!
It was a pretty
disappointing day.
It was kind of a slap
in the face to realize that
I wasn't as important
as I thought I was
to a certain young executive
who I'd cared about.
But, you know,
I'm not gonna cry over it.
I did that in the car
on the way home.
How are we
doing on time?
The party starts
in an hour.
Good. These are some things that
I would like to have happen.
"Beer, light beer,
streamers, orchids,
"better lighting,
something made of ice"?
Those are just things.
This is how I want it to feel.
"Pizza, pizza with mushrooms, pizza
without mushrooms, white pizza, steak"?
I would like this
party to be sexier,
cooler, more important...
"Chocolates,
someone famous"?
Yes.
"Cool music,
"confetti,
go-go dancers"?
I want it to embarrass
all other parties.
I want it to be a party
that the guys in New York
watch on the webcam and say, "Wow,
how did they get Al Roker to come?"
I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
I can't do it.
I know you can.
I wouldn't say that if
I didn't 100%% believe it.
Who else could do this?
Okay. Okay.
No, seriously, is there anyone
else who could do it better?
Because we don't
have a lot of time.
I'll get the pizza!
What do you
think of Angela?
I think she's efficient.
No, not like that.
As a woman.
W-O-M-A-N.
I hadn't noticed.
You hadn't noticed
she's a woman?
I hear she's single
and ready to mingle.
I'm thinking about
making a play for her.
What do you think?
Crazy, right?
I think it's inappropriate to
date someone you work with.
Isn't that
part of the fun?
No. I think you
should date Kelly.
She works here, too.
How is that any different?
She works in the annex.
You're also welcome
to date Toby.
Okay.
Good news!
We get to go home?
Guess who just ordered from your
favorite pizza place, Alfredo.
Wait.
Alfredo's Pizza Cafe?
Or Pizza By Alfredo?
Same thing.
No. No, it's not.
All right. You know what?
I don't understand
when you all talk
at the same time.
Oscar, talk to him.
Michael, there's a very big difference
between these two pizza places,
both in quality of ingredients
and in overall taste.
Which one did you
order from?
Pizza By Alfredo.
All right, you know what?
Okay, okay, what is better?
A medium amount of good pizza or all
you can eat of pretty good pizza?
Medium amount of good pizza.
Oh, no, it's bad.
It's real bad.
It's like eating
a hot circle of garbage.
You can pick
one of these things.
It's unreasonable for you to
ask me to do all of this.
It should take you no time at all if you
put the care into it that you normally do.
Ow!
That seemed
to shut her up.
You looking for
dinner and a movie?
'Cause you're not gonna
find it in that box.
It just so happens, I know where
you can find it, but again,
not in the box.
Angela, are you hearing
words that I'm saying?
What?
Hello.
I have been working
on a party for three weeks
that just got thrown
out the window,
so now I have to pull
together a whole new party,
and my useless
number two quit.
So now there's no one
in charge of orchids,
chocolates or the thing
that's made of ice.
And my upper back itches,
and it's itched all day,
and I can't reach it. And Kevin
had Greek food for lunch again!
They say you should never mix
business with pleasure.
Really?
Well, then explain to me how a
putt-putt golf company operates.
Yeah?
The Pizza By Alfredo
guy is here.
You don't have
to say it like that.
I said it normal.
Hey.
$63.50, and that's
not including tip.
Right.
I have a coupon,
so half of $63.50 and
half the tip on $63.50...
Half-off coupons only apply
to orders of two pizzas.
Yeah, no, I told them on the phone
I was ordering eight pizzas.
I don't care what you
told them on the phone.
That's our policy.
You didn't actually think that I was
going to spend 60 bucks on pizza?
It's not pizza.
Okay.
It doesn't say it anywhere on the
coupon, and if it's your policy,
it should say it
on the coupon.
What do you mean?
Not my problem.
It is your problem.
That's no way to do business, okay?
I ordered
eight pizzas with
a half-off coupon,
so I would like eight pizzas for half-off.
End of story.
It's a great story. It's $63.50,
and that's not including tip.
I'm not giving that to you.
Well, then you're not
getting your pizzas.
No. No!
You're not... No!
You are not going anywhere!
You're going to stay here
until we figure this out! What?
You know what? This young man needs to learn
that that's not how you treat people!
I don't care if it's pizza!
Good business is about respect and
accountability and follow-through.
You don't just
make promises
and pull the rug out from
under somebody, do you?
Dwight, please escort this young
man into the conference room.
Right now. Get into
the conference room.
I'm not going in there. Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you are.
And you will come out when you decide
to give me a discount on the pizza.
Please. Thank you.
This is stupid.
No, you don't even
know what stupid is.
It's about to get
all stupid up in here!
You find anything?
We think it's a
straightforward kidnapping.
Stanley, could you
look up accomplices?
Why can't you guys do it?
Because we're
looking up jail time.
F'ine.
I've seen this kid before.
He's one of the kids that sneaks
onto my farm and steals my hemp.
Yeah, I know that guy. He's that
farmer that grows really crappy weed.
You ready to give me
my discount now?
No.
Okay, what have you been doing
in here this whole time?
What kind of
business is this?
We're a paper company.
The best paper company
in the whole wide world, okay?
All right, Dwight,
knock it off.
You'd better think about what
you are doing, young man.
You better think about
what you're doing.
No! I'm an adult. I don't
have to think or do anything.
You're a kid. You're a
little, snot-nosed punk kid
who thinks he's better
than everybody else,
because he's some hotshot.
And you don't know
anything about sales!
So stop being a disrespectful
little jerk, okay?
Sales?
Yes, sales. You sell pizza. Last
time I checked, that's called sales.
You're such a loser.
What did you
just call him?
A loser.
What did you say?
What?
A loser.
What was that word?
Stop getting him
to say it!
You just made this worse,
a whole lot worse.
I can make
him talk, Michael.
- Michael!
We are accomplices. I'm not
going to jail for this.
Stop talking all at once!
You need to let him go.
Let go of little jerk-boy before
he has learned his lesson?
Yes.
You know what, Jim?
The world would be a better place if people
were held accountable for their actions.
Yes, but not by
kidnapping them.
I'm not kidnapping him.
I'm keeping him
until I get what I want.
As a hostage.
I think you're
over-thinking it.
under-thinking it.
Yes.
Is Alfredo there?
May I speak to
a manager, then?
Okay, could you tell the manager
that I am keeping his delivery kid
until I get my discount on
the eight pizzas I ordered?
Yes, I know it is
not on the coupon.
Also, I would like him to
throw in two, three pizzas,
just for our...
Ransom.
trouble.
Okay. All right.
What did he say?
He said no.
So we should let him go.
No. No.
Okay.
Listen up, kid,
I don't like you,
but because some town in Switzerland
says so, you have rights.
I have to hang these.
Why are you looking
at her like that?
Hey!
What's going on?
Michael just called the pizza
place with a list of demands.
Mr. Overdramatic.
What's up, Kevin?
We're getting hungry
out there.
We're all accomplices now anyway,
so we figured we might as well eat.
We would like to order some good
pizza from Alfredo's Pizza Cafe
while we wait for the hostage
situation with the bad pizza to end.
I needed another hour. It could
have been done in another hour.
I think it looks good.
That's why you're not
in charge, Meredith.
Here you are, my dear.
One thing made of ice.
How did you...
Where'd you...
It's just ice. It'll
melt all over the floor.
Will you help me
put it over there?
Yes, I will.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I stole it.
Thank God.
Michael? Ryan wants to introduce the
branch managers in a few minutes.
You just have to wave
and introduce yourself.
I'll just wave and
introduce myself.
Hey, quick question.
Yeah?
If I take a pizza,
do you think you could take some sodas
and some napkins up to the roof?
I'm all over it.
Good.
What do we got here?
Good pizza.
Yeah?
Cheese? Or do we
have other flavors?
Different stuff.
Which one is this?
Perfect.
Do you remember what you said
to me on my first day at work,
just before you walked
me over to my desk?
Yeah.
"Enjoy this moment, because you're
never going to go back to this time
"before you met
your desk-mate, Dwight."
And that's why
I knew. You?
You came up to
my desk and you said,
"This might sound weird, and there's
no reason for me to know this,
"but that mixed-berry yogurt
you're about to eat has expired."
That was the moment that
you knew you liked me?
Yup.
Wow.
Can we make it
a different moment?
Nope.
Can I start talking?
Is this thing on? Give me a
signal when you want me to start.
And now from my old hometown, Scranton,
Pennsylvania, my former boss,
Michael Scott.
Hey, I just think
you should know
that one of my salesmen
beat your stupid computer.
So take that,
Always a jokester.
How about that image?
Crystal clear.
If anyone out there is listening, I
am being held here against my will.
I'm a minor.
Ow!
What are you doing?
You said your
upper back itched.
I didn't ask you
to scratch it.
Look, Angela, I know this is
weird because we work together,
and because up until and possibly
including now I've repulsed you,
but I like you.
I'm not dating you.
So Angela is
stubborn as a mule.
She's giving off fairly strong
vibes that she's not interested.
But do I like her or not?
Because if I like her,
then I can't back down.
If you're going number one,
you've got 10 more seconds.
Hey, have you seen Jim?
I guess he wanted to get out of
here before the cops find out.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm just scaring him.
Now the trick is to make him think
you're going to do something to him.
I can hear you, man.
Shut up,
or I'm going to
punch you in the throat!
Hey, hey, hey,
stop it. Stop it.
No. God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no. No.
I kidnapped a kid.
You had to.
What other choice
did you have?
I could have
paid for the pizza.
Well, yeah.
Oh, my God.
This is Michael.
Hello, Michael.
This is Ryan.
First off, thanks
for the shout out.
You're breaking up.
I can't hear you.
And why is there
a kid on your webcam
saying that he's
being held against his...
Okay.
I want you to go in there
and pay him for the pizzas
and give him a generous tip,
no more than 10%%.
What will you do?
I will open the door.
Yeah.
And hopefully
he will walk out.
And the rest
is out of our hands.
So I'm paying full price?
Yes.
Here we go, 65.
You know what?
Here's two more.
See you.
Drive safely.
Okay.
Now what?
Now we wait and hope
that nothing happens.
All right. I assume I'm going to
be reimbursed for the pizzas?
Not now, Dwight.
Please, not the time.
A toast.
I'm gonna make it good.
To avoiding a class-two
felony charge.
Hello? Hey.
Hang on a second.
Hello. Hang on.
If you change your mind
I'll be first in line
Honey, I'm still free
Take a chance on me
If you need me, let me know
Going to be around
If you got no place to go
If you're feeling down,
if you're all alone
When the pretty birds
have flown
Honey, I'm still free
Take a chance on me
Going to do my very best
And that ain't no lie
If you put me to the test,
if you let me try
Take a chance on me
That's all I ask of you,
Angela.
Take a chance, take a chance
On
Me
- Hey, how'd it go?
- Yeah. What did she say?
I don't know yet.
I have to call you back.
Come on,
you gotta give us something.
I'll call you back.
I have to go clean up
after the party.
What a horrible day.
Well, I need to get the horrible
taste of this pizza out of my mouth.
I'd really like some sushi.
I was hoping that I would have
New York-style sushi today,
and you know what?
What?
I'm gonna get it.
Coopers has calamari.
No. There's only one place to get
authentic New York-style sushi.
Tokyo?
New York.
Wanna go?
Yes.
All right.
You drive.
Okay.
Nice.
Here we go.
Mmm.
Perfect.
I'm sorry.
You guys are going
to have to leave.
Hey.
You know what?
Come on,
come on, let's go.
Hey, you're the
Scranton guy?
Guilty.
I liked your
statement tonight.
Thanks.
This is the guy that
beat the computer.
Very cool. Yeah, it was funny to
see Ryan all embarrassed by that.
Yeah.
See you later.
Later on.
I'm Ryan and tonight didn't go
the way that I thought it would,
because it didn't work out for
me, and I'm very embarrassed.
I have egg all over my face.
I'm 12 years old.
I spent so much time in Scranton,
but I never sold any paper.
I never sold any paper
because I'm an idiot.
I started a fire
with my cheese pita.
I dated an Indian girl.
I started a fire.
Now I've got a beard.
And I got a new suit,
and I'm your boss.
I get everything
I want 'cause I'm very...
I'm hot. I'm so hot.
That's why everybody...
I didn't get...
I don't
understand that.
That's part of it,
just a...
Wanna head back?
Yeah, let's go.