Champagne, a champagne,
a champagne
with a packet of Splenda in it.
- You know what I call this drink?
- A waste of champagne?
No. A Dr. Cooper.
Because...
He's alsosweet and bubbly.
All right.
A... a toast
to Sheldon and Amy
and the publication
of your super-asymmetry paper.
We are so proud of you guys.
- Cheers.
- Thanks.
Ooh! That is PhD-licious.
So, have you guys gotten
any feedback yet?
Well, there are
some comments online,
but we haven't read them.
We decided we don't care
what people say about our work.
- Good for you.
People online
can be so mean.
I posted a picture of myself
on Instagram,
and some jerk said I looked
so skinny I might disappear.
And yet,
somehow she soldiers on.
Mm.
Although, Amy and I did
give the world a gift.
It would be nice to read
some of the thank-you notes.
I'm surprised you're interested
in some stranger's opinion.
Well, as I always say,
a stranger's just a friend
who hasn't complimented me yet.
Okay.
- I'll read them.
- If any of them
accuse you of being too pretty,
Penny can help you through it.
Okay, here's one
from Dr. Saltzberg at UCLA.
Wait, no, stop.
I don't want to know.
What if he's mean?
Well, what if
he's complimentary?
I want to know.
Okay. He says...
I don't want to know. All right,
just...
let me see it.
Okay, this is...
this is really positive.
Wow, it's,
like, reallypositive.
He says it might be
the discovery of the decade.
He's right.
They love it!
This is so exciting.
Oh, this may be the
Dr. Cooper talking,
but pour me
another Dr. Cooper.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪ We built the pyramids♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang!♪
Hey, Penny and I
were thinking of getting
a big paintball game together.
Oh, Leonard,
why does she want
to shoot you?
She doesn't want to shoot me.
- Who doesn't want to shoot you?
- Penny.
No, that doesn't sound right.
She just wants
to play paintball.
It combines my love of whimsy
with her love
of making grown men cry.
Sounds fun.
Bernadette and I are in.
- You don't need to ask her?
- No. I've been pretty annoying lately.
She's gonna want
to shoot me.
Dr. Cooper.
Ah, President Siebert.
What are you doing
in the regular cafeteria?
You're a superstar.
No offense, worker bees.
You should join me
in my private dining room.
Dr. Fowler is already there.
Can I bring my friends?
No.
Can I bring my tater tots? Yes.
All right, let's go.
Welcome to
the inner sanctum.
Oh, I do love
a good sanctum.
Sheldon, look at my fruit plate.
It's got kiwi on it.
Ugh. I don't like kiwi.
Neither do I, but it's so fancy.
Well, this is nice.
Why have we waited
so long to do this?
Because you
never invited us.
Ha-ha-ha!
Well, the important thing
is you're here now,
and we're so excited
about your work.
This paper's going to do
big things for all of us,
so if there's anything
that you need...
You know, actually, I could use
some barbecue sauce for my tots.
Oh, wait. No. Ketchup.
Can we have some barbecue
sauce and ketchup over here?
Both?
So this is how
the other half lives.
I just want you to know
that you have our full support,
and we're organizing
a big media push.
Articles.
Interviews.
Oh, you want us
to do interviews?
Well, we're thinking
a divide-and-conquer
approach here,
where you do the interviews,
and Sheldon stays here
and holds down the fort.
You know...
in case there's an emergency.
What kind of an emergency
would there be in physics?
I don't know, maybe there's
an object in motion
that won't stay in motion.
Or a reaction
that's equal but not opposite.
It sounds like
you don't want Sheldon
to do the interviews.
It's not that we don't want
Sheldonto do the interviews,
it's just that we really
want youto do the interviews.
Without Sheldon.
Now, wait, wait,
are you trying
to exclude me?
Look, Sheldon,
you're a brilliant man,
but your people skills are...
This is not barbecue sauce!
This is steak sauce!
What are you trying to pull?
Like that.
This is ridiculous.
It is my work, too,
and I am perfectly capable
of keeping it together
for an interview.
Okay. Say somebody asks
if you feel your work
is derivative of the work
of Professor Joseph Polchinski.
Seriously, can we get
this man some barbecue sauce!
Would you mind stocking these?
Actually, I'm not
on the clock today.
I'm just hanging out
with my boyfriend.
Ah, cool. Huh.
That's me, right?
Oh, I forgot to tell you—
I broke up with you,
and now I'm
dating... that guy.
I know you're joking,
but my flight-or-flight
response doesn't.
Isn't it fight-or-flight?
Not for me.
So I told my mom
she just needed to back off.
This is our wedding,
and if anyone's gonna design
the floral arrangements,
it's going to be my man.
Thank you.
I mean, I-I'm not trying
to be a groomzilla,
but... this is my specialty.
Someone texting you?
Uh, no. It's just my,
uh, doorbell camera.
Oh. I got one of those for my
place, but I never installed it.
Oh, it's easy.
I can do it for you.
You're gonna love it.
It's how I found out
a raccoon was stealing my
cheese-of-the-month club.
What did you do?
Nothing. I didn't
want to piss it off.
It was, like, huge from
eating all the cheese.
Hey. We're doing a big
paintball game on Saturday
if you two want to join.
Oh, my roommate asked me to
help her move out on Saturday.
Ugh. That sucks.
Sucks for her.
I'm playing paintball.
I-I didn't know
your roommate was moving out.
Yeah. I've been looking
for a new one,
but... so far no luck.
You hear that?
She needs a roommate.
What do you think, Stuart?
Uh, i-i-it, uh...
Flight.
- That was hard to watch.
- Yeah.
Okay, I need you to
be honest with me.
How do I look?
A little shorter, but as we age
that happens to all of us.
Come on, help me out here.
I've got a bunch
of interviews today.
Well, no one'll notice.
They never met you before.
Sheldon, I'm nervous,
and I wish you were
coming with me.
If it helps, I wrote up
some possible questions
and answers for you.
"Whom do you love more,
"Sheldon the scientist
or Sheldon the man?
"Answer: Sheldon
the scientist,
but by such a slim margin
that it's statistically
insignificant."
Well, you really managed
to capture my voice.
Well, don't worry.
I'm sure you're gonna do great.
Thank you.
- Okay, bye.
- Wait-wait-wait.
- You forgot the cards.
- Love you, too.
Really? She asked you
to move in with her?
Yeah, she was
hinting around about it,
but I think I handled it
pretty well.
"Pretty well"?
You ran out of there so fast,
if it was a cartoon,
there would have been a
Stuart-shaped hole in the wall.
Was she mad?
Uh, no. I talked to her after.
She said she's fine.
- Oh, no. - Yikes!
- You'll find someone new.
Everything okay?
Yeah, it's just
Anu's doorbell camera.
I helped her install it.
You can't look at it.
That's spying.
Who the hell is this guy?
Ooh, let me see.
He's got... bags.
He's probably
just delivering food.
Why is she hugging him?
Maybe she doesn't
have tip money?
W-Wait, why is she
inviting him into the house?
She's a good tipper?
Do you ever feel guilty
that we get to eat
in the fancy dining room
while our friends have to
eat in the regular one?
Yes. Wait, did you say
"guilty" or "happy"?
"Guilty."
Oh, then no.
In fact, take a picture
of me with the garlic
knots to send them.
There's my MVP—
Most Valuable Physicist.
Thank you.
And my star
of NPR Science Friday
and a potpourri
of popular podcasts.
I don't know if I'd
use the word "star."
I would. I got an early look at
the interview you did for Wired,
and it is glowing.
They loved you.
That's great.
Thanks for telling me.
Congratulations, Amy.
I'm so proud of you. And that headline—
"The Neurobiologist
Who Revolutionized Physics."
I'm sorry.
The who who did what to— huh?
Oh, hey,
how did your interview go?
Okay, I guess.
You don't sound
very happy.
Oh, why wouldn't
she be happy?
She's the neurobiologist
who revolutionized physics.
Sorry.
This should be fun.
I've never played before.
Oh, fair warning— it can
get pretty ugly out there.
Okay, well, remember,
I'm your fiancée.
Oh, I remember. Do you?
All right, we need two teams.
Who wants to be the captain?
Oh, me.
Uh, sure.
Why not?
All right, why don't
you pick first?
Okay, um... Leonard.
Yeah?
No, I'm picking you.
First? For a team?
What is happening?
All right,
I take Bernadette.
Really?
You're picking her over me?
Yeah, 'cause she's vicious
and can hide behind a mushroom.
Um... Sheldon.
Raj.
Amy.
I'll take Anu.
Howard.
All rightie.
Come on, pick me, pick me.
I will take... Stuart!
Yes!
Okay, guys, we
need some people
to stay here and
guard the flag
and some people to move out
and try to capture theirs.
Okay. Sheldon,
do you want to stay here and...?
What? Hold down the fort?
'Cause that's all I'm good for.
Is that what you
were going to say?
You know
that's not what he meant.
Oh, why don't
you go out there?
Maybe you'll be
the neurobiologist
who revolutionizes
paintball.
Stop it.
You're being ridiculous.
Am I? Maybe it's just
my poor people skills.
Oh, it's definitely
your poor people skills.
All right, the choices are—
get shot at
or stay here
and listen to them fight.
Shot at.
This is pretty exciting,
sneaking around like this.
Oh, so you like sneaking around.
Good to know.
What's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing. Never mind.
Let me see
if the coast is clear.
- See anybody?
- Yes, I saw a strange man going
into your house the other night!
What?
But out there,
there's nobody.
Ow!
I'm hit.
I said I was hit!
Sorry.
Ow!
Why do you keep shooting me?
Why don't you want
to move in with me?
I-I didn't say I didn't want to.
No, you just ran away.
Stuart?
Did you run away again?
No!
Bang, you're out.
What? I'm not out.
You didn't even shoot me.
I'm not gonna shoot you
from right here.
It's too close.
It's gonna hurt.
Oh, come on. It's not
gonna hurt that bad.
I'm telling you, from
this distance it's gonna... Ow!
See? That hurt!
All right. Fine,
you can shoot me.
No, I'm not gonna shoot you.
Ow!
Ow! Ow!
Aah, you were right.
We're way too close.
See, I told you
it's gonna hurt...
Ow!
I can't believe
you're taking this out on me.
I was just trying to get
publicity for ourpaper.
By making it seem
like it was your idea?
I didn't write the headline,
Sheldon.
Did you even read the article?
Because I talk
about you continuously.
I know, and it just made you
sound modest and charming.
Why can't you just
be proud of me?
I am proud of you.
Really?
Because you sound jealous.
Well, I'm that, too.
I've seen Inside Out.
I know I can feel
two things at once.
Ow!
Well, now I feel
three things.
Hey.
Who shot you?
Oh. Uh, oh...
Denise, uh, Denise, Denise,
Denise, Denise,
Denise, Denise, Denise,
Denise, Denise
and me when I was running
from Denise.
What is up with you two?
Well, it's kind of
hard to explain. Uh,
you know when things
are going great, but you worry
that any minute
you might screw everything up?
No.
Yes.
If you really like her, you
can't let fear get in the way.
You have to move forward.
And at a certain point, the fear
of losing her goes away?
I will let you know.
- You were spying on me?
- That is not the point.
The point is who was that man?
Fine. That was
my ex-boyfriend.
Some of his stuff
was still at my house,
and he stopped by
to pick it up.
And did you give it to him?
Did you give him his stuff?
If "stuff" means
sex, then no.
If "stuff" means his
Waterpik, then yes!
I got the flag!
I'm gonna make a run for it.
Cover me!
So you're still talking
to your ex-boyfriend?
Yes, and I'm not gonna
apologize for that.
And you need to delete
that app from your phone.
Because you're hiding
something from me?
No, because you
should trust me!
How can I trust you?
I barely even know you!
Then what are we doing?
Why are we planning
a wedding?
I don't know.
Aah,
sad man!
Ow!
Ha, ha! Oh. It's you.
I can't believe you shot me!
I can't believe I did, either.
Right in the chest.
Sorry. That's gonna
leave a bruise.
Yeah, a big one.
Does it hurt?
A little.
Want to kiss it
and make it better?
I do.
Where are you going?
Home.
Don't worry. I'll wave to
the doorbell when I get there.
Wait, wait, wait.
At least let me drive you.
That's okay. I'll Uber.
We can take you.
Come on, Sheldon. Okay.
But I should warn you,
we're in a bit of a spat.
At least I think we are.
Amy, are we still in a spat?
Are you ready to apologize?
We are.
Aha! WOLOWITZ:
Hey!
Get out! Sorry. Sorry.
I didn't see anything.
Actually, could I...?
Ooh, thank you!
Hey.
Wow. That's a lot of bruises.
Yeah, well,
you shot me a lot of times.
That's not even counting
the bruises on the inside.
'Cause I hurt your feelings?
Let's hope that's all it is.
Ah, look, I'm sorry
that I freaked out.
It's just that things are
going so good with us,
and I'm afraid that if we go
too fast, I am gonna mess it up.
I get that. I don't want
to mess things up, either.
Um, I got you something.
It's a key to my place
to show you that I'm serious.
Thank you.Mm.
Well, isn't this technically
a key to Howard
and Bernadette's place?
Yes, so don't ever use it or
let them know that you have it.
Come here. Oh. Uh, no.
I appreciate it, but
seriously, this is all bruise.
Kiss?
Gently.
Ow.
I'm about to start recording.
Are you guys ready?
Sheldon, are you ready?
Absolutely. Great.
So, Dr. Cooper,
my first question is for you.
Oh, goody.
Would you say that your paper
is an extension
of the work
of Professor Joseph Polchinski?
I'll be in the car.
Captioning sponsored by CBS,
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org