It's Britney, bitch,
and I am back
in the form of
a new company,
the Michael Scott
Paper Company.
Okay.
Not going to make this one.
Love the hair.
- Morning, Michael.
- Hello.
They took away
my parking space,
but they can't
take away my pride.
I would like to invite you all to
come along with me on a journey.
Welcome
to the Michael Scott
Paper Company.
So, I thought we could
take the customer list
and...
And we could...
You realize you're not
actually talking to me, right?
And...
Hey, Kelly.
Yes, Charles,
you wanted me.
Oh. No, I meant
that Kelly.
The new receptionist
is also named Kelly.
So Kelly Kapoor has decided
to hover around my desk
so that she can run
into Charles' office
every time
he calls for Kelly.
She thinks that if she says
"You wanted me" enough,
he will, in fact,
want her.
It's not the worst plan
she's ever had.
Oh, and Kelly...
Yes, Charles,
yes, you wanted me.
Okay, I'm going
to call you Kapoor,
okay, and you Hammond.
If we're changing names, can I be Erin?
It's my middle name.
Erin? Okay,
that's very pretty.
Thanks.
Well, you know what
my middle name is?
Rajnigandha. And I hate it.
I hate it!
I thought Rajnigandha
was a boy's name.
We are in the heart of it.
And the surge of water carries
our business out to the sea.
What should we do now?
We wait and hope that people
show up to the pancake luncheon.
I don't know. I think
I have done absolutely
everything you can do
to prepare for the day.
I've updated
our contacts,
I have gotten quotes
from suppliers,
I have sent out an Evite
for our big grand opening
pancake luncheon.
Six yeses, one maybe,
only 11 nos.
And 788 not-yet-replieds,
but of that group,
782 have viewed it.
I'm going to need
800 of these
on nice bright paper.
It is a coupon for
unparalleled customer service.
I make that one copy and I become
the girl who makes copies.
And by the end of the day,
I'm receptionist again.
And the worst part is
I like making copies.
The paper comes out
all warm and stuff.
And it's cold in there, because
it's technically a closet.
What do you think?
Let me check.
No! Clearly a hunter,
who knows how to throw an
outfit together. Thank you.
Yes, I am taking Andy
hunting after work.
Not long ago we were
sexual competitors.
I used to hate him, hate
him, hate him, hate him.
I studied him to figure out
why I hated him so much.
But that blossomed into a very real
friendship, as these things often do.
You should come in town
this weekend, man. Yeah.
We'll hang out Scranton-style.
Hey.
You said you were going to
be out of town this weekend.
Please don't listen
to my phone calls.
Yeah, she's, like...
She'd probably be a six in New York, but
she's like a seven here in Scranton.
And then the boss is my old
boss from Dunder Mifflin.
It's a small space.
Hey, Jim,
can I get a, um...
Hi.
I need a rundown of your clients.
Can you get that to me?
Sure.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
What the hell
is a rundown?
When did you need
that rundown by?
Soon as possible.
Okay.
Just get it right.
Yeah, gotcha. Of course.
Really dive into
the rundown.
I'll be exhausted, because
it's like a triathlon.
Did you want
to close this?
Keep it...
You know there's a ghost
in this office.
Really? A woman was
murdered on this very floor
in 1816.
Haddy McGonigal.
She was a prostitute.
Why was she
in this building?
This whole place
used to be a brothel.
There was a tavern
on the ground floor.
That's crazy.
Yeah, isn't it?
She was bludgeoned to death by the
business end of a riding crop.
Oh, my God.
It was gruesome.
They say she walks
these hallways.
If you ever feel a tapping
on your shoulder,
that could be Haddy,
begging for her life.
And it could mean
that you're next.
Just kidding.
You finding everything okay?
Yeah. Just got some ice.
Yeah.
Erin. Erin.
Oh. This is awkward.
Uh-oh.
Oh.
Oh!
So, I'll see you
guys around.
Hey, buddy.
Hey, Ryan, could you get
to that copy from before?
Pam's better
at that stuff.
That is so insulting.
How is it insulting to say
that you're good at something?
Because the thing
you're saying I'm good at
is pushing a big green
button a bunch of times.
I'm not judging it.
It's like,
I could run GM,
but I couldn't fix a car.
It's not saying that
one's better than the other.
Seriously? Because it sounds like one
of those is better than the other.
What the hell?
Listen, listen, listen!
I need somebody to make
a copy of this,
because I don't make
copies, I'm the boss.
Got it?
I make originals.
Yeah, I make originals, too.
Shut up! Stop it, stop it!
Bickering, stop it!
Really.
Yeah.
Not much.
What's up with you?
No, it's okay,
I'm in the bathroom.
Hey, you been watching Damages this year?
It's been so good.
No, you gotta tune in. It's
as good as anything on HBO.
Hey, does blue
go with tan?
Would somebody
just make the copy?
Like a blue shirt.
I don't wear a lot of colors.
I have a lot of tan.
Uh-huh.
Just make the copy, okay?
Seriously? This is
what's so important.
Putting naked pictures
on the desktop.
That's me and my friend
Jasmine from Thailand.
I don't want to look at your
friend Jasmine's boobs all day.
You could be hot, too, if
you made any effort at all.
Like how?
Dying my hair blond?
This is from the sun.
Oh, yeah, I bet.
They're getting on my nerves, Mom.
Both of them.
R thinks he's too good
to be here
and P is not as much fun
without Jim.
Michael, we can hear you.
I'm on the phone, please.
Mom, I'm gonna have to call you back.
P's being a giant B.
Okay, it's my turn.
No, don't take that,
give that back.
Go make the copies.
Give it back for what?
What are you going
to do with it?
You're gonna make
another spreadsheet.
Yeah, exactly, it's my turn, come on!
Go make the copies, secretary.
Ryan! They always say
that it is a mistake
to hire your friends
and they are right.
So, I hired
my best friends.
And this is what I get?
Hey, buddy.
What are you up to?
Hmm. Nothing.
Listen, when I saw you
talking to Erin earlier,
I noticed that your pupils
dilated and your skin flushed,
and I'm assuming a little bit of
blood rushed into your penis.
Well, a little bit of blood rushed into
mine as well, so where does that leave us?
The last thing I want to do
is step on your funk, man.
And I yours,
so I will cede her to you.
No, that's ridiculous.
No, no, no.
Look, you've been here
longer and, besides,
I'm a better wingman
than I am a boyfriend,
so... But I just want
you and I to hang out.
You know, just...
Boom.
Listen up.
It has come to my attention
that some people
in this office
are not getting along with
other people in this office.
And I think I have come up
with the reason why.
This office space
is too small.
Definitely.
Okay.
There are four corners
in this room.
Each corner is to be a personal
space for each one of you.
Whichever corner you want,
and make it your own.
We could work from home.
Or you could fire
one of us.
Whoever has
less education.
Okay, guys,
thank you for the offers,
but I want you to get pumped
about this corner idea.
All right, one, two, three,
what are we going to do?
Corner idea.
No, you're supposed to say,
"Rock the house."
Rock the house.
How would we know that?
Hey, dude, do you know
what a rundown is?
Use it in a sentence.
Uh...
Can you get this
rundown for me?
Try another sentence.
This rundown better
be really good.
I don't know, but it sounds like
the rundown is really important.
Charles asked me to do this
rundown of all my clients.
Why don't you just
ask him what it...
No, I can't,
that was like hours ago.
What have you been doing?
Try another sentence.
Last night
was crazy.
Jojo? Yeah.
He did a doughnut in the
parking lot in front of a cop.
Then he yells, "Hey, cop,
you like doughnuts?"
And we drive off.
No, he just
stayed there.
I want that new phone.
No, the other one.
No, the other one. No, you know
which one I'm talking about.
It's the one...
No, the one with
the awesome browser.
That's my corner.
I thought that
was your corner.
No, this is where I work.
I can't relax in the
same corner where I work.
So my corner's the one
with the copier?
Pam, I don't make
the rules.
I wish my iPod
could make phone calls.
No, I don't want an iPhone.
I know what an iPhone is.
You started on that
rundown yet?
Oh, this is just something
I'm taking a break with. Oh.
I will get back to
the rundown right now.
Okay, great.
Hey, you know what?
Do you have a rundown
that I could take a look at,
just so I know what type of
rundown you're looking for?
Just keep it simple. Keeping it
simple, that's what I'm doing.
But I am working
hard on this one.
Real hard, so...
You're working hard? On this?
No, not too hard,
not harder than I should.
Right, I mean, why work
harder than you should?
No, I...
Can I help you?
No, thanks.
Hey. Hey, I'm here
to see Charles.
Okay.
Hey, Charles.
Hey, Pam.
I know you're a very busy man,
so I'll cut right to the chase.
Okay.
I'd like my old job back.
I don't know what to tell you.
The job's been taken.
Well, I could come back as a salesman.
I have experience now.
Or I could come back
as your personal assistant.
You know, sort your mail,
set your appointments.
I know all the people.
Yeah, no.
Personal shopper?
No.
Well, it was great
catching up with you,
and I'll see you
around the building.
Okay.
I'm just going to sit here for a
little bit longer if that's okay.
The air smells so good.
I don't remember it
smelling so good.
Chairs are so comfortable.
Oh, hey, Stanley,
Phyllis, come on in.
Welcome, welcome.
Let me give you the tour.
I get it.
You need to see more?
It's really cute.
Thank you.
Do you remember Ryan?
And Pam,
around here somewhere.
She's upstairs
talking to Charles.
What for?
I don't know.
Are we staying
until 5:00?
Yes.
Maybe the Michael Scott Paper
Company was a huge mistake.
I should leave.
I should go
and start my own paper company.
That'll show them.
Get your free pancakes.
They are delicious.
They are nutritious.
They are complimentary.
Young sir, would you
like a free pancake?
I'm texting. I don't want
to get my hands sticky.
Ryan, enough with the texting machine.
Come on.
Tuck in your shirt. You're
the face of this company.
Hey, Pam.
Hey.
You sort of disappeared there for a while.
Where you been?
Yeah, I needed to take
care of some stuff. Yeah?
That's as specific
as I'd like to be.
Well, at least you're still
being honest with me.
There's the rundown
you asked for.
I may have expanded some areas
that you weren't prepared for...
Great, fax that to everyone
on the distribution list.
Uh, sure.
Do you want to look at it first?
Do I need to?
No. No, I just...
Wanted to make sure
we have the same format.
So that distribution list
is going to be my...
What's that? The one I have.
I'll use the one I have.
Just faxing my dad a rundown.
We're small, but we're eager
to make a name for ourselves.
Do you have a card?
No, I don't have a card,
but I'll do you one better.
A little scrap of paper.
These are terrible, boss.
You got to make them in a circle,
so that they cook evenly.
They're shaped
like paper.
Well, I don't even
want these.
I'll take them
for my kid.
Country roads,
take me home
To the place...
Sorry, I like that song.
You're good.
Thank you.
That was great,
but it's just sort of...
It's still a little choppy, like...
But don't worry, it's hard, I mean,
it took me a while, too.
It's like...
Wow.
What?
Oh, my God, you heard that?
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so, like, rusty. It's good,
you're really coming along.
It's really technically
proficient,
but, you know, there's really
no heart or soul in it.
Really?
Hey, do you want
to sing it with me?
Almost heaven
West Virginia
Blue Ridge Mountains
Shenandoah River
In German!
Take me home, country roads
To the place I belong
West Virginia, mountain momma
Take me home, country roads
Take it, Andy!
Take me home to the place
You have to stop.
I once had a dream
that I was eating a peanut
butter and tuna fish sandwich,
and let me tell you
something, it was delicious.
So, the next day, I decided
to make that sandwich.
And in real life
it is disgusting.
It is a disgusting sandwich.
And the reason
I tell you this story...
Pick up the phone. Just...
Dunder... Michael Scott
Paper Company, this is Pam.
Oh. Hi, Russell from the
pancake luncheon, how are you?
Well, we'd like to do
business with you, too.
How can I make that happen?
Keep going. Tell him
we have free delivery.
We already offer
free delivery.
They don't know that.
I can offer you free delivery on
any order that you place today.
God.
Okay, 20 boxes, I can do...
Just a second.
I can do 20 boxes
at $43 a box.
Great.
Write it down.
Give him a guarantee.
A guarantee of what?
Just say the word.
And I guarantee that
you will be satisfied,
because your satisfaction
is our guarantee.
We guarantee it.
We look forward to doing
business with you, too.
Thank you, Russell.
Yes!
I made a sale!
You did! Oh, yeah!
Oh, my God.
We did it!
She did it! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Who would have thought
that the thing that
would save this company
would be work?
And pancakes.
In the end, this day definitely
had its ups and downs.
I realize that we don't
have the biggest office,
which is a surprise, because 165
square feet sounds like a lot.
But we have people
with the biggest hearts,
and I think
for a small company,
that is really...
Someone went
to the bathroom.
That is really
what's important.
Literally every song is better a cappella.
Name a song.
Cherry Pie, Warrant.
Better a cappella.
No, really?
Yeah, name another.
Enter Sandman, Metallica.
Better a cappella.
Rebel Yell, Billy Idol.
Way better a cappella.
Really?
Yeah.