What's this?
Looks like a red wire.
Well...
It wasn't here before.
It's a computer, Dwight.
I mean, computers have wires.
Yours doesn't.
Doesn't it?
No.
It's going in a different
direction than the other wires.
Dwight, I'm really busy. I
can't talk about this anymore.
Dwight, get out of here.
Just shut up, Phyllis.
What are you doing?
I got 500 feet of red wire at a flea
market out by Dunmore High School.
Twenty bucks for
the whole spool.
Crazy. What a deal.
Oh! He'll be fine.
I made it up there.
What you talking
'bout, Wallace?
Hi, Michael. How are you? Hi.
I'm well. How are you?
Very good.
So, listen,
as you know,
we haven't yet filled
the Regional Supervisor job.
Oh, have you not?
Correct.
And I was wondering if I could get
you to do some of the fieldwork
that would normally go
to the supervisor.
Okay. There's an area from
Carbondale to Marshbrook...
Yeah... where we've
never done any business.
There's a small company
there, Prince Paper.
I can't get
a report on it
because it's not
a public company,
but we've been talking about
going after their market,
so I was hoping you could do
some fact-finding for me.
Okay.
I'll fax over some of the
things we're looking for, okay?
Fax? Why don't you just
send it over on a dinosaur?
This is important,
Michael.
Oh! Well, then
e-mail it, David.
You've got no taste,
Stanley Hudson.
Oh, I do.
What are you guys
talking about?
Some actress,
whether she's hot.
Who's the gal
in question?
Hilary Swank.
Ah! Hilary Swank.
Not at all.
She's got mean eyes.
Have you seen her
with her bangs?
She looks like
a monster.
Guys, she is
a beautiful movie star,
so maybe we should
just go to work.
She is an
amazing actress.
That's not the question.
She's not hot.
- Yeah. Thank you, Phyllis.
- Okay, okay, okay.
Why don't we just
put this to a vote,
and then we'll be
done with it?
I'm not voting.
No one cares.
Who thinks that Hilary Swank is hot?
Raise your hand.
Okay, and who thinks that Hilary
Swank is not hot? Raise your hand.
Five. Five to five.
Thank you,
accounting department.
So, what do we do now?
What if the owner of Prince Family
Paper has a beautiful daughter,
and we have to seduce her in
order to get their secrets?
I will seduce her.
No, I want to seduce her.
I'll seduce her.
Let me seduce her. Michael, please.
No, no, no. I got it.
You'll fall in love
with her.
Yeah? So what if I did?
That would take precedence, and
I would expect your support.
Okay, so let's go over
the plan again.
All right. I am a local business owner.
Mmm-hmm.
I need to buy paper.
Yep.
I find out everything about
their prices and policies.
Your fictitious name?
Michael Scarn.
Good. I am a paper salesman
looking for a new job.
I find out everything about
their expenses and salaries.
Okay. Then we meet
at the Denny's,
and we compare notes. No. No.
I never said Denny's. IHOP.
No. I said Denny's.
IHOP. We're going to IHOP.
You know how I feel about IHOP.
Don't start.
Don't... You know what?
Socialist.
I don't want to get into
this debate again. Okay.
I enjoy IHOP.
I'll have
a cup of coffee.
You will have pancakes,
and you'll like it.
The store next to
them is for lease.
So what?
It means they're
not expanding.
Maybe they're shrinking. No.
They could be shrinking. No,
because the sign is centered
perfectly above their store. No
sign of the sign being moved.
Ah-ha!
Yep.
It's lunch-time, but no sign
of anyone coming in or out,
which means they're not taking
new customers out to lunch,
which means they're not
acquiring new business,
so once again,
no growth.
Yeah. There are clouds,
clouds in the sky.
Means it's going to rain.
Bad for business.
It would if they were altocumulus
and not cirrostratus.
Why do... Okay.
Michael.
Whatever.
Get your clouds right.
Shut up.
Okay, so you go in now.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm gonna go in,
in exactly 10 minutes.
We have never met each other.
We are complete strangers.
Right. Also, we're
going to need a signal
to bolt out of there, in
case there is danger. Fine.
And that signal is lick your lips.
Try it.
No, no, no, like this.
Good.
Ready to do this?
Yeah.
All right,
here come the sharks.
In nature, there is something
called the food chain.
It is where the shark
eats the little shark,
and the little shark eats
the littler shark,
and so on
and so on and so on,
until you get down to
the single-cell shark.
So, now replace sharks
with paper companies,
and that is all you need
to know about business.
Hello?
Hello.
Hi.
How can I help you?
My name is Michael Scarn.
I am a local
business owner,
and I would like to find
out about your company.
Please come in.
Thank you.
What kind of business
are you in?
We're a law firm.
I assume your primary paper needs
are stationery, general office.
You know, I'll be honest
with you about something.
Where I used to live, our paper
supplier had a lot of big clients,
and I just didn't
feel like a priority.
So I guess my question
to you would be,
how many clients
do you have?
About 80.
Really? That many?
This doesn't seem like
a very big operation.
Well, it's just me,
my wife and my son.
Ah! So, when did
you set up shop?
I opened this place after
I came back from Vietnam.
Ooh, Vietnam.
I hear it's lovely.
Mmm.
Each side will have three minutes
to prepare opening arguments.
Topic. Hilary Swank
is attractive.
Hot.
The debate is
whether she's hot.
What difference
does it make?
Attractive, hot, beautiful. We're
talking about the same thing here.
Huge difference. A
painting can be beautiful,
but I don't want
to bang a painting.
Okay. TMI.
So, even specialty paper, say
94 brightness, double-bonded,
you would put that on the same
truck as your conventional stock?
You sure know a lot about
paper for a lawyer.
Oh! Well, that is
because I am a genius.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Well, about some things, and other
things I'm just... I'm very stupid.
Like, watch this.
Is this the cup?
Is this the cup? Is this
what I drink out of?
Laughter is my job.
Tears are my game.
Law is my profession.
- Well...
- Hello.
I'd like to apply
for a job.
Hi.
I'm afraid we're
not hiring right now.
Why don't you just
get rid of this guy?
That's my son.
I'm your son now. You can
visit him on holidays.
Dwight Schrute.
I'm a paper salesman at a second-tier
paper company called Dunder Mifflin.
I'm the top salesman there, and
I'm looking for a new challenge.
I would say you guys
have, what,
40 high-volume clients?
Try 80.
Eighty,
that's nothing.
I've got 90 clients
myself.
Better look out. Someone might
run you out of business.
Well, I sure hope not.
Me, too.
I think all of us have a tendency to view
celebrities as sort of mythical figures.
You know, we don't
really see them as real,
so, therefore, we don't
judge them as real people.
Are you serious? Jim,
just show us a picture.
- Kevin, come on.
- Yeah, shut up, Kevin.
No, but he's making
all these fancy...
It's a gut thing.
That's fair. You know what, Kev?
Do me a favor.
Why don't you
close your eyes?
Okay.
Now, imagine that Hilary Swank
comes into this office for real.
She walks over to you
and she says,
"Kevin Malone, I just
read your online profile,
"and there's nothing I'd rather do
than make out with you right now."
Now, you tell me something,
is she hot?
Does that end the debate
or is there... Oh!
Hey, Kev,
what are you doing?
Nope. It's, "Is she hot?"
not, "Would you do her?"
Respect the game.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
This close.
So why are you considering
leaving Dunder Mifflin?
My boss.
Oh, yeah? Do tell.
His insensitivity could
border on the cruel.
This is a man who does not listen
to the needs of his underlings.
Hey!
He's way...
Hey, how's the
interview going?
It's going very well.
Don't blow it.
Hey, Linda, can I get
a picture of you?
You want a picture of me?
I would.
Could you just
stand right over here?
That would be great. Just something
to remember the trip by.
Just a little
to your left.
There you go. Good.
Perfect.
Can I have
a copy of that?
Um...
Grandma, I can't do this.
What's going on? A little
homework over here?
Yeah.
Let's see if I can help.
Right there.
Oh! Math.
That's not so hard.
Okay. There are four of these.
All right.
Ignore the parentheses,
right?
Right. Why is this
little 2 so small?
It's weird. You just don't...
Just go by the "X."
The "X" means times, so that
means four times "X," 2.
What is double 4?
Eight.
Right. Excellent.
Don't put that.
Ladies and gentlemen, even
though the penis was fake,
I kept expecting
a second plot twist
where we found out that Hilary
Swank actually was a boy.
Kevin.
Okay.
I wasn't going to dignify this
discussion by getting involved,
and I don't even
get the discussion.
Hot is a temperature,
people.
But Kevin deserves to
lose for what he said.
So, yes, she's hot.
She's hot as heck.
She's a female
Boris Becker.
All right.
Well, thank you very much
for all of your help.
It's going to be an
incredibly hard decision.
Wait. Let me get
something for you here.
Here's some references.
Our top clients.
You call any of them. I trust
you'll hear some good things.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
All right, thank you.
You're welcome.
Excuse me, sir.
Mmm-hmm?
I took the bus here
and was wondering
if I could catch a ride
home with you in your car.
Of course.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for your time.
Thank you for your time. I cannot
wait to contact your clients.
I'll look forward
to getting your calls.
All right.
Bye now. So long.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We struck
the mother lode.
Come on!
Wallace is gonna freak.
He is going to absolutely freak.
All their top clients.
I can't believe it. Someone's
looking out the window.
Go, go, go.
Go, peel out! Go!
Shoot.
What the...
Okay, I'll just... I know.
You drove over the...
I know. I know. Oh!
Go back.
God, what was that?
That's not good.
Oh, come on.
Yes!
No, no, no.
She's hot, okay?
Because if you are saying
that Hilary Swank isn't hot,
then you're saying
I'm not hot,
because obviously I'm not
as hot as Hilary Swank!
- Oh.
- Darn it.
Oh, come on.
Oh, man.
- My car.
- Are you all right?
Not good.
Is everyone okay?
- Yeah.
- It sounded bad.
No, no, no. We're fine.
We're fine. Yeah.
You folks have done enough already.
You don't...
You've done more than
you could possibly know.
Dwight, just...
Okay.
You know, we're just gonna
call a tow truck, so...
No, a tow truck is gonna charge you
100 bucks just to take you a mile.
Let me take a look.
No. No.
You know, really not necessary.
He drove over the divider,
- and then backed over it.
- Dwight.
It caught the bumper.
I'll be right back.
I'm just gonna
grab my toolbox.
Don't...
Ladies, are we prepared to let the Kevins
of the world decide anything for us?
Anything at all? We don't even
give him full Internet access.
Wait, what?
See that? The obvious
symmetry of the face.
This is a natural appeal of the
scientific standard of koinophilia,
features that are a composite
average of many features.
Yes, she's attractive,
but she's not hot.
How much longer is this gonna take?
Put that over there.
You know, let me give you
some money for this.
No. I sit all day.
It's nice working with my hands.
Well, I...
Oh! Coffee.
That's too much nice.
Maybe
not enough oil.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Ah. Disgusting.
What is this? Instant?
Well, that ought to do it.
Okay.
It's all better.
Thank you.
Gosh, well, so long.
Bye-bye.
That looks great.
- Drive safe.
- Bye.
Look forward to hearing from you
about that job application.
Bye.
Okay.
Goodbye, Prince family.
Should be called
the "Sucker" family.
"Here you go, shark.
"Let me fix your fin for you and
sharpen your teeth while I'm at it."
Bye-bye, suckers.
I'm just saying.
No, it's...
All I'm saying is Kevin's
not necessarily a feminist.
That's all I'm saying.
What are you...
Dwight, what will
happen to that family
if I call Wallace and give
him this information?
It's simple. Wallace would use
that information to destroy them.
Okay.
You know, our sales are fine.
Well.
We're doing fine.
They're doing fine.
Could be better. Why don't
we just live and let live?
What?
Live and let live.
I'm not familiar
with that expression.
It's a James Bond...
It doesn't make any sense. Okay.
Of course I'm alive.
I'm not going to make this call.
Michael, you have to.
Have you ever seen a
lioness devour her cub?
Oh, God, not this.
Have you ever seen a baboon
devour its mate?
Have you ever seen a
raccoon devour a squirrel?
My heart...
My heart says no.
Your heart is a wonderful
thing, Michael.
But it makes some
terrible decisions.
That's true.
Yes. Gosh.
It has gone down the wrong
path many, many times.
Jan, Ryan.
Yeah, save your
heart for love.
And use your brain
for business. Right?
If we don't do this to Prince
Paper, then someone else will.
Or worse yet, someone
else will do it to us.
I am trying to be
more optimistic in life.
I've got, what,
20, 30 more years left,
and my family history says
I have less.
Now, the old Stanley Hudson
would have found
something to complain about
with this actress,
but that's no way
to live life.
Look at this healthy, sexy,
pretty, strong,
young woman.
Come on, people.
She is hot.
And it was
a terrible war.
Oh! So many died.
Far too many died,
but if Frodo hadn't
destroyed the ring,
then goodness itself
might have died.
You're right.
Yeah.
You are right.
I will call Wallace,
and I will give him
the customer list.
And I will give him
all of my info.
You are doing the
right thing, Michael.
Good. So...
Where are you going?
Just something
I have to do first.
Where are you taking
the client list?
Someplace safe, where
it can't hurt anyone.
Michael!
Michael! No!
I will get it.
Michael, don't do this!
Don't do it!
Michael!
Oh, shoot! My keys.
Come on, stop. Freeze.
Stop! Give me the list!
No, no, no. No!
I can't let you do this.
Those people will be ruined!
It's business!
It's not personal!
No!
Give it!
Dwight, give it!
You can't do this
to those people!
It's over, Michael.
It's over.
I'm not a shark.
No!
Okay, time for
the final vote.
All those in favor of the
resolution, "Hilary Swank is hot."
Okay.
And all those opposed.
This is ridiculous. That's
the thing about debating.
People just get entrenched in the
view they had in the first place.
I could tell when I was talking
you were not listening.
This is great
stuff, Michael.
You are a titan
of industry, pal.
Yeah. Thank you.
Good work.
Look, I'll be in touch.
Thanks, buddy.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Well, guess whose stock
just went up, golden boy?
I guess this is what they
call a bittersweet moment.
It is bitter because I slightly
destroyed a wonderful little family.
But sweet because David Wallace
thought I did a good job.
That's why I hate
bittersweet chocolate.
I don't even...
What's the point of that?
Why not just sweet? I mean,
who are you helping?
Oh, hey, what is this?
Hilary Swank.
Oh, she's hot.
Yeah!
Damn it.