What is this?
Happy holidays, Dwight.
But do not open it
till Christmas.
You're so pathetic. How long did
this take you, three hours?
Five minutes, actually. I'm a
black belt in gift wrapping.
Yeah, no such thing.
They don't give out black belts
for things that are stupid.
Well, I hope
it was worth it,
because I'm going to take it
apart in about five minutes.
I think it'll take you a
little bit longer than that.
Really. If I can skin a mule
deer in less than 10 minutes,
I ought to be
able to cut my...
I'm sorry. It's the
largest one I have.
I will not be the big
guy in the tiny hat.
This is the first
Christmas party
I'm throwing as head of the
Party Planning Committee.
The theme is
Nights in Morocco.
This isn't your grandmother's
Christmas party.
Unless of course
she's from Morocco,
in which case
it's very accurate.
Hey, Phyllis, do I need this
invite to get into the party?
Yes.
Awesome.
I think this is going to be the
best Christmas party ever.
Angela, you're going to move
this for the party, right?
It's not on theme.
It's the Nativity scene.
All right.
You can keep your camel,
sheep, elephant... Hey.
And the North African
king can stay.
Everything else
goes in the drawer.
I am not going to judge Phyllis
for desecrating Christmas.
There is one person
who will, though,
and Phyllis just
stuffed him into a drawer.
I need you to
get rid of the tree.
But... But...
Thank you.
Oh, I don't
think it's blackmail.
Angela just does
what I ask her to do
so I won't tell everyone that she's
cheating on Andy with Dwight.
I think for it
to be blackmail,
it would have to be
a formal letter.
Ah, you brought in
your doll collection.
These are not dolls, Jim.
These are commodities,
same as gold or oil.
Every year,
I do research to determine
which toy will be the most
popular of the Christmas season.
This year, it's a doll.
Half-girl, half-unicorn.
Catchphrase, "My horn
can pierce the sky!"
Pathetic.
I bought out every store in the
area over the last couple of weeks.
And as lazy parents
become more desperate,
I will sell them
at an enormous profit.
Isn't that right, princess?
That's the Christmas spirit.
I am simply punishing
those parents
that would wait till the last
minute to give their child a gift,
and such a genetically
improbable one.
Look at that.
How does that happen?
The king has sex
with a unicorn?
Man with a horn has sex
with a royal horse?
Yes. Hey, is that
Princess Unicorn?
I thought they were
all sold out.
They are now.
Cool.
My horn
can pierce the sky!
This is equal parts scotch,
absinthe, rum, gin,
vermouth, triple sec,
and two packs of Splenda.
Call it a
"one of everything."
Oh, my God!
Hit me again!
All right.
One more time
around the block.
I will grant you one wish.
I wish you would stop rubbing
that lamp in that creepy way.
Stupid. Everybody knows to
ask for 100 more wishes.
Dumb.
Hey, hey, Ang,
check it out.
There's a place in France
Where the naked ladies dance
Really, Andy?
It's Christmas,
and you're singing
about nudity and France.
There's a hole in the wall
Where the men can see it all
Jim, check that out.
What is it?
That is vodka, and I mixed
it with orange juice.
I call it an
"orange vodjuiceka."
Wow, that is delicious.
Yeah.
I can't believe no one's
thought of that. I know!
Belly dancing.
$120, $180, $200.
All right.
Oh, thank you so much. My
daughter is going to love this.
Oh. So glad I could help.
Thanks.
Merry Christmas.
You, too.
Fa la la la, la la, ka-ching
Oh. So this is what every day would
be like if you hadn't left India?
She's burning.
Oh, my God!
We got
a live one! On fire!
I'm all right.
Sorry.
We're back on the 5th.
Should we just do it then?
Cannot do it then, monthly
dental appointment.
Soft teeth.
What about
February 2nd?
Would you want to
do it on Groundhog Day?
No. No. I celebrate privately.
That's right.
Why don't we just do it now?
We'll do it quickly.
Now? It's our Christmas party.
Well, what if we
can't do it quickly?
"What if we can't
do it quickly?
"What if we can't do it?"
Do you know how
to do an intervention?
Hey, shut up.
Here we go.
Everybody, gather up.
An intervention, it's
sort of hard to describe,
but, really,
it's a coming together.
It's a surprise party for
people who have addictions.
And you get in their face
and you scream at them,
and you make them feel really
badly about themselves.
And then they stop.
It looks like we're going
to be here for a while,
so why don't you make a little
plate of hummus for everyone?
Little triangles of pita,
toasted on both side,
fanned so you can
easily grab them.
I know...
And napkins, fanned.
Okay. How do you feel?
Little better.
I threw up.
TMI.
Fire girl.
Too soon.
Yeah.
Okay, you know what I
thought we should do
is have a quick intervention and
then get back to the party.
Michael, we're only allowed to talk
about Meredith's work performance.
We cannot ask her
to stop drinking.
I am not asking her
I am imploring her to
quit being an alcoholic.
I'm not an alcoholic.
Yeah,
obviously you are.
Okay, everybody who thinks
that Meredith is an alcoholic,
please raise
your hands.
Aye.
The ayes have it.
I don't care what
everyone thinks.
I know I am not an alcoholic.
All right, well,
let's look at this a little
bit closer, then, shall we?
When I was in college,
I used to get wicked hammered.
My nickname was "Puke."
I would chug a fifth of So-Co,
sneak into a frat party, polish
off a few people's empties,
some brewskies,
some Jell-O shots,
do some body shots
off myself,
pass out, wake up
the next morning,
boot, rally, more So-Co,
head to class.
Probably would have gotten expelled
if I'd let it affect my grades,
but I aced all my courses.
They called me "Ace."
It was totally awesome. I got straight Bs.
They called me "Buzz."
Meredith, "have you ever used
alcohol to alter your mood
"or deliberately change
your state of mind?"
Sure.
"Do you sometimes have
a drink to celebrate
"a special occasion
or mark a holiday?"
Obviously.
"Have you ever, under
the influence of alcohol,
"questioned the teachings
of the Mormon Church?"
Where did you get this? I got it on
a website. That's not important.
Michael, we should
contact some experts.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Okay, you know what, Toby? One of my
employees is undergoing a crisis,
and I wish, for just once,
you would take
my side on this.
I'm doing your job, man.
Hey, are you texting?
Yeah, 'cause
this is kind of a drag.
Alcohol is a drag, yes.
Here's what I'd like to do.
I'd like to go around the room and
have us each express to Meredith
how her alcoholism
has affected us.
I'll begin.
This Christmas party
is perhaps the best Christmas
party I have ever been to.
But then you got so drunk that
we had to stop and do this.
That's how your
drinking affected me.
Anybody else? Another time when
Meredith's drinking affected you?
Come on, people.
If we don't say anything,
she's not going to
get any better.
Yes, Kevin.
Well, Meredith,
there was that one time
that you bought
movie tickets
and then you got
too drunk to go,
so you gave them to me,
and that was really cool.
That's... You didn't...
You weren't hurt by that.
Yeah, you said
"affected" by it.
Thanks again, Meredith.
You're welcome.
No, that's not
what we're going for.
Who has a problem with Meredith's drinking?
It has to bother you.
It bothers me, right?
How does it bother you?
Dwight, don't you
have anything?
No. I like Meredith.
Actually, I don't
care for Meredith,
but I don't believe in
this kind of thing.
In the Schrute family, we believe
in a five-fingered intervention.
Awareness, education, control,
acceptance and punching.
Who's going to tell us
the latest dirty joke?
Who is going to tell us what you
watched on television last night?
I am fine.
Was John Belushi fine?
Was Bob Hope fine?
Hey, come here.
If anything ever
happened to you,
I would be very angry at myself for
not doing all that I could do.
I know I drink.
I like to party.
I want you to say,
"I'm an alcoholic."
I'm not an alcoholic!
You can say it
as loudly as you want,
but we're not going
to believe you.
I was waiting until later to hand out
this year's gifts from corporate.
I don't think they're
appropriate anymore.
Please stop making me
do these things.
Sorry, it's your job.
But it's the season of mercy.
You never showed me mercy
when you were in charge.
Why aren't you
wearing the hairnet?
I lost it.
Fine.
Okay. Nice.
I don't mind telling you that
I have an addiction. I do.
To porn.
All right,
no, no, no, no.
That is... The image, I think we
can all agree, is very disgusting,
but you know what,
Meredith?
You lit your hair on fire today.
What about tomorrow?
What is going to happen when you
come into work and you're dead?
I stab her in the brain
with a wooden stick.
There are several ways
to kill a zombie,
but the most satisfying one is to stab
it in the brain with a wooden stick.
Everyone in this
room loves you.
But mark my words, we are not going
to support your alcoholism anymore.
The next time you light
yourself on fire,
we are not going to
help put you out.
Oh, as fire marshal,
I would have to.
Dwight.
She is a hazard
to the other people of the office.
Okay.
I suppose I could do it if it was a
controlled burn in a well-ventilated area.
Yeah, but you're going
to need a permit for that.
Right. That'll take
a couple weeks.
I can get you one
in an hour.
Really? Okay, you
know, this is over.
I agree.
I think you did the best you could,
but this is bigger than all of us.
Enabler, enabler, enabler,
enabler, enabler, enabler.
It's Christmas, and we
are turning our back
on somebody who is
asking for help.
You know what the only thing
I want for Christmas?
I want Meredith to get better.
That's my only wish.
But you know what?
My wishes never come true.
So I'm not going to
wish that on her.
A watch would be nice.
They've been in there
for 45 minutes.
I know.
If she wasn't an alcoholic
before, she is now.
That's a halwa
shebakia cookie.
They serve it
during Ramadan.
Mmm. Chewy.
Hey.
What's up?
Do you take requests?
Sure.
Please stop,
because we're having
a Christmas party.
I'll be down in a minute.
Could you write
down the number
of that rehabilitation
center that you mentioned?
Sure. Wow.
Ow!
We just missed
Poor Richard's.
We did?
Yeah.
I thought we were going out for a drink.
Oh, shoot.
Oh, well, we'll have to go
someplace else, then, I guess.
The Bog.
Yeah.
Cooper's.
We could go there.
Kelly's.
Sure.
Brixx's.
Yes. Yes.
Carmen's.
Fort, Andy Gavin's.
I have a new place.
It must have
just opened up.
Yeah, recently.
Yeah. All right.
All right.
All right, enough
of this Christmas crap.
Let's just get some
party music. Yeah!
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah!
That's good.
Yeah, that's better.
Party girl.
Hey, Sasha, it's Daddy.
Have you ever heard of
this doll Princess Unicorn?
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy...
Nope, no, no.
No. I'm just curious
if you heard of it.
This is great. My ex-wife's
going to be so pissed.
For once,
Daddy's going to be a hero.
$200.
Yep.
Hey, I'd like to buy
one of your dolls.
Oh, that's my last one.
Oh, no.
No, no. I was going
to buy that doll.
Thanks, man.
I was going to
get the doll.
Not my problem.
But I...
I promised my daughter.
Darryl, look, hey...
I need the doll.
I'm begging you.
I just...
I need it more than anything in the world.
I need this doll.
Darryl, man,
Okay, all right, man.
Don't cry. It's cool.
I'll let you
get it for $400.
I only have two.
You can owe me.
Oh, man. Thanks. Thanks.
Thank you. I know, right?
Merry Christmas.
Oh, thanks.
She's going to...
Oh.
Something wrong
with the doll?
No, it's...
It's even better
than the one I wanted.
Sunrise Rehab? No! No!
No! I told you no!
Yes.
There is no way!
No. It's okay.
It's all right.
No way! There is no way!
Meredith, we're doing this
for your own good.
Okay, come on.
No way!
There is no way! Here we go.
This is going to be good.
It's going to be...
No way! I told you.
We talked about this!
Open the door. There
is absolutely no way!
Here we go.
No, no way!
No! There is no way! No!
No! I am not going in there!
All right. Here we go.
Yes, you are.
I am not going in there!
Yes, you are!
Wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Just wait.
Calm down, calm down.
Oh, my God!
No! No!
Come on!
There is no way!
Here we go.
Almost at the door.
Here's the door. There is no way!
There is no way!
No! No!
Let's start meeting...
No!
Hello.
This man is crazy!
How are you?
Can I help you?
I have a deposit, alcoholic.
No! No! No!
So do I sign?
No!
I need you to put the
Christmas tree back up.
It's outside.
I didn't ask you
where it was.
I told you where
it needs to be.
Shut up.
Excuse me?
I'm not moving the tree.
Face it.
The only power
you have over me
is this little secret that I
know you're not going to tell.
Oh, and you want
to know how I know that?
Because then you won't be able to plan
your stupid, tacky parties anymore.
So you move the tree.
Okay.
Angela's having sex
with Dwight.
I caught them doing it
after Toby's going-away party.
Well, don't look
so surprised.
I knew it.
You did not know it.
I knew some of it.
Everyone knew some of it.
It's Christmas.
You knew it.
Thank you.
I knew it.
She knew it.
As it turns out, you can't just check
someone into rehab against their will.
They have to
do it voluntarily.
They have to hit rock bottom.
So I think I know what I
need to do at this point.
I need to find ways to push
Meredith to the bottom.
Um, I think I can do it.
I did it with Jan.
All right, everybody's
still here, perfect!
I've got a little surprise
I've been working on.
Angela, my bride,
I just wanted you to know
that for the rest of our lives,
no matter the cultural milieu,
I will always be there to bring
you some Christmas cheer.
Deck the halls with boughs of
holly Fa la la la la, la la la la
'Tis the season to be jolly
Fa la la la la, la la la la
Don we now our gay apparel
Fa la la, la la la
Troll the little
old yuletide carol
I think I'd like to
go home now.
Sure.
Tough room.
Come on,
I just learned it.
Just so you know, protocol is a
little round of applause, but...
"Merry Christmas to all
and to all a good night."