Things are
a little slow here.
And there's only
so much cold-calling
you can do in a day.
Turns out there's no limit
to the number of cheese puffs
you can throw at
someone's face.
We're getting
pretty good at it.
Andy put down
a bunch of deposits
on stuff for his
wedding with Angela,
but then she was sleeping
with Dwight for...
Several years. Wait, no,
that can't be right.
No, timeline's messy.
Anyway, now we are
going bargain hunting
in the haunted graveyard
of their love.
This is my solo.
I'm confused.
Am I walking down the aisle
to You Can Call Me Al?
Trust me, you will not be
walking, you will be boogying.
I am extremely interested, so
how much will all of this cost?
Well, 12 guys, airfare,
three nights in hotel,
food per diem, table
upfront for merch...
$9,000.
I don't know, it seems like a
lot for an a cappella group
from a college
we never went to.
Did you even hear the music
I just played for you?
What's wrong with you?
These sleeves are cutting
off my circulation.
There's not enough blood
getting to my hands.
I think you look nice.
Doesn't Charles know he's
compromising my attack readiness?
It's not a dress code.
It's a death sentence.
Looking good.
Okay, thank you.
It's a straightjacket! Okay.
When Michael was in charge, this
place was like the Roman Empire.
And the Wild West.
And war-torn Poland.
And Poland.
There was just
a lot going on.
So what you wore to work was the
least of anybody's worries.
And in that chaos,
I soared.
Hey.
Ed's Tires. He's thinking
of making a change.
Is this good?
They have some
great kitchen ideas.
Okay, Ed's Tires, huh?
It's small, I know.
I really appreciate it.
Thanks, Michael, we...
What is this?
It's for your trouble.
I don't need $6
to help a friend.
No, no, listen,
as a friend,
I want you to have it.
You know I can't take this.
Yes, I do.
But don't forget,
you owe me $10.
That was four years ago.
Why don't you let it go?
Michael.
What was up with Pam being all
pushy and negative in there?
I think she just didn't
want a crucifix cake.
It scares me to see you going
down a road that I went down.
Am I going down a road?
When I see her bossing
you around like that,
it just makes me wonder if
this thing really has the legs
to go the distance.
It's so scary how right
the things you're saying are.
And you're coming at it
with almost no knowledge,
so of course I trust
your opinion on this.
I know a few things
about love.
Horrible, terrible,
awful, awful things.
I was gonna use today
to purge my inbox,
but now something much
more pressing has come up.
Ed's Tires. Why don't you tell
them that we have fewer clients,
so that we can spend more
time with each of them?
Also, try to discuss
it over Indian food,
and try to mention
how you distrust women.
I'm not gonna do that.
That is smart. That would
not seem genuine. Ryan?
I can get there.
Good. You take
the lead on this one.
Also, do not forget that he has
just gone through a messy divorce.
Awesome.
Bring it in.
Morning cheer.
U-G-L-Y, you ain't got no alibi, you ugly.
You ugly! Your mama say you ugly, hey!
Go Michael Scott Paper Company!
I'm here.
I'm part of this now.
You needed to speak to me?
Dwight, take a seat.
I prefer to stand.
Less blood clots.
No, that's weird.
You can just sit.
Great. You know, Dwight, it has been
quite a transition for all of us.
Are you happy with the way
things have been running lately?
Why do you ask?
Do you mean
compared to the way things
ran with other bosses?
Comparisons are hard.
I've just been impressed
with your performance,
and I wanted to make sure good
work doesn't go unnoticed.
Your concern is noted.
Yeah, I like your work ethic.
You're so focused.
Like a wolf,
thank you.
I want to start giving
you more responsibility.
What do you say you and I
go out for a drink this week?
Really?
Definitely.
It's firm.
I need you to get me the prices
that you're charging Ed's Tires,
so I can undercut
Dunder Mifflin.
I don't know that
I can do that now.
You know,
something's come up.
Oh, no, is it Mose?
Did you put
the cover on that well?
No, Mose is fine.
I roped it off.
It's not about Mose. Listen,
things are changing here.
Michael,
they're changing fast.
I'm not following you.
Imagine someone has a personal
hero they really want to help.
But then there's
this new guy.
Very cool,
very Will Smith-esque,
who would not like it
if he helped his hero.
Personal hero,
cool new guy.
Okay, I think I'm
getting your drift.
Good, so you see
what I'm saying.
Crystal clear.
So is this for a movie
that you're writing? No.
Can I use it?
No!
Dwight, are you
talking about us?
It is possible that I could
be talking about us.
Someone could say it is like the
situation that we are in now.
It is the situation
we're in now.
So I would say
that the old boss
has always been
good to Dwight,
and he was there first,
so he has dibs.
You respect dibs,
don't you?
I'm not a barbarian.
Good.
Will you meet me in
20 minutes at the spot?
I will.
Dwight?
Yes?
Is the cool new guy Charles?
I've said too much.
Is it Stanley?
Hey, Andy.
You know, I've been thinking
about what you said...
Nice. I just don't
know if I can do it.
That's interesting, because
what I hear you saying
is that you do
want to do it,
which means
you can do it.
Believe me,
I broke up with Angela,
and I'm, like,
the happiest guy ever.
I mean, I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
Like, total freedom,
you know?
It's just that Pam gets me
through the day, you know?
I really rely on her.
I'm pretty
emotionally needy.
And you know what?
I am here for you.
Let me be your
traveling pants.
What'd you do that for?
You know what
I was doing. Okay.
Totally.
Dwight?
What's with the shirt?
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, Michael.
Hi, Michael. Oh, my God, run, run!
It's a setup!
Dwight, run!
No, Michael.
Michael, no.
Let's be cool, okay?
You be cool!
Yes.
Just... What's going on?
We need to talk about our two
companies and how we should behave.
Dwight tells me you've been
pestering him for company info.
Dwight would not...
He did.
I did, Michael. I was upset about
the shirtsleeves at first,
but now I'm okay with it.
Michael, I want you to stop
pestering my salesman
and I want you to leave Dunder
Mifflin alone. Do you understand?
I understand nothing.
Wow.
Michael, are you all right?
It was a setup.
Dwight told Charles.
He told him.
Tell us what
you're talking about.
Yeah.
It's like a girl says
she'll make out with you,
but then her boyfriend is waiting around
the corner with a pee-filled balloon.
We can't help you if you don't
just tell us what happened.
I got hit in the face with a
pee-filled water balloon, Pam, okay?
I don't know
how they did it.
They filled the balloon with pee.
A funnel.
I don't know! Is that
clear enough for you?
Hey, Jim.
I just totally
blew a sales call.
Bro, I do that
all the time.
Yeah, well, with you
it's different, okay?
'Cause I just...
I just suck.
I just... I suck!
Tuna? Be nice to
my friend Jim, okay?
Why?
When I look in the mirror, I don't
like the face that looks back.
Well, so what?
Your body's a 10.
Just forget it.
Jim!
I said forget it!
Dwight Schrute.
Hello, traitor.
I think you have the
wrong number, Michael.
I want you to listen
to me, friend,
and I want you to
listen to me good.
I am going to come at you, and
I'm going to come at you hard.
I am going to steal
all of your clients,
and then I am going to
kill them in front of you.
Michael! Just getting
hardcore with him.
Finally.
Yes. And hear me, Dwight,
when I say I brought you into this
world, and I can take you out.
Bill Cosby.
- Mr. Schofield, please.
- He's in a meeting.
Damn it!
Is Mr. Schofield there?
If you'd like to
reach an outside line,
please dial 9 first.
Shoot.
So, you think Michael's
going after the whale, huh?
I have a long relationship
with HarperCollins Publishers
and Mr. Schofield.
I'm not worried.
You sound worried.
And you have bad skin.
Look, everyone, we're all
making observations!
Well, if you could do me a big
favor and tell Mr. Schofield
that Michael Scott
has tickets to the
Wilkes-Barre Penguins
game this weekend,
and if he would
like to join me...
Hello, Daniel,
how are you? Uh-huh.
I sure do. Yes.
Wanted to ask, did
Kathy ever make JV?
Look at that old dude
and his Rolodex go.
I spent a month putting that
Rolodex on his BlackBerry,
which he now uses
as a nightlight.
Wow. High score?
And, no, I cannot
lower my current prices.
Hold on.
Hello. Mr. Schofield, thank you so
much for taking the time to talk.
I wanted to discuss
your contract with us.
You're considering him.
I thought Michael Scott left the paper
business after his nervous breakdown.
Michael has been talking
to my biggest client.
Master and apprentice
pitted against one another
for the fate of the greater
Scranton area paper market.
So it's not exactly
like Highlander, but still.
Hello, Dwight. I've been expecting
your call. What do you want?
I would like to
arrange a truce.
So you heard Schofield is considering
a switch, and you want mercy.
Meet me in our spot
in four minutes.
No.
No, you think I'm going to fall for that?
There's no...
Michael.
Meet... Okay.
Go to the spot and
then walk 100 feet.
In which direction?
Toward the sun.
At what time?
Noon. You have two seconds.
Michael.
Sorry.
Dwight.
Michael.
I hope you're not recording
this conversation.
Good.
I cannot believe that
you sided with Charles.
You were making me do things
that were not all right.
So you just rat me out?
You could've said no.
And not come
through for you?
If you want a truce,
I will give you a truce.
I want a truce.
I do, too.
Let me take you and your whole
company out for lunch at Alfredo's.
Cooper's.
I had fish yesterday.
Damn it.
Dwight-a-licious.
Where you at?
Hi, Michael.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I got stuck in traffic.
Really? That's weird.
We didn't see any.
I hit a bear.
What?
He's technically fine.
I imagine the true horror will
be when he wakes up in a zoo.
Hey, listen,
will you do me a favor
and order
the meatball parm for me,
with extra cheese?
Yeah, sure.
Good. I will see you
very soon, all right?
Okay. See you in a bit.
Dwight hit a bear.
He'll be here in a sec.
Oh, my God, I think
we've been robbed!
Yeah?
Did you enjoy your lunch?
Dwight, not now,
we've been robbed.
No, Michael.
You were sabotaged!
No, Dwight,
we were robbed.
How would you even know?
You're still stuck in traffic.
You?
Me.
What about our truce?
I broke it.
On purpose?
Yes.
Why?
You think this is
some kind of game?
No, this is a war, and I will
not stop, I will not rest.
You have no idea what kind
of enemy you've created.
You have unleashed a wolf!
Be that as it may,
I have your meatball
parm sandwich here,
and I am going to eat it.
And I knew that
you would do that.
Their meatball parm is
their worst sandwich!
Bastard!
Hi, there.
Dwight Schrute here.
I was just calling to see
if Michael Scott Paper
was meeting all of
your paper needs,
and how is Brenda, age four,
ponytail, and Simon, age seven?
You don't say.
Schrute comma Dwight.
And on the back he wrote, "Great
salesman, better friend."
"Tall" and "Beets."
And say hello to Shari,
who is your black wife.
So you're
begging for mercy, huh?
Well,
you will find none here.
Dwight,
do you mind if we talk?
Sure. That'd be fine.
If you keep coming after us, the
Michael Scott Paper Company
cannot succeed.
This is war and
that is what happens.
One more thing. I'm going
to have you listen
while I steal
your biggest client.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no!
Michael. Michael. Michael! I'm
turning you down right now.
You can hear me,
but I can't hear you.
Mr. Schofield's
ready to see you now,
Mr. Scott.
Great, Mr. Schofield's
ready to see me.
Thank you so much. Don't let
him in, he's a traitor!
Walking in the door.
Michael!
Michael.
Good to see you.
Mr. Schofield,
good to see you.
And I'm closing the door.
Now,
when Dwight tells you
that he will keep prices
steady for a year,
I think he is
speaking out of turn.
Really?
Yes.
He does not have
the authority to say that.
I, on the other hand, am the
president, the owner and the founder.
It is like you are buying
software from Bill Gates.
Are you saying
you invented paper?
Okay, okay.
God.
Okay, Tuna.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
Hello.
Excuse me, can I have
your attention, everyone?
Here's the deal, everybody.
Jim Halpert is very
upset and disturbed.
I don't know if it
was something you did,
something you said,
a look you gave him.
Maybe it was nothing at all, but
here's the deal, okay? It stops now!
I guess I could be nicer.
Andy, I think Jim
is messing with you.
Really?
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
What the heck is
happening here?
Two things I need
you to understand.
One, Pam and I are
very happy together.
That's not what was...
And two,
that stuff that happened with
you and Angela is a bummer.
And I know that
you don't think
you're ever going to find
someone else, but you will.
I promise you, you will.
Man, he got me so good.
I learned something
about myself today.
Yeah.
I wish this was a sofa,
'cause I feel like I could
sit here and talk for hours.
What is that thing
that Dwight always says?
"Paper is the soil in which the
seeds of business grow..."
It's not the soil,
it's the manure!
Paper is the manure!
On-time delivery
is the soil!
Hello, Dwight.
Spin move!
April 13th, 2002.
Dwight! I'm in a meeting.
That's very rude.
I barge, because I care.
April 13th, 2002.
That is the date
when you tried to
switch paper providers
for an obscure sociology textbook,
but were hung out to dry
when the price of
glossy stock increased.
Maybe we should schedule a
meeting on another day.
Hey, hey! Continuing. Notice my
persistence and recall. Continuing!
You called Dunder Mifflin and your
order was filled within an hour.
I'm going to pull a date
out of the air right now.
April 13th, 2002.
That is the last day that you
evaluated your paper needs.
Is it not? We all know
that the economy is bad,
and bloated companies like
Dunder Mifflin... Come on.
are going to
fall by the wayside.
Two of their branches have
closed within the last year.
The Michael Scott
Paper Company, however,
has opened a new
branch this very month.
What he's not telling you
is that he will abandon you.
Why don't you guys just
e-mail me your best offers,
and we can
finish it up that way?
That sounds like a great idea.
That sounds like a fantastic idea.
I will see you this weekend for
the Penguins, box seats as usual!
Okay, sure!
Good, good, good.
Thank you, Mr. Schofield,
for your time.
Much appreciated.
And tell me,
how's your gay son?
Excuse me?
I color-code all my info.
I wrote "gay son" in green.
Green means go, so I know to
go ahead and shut up about it.
Orange means, "Orange you
glad you didn't bring it up?"
Most colors mean,
"Don't say it."
How is Tom,
the homosexual sophomore?
I wanted to start
a company, not a war,
because, in a war, you always
fight those you are closest to.
And the great tragedy
of the Civil War
is that brother
fought against brother.
For what? What purpose
did that serve,
apart from
abolishing slavery?
In that case,
war was the right choice.
This doesn't feel
as important, though.
That's just how the
world works, I guess.
Michael Scott Paper Company.