All right, everybody, this is
your last meal, so eat up.
From this point forward,
you will not use the bathroom.
We need to keep our starting
weights high so we can lose more.
This summer,
corporate is sponsoring
a little weight loss contest
between the branches.
Whichever branch
loses the most weight
gets three extra
vacation days.
What should we do
with all these leftovers?
I'm taking the dumplings
for my wife.
No, no, no. This
is your last meal.
There will be no leftovers.
I can bring
these to my shelter.
I'm taking my dumplings.
There. Take those
home to your wife.
Dwight! Dwight!
Michael, it's time.
Hit the scales, everybody.
Right on that black platform.
This way. Step it up.
Don't go breaking my scale.
I'm excited to lose
weight for the wedding,
because I really want
to have washboard abs
the first time
Angela sees me naked.
Ex-squeeze me.
No, I will ex-squeeze you.
Okay, everybody,
get used to this,
because we are going to be
standing here briefly
every Monday for the
next seven Mondays.
Wait a minute. One more
bite of éclair each.
Hold it in your mouth
if you can't swallow.
Really? Nothing?
2,336 pounds.
You all need to learn
some portion control.
Wait a minute,
Pam is on the scale.
Pam-cake, no, no, no. We would
love your extra poundage,
but you are going to be leaving
us next week, so vamoose!
Okay. Vamoose, Pam. Dunder
Mifflin family only.
Family only.
All right, got it.
2,210 pounds.
Pam, you weigh 226 pounds?
Almost, Kevin.
Not almost, though, Holly.
I mean, not...
Not close to 200.
Math is hard.
Yeah.
Just...
We'll, just keep going.
I'm totally going to slaughter
at the weigh-in today.
All I had this
weekend to eat
was a chicken breast
and a case of Diet Coke.
Really?
Yeah.
'Cause I haven't eaten
anything since noon on Friday.
Okay. Stanley, come on.
Oh, I forgot
something in my car.
I'll see you guys up there.
All right.
I happen to be losing weight
on my own for my own reasons.
The truth is, I have lost a little
of my speed, a little of my fire.
Here's what I
used to look like.
Look at those biceps.
We were fighting the power
and eating whatever we wanted.
And arch your back and
slowly bring up your head.
Jimbo. Oh. They
moved the shower.
Did you see Holly's butt?
No, I didn't.
You know why?
Why?
Because most of the time, friends don't
talk about other friends' butts.
I... I know.
But what have you
learned about her?
I learned that she broke her
left leg twice in one year.
I learned that she's
allergic to sesame seeds.
I learned that she has read
Lonesome Dove three times.
Nice.
And that her butt
refuses to quit.
Well, I tried.
You have to... You have to agree with me.
That's insane.
I'll just go later. That's insane.
I thought you had to pee.
Hey, if you're into yoga, I take a
great Bikram class in Dickson City.
Oh, thanks.
I should check that out.
Also, and no pressure,
the teacher, he's a catch.
Actually, I'm a lesbian.
I'm gay.
I'm not a lesbian.
I don't know why I said that.
Stupid joke.
What's the joke?
No, there is no joke.
I just said it because I
haven't had much luck lately
and I'm not really
looking to date,
so maybe I should
switch to women.
You think it's a choice?
I'm going to head back to
my work area and just...
I'm messing
with you, Holly.
I knew that.
Okay, bye.
Okay.
So you have the directions?
Yeah.
You have a toothbrush?
Yes.
You have a cell
phone charger?
I have everything.
Tomorrow, I start a
three-month design program
at the Pratt Institute
in New York.
I will be a little
fish in the Big Apple.
What up, two-one-two?
Fax this for me.
Come on, man. She goes to New
York in, like, 10 minutes.
It's not going to take her
10 minutes to fax it, Jim.
If I don't see
you again, goodbye.
Well, actually, I'll see you when
you give me the fax confirmation.
So never mind.
Ang... ela.
Ela, ela, ela
Under my Angerela
Ela, ela, eh, eh
What?
Hey, check it out.
This is The Breakers,
Newport, Rhode Island.
Huge, awesome, gorgeous mansion
overlooking the Atlantic.
And my dad went to Cornell with
the current groundskeeper.
Every little boy fantasizes
about his fairytale wedding.
No. No.
This is where my parents
decided not to get divorced.
I don't care.
Okay.
How do you feel
about Maine?
I'm on it. I'll see
you later, love.
We done good in there,
half-pint.
Well, that was the last time, Dwight.
I mean it.
Monkey.
No. No.
I have a fiancé
I very much like.
Hey! Hey!
Pam! Pam! Hey.
What happened?
I wrote you
a goodbye poem.
It's really long. I left
it up in my office.
Could you just please
wait until I go get it?
I should really get going.
No. Okay. Okay.
The last word is "seagulls."
I'm sure it was
really lovely.
I took a lot from other poems.
Call me when you get in.
Okay.
Bye.
All right, call...
No, Michael.
Why haven't I
proposed yet?
Actually, Pam and I talked about it.
And we just decided that,
well, we didn't want to spend the first
three months of our engagement apart.
And Pam's always said she
doesn't want a long engagement.
Something in her past,
I guess.
Not really sure
of the whole story,
but something about a guy
who used to work here.
Okay. No, no, no, no, no!
Same places as last week.
It doesn't matter, Michael.
Yes, it does.
No, this is about
weight displacement.
We have to have the same
weight distribution.
Right here.
There we go.
Let's move that up.
Fancy meeting you here.
Okay, everybody smile.
You lost 31 pounds.
Hey!
Yeah!
All right!
Yes!
I can't believe
I'm saying this,
but Michael is actually
killing it with Holly.
And I think I know why. It's because
Holly is kind of a major dork.
I'm MC Mike Scott and I am hot
She's DJ Jazzy Flax
and she is the best
All the sucker branches
can suck our fat
Wicka-wicka-wicka what?
Dunder Mifflin.
This is Ronni.
I don't
really know Ronni.
But I have a feeling I will
get to know her very well
over the next few years.
And eventually
declare my love for her.
Sorry I'm late. I accidently
switched my alarm clock setting
to Zapf Chancery.
Which is my terrible
segue into our course,
Expressive Typography
in New Media.
I'm in the wrong class.
Some of you may remember from last
semester, I am Professor Monahan.
And it looks like I'm
boring someone already.
No, I just...
Please sit down.
You're shaking.
Are you all right?
Just leave me alone!
I am on the third day
of my cleanse diet.
All I have to do
is drink maple syrup,
lemon juice, cayenne pepper and
water for all three meals.
I just bought some bikinis
online, size two. So...
Gonna look amazing!
Hi, can I help you?
I need you to make me 100 copies
of this on canary yellow.
Hey, Jan.
Hi.
How's the candle game?
Oh, great. Yeah.
Serenity by Jan is kicking
ass and taking names.
You remember last week
when that girl went missing,
guess whose candles
they used for the vigil?
Cool. Thank God
they found her, too.
Oh, they found her?
Hi, Jan.
Hello, baby. How are you?
Good to see you.
Who's your daddy?
You don't know who
your daddy is, do you?
No, you don't. Come on.
Let's go in.
When Michael told us
that Jan was pregnant,
he led us to believe
that he was the father,
by telling us that
he was the father.
Hey, Oscar.
Who's that woman in Michael's
office with the feet?
That's his ex.
Oh. She's very beautiful.
Yeah, she is.
And clinically insane.
So, listen, I don't know if your
offer still stands or whatever,
but you can give your
yoga teacher my number.
Okay.
Listen, dummy,
it's not that hard.
All you have to do is take the
numbers from the sales report
and type them into
a master spreadsheet.
A GD monkey could do it. I do not
understand why you can't do it!
No! You do not
talk to him like that!
But he's an idiot.
Hey.
He is not an idiot.
Thank you, Holly.
He is mentally challenged.
But he's doing
a super job here.
Wait, back up.
Do you think
that I'm retarded?
What... No. Dwight.
Oh, Holly,
that is very offensive.
I'm sorry.
Hey, so,
since my little lady has such particular,
impossible-to-perceive taste,
I've made
non-refundable deposits
at four totally different
wedding locales.
Hot air balloons
over Napa Valley,
world famous Walt Disney's
Epcot Center,
scuba diving
wedding in the Bahamas
and Wilkes-Barre
Marriott Ballroom C.
Dangerous, tacky,
sharks, haunted. No.
Hurry, we have to
make this fast.
Let's do this thing!
Hey!
I have a nice comforter
and several cozy pillows.
I usually read a chapter of a
book and it's lights-out by 8:30.
That's how I sleep at night.
All right, I am connecting.
And you are not there.
Did you install it right?
How about this?
Go to applications...
I can see you!
All right!
This is so cool!
So what is going on,
girl in the computer?
Lunch with a girl from my hall.
Uh-huh.
Ceramics class,
then dinner by myself.
I'm going to watch HGTV,
and maybe go to Bungalow 8
with John Mayer.
Okay, can you turn the
girl off, please?
I'm trying to
get some work done.
No way! No way!
Pam Beesly! Hello!
Hey!
Hey, everybody, look! Pam!
Pam! Say hi!
Say hi to Pam!
Hi, Pam.
Don't we
all look skinny?
Almost dropped you.
Can you put me down?
I'm getting a little nauseous.
Pam, I would like you
to meet Ronni.
We call her
"Rice-a-Ronni."
She is hilarious,
she is wonderful,
a beam of light in this
dark, dark office.
Not really so much.
All she does is plop herself down
there and answer phones all day.
The nerve.
Calm down, weirdo. Just a joke.
She's such a weirdo.
You know what? My real beef
with her, though, Pam,
is that she can't
find those little
colored paperclips
that I like so much.
Would you help her
find them, please?
They're on the supply shelf.
Let's go!
Yeah.
We are following Pam
to the supply shelf.
Let us go.
New York is so exciting.
I love my classes.
The city is awesome.
Can you give me
back to Jim now please?
Okay, everybody,
let's suck in our guts.
2,184 pounds for a grand...
Oh. You all gained
five pounds back.
Damn it. Come on!
Oh, my God.
- Come on, Bernard.
- Here we go.
- Move it.
- Everybody on.
All right, we're set.
Still good.
You guys lost a pound.
You lost one pound.
I was on an IV for two
days at the hospital.
I lost four pounds.
I don't know what those
other fools were doing,
but I lost four pounds.
Angela, you'll
go to the supermarket
and get the
New York cheesecake.
Make sure it's
the generic one.
It's Stanley's favorite.
Yes, I've replaced Angela as head
of the Party Planning Committee.
I guess I was just in the right
place at the right time.
How's it going?
- It's going well.
- Good.
I have a crazy idea.
What if we did fruit
instead of cake?
Cake?
Who suggested cake?
We lost weight today.
I think it's okay
to reward ourselves
once in a while.
Are you kidding me?
We only lost
one pound, Phyllis.
What is wrong
with these people?
They have no willpower.
I went...
I once went 28 years
without having sex.
And then again
for seven years.
Does anyone have any idea
what the number one cause of
death is in this country?
Shotgun weddings.
That's not what that is.
Fright.
Being scared to death.
No.
Obesity-caused illnesses.
Thank you.
Holly is right.
People, this is not just about
winning some extra vacation days.
This is about a very cool HR
initiative that if we don't follow
we are all going
to die of obesity.
So how much are
we going to lose?
I would like to
lose 65 pounds.
Yes! All right. Who else?
Angela, can I put you
down for 10 pounds?
No. My doctor wants me
to gain weight.
If you gain weight,
you will die.
I want you to live forever.
I want us all to live forever.
How? How are we
going to do this?
Cryogenics.
Beer me five.
This is how
we're going to do it.
Five pounds. I'm asking each
of you to lose five pounds.
That, plus Jim's 65,
give us a very good chance
at winning this thing.
All right, I'm taking off.
Booty call.
No, just going to see Pam.
Maybe put up some shelves.
Here. Wait a second.
I don't want you to end up with
a surprise pregnancy like me.
Okay. Thank you for this.
You want more?
No.
I don't know if there's any one
place that has all these things.
That's not my problem.
"Thousand-year-old church in
the continental United States.
"There has to be a rainbow,
"24 hour
veterinarian on call."
That is very
important to me.
So, I have work to do.
Just do it.
Sweetheart,
just so you know, I don't
care where we get married.
I'll marry you right
here in this building.
I'll marry you
in the parking lot.
I'll marry you in the eye of a hurricane
in the middle of a snow storm
on top of a monsoon.
All I care about is
that we're going to
spend the rest of
our lives together.
I know I haven't
made this easy on you.
Hold on.
Hi.
Oh. So rude of me. Have
you seen Pam's new art?
It's right there.
Check it out.
It's a pretty lame party.
Does anyone want to dance?
Some girl came into Pam's room
crying about her roommate
stealing her soy milk.
So I'm in here
waiting it out.
Stanley, Michael's not here.
You can eat a slice
of your birthday cake.
I don't like cake anymore.
Why not, dawg?
Taste changed.
Now all I like is baklava.
Michael, we have a situation!
They should not
be in that room.
That's so lame.
They didn't invite us.
You know what we should do?
We should have a party
and not invite them.
Yeah.
Let's go mini-golfing.
Yeah?
Oh, hey, could I have a rain
check on the mini-golf?
I actually have
a date tonight.
It'll probably be
a total disaster, but...
I think you'll have fun because
men from Scranton are handsome
and they know how to show
a woman a good time.
Not that guy who
murdered his mother.
He was not so handsome.
Also Kevin.
You know what?
We're pretty much
done here today.
Why don't you
just take off early?
Really?
Yeah.
That's sweet.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Hey.
Holly doesn't need luck.
Everyone that meets her
instantly loves her.
Party's over!
You're so busted!
Okay, everybody.
Phyllis, did I or did
I not say fruit?
You said fruit, Michael.
And what is that?
Cake.
You know, we're going to have
to try a little bit harder
if we are going
to win this thing.
Happy birthday, Stanley!
It's kind of a good news,
bad news situation.
The bad news is,
we're not doing very well,
so we really had to starve
ourselves this whole week.
But the good news is that
all the other branches
are doing just
as bad as we are,
so corporate upped
the prize to five days.
So if we stay fat long enough,
we may actually get
a whole month off.
What?
Oh, nothing.
It's just some of us are
taking this really seriously.
I swallowed
a tapeworm last night.
It's going to grow up to
three feet inside of me
and then it eats all my food
so that I don't get fat.
And then after three months, I take
some medicine and then I pass it.
Creed sold it to me.
It's from Mexico.
That wasn't a tapeworm.
How's my favorite
branch doing?
All right.
Ronni was...
Things were at
an all-time sad here.
But then I got
an e-mail from Ryan
that he was coming back to town.
And I called the temp agency
and I told them, "I will pay you any
amount. Just give me Ryan Howard.
"Give him to me.
I want him. I need him."
And you got a goatee.
I did.
Did you get that after you
helped me move and you saw mine?
Yes. Goatee!
Fired guy!
Hey, Kevin.
That's really funny.
Yeah.
It's great to see you, Kev.
You, too.
I'm keeping a list of
everyone who wrongs me.
So when I'm back on top,
they'll be sorry.
Kevin just made the list.
Jim!
I want to apologize for how
I treated you last year.
I lost sight of myself and now
that I've quit the rat race,
I realize there's
so much more to life
than being the youngest VP
in the company's history.
I've even started volunteering,
giving back to the community.
That's great.
You're talking about your
court-ordered community service?
I don't need a judge to tell
me to keep my community clean.
But he did, right?
All right.
Well, you lost zero pounds.
No change.
On the brighter side,
you gained zero pounds.
Hey, you know what? I can't
do this by myself, people!
Kelly and I are the only ones who've
either passed out or almost passed out!
Damn it,
I need these five days
for my honeymoon!
Who is slacking?
Okay, let's just all try
and work harder, okay?
No! I want names!
This is the hardest thing I've
ever had to do in my entire life.
I haven't had
a very hard life.
So how was your date?
8.5.
I got a red wine stain
on my favorite shirt.
But he's cute, right?
What's wrong?
Mmm...
Um...
Close the door.
This is your fault.
No.
Your stupid friend zone.
I should have been lovers with
her first and then friends.
That was terrible advice.
Terrible advice!
You know my seduction method.
I like to get in there
and get my hands dirty.
You sabotaged me.
You sabotaged me, man!
Attention! Attention!
We only have a few weeks left
and most of you are just as
fat as the day we began.
How much weight
have you lost, Dwight?
I am hardly the problem, Jim.
No, you're
definitely the problem.
This is what I'm going to do. I'm
going to randomly select three names
and these three people
will get liposuction.
Um...
Stanley, Phyllis, Kevin. And you will be
responsible for your own medical bills.
Kelly?
Hello, Ryan. You look well.
I wanted to say I'm sorry for treating
you bad the past couple of years.
I was in my mid-20s and I was
going through a lot of stuff.
I think I never
really processed 9/11.
I want you to know
I've changed.
Cool.
We should get a drink
later, catch up.
Pick me up around 8:00?
That is so sweet.
Um, but I'm dating Darryl still and
we're like crazy in love, so...
Cool.
Well, maybe I'll
see you around.
It's a small office.
Yeah.
Hey, Phyllis,
do you have a minute?
Listen, I'm really sorry
about what I said before.
Okay?
I was way out of line.
Yes, you were.
But you know what?
I want to make it up to you.
There is a surefire sale, but
it's a two-man job. Interested?
Split the commission?
Sixty-forty.
I'll drive.
Dieting is only half of it.
Mmm-hmm. Saunas.
And exercise.
Although I know everybody
loves going to the gym.
The dreadmill.
Probably the weirdest thing about Pam
being gone will be lunch, actually.
But it will force me
to become acquaintances
with people I
consider co-workers.
Oh, my God.
Okay, everybody just act normal.
Don't say anything.
What?
My ex-girlfriend,
she's right behind you.
Really? Where?
Just hide me.
No, no, don't look.
Wow, was it
the age difference?
Actually, kind of, yes.
I just didn't like
eating dinner that early.
Hey, Jim. Listen, can I call
you back in a little bit?
I made friends.
Are you insane?
Hey, hey.
What happened?
There was no client.
Dwight drove me to an abandoned
warehouse five miles away
and pushed me out of the car.
I had to walk home
with no money and no phone.
And you burned over a thousand
calories walking home,
and this branch just got a little
bit closer to winning the contest.
Phyllis Vance,
ladies and gentlemen.
You left me in
a bad part of town.
Yeah, I took your purse.
What are you worried about?
You look great.
I can definitely
see the difference.
Phyllis Vance
for David Wallace.
"Dunder Mifflin
wants to make it clear
"that Dunder Mifflin
does not discriminate
"nor does it condone
unhealthy dieting habits
"or extreme
weight loss strategies,
"as was clearly
stated in the official..."
Oh, bang, boom,
shake, klump!
Why, hello, everybody.
What are you doing?
Fair question.
I say, I say,
I say, sit down, Holly!
I'll take it from here.
I am beautiful.
They are beautiful.
He is beautiful. This big
fat pig is beautiful.
It's my sumo suit.
I just didn't
inflate it all the way.
I'm so glad that
I bought instead of rented.
Body image.
We are here because there is
something wrong with society.
See, you're always saying there's
something wrong with society,
but maybe there's
something wrong with you.
If it's me, then society
made me that way.
Now, I know a lot of you are
probably asking yourself,
"Why are you dressed
in a plus-size suit?"
Because you're kind of doing
Michael Klump.
How do you know
Michael Klump?
Because it's your "making fun
of fat people" character.
How dare you!
Michael Klump is a
celebration of fat people.
I think of him as
more like a monster.
What about, "I say, I say,
I say, I'll sit on you"?
No, no. It goes... Look. "I say,
I say, I say, I'll sit on you."
No! No! No! No! No!
You know what?
Fat people are not monsters.
Why don't you guys have a little
more sensitivity to the subject?
Bang, boom, case in point.
Look at the outside
of this building.
It is ugly.
But you come inside
and it is beautiful.
Just like this
unappealing fat suit.
Inside is a rather
handsome, sexy man.
Vamping.
Hey, why don't you
just sit down, please?
I've been sitting all day.
We're doing this
because of you.
So why don't you just
go stand somewhere else?
Hey, hey, shaved?
I did.
Why?
So in the year 2000,
fungus and even black mold was
discovered growing in the cave.
Some blame it on the new
air conditioning system
that was installed, some on
the high-powered lights.
Others feel that fungus
is due to an overgrowth...
Nice.
Quiet, please.
Sorry.
Dwight, I would like
you to apologize
to this beautiful,
beautiful woman
for forcing her
to walk five miles,
which, for her, is
basically a death march.
She should thank me. Okay,
Phyllis, thank Dwight first.
Why should I
have to thank him?
You're right. You're right!
Just... Dwight, do it.
Just say it, okay?
I apologize for creating a ruse
which forced you to exercise.
Finally. Right? Okay.
Phyllis, you must be exhausted
from standing on those gams.
Why don't you have a seat?
Let's all clap at Phyllis.
Okay! Michael Klump wants to
remind you that corporate,
their idea, yes, was to
urge you to lose weight.
But more importantly, what
this whole thing is about,
this contest is
really about being healthy.
And in order to be healthy, you
have to eat. Kelly. Kelly...
Kelly, I want you to
stand up on your chair.
Come on. Stand up on
your chair. Stand up.
Stand up. Stand up.
Somebody help her.
Here we go. Okay.
I want you to look at her.
She's a beautiful
Indian woman.
Why? What makes
her beautiful?
Everything. She's perfect.
I like her nails.
Okay, be more specific.
I like her fingernails.
I like her purple dress.
What about her looks?
Hell of an ass.
What else do people like?
I wonder what
people like about me.
Probably my jugs.
Kelly, will you just agree
to stop this madness
and stop trying
to kill yourself?
I hate dieting.
I hate it so much.
I hate this
worm inside of me.
I want you to know...
Kelly, look at me.
I want you to know
that you are beautiful.
You are truly,
truly beautiful.
Give me a hug.
Mmm...
Summer's going great.
Just spent two hours
listening to Michael Klump.
I have a weird pain in my left side
that I'm convinced is an ulcer.
My girlfriend
lives in New York,
and I haven't
seen her in 10 days.
How's your summer?
Hey, Ryan, look.
Shaved off my goatee.
I am goatee-less. We are
the goatee-less brothers.
Yep.
How was Friday night?
Oh, I had a good time.
But it's been
three days and no call.
I even have two tickets to see
Counting Crows for tonight, so...
He'll call.
Oscar, enough of
the girl talk, please.
You guys lost four pounds. Hey.
I say we have a parade.
- Excellent.
- We better.
Good job.
So, as it turns out, tonight
is my nephew's tee ball game
and I kind of missed
the first three, so...
You've already
disappointed him so much.
He can't be expecting
a lot from you.
I know. I suck.
Yes, you do.
Dwight says hi.
I do not.
I do not say hi, Pam.
He's saying hi louder.
All right, listen, we're still
good for this weekend, right?
No tee ball games, recitals,
karate tournaments.
Hey, can you go to IM?
Okay.
What are you
writing about me?
I'm going to write you
both up for not working.
I'm going to write
you up for not working.
Okay. Well played.
Neither of us will write the
other up for not working.
Yeah? Oh, hey.
Did he call?
I just got... Kendall? I
just got off... No, no.
Did... I heard you talking
to Oscar about that guy.
What... What happened?
Did he call?
Oh. No.
Really?
No.
And you know what?
I even got two tickets
to see the Counting Crows
tonight as a surprise.
Why do guys not call when they
say they're going to call?
I don't know. I always call
everybody back right away.
But he'll call back, though.
Give him until
the end of the day.
He'll call. He'll call.
If he doesn't, he is loco.
Thanks. That's sweet.
Anyways, it seems like we lost
to Utica by only eight pounds.
Well, at least
everyone lost weight.
That's all that
really matters.
Wait, could we have
till the end of the day?
So we're only eight
pounds behind Utica.
Now, I know it's a stretch,
but we could weigh ourselves
again at the end of the day
and maybe win
this thing after all.
Leave it to me, boss.
I can get this whole
office to make weight.
It's going to be
a little toasty in here.
Good old-fashioned
sweat lodge.
Andy Bernard does
not lose contests.
He wins them.
Or he quits them
because they're unfair.
Hey, is that healthy food?
Nope.
We're trying to win a contest
here, Kelly. Please.
Hey, Michael, I just scheduled
lunch with a client,
so I might be back
a little late.
Okay, that is fine.
Just water and be back by weigh-in.
Okay?
Perfect.
I hate to even ask because
you've been so accommodating
about all the wedding stuff...
Your wish is my command.
Is there any way our first dance
can be to my favorite song?
The Little Drummer Boy.
Of course.
Really? Yeah! I mean,
it's a great song.
I always thought it was
bigger than Christmas,
anyway, you know?
Mmm-hmm.
And you know what?
The guys already know it,
so it's easy breezy.
The guys?
I didn't tell you.
Here Comes Treble,
class of '96,
was available
for our big day,
so I booked them.
I don't think that...
And they're collectively
my best man.
And they're crashing with us for three
weeks, so it totally works out.
I don't know if I want your
old college a cappella group
to be our wedding band.
Okay, I hear you, sweetheart,
but this is a deal breaker.
But you know what? You're
going to love these guys.
Carl I, Carl II, Broccoli Rob,
Spare Rib, Doobie, Lunchbox.
Boner Champ, that's me,
Pubey Lewis and the News,
Hopscotch, Jingle Jangle, Sandwich.
These are the best best men
a guy could ever hope for.
Let's talk about
this later. Okay.
Hey, this is not halfway.
I did the math. I had to
drive way longer than you.
Montclair would have been closer,
so you have to buy lunch.
What are you doing?
I just can't wait.
Oh, my God.
Pam, will you marry me?
Oh, my God!
So?
Yes.
God! Where is Jim?
I'm calling it.
I guess that's curtains
for the yoga guy.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I have to say, I think the
problem with that whole thing...
Yeah?
was that he was
a complete stupid idiot.
Oh, man, I really
wanted to see them.
I know.
I love...
I love Counting Crows.
Look where my seats were.
Wow! Really?
Yeah.
That's a shame.
Shame to waste these.
I want to buy them from you.
Michael, you don't have to buy them.
I do. No...
I do. I... I want to.
Trust me, I really do.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Just... I want you to just forget
about him, okay? Case closed.
Can I pay you tomorrow?
I have like a $60
limit on my ATM, so...
Yeah.
Is that good?
Hey. Sorry, everybody.
Hey, what are you
smiling about there,
smiley pants?
You're late.
Wet Tuna.
- Hey, Dwight.
- Okay.
What's up, Meredith?
Nothing.
You're dripping on me.
Darryl,
would you do the honors?
2,175.
Sorry, guys.
No, no, no. No, no.
I don't want to hear moaning.
This is a good day.
You guys accomplished
something big.
You lost a ton of weight,
literally, a lot of weight.
And I don't care what
any stupid scale says,
you guys are all
gigantic losers.
I don't know
about anyone else,
but it was
a good summer for me.
I lost seven pounds.
And you know what?
I'm just going to take
five days off anyway.
I went zip lining my
third day in Costa Rica.
I guess the harness wasn't
strapped in exactly right.
I broke my neck. And...
I've been in the hospital
five weeks now.
I still haven't
seen the beach.
It's nice to have visitors.