Hey, sport!
I heard someone
got engaged, you dog!
Yeah.
God!
Nothing can
hurt you now.
You're a man in love!
I was there, and that
dude is not engaged.
I'm not a big believer
in therapy,
but I would go into my own
pocket to cover his copay.
Big idea,
double wedding!
Me, Angela, you, Holly.
No. We would never do that.
And if we did, it would
be with Jim and Pam.
Yeah, we'd never
do that.
Yeah, so there you go.
Michael, I got
my bridesmaid's dress.
Wow, so quickly.
Yeah, and you said
I could get it
in any color I wanted,
so I picked white.
Michael, did you tell
your mom yet?
Nope. Nope, not yet.
Why not?
You wouldn't tell your mom?
- You love your mom.
- Yeah, I do.
Call your mom, Michael.
Yeah, I'll call her
and tell her tomorrow.
Call her! Call her! I don't
wanna do it in public.
All right,
I will call her.
She is going to
freak out!
Speakerphone!
Not...
Thanks.
Hello?
Mom, I'm getting married.
No, you're not.
Why do you always do that?
Whenever I'm getting married,
you don't believe me.
Are you getting married?
No.
Are you...
I'm not.
I'm not getting married.
Psych.
So I've returned
my bridesmaid dress
and it was on sale, so I'm
out a hundred dollars.
And I'm out a fiancée.
Are those
the customer surveys?
Yeah, this is all of them.
Jim, Dwight,
Phyllis, Stanley,
Andy and...
It's the receipt
to my bridesmaid dress.
What's that doing there?
I'll take care of that
for you. Thanks.
Kelly Kapoor is our dusky,
exotic, customer service rep.
And once a year, she
will contact our clients
and find out how happy they
are with our sales people.
Sort of a "Kapoor's List."
Schindler's List parody.
That's not appropriate. No.
Those reports
affect our bonuses,
which is kind of
great for me,
because you wouldn't know
from looking at her,
but Pam's a gold digger.
- Hey, New York ain't free.
- Get back to work.
It's the world's
tiniest Bluetooth.
I found it in a Japanese
gadget store in the Village.
I got one for Jim, too.
Jim, say something.
Testing, testing,
hello, everybody.
We wanted to stay
on the phone all day,
but the company has a policy
against eight-hour personal calls,
so we're not
telling anyone.
Pam, what do you
want on your coffee?
- Sprinkle of cinnamon.
I should go.
All righty, Dwighty,
let's see how you did.
Bring it on.
No.
Sorry.
Wow.
What does it say?
Dwight, your feedback
is horrible.
That's impossible.
A number of your clients
found your personal style
abrasive and distasteful.
I sell more paper than anyone.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, is this a joke?
I'm getting that queasy feeling
that sometimes accompanies jokes.
Do I look like
I am joking?
No, but that's
sometimes part of it.
If I were joking,
you'd be laughing.
Do you look like
you are laughing?
Impossible to say,
I can't see myself.
You're not.
Yo, Tommy Tuna.
Did you get
your scores yet?
No.
I got mine,
they were really good.
I miss him.
You must be really proud.
Yeah, I'm pretty psyched.
Whoa!
That's my mug.
Sorry, I was just...
It was right here.
Right. Well,
it's mine, so if you could pour
it out and get another one.
Okay, or maybe I could finish
the coffee that's in here,
and you could use...
Snoopy! He's funny.
Don't give him Snoopy.
That's mine!
That is a great mug,
but it's not my mug.
That is my mug,
so give it back.
How can you even be sure?
That's my face on it.
Make the face.
I don't see it.
Dude, that is my face.
What was that?
Wow. That was Dwight.
He seems upset
about something.
Describe him exactly.
What color mustard is his
shirt, yellow or Dijon?
It is spicy brown, actually.
What are you
mumbling about?
How was your meeting
with Michael?
None of your business.
Was it your scores?
These can't be
my scores, Jim.
For your information,
I'm being sabotaged.
Of course.
And I'm gonna find that
person and punish them.
Absolutely.
Or you could just be
nice to your customers.
You're an idiot.
There's the charm.
Jimbo, let's do this thing.
That is me.
Wish me luck.
No way.
Good luck.
Thanks.
I didn't say anything.
I love you.
I love you, too.
What do you think
I'm saying to you?
I'm not talking to you.
I caught Jim talking to
himself several times today.
What a loser.
Get a friend, loser!
Yeah, I'm looking at it right
now, it's really gorgeous.
You guys do great work.
I found the best "tentist"
on the East Coast.
He personally tented Giuliani's
first and third weddings.
And I got him.
I got him.
Would you be able to do the same
design, but with walls of gray?
And a top that's gray, too?
Fabulous.
Come on.
What?
You, too?
Did my scores drop a little?
Jim, they are poopy.
Jim?
Are we even sure
that's my file?
No.
Yes, I am sure, Jim, it...
Well, there's gotta
be an explanation.
I agree.
Yeah.
So, let's see
what we can find out
from reading.
Jim Halpert is
smudge and arrogant.
I think he means smug.
Arrogance.
Michael,
I'm just trying to...
And there is
our smudgeness.
I need a decent bonus
because I'm actually in the process
of buying my parents' house
so that they can retire.
And if history tells us anything,
it's that you can't go wrong
buying a house
you can't afford.
Pam doesn't know about the
house, so it's a fun surprise.
Pam, sorry about that.
Lost you for a second.
So, as it turns out,
I may not have done so hot
on my customer
reviews this year.
Maybe it's 'cause you
spent the whole year
flirting with
the receptionist.
Little bit. Worth it.
Here's what's going to happen,
I am going to have to fix you.
Manage you two
on a more personal scale,
a more micro
form of management.
Jim, what is that called?
Micro-gement.
Boom. Yes.
Now, Jim is going
to be the client.
Dwight, you're going
to have to sell to him
without being aggressive,
hostile or difficult.
Let's go.
All right, fine.
Ring, ring.
Hello?
Hello, this is Dwight Schrute from
the Dunder Mifflin paper company.
Well, that's great,
'cause I need paper.
Excellent, then you are in
luck, because we are having
a limited-time offer
only on everything.
Wow, this is
my lucky day.
Ask him his name.
What is your name, sir?
I am Bill Buttlicker.
Really?
That's your real name?
How dare you?
My family built this
country, by the way.
Be respectful, Dwight. Please.
Yes, Michael.
Could you hold on one second?
That's my other line.
What? No, but I... I'm on hold.
Hello? Yeah.
No. I'm just on the phone with this
stupid salesman. He's so dumb.
Probably just going to keep
him on the line forever
and not buy anything.
Okay.
It's up to you
to change his mind.
Sorry, that was
a family emergency.
Oh, no, what's wrong?
You know what?
That's private.
Boundaries, Dwight.
Come on!
I'm sorry,
Mr. Buttlicker.
As I was saying...
Sorry, you just have to
speak a little bit louder,
I'm hard of hearing. He's hard of...
He's an old man.
Okay, as I was
saying, right now...
You're gonna
have to talk louder.
Okay, our prices
have never been lower...
Son, you have to
talk louder.
Never been lower!
Louder, son!
Buttlicker, our prices
have never been lower!
Stop it! Stop it!
He...
That is totally
inappropriate.
You never yell
at the client.
You never yell at the client.
Now you listen to me, sir.
Here we go.
The three words I
would describe you as
is aggressive, hostile
and definitely difficult.
Please, Mr. Buttlicker...
I'm irate right now.
Give me the phone.
Please give me
another chance.
Mr. Buttlicker, I have to
put you on with my boss.
Well, I should hope so.
Who is this?
Hello, this is Michael Scott,
regional manager.
Well, this is
William M. Buttlicker.
Hello, Mr. Buttlicker,
how may we help you?
Michael, I like the
sound of your voice.
You know what
I'm going to do?
I'm going to buy $1,000,000
worth of paper products today.
See how it's done?
Thank you very much, sir.
I don't think you'll regret it.
See what I did?
You are the master.
There is one condition,
Michael.
Yes. You have to
fire the salesman
that treated me
so terribly.
Don't do it, Michael.
It's a million-dollar sale.
So it's called the Shangri-la Tent.
It's two stories, heated,
and it has a bridal suite
for my bridal sweet.
It's just really simple,
really tasteful.
I don't want to be married
in a tent like a hobo.
Hobos live in trains.
Nana Mimi can't be
in canvas that long.
Well, Nana Mimi...
Okay, look.
This tent is awesome,
and it's in high demand,
so I really think we should
put a deposit down now.
Okay, fine. You can have your tent,
but only if it's in a field.
A hand-plowed field.
Done and done-er.
There has to be a barn that's old
enough that you can see the stars
through the roof slats,
when you lay on your back.
And antique tools to look
at when you roll over.
Do you have a specific
place in mind?
No.
But anything within a five-to-eight
mile radius is acceptable.
On it.
Dwight.
Get in.
Are you serious?
Okay, what are you...
They might be
listening to us.
What's that? Who is "they"?
They might be listening to us.
Customer service might be
monitoring this conversation!
In this car?
You never know.
Better safe than sorry.
What are you thinking here?
Who stands to benefit
from our downfall?
The mob?
Maybe NASA.
Could be the mob.
But then Dunder Mifflin
would need to
be a front
for money laundering,
and there's
little evidence of that.
Is there some evidence?
Cute shoes online.
How many shoes
do you need?
I don't know, two, maybe
three, if one wears out.
How many shoes
do you need?
I'm not talking to you.
Who are you talking to?
Pam.
She's not here, Jim.
No, she's not.
Yes!
I found it. I found the perfect place.
A local bed and breakfast
which is on a 60-acre beet
farm, and even better,
I have an in
with the owner.
Yeah, we work together.
It's Dwight Schrute.
As in Schrute Farms.
So I'd like to
redouble my order.
If you could
put me down for...
Wait, shut up!
I'm sorry?
Do you hear that?
Hear what?
Breathing. Is that you?
Well, I am breathing, yeah.
Well, stop.
Hold your breath.
I still hear it.
Who's there?
Kelly, is that you?
Hold on.
I need paper.
Oh, my God,
you scared me!
Hear anything interesting?
What are you talking about?
I think you know.
You always say that,
and I almost never know.
What are you up to, girl?
Did Phyllis
put you up to this?
Stanley?
Are they paying you?
Are you accusing me
of something?
Of course I am. I know
you're the mastermind,
but you're too stupid
to do it by yourself.
Easy. Let's just
head back to the desk.
You just can't come into my
nook and call me stupid.
And maybe if you were a little
bit more nice and polite,
then people wouldn't give you
such bad customer reviews.
The reason that I got bad customer
reviews is because I didn't.
There is a massive conspiracy going
on here, and I know you're involved.
Dwight, get out of my nook.
That's what she said.
That's what she said!
Good one.
Hey. Sorry about Dwight,
by the way.
Yeah, he's weird.
Well, we all
handle it differently.
I personally choose to handle
it like a normal person, but...
Okay.
Hey, how are you
and Darryl?
We're cool. Bye.
Bye.
That was weird.
What was?
Have you ever had
a conversation with Kelly
where she didn't go on for 15
minutes without taking a breath?
No, actually.
Did you do something to her?
I don't think so.
Well, something's off.
Hey, how's things?
All right.
Yeah?
Living in the moment.
Do you have
any reason to believe
that Kelly
would be mad at me?
I don't play the politics
game anymore, Jim.
Can I tell you something?
I played it
full-on in New York.
I played it high stakes,
for keeps.
Made it to the top,
but look what it cost.
Can I tell you
what else I learned?
Wait, that's pretty weird.
What?
Well, Andy has
a mug just like that.
Yeah. Kelly gave them
out as party favors.
Remember? You got one.
No.
What party? Her America's
Got Talent finale party
over the summer.
That's crazy. It was packed.
I thought everyone was there.
You were there. I
remember you being there.
I wasn't, but thank you.
Hey, do you know
anything about this party?
Yes. I said you
definitely should go,
but you wanted
to visit me instead.
I can't be the only one
who didn't...
Dwight, let me see
your coffee cup.
No.
Is that it?
Why? No.
Okay, I'm going to
assume that was it.
Here's the thing.
I think you're right.
I think it was Kelly. I think she's mad
at us for not coming to her party.
Man, I knew it. Who are
her co-conspirators?
Probably just Kelly.
Obviously. I knew it.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. What?
You were right.
I was right.
You knew it.
I knew it.
You knew it
the whole time, buddy.
I knew it
the whole time, buddy!
- Wow!
- Yeah!
Right Dwight is loud.
Yes! I knew it!
Yeah!
Boom! Kelly the whole time.
Let's get her.
No, no, no, no.
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight.
Let's just
talk about this.
Get out of the way.
What's going on?
Why don't
you tell us?
Nothing's going on.
Let me
paint you a picture
of a little girl
from southern India,
who despite being welcomed
into this country
will now spend the rest of her life
in prison for a crime she did commit.
Dwight.
I was informed
by these gentlemen
that the reports
that you filed
may not entirely
be accurate.
What? I don't know
what you are talking about.
This is the first that
I'm hearing about this.
Come on.
You juked
the stats, cupcake.
We called about
a dozen customers and
they all said that they
gave us great marks.
What's going on?
I love your tie, Michael.
Kelly...
I was raped.
You cannot say
"I was raped"
and expect all your
problems to go away, Kelly.
Not again.
Don't keep doing that.
I'll give you one last
chance to come clean.
Just tell me
what happened.
Okay, all right. Okay, I did it.
All right? I lied.
Whatever, just fire me.
But you know what?
I did it because
you guys didn't
come to my party,
and you said
you would try to,
and then you
didn't even show up,
and so you're bad friends.
We have our confession.
I'm calling security.
Don't, don't.
Get away from that,
Dwight, please.
You know what? She's got
a point about you, too.
You do have a problem
dealing with people.
See? I wasn't lying.
You were lying.
I was lying.
Yes.
Jim, Dwight,
please excuse us.
But I want to be here
when you fire her ass.
I will call you
when it is time.
I have an enormous
amount of trouble
trying to get people
to come to my place.
And I hate it.
I can't tell you how
much leftover guacamole
I have ended up eating
over the years.
I don't even know why I make
it in such great quantities.
Here's what
we're going to do.
We are going to
sit here for a while,
make it look good.
And maybe you should cry.
Can you make yourself cry?
No problem.
I think
you should do that.
Pam Beesly?
Hey. What are
you doing here?
Who's that?
It's Alex.
It's Pam.
I came to kidnap you.
There's free wine and cheese at the
Chuck Close retrospective. Let's go.
That's going to be great.
Who's Chuck Close?
I love Chuck Close and his
photorealist paintings.
But I have to work.
Well, actually,
there's something else
I'd love to
talk to you about.
Can we go somewhere
else to talk about it?
Okay.
That's it.
I want to talk to this guy.
Put me in his ear.
What's up?
I want to take a big leap.
And I want to tell you that
I think that you should not
move back to Scranton.
Wow.
I want to make
a bigger leap here.
He is into you.
Why did you come to New York
in the first place?
Because they have
a great design program,
and I wanted to see
if I was any good at it.
And I wanted to
work on my art, too.
Right.
And that's why I think
you should stay here.
Because, I mean, you
really just got here,
you know, and you can't do
New York in three months.
You know, it has everything.
All the opportunity is here,
all the... The whole art
scene is in New York.
You know, it would be nuts
to go back to Scranton
without getting to
fully experience it.
Jim's in Scranton.
I know, but...
All I'm saying is, if there's
even a teeny, tiny part of you
that really wants
to be an artist,
then I think you should stay
here, because you don't want
to wake up in 50 years
and look back and wonder
what could have been.
And that is
the end of my speech.
I planned it all.
Anyway...
I will see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Is that the
Matsahashi B-400?
The world's
tiniest Bluetooth.
May I?
Don't.
Congratulations on choosing
Schrute Farms for your wedding.
No, we haven't decided
on anything yet.
We're still
reviewing some options
and it's going to come
down to the numbers.
Well, then, why don't you look
over some of our materials,
while I describe to you
the Excalibur package.
In addition to the
breathtaking natural beauty
and smell
of Schrute Farms,
I can promise you that our
grounds can be catered
to fit your
exact specifications.
I will work tirelessly for
you over the coming months
and be at your
constant disposal.
Please feel free to call or stop
by any time of the day or night.
That's very generous.
Well, you,
my good friend,
have nothing more
to worry about.
This wedding is officially
out of your hands.
Thank the good Lord. Deal!
Okay.
What are we
talking pricewise?
You already said,
"Deal."
Pay him
whatever he wants.
Can't argue with that.
Dwight,
you are going to
make us so happy.