At least once a year,
I like to bring in some of
my Kevin's Famous Chili.
The trick is to
undercook the onions.
Everybody is going to get to
know each other in the pot.
Now, I'm serious
about this stuff.
I'm up the night before, pressing
garlic and dicing whole tomatoes.
I toast my own
Ancho chilies.
It's a recipe passed down
from Malones for generations.
It's probably
the thing I do best.
Someone
is returning.
He started his own company,
and now he's back.
Who could it be?
I'll give you a hint.
He is a man.
A man you have missed
with all your heart.
A man who has ruined
all other men for you.
Who is it?
It's Michael Scott.
Hold up!
Conference room,
five minutes.
Well, I guess the first
order of business
is to welcome back
me and Pam and Ryan.
And how about Casual Friday again, huh?
Reinstituting Casual Friday?
You all look great.
What I want to do right now is try
something a little different.
I'm going to throw it out there,
starting with this meeting.
I want you guys to run it. I want
you to say whatever you want.
Take it away.
Your meeting.
What are you doing?
If there is something that you
would like to say as a group,
then by all means, you may
say it to me right now.
- Okay.
- Yes.
People are dressed
inappropriately.
Take it up with Toby.
What I want you to do
is I want you
to look inward,
and I want you to reflect, and I
want you to say something different.
Can you give us a hint?
When I needed salespeople
for my new paper company,
everyone here turned
their back on me.
Am I going to ask them to
beg for forgiveness? No.
Am I going to ask for a
big, crying apology? No.
Am I going to ask them to
slit their wrists for me? No.
I just want a tiny,
microscopic version of that.
Oscar, what were
you going to say?
Nothing. I didn't
say anything.
All right.
Do I still have a job here?
Not important.
Michael, she's...
Okay.
All right,
yes, yes.
She deserves to know.
You have a job.
Frankly, you have a job
because Ryan and Pam
are starting with us
as salesmen.
Wait, what? How is
that going to work?
It's going
to work very smoothly
because Pam and Ryan
are bringing over
a ton of clients from Michael
Scott Paper Company and...
You mean the clients
you stole from us.
Yeah, aren't we getting
those clients back?
No, you lost
those clients.
I call foul, sir.
Okay.
You were bought out.
They...
So the company, then, bought
out all of the stolen clients.
Okay, Dwight, let me
explain something to you.
I set the rules, and you
follow them blindly, okay?
And if you have
a problem with that,
then you can talk to
our complaint department.
It's a trashcan.
Don't fall in
love with me, kid.
Boscov's
at the Steamtown Mall?
It sure looked good
on the mannequin.
Well, you have good taste.
Well, thanks.
I sure wish I had more time to
talk to my clients, though.
What?
Isn't that what you said to a bunch of
my clients when you were stealing them?
That I didn't have
enough time for them?
Oh, I, uh...
Close your mouth, sweetie.
You look like a trout.
The man is
wearing sandals.
I don't need to see Oscar's
toes at work. Gross.
I mean, he looks like
he just got off the boat.
Can't you just not
look at his feet?
Excuse me?
Oh! You're so educated,
aren't you, Toby?
So trained to deal
with a hysterical woman!
I don't want to
look at his feet!
Do your job!
Well, I was in the seminary
for a year and dropped out
'cause I wanted to have sex
with this girl Kathy.
Followed her
back to Scranton,
took the first job
I could find in HR.
Later, she divorced me.
So, no, I wouldn't say
I have a passion for HR.
There you are, my friend.
Oh. Thanks, man.
Pamela.
Thanks, Michael.
Yep.
Fresh, hot ink.
New file system?
Trust me, Stanley, you're going to
want to read this memo very carefully.
I am not changing
the way I do my files.
No, no! This goes
for all of you.
Believe me, you are going
to want to heat my words.
When held over heat, the
invisible ink will reveal
that everyone should meet
at the warehouse immediately.
Do not ask me where
I got the invisible ink.
Urine. It was urine.
I'm sorry you're
offended by my shoes,
but I'm not going to
drive home to change.
Okay. I could loan you
a pair of socks. No.
No, they're clean.
I was gonna wear them
to volleyball practice.
I don't think so.
Andrew Bernard.
Okay, what are you
still doing at your desk?
What are you still
doing not at your desk?
Did you even
read the memo?
All my files are now in
reverse alphabetical order...
No, you idiot! There is a
code embedded in the memo.
Listen, you need to round up all the
salesmen, except for Ryan and Pam,
and get them down to
the warehouse, pronto.
Oh, it is on, like a
prawn who yawns at dawn.
Stop doing
rhyming poetry.
Just tell them, please.
God, the simplest thing.
We're in crisis
mode here.
Do you understand
that two unqualified
so-called salespeople
are being favored
because they all
failed together?
And frankly, I'm not convinced
that Michael and Pam
didn't have a thing going
while they were gone.
Can I address that?
No, you're too close.
Okay.
Stanley, how do you feel about
those two taking your clients?
It's not right.
I don't like it.
He doesn't like it.
You don't take my clients away
and give them to a secretary.
No offense, Jim.
I think she's very pretty.
Her face is okay,
but...
Jeez, what... What
are you doing here?
I don't know. I saw a crowd. Thought
there might be a dog fight or...
Get out!
We need to
do something.
I'm thinking maybe a coup,
or we take Ryan hostage.
Those sound too harsh.
No, I'm not saying
we do those things.
I'm saying something
like those things.
Of course.
What is like a hostage?
Excellent question.
We could write a
strongly worded letter.
Words will never
be enough.
Strongly painted picture. No,
pictures are too interpretive.
Can I just say something?
I know that tempers are high.
But I think the best
way to handle this
might be to just talk
to Michael directly.
Oh.
That... That's a
great idea, Jim.
I totally see
your point.
Okay, we'll talk to Michael directly,
so, uh, meeting is over, I guess.
I'll see everyone upstairs.
Great. See you upstairs.
Come on.
Listen, now is the time for action.
I'm talking...
That one's great.
I know.
- Why are you so mad?
- You look so classy.
I do? Well...
Hi, you have a second? Michael
Scott Paper Company only.
Yeah, I think you're gonna
wanna cool it with that,
'cause it's starting to
upset the other salesmen.
Okay, well...
Tough.
I will... No. No.
I'll talk to them when they all
get back from the bathroom.
This is awkward to talk about,
but there may or may not be,
but definitely is, a mutiny forming
in the warehouse right now.
Against who?
You.
Us.
What?
It's gotta be because they
all want their clients...
The old Michael Scott
might have taken this,
but not the new
Michael Scott.
They are in for a bitter surprise.
I am not to be truffled with.
Six weeks ago, none of these
people wanted to come with me.
You two were the only ones
with the stones to follow.
Mmm-hmm.
That was us, right there.
We were something else.
What you gotta do is you gotta
go down to that warehouse
and you gotta crack some skulls,
Chiklis style. Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, The Commish.
Yes, but Chiklis Shield style...
Okay.
not Commish style.
Yeah, yeah. The Shield.
It's crazy, what's going
on out there today, huh?
I know. Yeah,
it's kinda...
Sometimes it's best
just to stay out of it.
That's true.
That's right, yeah.
Want to play a game?
Hey, gang,
where you been?
Lunch.
Where'd you eat?
A restaurant.
What did you
have, Stanley?
I had a salmon salad
with water, no ice.
I was going to get a soda, but the
waitress talked me out of it.
Her name was Flo.
She had black hair.
I had Mexican food.
So since you
guys already ate,
you won't be eating the stuff that you
brought with you for lunch, will you?
Wow, Stanley,
is that egg salad?
Andy brought
some salmon.
That looks great.
Dwight, is that
a meat sandwich?
You guys hungry?
I can eat.
I'm going to have some
of this meat sandwich.
It's pony.
Mmm! What kind of sauce
is on your salmon?
Dijonnaise.
Thanks for going out, guys.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, Meredith, can I talk to
you privately for a second?
About what?
Your outfit.
What? What's wrong
with my outfit?
You might consider
pulling it down a touch.
It's riding up
a little high.
Bunch of prudes. You know,
Oscar's allowed to wear sandals,
but I'm not allowed to
wear open-toed shoes?
Is that how it goes?
Meredith, your boob is out.
Fine.
Damn it, Meredith, where
are your panties?
It's casual day.
Happy?
- Toby.
Toby?
No. If you do that,
I'm going to do that.
If you do that,
If you do this,
I'm going to do that.
What if I just do this?
You don't want
to do that.
I'm just hiding out until
all this stuff blows over,
with Creed, playing
chess, at work.
He's winning.
I feel like I'm
describing a dream I had.
I'm sorry you feel
that way, Mr. Bart.
Is there anything I can do
to make things better?
Give me the phone.
Exactly, if this is your first complaint
in 10 years... That's my client.
things have been generally good.
Give me the phone.
Tell him Dwight Schrute
wants to talk to him.
- Look, Mr. Bart...
- Hi, Mr. Bart!
at these prices, with this service...
Hey, it's Dwight here!
you're not going to
find this anywhere else.
Dwight Schrute here. Hey,
don't hang up, Mr. Bart.
No, sir, don't listen... Listen, I
know times are tough right now,
and I laud your thriftiness.
Look, let me...
Ryan, hand
the phone over!
Stop flustering me,
everybody!
Who let this boy
on the phone?
Mr. Bart!
I cannot believe
you lost that account!
He was my client
for 10 years!
You made him lose the account by
screaming at him the entire time!
It's okay, Ryan.
You're a secretary!
What do you know?
And you're a temp!
And I'm taking your phone.
I'm confiscating this!
Hey, guys...
You know what I want you to do?
Shake hands, get over it.
That was not
a shake, Dwight.
We want our clients back
or we quit, Michael.
Who quits?
Me.
And me.
Me, too.
You guys gotta be kidding.
No, we gotta be
deadly serious.
We'll start our
own paper company.
The Schrute-Bernard-Lapin-
Vance-Stanley Paper Company.
I love it! I love this idea,
and I fully support you.
As a matter of fact, I'm going
to give you some seed money.
There you go. There's
some seed money for you.
And you can take it,
no hard feelings,
but if you stay,
I want an apology,
and I want a big one.
You want us to apologize to you?
Yes, I do.
That's completely backwards.
It's frontwards!
Michael, you thought you
were attacking Corporate,
but we were the
ones who got hurt.
You should be
apologizing to us.
That's right.
Michael, you always said we were a family.
Then you went after us.
No matter how I look at
this, I am in the wrong.
And I have looked at this thing
like 100 different ways,
from my point of view,
from their point of view,
98 others, and bottom
line, I am in the wrong.
I'm the bad guy.
I need you
to arrange a meeting
between me and
the sales staff
without Ryan
and Pam knowing.
Gasp.
Are you talking
about a secret meeting?
Whatever you guys
did earlier.
I don't know the first thing
about secret meetings.
Just do it, okay? Get them there.
Get them there.
I'll do the best
I can, Michael.
Are you kidding me?
Deceit does not come easy to me.
Okay, okay, okay.
I really love
your outfit.
Thank you so much
for saying that.
I can't believe that Toby
thinks this is inappropriate.
You look like J-Lo.
So, from the bottom
of my heart
to the top of
my heart, I am sorry.
Are you giving us
our clients back?
If we could just focus
and go down the line,
and everyone would say,
"Apology accepted,"
I think we would
all feel better,
and then we can break
out my gift to you,
complimentary
white chocolate bark.
Nobody likes that stuff,
except for you.
They wouldn't make it
unless people liked it.
Michael, just give us our clients back.
That's all we care about.
Okay, if I give you
your clients back,
there won't be enough
clients for Pam and Ryan,
and I promised both of them that
they were going to be salespeople.
So?
Fine, have your clients.
I can see that's what you
wanted all along. Okay.
However,
I rescind my apology.
- That's fair.
- Absolutely.
You are not reacting
at all as I had hoped.
What did I tell you about
building forts in my warehouse?
Michael gave all of our clients
back to their old salespeople.
So now there's not enough for
both me and Pam to stay on.
He can only keep one of
us as a salesperson now.
He'll make his decision
by the end of the day.
I think you
should get it.
You really
grew into it.
Oh.
I think you
should get it.
You've changed a lot,
and you'd be good at it.
If you really think that, will
you tell that to Michael?
That would go a long
way, coming from you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
So, hey, I want to set
you up with my daughter.
Oh, I'm engaged to Pam.
I thought you were gay.
Then why would you want to set
me up with your daughter?
I don't know.
Jim, could I talk
to you for a minute?
Sure, let me just
finish this turn.
And Bingo was
his name-o.
Let's go.
Challenge.
I need your help.
This whole Pam-Ryan debate
is screwing with my head.
Well, I don't want to be biased, but I
am very close to Ryan. You know that.
You're close
with Pam, too.
Oh. She's nice, I guess.
You know what?
Best thing to do,
pros and cons list.
Pro for Ryan, he went to business school.
He's my number-one choice.
Well, that's...
I like his hair.
Cons, Ryan, he
defrauded the company.
He has never made a sale. Okay.
He definitely
stole my iPod.
That sounds pretty biased.
You didn't
hear my pros.
Environmentally conscious, 'cause his
mom drives him to work every day.
Okay. Pam, pros, I like her.
Mmm-hmm.
I think that she
is a fast learner.
Cons, she doesn't
always follow through.
New York and the whole
art school thing.
And Roy.
She has a weird voice.
That's not true.
I don't need to
tell you that.
I think she'd be a
really good salesperson.
I don't think you're being
totally impartial, though,
because you haven't said
one bad thing about Pam.
And I won't.
Okay.
So be it. Then you've
lost credibility,
and I'm going to go with
my gut, and that's Ryan.
Okay.
You're right. Sometimes,
when she is tired,
she can be
a little bit shrill,
but that's not a weird
voice, that's just...
Take it easy.
Oh. Man! Wow!
"Honey!
"I want you to
put the garbage out!
"'Cause I'm not gonna
have sex with you
"unless you bring
out the garbage!"
I have a very difficult
decision to make.
It's like last week
I was at the video store.
Do I rent Devil
Wears Prada again
or do I finally get around
to seeing Sophie's Choice?
It is what you would call a
classic difficult decision.
You don't understand
clothing, Toby!
You're dressed like this
amorphous blob of khaki.
All right, look, what
you've got to understand is
when you come to work,
Listen up, Flenderson, you're
being weak and ineffectual.
I'm cowboying
this meeting, okay?
Here are the new rules,
okay? Earth tones only.
Also, women are forbidden
to wear pants.
All right, come on,
sit down, Dwight. No.
I'm running this meeting.
That's debatable.
It's not.
Listen...
It's not. Sit down,
or I'm writing you up.
Hmm. Where's
this guy been?
Casual Fridays
are canceled.
What? Let's just
not do it anymore.
That's not a solution.
No, it is a solution.
You're running
from the problem.
There's not a single
appropriate outfit
in this whole... Except
mine, quite honestly.
Pam, could you
come in here, please?
Have a seat.
Okay.
Well, there's no
easy way of saying this,
so I think I will
just drag it out.
Since the dawn of time, there have been...
Just tell me.
I gave Ryan
the sales job.
There just weren't enough
clients for the two of you.
So I had to...
I'm sorry. Sorry. No, okay,
okay, I get it, yeah.
Why are you giggling?
Is this a joke?
Michael, is this...
Did I get the job?
Yes.
I did?
Yep.
For real? You're not
kidding? I did?
No, you're the best person for the job.
You're going to be great.
Oh, Michael, thank you!
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
You will not be sorry.
You should have seen your face.
Oh. Man! That was classic.
I really thought
I didn't get it.
Oh. Really?
Yeah.
Man.
That was really good.
'Cause you said I didn't.
What about Ryan?
I don't know. I offered
him his temp job back.
We'll see.
He was not happy at all
when I offered him this job,
and then I told him that he
didn't get the job, so...
Yeah, maybe you shouldn't
fake-fire people anymore.
I don't appreciate you
telling me what to do,
so clean out your desk.
You are through.
Thanks, Michael.
Oh.
What's our
receptionist's name?
Erin.
Could you send her in?
Erin, Michael
wants to see you.
Hello.
Hi.
Have a seat.
This is very
difficult to say.
But no one here likes
you in the office,
and we're going to
have to let you go.
Hank, would you come up here, please?
Hank is our security guard.
Oh. I can go... He will
be ushering you out.
Oh.
Oh, your face.
Oh!
Is... Do the people... No, I'm kidding.
You're not fired. Yet.
Do they not
like me, though?
I don't know, actually. Okay.