Hang on, hang on -
you're not supposed to be here either?
You're a mistake, just like me?
Yeah, and I'm freaking out, dog!
There's so much thoughts in my brain
it's like my head is filled with rocks.
How have you managed
to stay undiscovered?
Because I have had to dodge and weave
and barely escape with my life
and you don't seem... like a super genius.
Hello, Jianyu, I'm Michael.
Before we start, I know you were
a Buddhist monk and kept a vow of silence.
Would you prefer
to remain silent here, as well?
You literally haven't said a word
since we got here?
Yeah. When I say I'm meditating,
I'm just trying to figure out
what the fork is happening!
I think we might be in an alien zoo.
Or on a prank show.
No, Jianyu, we're dead.
Whoa, that's a dope prank.
Whew, gotta give it up.
Okay. I need to make sure
that this isn't some sort of weird trap.
Is your real name "Jianyu?"
No, it's Jason Mendoza.
And, by the way,
everyone here thinks I'm Taiwanese.
I'm Filipino. That's racist.
Heaven is so racist!
But Tahani said that you helped Michael
by putting your hand on his chest
and doing some sort of healing magic?
Yeah, a nurse did that to calm me down once,
when I crashed my jet ski into a manatee.
You crashed your jet ski into a manatee?
Yeah. I'm from Jacksonville, Florida.
It happens a lot.
What did you do for a living?
I was an amateur DJ.
specialising in EDM.
Electronic Dance Music?
I was also an amateur
hip-hop backup dancer
an amateur body spray inventor,
um... I did pranks on Vine...
None of those are jobs.
What did you do to make money?
Oh, I sold fake drugs to college kids.
Okay. Good.
Okay, here's my biggest question.
How did you know
that I didn't belong here?
I figured it out the very first night,
at the party, using my powers of deduction.
I heard you don't talk.
Well here's something for you
to not talk about - I don't belong here!
They made a mistake.
Total phony. So, shh!
Okay. Later, man.
Okay, I vaguely remember that.
I believe you, Jason.
You're not supposed to be here.
Welcome to the bottom of the barrel.
Hello, Tahani!
Oh! Hello, Michael!
I was just picking out some fresh orchids
for my nightly orchid bath.
So, Tahani, one of your fellow residents
is opening a new restaurant tonight.
This Neighbourhood could use
a real morale boost -
and since you're an expert
at event planning
I was hoping that you would help
with the Grand Opening.
Oh, Michael! Say no more!
I wasn't going to! I was done!
Well, good! Because of course I will.
Janet?
- Hi there.
Oh! Hello, darling.
I would like to model tonight's event
on my most successful gala.
That would be 2006 fundraiser
for stem cell research in Barcelona.
"Barthelona," actually.
Oh, it was a perfect evening.
Princess Stephanie was there,
as were Posh and Becks.
You know, International Sophisticate
Magazine gave us five Gwyneths!
Tonight I'm going to select
my jauntiest suit.
And I may even wear suspenders.
Ah!
It's one of the human clothing items
I'm most eager to try.
Oh. Well, good luck.
Thank you, yes, yes.
I'm excited and... a little nervous.
I'd say that I'm "cautiously optimistic."
I hope I don't chicken out
at the last second.
Sorry, we are talking
about suspenders, right?
Like, these?
You can do that with them?
Oh! I cannot wait!
Excellent.
So Tahani has no idea about me?
No. She thinks I'm a monk,
and she thinks you're her best friend.
Great. I mean, for us.
That's a huge bummer for her.
We need some place
that we can talk in private.
I agree.
Let me show you my bud-hole.
What?
- I should warn you, it's a little messy.
This is my Bud-Hole.
It's just like a hole where me
and my buds can hang out.
Oh! "Bud-hole." Okay, now I get it.
I wrote down on a piece of paper
that I needed a private "meditation area."
Tahani will never come in.
Pretty unique decorating style
you have here, Jianyu.
It's like, "12 year-old boy"
meets "13 year-old boy."
Thanks! Janet helped me get all this stuff.
She rules.
Is she single?
Or is she married to Michael?
No, no, dude. You cannot date Janet.
"A," she's not human
and "B," you have to keep pretending
to be Tahani's soulmate.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Cool.
Okay, just sit tight, dude.
I have a class to get to.
What? A... a class?
I... I didn't know there were classes!
I was sick.
I have a note.
- No, no, no.
Chidi is trying to teach me
to be a good person, and it's really hard.
Also, Michael has asked me to be
his "assistant," whatever that means.
My whole situation here is getting
like more and more dicey.
So I'm actually really glad to have a place
I can come when I just want to be myself.
Yeah. I miss being myself.
Myself was the best.
Whoo!
What's up, man? You Jason?
You got two minutes.
Fred Durst is throwing an orgy
on a partially capsized yacht.
My dad just texted, it already started.
So I'll get right to the point,
I listened to your demo. You're terrible.
Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, you just don't have any...
what's the word? Talent.
But don't worry, you got something
better than talent, man.
You got my approximate size and weight.
I'm supposed to play this club
for the rest of the week
but I just got an offer
to DJ Scott Disick's afterparty
for the Amateur Porn Awards in Reno.
Whoa! Congrats, bro! That's the dream!
It's your dream, man. It's my Tuesday.
I just need somebody to fill in.
Put on the helmet,
press "space bar" on the computer -
those idiots
won't know the difference.
For the next week,
Jason, you are "Acidcat."
Whoa! There's a lot
of old gum in here!
Tahani! How are things going
in the front of the house?
Because to be perfectly frank,
things in the kitchen are going great!
Okay, I am right on schedule!
Chef Patricia, I have triple-checked
every single detail.
Your restaurant opening is going to be
the talk of the entire Neighbourhood!
Thank you for your thoughtfulness
and hard work!
I could not have done this without you!
Ah! Hello, Tahani.
Sorry, I should've warned you.
Patricia is actually very happy
but she's also very intense.
It can be confusing.
No, no, no, that's not
what's bothering me.
It's just that, well...
I looked at the guest list earlier
and Jianyu isn't invited?
Right.
Jianyu is a beautiful spirit.
But he literally doesn't talk.
And since this will be
an evening of lively conversation
and you'll be busy working,
I didn't want him to feel uncomfortable.
I totally understand.
Well-reasoned, Michael.
As us Brits are fond of saying,
"Try your best to hide your sadness."
So the concept of the "self"
is a key subject for a lot of great thinkers.
In the Tao Te Ching, Lao Tzu wrote -
"Knowing others is wisdom.
But knowing the self is enlightenment."
Ah! "Knowing yourself?"
Is he talking about
what I think he's talking about?
No, Eleanor, once again
none of these philosophers
is ever talking about masturbation.
Let's, uh... move on
to this week's main event...
David Hume's
"A Treatise of Human Nature."
You read this, right?
- I did.
Well, I tried to.
Well, I tried to want to.
Um, actually,
could we postpone this lesson?
I've befriended Jianyu from next door,
and I thought I could learn from him.
That's a great idea.
Hume's "bundle theory" of the self
is fairly close to Buddhism.
Yeah, no "durr!"
That's why I'm doing it.
Do you hear music?
That's not music.
That's EDM!
What are you doing?
Eleanor, you were right!
No more pretending!
It's time for me to be myself!
What's up, homey?
Eleanor? You broke Jianyu!
Okay, did we miss anything?
Ugh! Take that jersey off,
you goofball!
Okay. This is not my fault, I swear.
Eleanor, one hour ago,
that man was a silent Buddhist monk!
Right, but here's the thing.
Jianyu is actually...
a guy who is nice! Hi, Tahani!
Eleanor! Chidi! What a lovely surprise.
Don't mind me, I'm just dropping off
my afternoon gloves
and picking up my early evening gloves.
How are you, soulmate?
- I'm cool.
I'm sorry, am I going mad
or did I just hear you say, "I'm cool?"
Mmm. Mm-mm. I don't think so.
I don't think that happened.
You're... you're wrong.
Oh, I see what's going here.
You've got a Whisper
in your Snicker box!
You're both helping Jianyu
to regain his confidence
to be able to speak again!
As a surprise for me!
- Oh, busted.
My heart is soaring!
So Jianyu is talking? Oh, how wonderful!
I will do everything in my power
to encourage him.
Well, not everything.
I won't give him a second mouth -
unless that would be helpful?
No. Better not risk it.
I've actually had a better idea.
Oh!
- Let's add Jianyu to the guest list.
Chidi and Eleanor
have been working with him
and they're going to be here.
- What a great idea!
Patricia?
We can fit another chair, right?
Change the floor plan?
An hour before opening?
Of course! The more the merrier!
Oh, hurrah!
I knew tonight was going to be perfect,
but now it is going to be even perfect-er!
Obviously, it's impossible for something
to be more perfect than perfect.
Well, it isn't, actually.
Any place or thing in the universe
can be up to one hundred
and four percent perfect.
That's how you got Beyoncé.
Oh!
Oh. "Bud-hole."
Okay. Now, tell me everything.
Okay. Jianyu is a fraud
just like me.
His real name is Jason.
He's a drug-dealing DJ from Florida.
It's gonna be fine. We just need a plan.
Oh, I got a plan.
We hack into Michael's phone
download all his nudes,
and then blackmail him.
No. What are you ta— No!
Yo, you should listen to me!
I came up with hundreds
of plans in my life
and only one of them got me killed.
Dude! Be quiet!
You are not Jason. You are a monk
named Jianyu.
Got it?
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Dude, another great set, Jason.
They love you, dude!
They don't love me, man.
They love Acidcat.
These cheers are fake.
They hit my ears
like boxing gloves of sadness.
Whoa.
That's some poetic thoughts, "B."
I gotta be myself!
Attention Jacksonville.
I'm not Acidcat.
I'm Mr Music, the DJ.
And this is a Mr Music, the DJ original!
"NO!"
- Pow!
Welcome to the opening
of "The Good Plates".
I just got that.
That's hilarious!
Anyway, at some point or another
every resident in this Neighbourhood
will fulfill his or her soul's true purpose.
Chef Patricia has done that tonight,
by opening this restaurant!
Now, if you'd all like
to take a look at tonight's menus.
That's right!
With Michael's help
Chef Patricia has recreated
each person's favourite meal on Earth!
Fun!
It's my Grandmother's maafe!
Fresh perch, slow roasted
in a peanut sauce.
Almost makes me forget
how miserable I am right now.
You want to try a bite?
Fish and peanut butter?
No, I'm good, thanks.
Tofu? Aw, man!
I'm ordering some jalapeño poppers.
Shh! Be quiet and eat your white sponge.
Janet?
- Hi, there.
Hi. I didn't get a meal.
According to our files
your favourite "meal" was
the hunger strike you went on
to protest Bolivian sex trafficking.
Oh, right. Of course I did that.
Tahani? Great party.
Check it out.
Oh!
- Suspenders!
So dumb.
So much dumber than belts.
Ah, congratulations, Michael.
How's Jianyu doing?
Is he opening up?
Mmm... not yet.
But I can tell he wants to.
Don't worry. I've got a plan.
May I have your attention please?
Later this evening,
we will be enjoying
Chef Patricia's delicious dessert -
a stunning, three-tiered cake
that took her a full week to complete.
But first, I'd like to try something fun.
Each one of you has a very special memory
attached to the meal you're eating.
Why don't we go around the room
and share our stories?
Who'd like to begin?
I'll start, Michael!
One day, I wasn't feeling so great
so I made myself
a bowl of this chicken soup...
When it gets to you, say something short
and boring about tofu.
No! I'm sick of pretending
to be Jianyu the tofu man.
I'm gonna tell the story
about my real favourite meal.
Which is?
The Buffalo wings at Stupid Nick's
Wing Dump in Gainesville.
Wings were free for ladies
if they took their top off!
Oh, boy. Chidi? A word?
Anyway, that's how this simple soup
saved over ten thousand lives.
If Jianyu starts talking about topless
buffalo wing restaurants, we're all screwed!
Well maybe we should just let him talk.
He says he doesn't want to hide anymore.
He doesn't know what he wants.
He's an idiot from Florida.
He's a "Floridiot."
Jianyu Li, Taiwanese monk who took
a vow of silence at the age of eight
and hasn't spoken since,
is ready to share with us.
Let me tell you about Stupid Nick.
We need a distraction!
Right the fork now!
No, no, no, no! Eleanor!
Chef Patricia poured her heart
and soul into this.
Destroying it would be
a truly cruel act.
Yeah, no "durr."
- No, no, no!
Sinkhole!
Everyone out, there's a sinkhole!
Glenn!
You broke the world!
It's not a compliment!
Glenn? Stay calm!
We're gonna get you out of there!
And we'll put your soup in the fridge,
so it won't go to waste!
I know that may not be
your number one concern right now, but...
It was up there. It's real good soup!
Let's go.
Hey, buddy!
You okay?
No. I was just about to tell
an awesome story
about a wing-eating contest
that I lost
and a barfing contest that I won
but then a hole opened up in the ground!
I know. I made the hole,
to save you from yourself.
You cannot let people know
who you really are.
It would be very, very bad.
Beautiful, beautiful Jacksonville.
What's wrong, dog?
You look like you're freaking out.
Things are bad, Pillboi.
Acidcat is suing me
for "bleach of contract."
I should have never pretended
to be someone else.
It could cost me
all my dreams in life.
You got dreams in life?
That's lit!
Course I have dreams, man!
I don't want to be a DJ
in Jacksonville forever.
I want to DJ in Daytona,
Tallahassee, Tampa, even.
I want it all.
That's big goals, man.
I know. But I believe in myself.
Someday, the world will see
what I already know -
that Jason Mendoza
is a beautiful, unique soul
who has so much to give this world.
Okay, that's Acidcat's speedboat.
Hand me the thing that blows it up.
That's lit.
Michael, I hereby tender my resignation.
I can no longer, in good conscience,
coordinate any further events
in the Good Place,
so I am turning in my evening gloves.
Tahani...
- Don't try to make me feel better.
The launch was a disaster.
Poor Jianyu was so terrified
that I fear he may never speak again.
My hair is barely
cascading down my shoulders!
Tahani, please.
I know your journey
with Jianyu has been frustrating.
But your situation is actually very typical.
Soulmates sometimes
take months to really click.
You have to be patient.
And if anyone should take the blame
for the restaurant disaster, it's me.
I thought this Neighbourhood's
troubles were behind us.
Now I fear the worst.
Michael.
I hereby rescind
the tendering of my resignation.
We must keep
the Neighbourhood together.
What can I do?
Oh! Well, the sinkhole should be
repairing itself in about three days.
Well, as soon as it does,
we shall relaunch the restaurant!
I'll hang posters to get the word out.
And in the meantime,
I'll host a brunch party, every morning,
to lift people's spirits.
While you "re-pair" the universe,
I shall "pre-pare" the eggs!
Oh! Fanciful wordplay!
Indeed! That is the Tahani
that you know and love!
So what do we do, here?
There's nothing to do.
He's just gonna blab and get him
and me both sent to the Bad Place.
It's hopeless.
Can't believe I'm doing this but,
Jason, please come to my classroom.
I will teach you ethics,
like I'm doing with Eleanor
and if you work hard
and absorb the material
you just might be able
to earn your place here.
Nah, I'm good.
Dude! Chidi is giving you a lifeline
right now and you need to take it.
Because you suck!
You suck!
- I know!
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
We both suck!
You know who doesn't suck?
Chidi. He is putting himself
in danger to help us
because he, unlike us,
is an amazing person.
I didn't get into heaven
to go to school.
You didn't get into heaven at all,
shirt for brains!
I just want to be myself.
That's a very, very bad idea.
Do not be yourself.
You need to be a better version
of yourself, okay?
And I do, too.
And our only hope right now
is this kind, selfless, amazing nerd.
Think about that.
Eh, do you have to call me
a "nerd" so much?
I said a lot of other nice things,
okay?
Toughen up, nerd.
Let's get cracking, teach!
I read this entire David Hume book,
and then I read it again
because I didn't understand it
the first time, and now I'm ready to go!
Wow. Uh, that's really impressive.
Uh, where's Jianyu?
Honestly, I don't even know
if he's coming.
I am here to learn about "ethnics".
Wow! That's great, man!
Um, I mean, it's "ethics"
but that's great.
Pretty sure it's "ethnics."
Hey, buddy? I'm proud of you.
This is your first step
towards not sucking.
Cool. I just have two questions.
When are football tryouts,
and does this school have a prom?
Oh, no.
- Oh, wow.
For the first time ever,
I'm the smartest kid in class.