No, no, no.
Sorry, Ron, doors
are locked.
We've taken your key cards
and your phones,
and the automatic timer won't go
off until tomorrow at 8:00 a.m.
You're trapped in there.
We told security not to disturb
you under any circumstances.
And the phones and internet?
Oh, they've been disconnected.
And I left a rusty
hacksaw on the table,
so the first person who hacks
their face off gets release.
That's not—what?
Is that true?
Guys, this is insane, okay?
Let us out.
Oh, my God, babe.
Game of Thrones is on tonight.
It's the series finale.
Khaleesi is marrying
Jack Sparrow.
Oh, God, that show has really
gone off the rails.
It makes sense
if you've read the books.
Look, our baby monitor
is on the table.
If you guys can talk this out and settle
your differences like grown-ups,
turn it on, and I will come
to get you from my office.
Otherwise, we will see you
at 8:00 a.m. tomorrow morning.
I am going to break out of here,
then I am going to snap you in half.
Hey.
This is not his fault, Swanson.
Be a man,
and get your house in order.
You too, Knope.
Good luck, you guys. I really hope
you can work out your differences.
Terry, look at me.
Is this what you
want to do?
Think very carefully, son.
There you go.
That's right, buddy.
Come on.
For once in your life,
do something right.
Stop it, Terry.
Both of you.
Come on.
Damn it, Terry!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
Okay, think.
There must be a way
out of here.
I don't think there is.
They installed these magnetic
locks two years ago.
There's no way around them.
Yes, there is.
I'll simply punch my fist
through a window.
Ron, there's security wire in there.
You'll slice your arm open.
I would rather bleed out than sit here
and talk about my feelings for ten hours.
There is another way.
We'll just wait a few minutes,
turn on this monitor,
and then we'll tell Ben that
we talked it out and made up.
I'll just tell them that
I apologized for...
whatever, heroically
caring too much,
and you admitted that you're a stubborn
butthead, and everything's fine now.
Why do I have
to be stubborn?
Why can't the problem have been that
I was reasonable and you were at fault?
Because we want
them to believe us
and not laugh really hard at a ridiculous
science fiction scenario.
We are not saying
I was the problem.
If we're gonna lie to them,
I will not let you lie to them.
Fine! I'll tell them that
for the past three years,
you've been a perfect
gentleman and scholar,
and I am an insane weirdo who,
despite being the only reason
we even had a friendship
to begin with,
decided to ruin it out of
the blue for no good reason.
That sounds good.
Let's go with that.
- What are you doing?
- I destroyed the monitor!
What if we have an emergency
and have to get out of here?
I did not consider
that possibility!
Everything's different.
I mean, the furniture,
the pictures.
Craig changed everything.
Did he?
I tried not to notice anything
when I worked here.
Or talk to anyone.
Or learn anyone's name.
You, of all people,
should know that, Lauren.
Look, we are gonna be here
for ten hours.
We could either talk about our issues
and work through our problems,
or we can just sit
here doing nothing.
I choose "sit here."
- Come on, Ron, why don't we just—
- Sit here.
- Ron.
I bet I can make you talk.
I'll take that bet
at any odds, for any
amount of money,
over any length of time stretching
from now into infinity.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Talk to me. Talk to me. Talk to me. Talk
to me. Talk to me. Talk. Talk. Talk.
Talk to me!
Drip. Drip.
One word,
and this is over.
I think wood is stupid,
and so does everybody else.
You guys, Ron
loves plastic.
Last chance, Ron.
You want to talk? Huh?
Aha!
Jackpot.
You know what
this is, Ron?
This is a mix I made for
the summer Parks barbecue, 2007.
I asked everyone in the Parks
Department to choose one song.
You chose Buddy
by Willie Nelson,
a fact I remember
because my mind
is a steel trap
of friendship nuggets.
But I am not going
to play your choice.
I'm gonna play
Jerry's choice.
Ooh, that's right.
And I'm gonna sing along.
And I'm gonna maintain eye
contact the whole time.
And guess what.
I don't know the words.
♪ Harry Truman was a guy ♪
♪ America, Red China ♪
♪ All the countries,
other people ♪
♪ Everyone is fun ♪
♪ Joe Mantegna, Ian McKellen ♪
♪ I have to buy a new toaster ♪
♪ This is awesome,
you're so stupid ♪
♪ Jumping up and down ♪
Whoo!
Oh, I got it on repeat.
Come on, Ron.
Do you want to hear it again,
or do you want to talk? No?
Okay, next verse.
♪ Freddy Krueger
bought some pants ♪
♪ Oprah has a turtle farm ♪
♪ Peter Piper
pee-pee poopy ♪
- ♪ Daddy ate a squirrel ♪
- Stop this!
♪ Eisenhower, vaccine ♪
I will speak with you
for three minutes.
Great.
So...
what would you like
to talk about?
Oh, come on, Ron. We were
friends for ten years.
We were work proximity
associates.
We were friends.
And now we're not.
And once again, it is up to me
to save our friendship,
and I will do so using the most
powerful tool known to man:
A well-organized chart.
Three years ago, I accept
a job at National Parks.
You and I see each other less,
admittedly,
due to my busy schedule
and your utter lack of interest
in maintaining
adult friendships.
Work proximity
associate-ships.
Three months later, April comes
to work for me. We throw her a party.
At her request,
the party's theme is
"Zombie Teenage Biker Gang
Pizza Jamboree."
I remember. You made me
wear a leather jacket.
That is the last time you and I see
each other for more than five minutes.
Three months later,
you come and visit me
at my office on the third floor
for the very first time.
One week later,
I return from a trip,
and I find out you have quit
the Parks Department
and you have started your
own building company
without even bothering
to tell me.
"Oh, well," I think to myself. "You
know, it was only a matter of time."
And then, two months after
that, Morningstar—
- the final twist of the knife.
- Oh, for God's sake.
I hear about Morningstar, and I calmly
saunter down to your office
and attempt to have a rational
discussion with you about it.
What the hell, Ron?
You're building your stupid building
on the block next to Pawnee Commons?
The park that I built
from scratch out of a pit?
This building is gonna ruin
the views, you jerk.
And you're gonna tear
all the houses down?
- Yes.
- Ann lived there, Ron.
That's Ann's old house. That's my
best friend's old house.
That was the house where I put on my
wedding dress the night I got married.
That is the house where April
and Andy met for the first time.
That is the house where Ann gave
me my first ever smoky eye look.
She hasn't lived there
for five years.
That's not the point.
This building is
a monstrosity.
And what's it called?
Morningstar?
"Oh, dear. We live
at the Morningstar.
That's so posh and
hibbley-fibbley-gibbley."
The world needs
apartment buildings.
The park you built is nice,
and people want to live next to it.
That's not the point.
You knew that
I would be furious,
and you didn't have the guts
to tell me yourself.
Enjoy your new job, Judas.
You tear down Ann's house.
You spend the next two years
cutting down trees
and fighting zoning laws
that I helped pass,
basically spitting on everything
we did together at Parks.
That's not
the whole story.
What does that mean?
It means what it means.
That...
is not the whole
story of why I left.
Sorry, time is up.
Wait.
Why then? What was the reason?
Ron, come on.
Oh, my God, you made a key?
Ron, please, don't—
Come on, Ron.
Ron, just talk to me.
- Ron, come on.
- See you tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Progress.
Is it that I sent you a birthday
card through the US mail,
so the post office
knew your address?
No. Go away.
Ooh, is it because
I had Food and Stuff
temporarily shut down due
to a health code violation?
That was you?
They had fresh produce out
right next to the roach spray.
The name of the store
is "Food and Stuff."
They sell food,
and they sell stuff.
If you don't like it, go to that
new place, Complete Food.
It's called Whole Foods.
- And is that really the reason?
- No.
How many more questions
are you going to ask me?
As many as I need to to solve
this mystery and get us engaged
in a deep and stimulating
conversation about our friendship.
- Ron, what are you doing?
- I know I saw it.
Aha!
Detonator.
The partially defused claymore
mine you gave me ten years ago.
I'm gonna use it to blow a hole in this
damn door so I can get out of here.
- Ron, just wait a second.
- No.
I'm being held as a prisoner
against my will,
and I have the right, as
a citizen of the United States,
to blow a hole in that fucking
door and walk out as a free man.
It's in the Constitution.
There's no cursing
in the Constitution.
Look, before you do that—
Too late. Here we go.
Fire in the hole!
Whoo!
♪ ♪
I gave you that as a gift
on your fifth anniversary
as Parks director.
You told me
this was a genuine partially
defused claymore mine.
Well, it was. I bought
the empty shell off of eBay,
and then I filled it with, you know,
balloons and confetti and such.
You mean to tell me I have had
a toy on my desk for ten years?
You mean to tell me
you've thought
you had an actual land
mine on your desk?
Congratulations, Ron. You've been
doing an explosive job!
Come on, Ron.
It's funny stuff.
Who gets angry at balloons?
Good talk.
What's all this?
I'm just reading back through
some of our old projects,
trying to figure out what
happened that made you quit.
Good God, woman.
This is a code.
I am going to break it.
And this is my best shot.
Is that nuclear waste?
No, this is my job application
from when you hired me.
How did you get that?
Freedom of Information
Act request.
But here's the thing.
I've never read it.
This application contains your
very first impressions of me.
It's the Rosetta Stone, Ron.
The beginning of
the whole shebang.
This is all you wrote?
Three lousy lines?
Why would anyone need
more than three lines?
I'm describing a person,
not something complicated like a wooden
sailing ship or proper dovetail technique.
I forgot what I wrote.
Can I hear it?
Why don't you read it yourself?
"Leslie Knope is an absurd
idealist whose political leanings
are slightly to the left
of Leon Trotsky."
So far, so accurate.
"If we were to work together, she
would undoubtedly drive me insane,
and it is possible that we
would murder each other."
You forgot
the last sentence.
No, I didn't.
I remember that part.
It says, "Hire her."
Did you hear that?
Oh, it's— it's a person.
It's another person!
Hello! Hello!
- Janitor!
- Hey!
- Hey, we're trapped in here!
♪ The best thing about
being a woman ♪
♪ Is the prerogative ♪
Please, Mr. Janitor. If you just
look over here for two seconds,
- I'll do anything.
- Hey!
I'll watch a foreign film. I'll talk
to a man with a ponytail.
Oh, he's gone, Ron.
He's gone.
Why did you give
me the job?
And that's what I don't get. We
should've never worked together.
Why did you hire me?
Because of your interview.
Okay, that doesn't
make any sense.
I mean, I remember
that interview.
You were wearing
that exact outfit.
And you said to me, "Ms. Knope,
I have one question for you.
What do you believe the role
of government is in America?"
You blathered on for
ten minutes about
social safety nets and honest
governance and improving lives.
Basic nonsense.
Then you said, "Everything that just came
out of your mouth is basic nonsense.
Good day."
- And that was it.
- No, that was not it.
After I said you
were full of it,
you got very angry and scrunched
up your face and said,
"Excuse me, sir,
but I disagree."
Did you let me have it.
That was one of your top
ten tirades, I'd say.
You were pounding your
fist and shaking.
You called me
a heartless thug.
I most certainly did not.
You were tough and honest,
and you stood up for
what you believed in,
even though it might've killed
your chance to get the job.
I would rather work with a person like
that than with a milquetoast yes-man.
Should be one more
thing in that file.
Aw, it's the thank-you note I wrote
to you after the interview.
You kept it.
"Dear Mr. Swanson, I'm sorry for
raising my voice in the interview,
and I'm sorry I called
you a heartless thug."
Oh, well, okay.
There you go.
"If it matters,
I promise I would never
raise my voice at you
if we worked together."
- Liar.
- Yeah, I was being really optimistic.
"Please enjoy these homemade brownies
as a gesture of goodwill. Leslie Knope."
That was the real
reason I hired you.
Those brownies
were damn good.
Ron, look how
far we've come.
We're doing so great.
Let's just bring it home, okay?
Let's just talk about our issues.
- Leslie, don't push it.
- Okay, fine.
If I guess and guess right,
you have to tell me.
Ready?
Two years ago, you found out
you were 1/4 French,
and you had a nervous
breakdown.
Okay, playtime is over.
I'm getting out of
here once and for all.
No, Ron! God, no!
That alarm is just
for sprinklers.
April kept pulling it, so the fire
department disconnected it.
I see.
Ron? I found some towels.
You okay?
Wow.
Apparently,
Craig is studying yoga.
These are the only
dry clothes I could find.
- Well, you look great.
- I feel extremely angry.
Oh, come on.
Stop whining, you big baby.
I've seen you with your
eyebrows blown off.
I've seen you
without a mustache.
I've seen it all.
There's nowhere to run, Ron.
You have tried every
possible means of escape.
There's nothing
to do but talk.
What happened to these "workplace
proximity associates"?
Hmm?
Spill it.
You left.
Then a month later,
you took Terry with you.
Yeah, well, we needed a mindless
factotum, and he's the best there is.
Amen.
Then you took April.
I didn't want her to go,
as she had become
one of my closest
workplace acquaintances.
But your offer was too good to pass
up, so I didn't try to stop her.
Then Tom left
to run his business.
Donna left to run hers.
One day, I looked up.
Just didn't
recognize anyone.
So I made a decision.
An unthinkable decision.
Hey.
Well, my, my, my.
Do my eyes deceive me?
- Is that Ron Swanson?
- Hello, Leslie.
Hello, April. Larry.
- It's Terry now.
- Okay.
- As luck would have it—
- One second. Oh.
Did you talk to Randy
about the vote?
Tell the Northeast that we
need to put pressure on them,
or else we're gonna be waiting forever,
and I'm tired of waiting on them, okay?
Sorry. This is
a crazy day.
So what's up with you,
you big lug?
Nothing important. Just thought
you might want to have lunch.
- Tomorrow?
- I would love to.
It's been too long.
JJ's Diner, 12:30?
- Excellent. See you then.
- Okay.
So Randy says the House
is voting tomorrow,
and they need us in
Washington to prep.
Oh, my God, really?
Okay, get us the first flight out of
here and grab the Missouri files.
Meet me at my car.
Hey, babe. I got
to go to Washington.
Can you pick up the kids?
Oh. Oh, no.
Ron, I stood you
up for lunch.
You did, yes.
I waited for a while,
but it was pretty easy
to figure out what
had happened.
Your life seemed
pretty hectic.
Is that the rest of the story?
That I stood you up?
You were going
to ask me something.
That's why you wanted
to have lunch.
- Ron, you were going—
- I was gonna ask you for a job.
In the federal government.
Just saying it out
loud feels dirty.
You missed your friends,
and you wanted to come up to the third
floor and work with us again.
I can't even imagine how hard
that must have been for you.
God, why didn't I see that?
Ron, I am so sorry.
I should've been
a better friend to you.
Honestly, Leslie, it's fine.
It was a punctuation mark on a sentence
that had already been written.
My time in government
work was over.
Sure, I loved
shutting things down
and bleeding the rotting
beast from the inside.
Your metaphors are
so beautiful.
But it was time
for me to leave,
and I didn't feel like
explaining why to you or anyone.
Everything that happened
after— the fight we had,
not giving you a heads-up when my company
took on the Morningstar development
and bulldozed
the nurse's old house—
I do regret that.
I had a good run here.
But after you and Tom and Donna
and April and Terry left,
when I looked around
this office,
nothing was the same.
Yeah, well, there's a way
to fix that.
♪ Laugh with me, buddy ♪
♪ Jest with me, buddy ♪
♪ Don't let her get
the best of me, buddy ♪
♪ Don't ever let me start ♪
♪ Feelin' lonely ♪
♪ ♪
♪ If I ever needed you, buddy ♪
♪ You know now
I really do, buddy ♪
♪ Don't ever let me start ♪
♪ Feelin' lonely ♪
♪ It's got a new queen ♪
♪ Everybody really mean ♪
♪ We didn't start the fire ♪
♪ It was always burning since
the world's been turning ♪
Well, this is different
from what I expected to find.
♪ Fire ♪
Oh. Morning, guys.
Good morning, Leslie.
What did you do
to the office?
Ron, you're wearing my yoga clothes.
You're gonna stretch out the elastic.
We're sorry.
♪ Fire and money and people ♪
Hey. I moved our
meetings to tomorrow
because you are drunk and hungover
simultaneously at 2:00 in the afternoon.
Yeah. Good call.
Also, you have a visitor.
No, whoever it is,
I have zero interest in—
- Hello.
- Ron!
Ron, Ron, Ron, Ron, Ron.
We just spent 12 hours
together, woman.
Mm, don't care.
I have three years' worth of hugs
to force upon you against your will.
I have a small
object for you.
Call it an official peace
offering, I suppose.
Wow. This is very sweet.
But you do realize I gave you
this picture six hours ago.
The frame is the gift.
When my company took on
the Morningstar development,
and I realized it meant
bulldozing Ann's old house,
I salvaged her front door.
Then I stripped off all
the terrible paint and lacquer—
people really don't know
how to finish wood properly—
and I made it into this frame for you
in the event that you and I ever...
Ron. You big,
fat, giant sap.
- That seems unnecessary.
- I love it.
But I feel bad. I don't
have anything for you. I—
For the first time in my
life, I am present-less.
How 'bout you
buy me a meal?
- You hungry?
- I'm starving.
April, Ron and I are going
to JJ's to eat too much breakfast food.
Why does anybody in the world ever
eat anything but breakfast food?
People are idiots, Ron.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther