We need to go over the schedule
leading up to the primary.
- Let's talk shop.
- Ooh, shop talk!
One of my five favorite
types of talk,
along with pillow, girl,
real, and TED.
Why are you wearing a poncho?
Oh, because every surface area
in your house is sticky.
Last time I was here, I found
a melted crayon on my blazer.
Okay.
I have a photo op
with Gryzzl tomorrow.
Between now and then, we
have a ton of stuff scheduled.
Looks like we're gonna have
to skip the pie-baking event
and the ceremonial squash toss.
- Oh.
- Oh, really?
We have to skip that?
I love watching those squashes
fly through the air.
I kind of like
the way they land.
Me too!
Okay, excuse me,
but I have to get back to a city
where things happen.
Okay.
This campaign is about to start
in earnest.
Things are about to get
real intense.
Leslie, you ready?
- Me Leslie?
- Yeah.
Well, I was an actual candidate,
so I think I can handle
being a candidate's wife.
I know all the issues
inside and out.
Mm.
See, that's the problem.
Being the wife of
is a minefield.
If you were just
a ding-dong,
I would just
slap a flag pin on you.
I'd pour some Valium
down your throat
and just shove you behind
the podium way upstage.
It's the smarties
that freak people out.
I think you're underestimating
the voters.
I don't think that is possible.
Stephen, be careful!
Poncho!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I know you normally
hate foundations,
but this one
I think you'll actually like.
We take people that don't know
what they want to do
and then put them to work doing
cool stuff all over the world,
and I start in a couple months.
Well, I had hoped you'd choose
a more dignified trade
like masonry or logging,
but you are
out of local government,
and that's a step
in the right direction.
It's definitely
the job I wanted...
But it means that we
have to move to Washington.
Well...
then bully for you.
If you intend to move,
I suppose you should return
the spare key to my house,
the one I gave you years ago
when you were my assistant,
for emergencies.
Okay.
Good talk.
This neighborhood
has been mostly abandoned
for years,
but now, thanks
to the new Gryzzl headquarters,
this district will soon
transform
into a hub of innovation
for decades to come.
Mr. Wyatt!
Your campaign released
a schedule,
and it looks like your wife
is skipping the Pie-mary.
Care to explain?
The Pie-mary
is a Southern Indiana tradition
where Congressional
candidates' wives
face off
in a pie-baking contest.
The last contest winner
was June Hartwell's
buttermilk meringue.
Last contest loser
was all women.
Leslie would be the first
candidate's wife
not to enter the Pie-mary.
What kind of a statement
are you making by skipping it?
We're... I'm not making
any kind of statement.
We're just focusing
on bigger issues,
like Ben's $150 million
revitalization project.
Pardon me.
I need to get through.
Pardon me. Excuse me.
Mike Patterson here.
Leslie, you've
made it pretty clear
that you don't think homemaking
is important.
Do you ever cook
for your children,
and who's even watching
your children right now,
while you're out
God only knows where?
What are you talking about?
I'm standing right here
in front of you.
Okay. Take it easy.
Let's not get emotional.
Okay.
We have to run.
We'll see you all
at my economic address.
Thanks for coming, everybody.
What other traditions
are you against, Leslie?
Baseball?
Hugging your children?
How much did that haircut cost?
None of your business,
and thank you for noticing.
My desk was right here,
sitting right on top of it
this whole time.
How much money is it?
It's not money.
I told you, it's Ron's key.
I hid it in here years ago.
Ah! Wait!
Yeah, no. No key.
Just a note and a movie ticket
stub and four teeth.
"If you are looking
for Ron's key,
"I moved it,
and you'll never find it.
Cordially, April."
Well, where'd you put it, then?
I don't know.
It was eight years ago.
Oh, God.
A key to Ron's house is lost
in a government building.
That's his worst nightmare.
Listen, babe.
All we got to do
is train Champion
to sniff out Ron's key.
Okay.
All we need is Ron's key
to give him a scent.
So give me the key,
and I'll get you that key.
No, You're Wrong
with Mike Patterson.
Welcome back to the program.
My guest is June Hartwell,
wife of incumbent Congressman,
Paul Hartwell.
Now, June, we all know
what Ben Wyatt's wife
is really saying.
By skipping the Pie-mary,
she's saying women who love
their families are stupid.
Well, Mike, we all
make certain choices.
Ms. Knope chose
to try to have it all.
I chose to put my family first.
Well, I'm just speculating here,
but do you think
that Leslie Knope's actions
indicate that she actually hates
her family?
Well, it only took three hours
for Jen to be right.
I'm officially a distraction.
I'm gonna enter
that Pie-mary.
This is just nonsense.
It'll blow over.
And the Pie-mary
is ridiculous and antiquated.
But the more
they talk about this,
the less they're gonna talk
about your economic plan.
Besides,
I'm good at making pies,
so I'll win,
and then I can promote
my self-published women's rights
barbecue cookbook...
The Feminine Mesquite.
Everything's fine.
I had it in a safe place,
and then I moved it
to protect it,
and I don't remember where.
I see.
Don't be mad, Ron.
She hid it too good,
and she left a string of clues.
It's an impossible puzzle,
and I love puzzles!
A minimal, unhelpful note,
these appear to be human teeth,
and what is this?
Twilight: New Moon.
It's a movie,
but I've never seen it.
It's, like,
about lame werewolves
and vampires and stuff.
Donna likes those things!
Dollars to doughnuts
this points us her way.
Finally, a scavenger hunt
worthy of my time.
Onward!
Okay.
Snacks given, kids tucked in,
books read,
three simultaneous meltdowns
for no reason,
kids tucked back in,
one of them briefly
got outside somehow,
kids back in bed.
They're all napping.
Okay, I got everything
you need for pie domination.
I even got
an extra whipped-cream can.
One for baking,
one for directly-into-mouth.
Oh, you know me so well.
That might be one of the kids.
Hi, Leslie.
Elise Yarktin
from the Indiana
Organization of Women.
Oh, my goodness!
Elise, please come in.
Wait!
Are you here to give me
the Woman of the Year award?
I have a speech prepared.
Would you like
to see it right now?
No.
Leslie, we were thrilled
to find out you were boycotting
that ridiculous Pie-mary,
but we just got word
you've decided to enter?
Yeah.
Well, I agree that it's dumb,
but this is not about me.
It's about Ben, and he will do
more for women than Hartwell.
So, you know, lose a battle,
win the war.
That kind of thing.
It's the way to go.
Look, the Pie-mary
is retrogressive
and misogynistic,
and if you participate,
we will have no choice
but to protest you and Ben
at the event.
Hope you like pies...
in yo' face.
Metaphorically.
We'll be civil.
Elise, there is no bigger
defender of gender equality
than Leslie Knope,
and my husband, Ben,
is a progressive champion
of women's rights.
Babe, the oven's ready.
Chop-chop!
Time to get baking.
Daddy want pie!
Hi. Ben Wyatt.
We have a wonderfully
small number of clues.
One is this ticket.
Did you see this movie
about vampires and such?
New Moon?
Yeah, I saw it with April.
She was so hopped up
on painkillers
from getting
her wisdom teeth out,
I convinced her
to see it with me.
The teeth!
They're yours.
You were super out of it.
You kept yelling,
"Team Voldemort!" at the screen,
and we were kicked out.
I was furious.
You only get to see
the second Twilight film
for the seventh time once.
Do you remember anything
about a key
or April doing
anything unusual that day?
She did make us stop
by the shoe-shine stand
before she left,
because she wanted
to drop something off for Andy.
She had a real bad crush on him.
Oh, babe! You had a crush on me!
That's embarrassing.
We're married.
Still!
To the shoe-shine stand!
- Stop! Stop!
- Ooh, chase me!
Garry, what the hell
are you doing?
Oh, gosh.
Well, I dropped my wedding ring
down this grate,
and then I was trying
to get it out,
and I dropped my keys
down there too,
so I can't leave.
Damn. This takes me back.
You mind if I stay and watch?
Oh, not at all.
Appreciate the company.
The I.O.W.
does not mess around,
which, normally,
is why I love them,
but now I'm on the other side.
Oh, my God, Ben!
I gave them $100
in their annual pledge.
Do you know how many anti-me
signs that could buy?
You just don't do
the pie contest, obviously.
Then we're just back
where we started.
Then it just seems
like I'm saying
I'm better
than the women who bake.
What should we do?
Should we get a divorce?
Well, how about this?
What if I register
for the contest?
I bake the pie.
I act as my own wife.
Oh, that could work.
We sidestep the controversy,
we refocus the campaign
onto the actual candidate,
and then we flip the antiquated
tradition right on its head.
Exactly, but more importantly,
we change the idea
of what a pie is.
I feel like
that's not more important,
but I-I like the energy
that we have, so let's hear it.
Okay. Picture this.
Crust on the bottom,
filling, crust on top.
What am I describing?
A pie.
No, but you're
in the right zone.
Oh.
- Calzone!
- Sure.
Pies are just
sweet calzones, honey,
and I'm good at making calzones.
You're amazing.
I can win this thing.
Of course you can, baby!
Get in there and start baking!
♪ Talk about the highway ♪
♪ To the calzone-zone! ♪
I am having
some serious déj? vu.
How many times have you lost
your wedding ring?
Oh, G...
Too many times to count.
And it causes
real trouble with Gayle.
Yeah, I mean,
anytime I lose my ring,
she turns
into a real grumpy goose.
- Is that so?
- Oh, yeah.
She'll say, you know,
"Garry, you'd lose your head
if it wasn't screwed
on tight."
And then she makes me go
for the fresh oranges
for the morning OJ.
Yeah, I mean,
she says, "Hey, Mr. Forgetful."
Well, I mean,
those words...
I mean, they rattle
around here for hours.
That's why
I've got to be extra careful
with this replacement ring,
because if I lost...
I'm gonna order us some dinner.
The shoe-shine stand
is gone...
or maybe it was never here.
They must have moved
it during the remodel.
It's probably
in basement storage.
To the basement!
- Tighter!
- Are you sure, dude?
Yeah, dude. Tighter.
I can do it.
Do what exactly?
Nothing.
We're not doing anything.
And we definitely
do not live down here now.
Guys, where's the old
shoe-shine stand from upstairs?
We don't know anything
about that.
Boys, think.
We are on a quest,
and we are not leaving
until we get an answer.
Well, we're on our own quest,
which is to squeeze this
just tight enough
to make my eyes bulge out
a little bit,
but not so tight that I die.
Oh, I've been there.
That's a real tightrope walk.
Oh! Hey!
Last week this real scary ghost
came down here looking for it.
It had black hair, but you could
see through its skin,
and it didn't like me,
but that's just 'cause
I got a soul of a Ghostbuster.
Yeah, it said something
about how it was worried
Brett was gonna mug it.
Okay, so we're looking
for a racist ghost
with black hair
who likes shoe shines.
I think I have the answer.
The chase continues!
Okay, wait.
The time that you told us you
were mugged in the park,
what were you
reaching for in the river?
- A burrito.
- That's right!
You fell in the river
reaching for a burrito.
Yes, ma'am, that was not
one of my finer moments.
Ooh, it's getting late.
We need to bounce.
- I can give you a ride.
- Oh, thank you, Donna.
Probably gonna get an earful
when I get home tonight.
Gayle might even call me
the B word.
"Bozo."
- Wow.
- Mm.
We are very different people.
Did you hear back from Elise?
Oh, yeah, we're good.
The I.O.W.
is not gonna protest us.
How's your pie?
I don't know.
I didn't make a pie.
Okay.
How is your dessert calzone?
It's ready.
The question is, are they?
All right.
Our next contestant is candidate
Ben Wyatt's wife, Leslie.
Let's see what Mrs. Wyatt
has baked up for us, shall we?
It's actually Ms. Knope,
and, actually, right now
it's Mr. Wyatt.
Leslie has her own busy life,
and I happen to be
an excellent pie maker,
so we figured
we'd switch it up a bit.
Now, pack your suitcases,
because we're going
to a little town
called a-Napoli
in Ital-y.
Free Ben Wyatt! Free Ben Wyatt!
Excuse me.
Free me from what?
From the tyranny of women.
We are the Male Men.
We are a men's rights
activist group,
and we are fed up!
I'm sorry.
What's happening now?
Behind every successful woman
is a man she has oppressed.
First, Leslie Knope
poaches her husband's campaign
by making it all about her.
Now she's forcing him
to bake pies
and enter a contest for her?
Oh, excuse me!
I'm not forcing him
to do anything.
He loves to cook.
He... he has five
personalized aprons.
Oh, so I guess
he was asking for it
because of the way
he was dressed.
We are sick and tired
of this feminized society!
Men have had
a very rough go of it
for... just recently,
and it ends now!
Male and proud!
Male and proud! Male and proud!
Leslie Knope exemplifies
the feminist attack
on our values.
She could learn
a little something
about traditional
family structure
from me and my husband,
Marshall.
Um, fierce alert!
Eat 'em up, honey!
The idea that feminism
is an attack on family values
is absurd.
Ooh, so you're
defending Leslie Knope.
No. Absolutely not.
Frankly, I don't
think she's done enough
to distance herself
from this misogynistic lunacy.
Let's turn,
now, to Sasha Dunkirk.
She is head of the group
Women Against Feminism.
What a surprise!
The woman is only talking
to other women.
Can we have one conversation
about feminism
where men get to be in charge?
I actually agree with him.
I don't need your pity.
Joan, Leslie Knope and I
are united
in our disgust
of this week's events.
Leslie, if you're watching,
I, Brandi Maxxxx,
star of 69 Jump Street
and 50 Shaved Old Gays,
have your back.
Oof!
Really stepped in it
this time, Knope.
Why isn't
the other candidate's wife
being scrutinized like this?
Because June Hartwell
is a lukewarm bowl of nothing.
She started
an awareness campaign
called "Bring a Sweater."
She calls it
goose-bump prevention.
Come on, you guys,
you know the drill.
Just ignore the fact
that you're right,
put on your blandest outfits,
so that one, hopefully,
and then just go out there
and publicly apologize.
Done.
- What?
- Apologize for what?
Doesn't matter.
Just say you're sorry.
It's like taking
a shot of tequila.
You just got to force it down.
Suddenly, the world feels
so much more pleasant.
I do three shots every time
I have to enter this house.
Donna, what are you
doing here so early?
I come bearing gifts.
First off,
I got a dude in maintenance
to open up that grate
this morning.
So here's your rings,
keys, credit cards,
and I found some heart medicine
I assume is yours.
Yeah, no, that's mine.
That's mine. Oh, my gosh.
Also, I thought I'd bring over
some fresh oranges
for you and Gayle.
Okay, well,
that is just so kind, Donna.
Thank you.
- You're one of a kind, Garry.
- Oh.
And I just want to thank you
for taking me down memory lane,
you big B word.
- Oh.
- "Buddy."
So much has
changed around here.
Uhh, I just wanted to remember
the good old days,
when a shoe shine was two bits
and there were no Mexicans
in the music business.
If you don't mind,
Councilman Milton,
we just need
to search this stand.
Yes! Found it.
"Hi, Andy.
I hate people, but you are okay.
It's weird. Woof, woof.
April."
Oh, my God, babe,
you were so into me.
That's hilarious.
That's it.
It's a dead end.
No more clues.
See me in my office.
If it makes you feel any better,
I had a big crush on you too.
It does make me feel
a little better. Thanks.
Oh, thank God.
Get off my boat!
Good afternoon.
I'm here today
to share with you all
my vision for the economic
future of Southern Indiana,
but first, Leslie Knope,
my wife...
has a brief statement.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you. Wow.
How about this weather
we're having?
Very temperate.
Okay.
Recently,
I made an attempt to...
Actually, hang on. Stop.
I'm sorry. This whole thing
just makes me queasy
I love how independent
my wife is,
and because of that,
I will not let her speak.
That came out wrong.
The point is
Leslie is a great mother,
public servant,
all-around person,
and I am tired of everybody
constantly telling her
that she's making
the wrong choice.
So you can say
whatever you want.
I couldn't care less about
the political consequences.
Thank you, Ben.
Well, the first thing
I'm gonna do is say sorry.
I'm sorry that the spotlight
is on me and not on Ben,
because he is going to make
a great congressman.
Second, the Male Men.
Where are you? Ah!
You're ridiculous,
and men's rights is nothing.
Third, I'm now gonna give you
permanent answers
to all the silly questions that
you're gonna end up asking me
and every other woman in this
election over the next few months.
Why did I change my hairstyle?
Well, I don't know, I just
thought it would look better.
Or my kids got gum in it.
Are you trying to have it all?
That question makes no sense.
It's a stupid question.
Stop asking it.
Don't ask it.
Do you miss your kids
while you're at work?
Yes, of course I do.
Everybody does.
And then, you know,
sometimes I don't.
Yeah, and by the way, no one's
ever asked me that question.
No one asks me,
"Where are your kids?"
Or "Who's taking care
of them?"
By the way, who is taking care
of the kids right now?
My mom, babe.
Everything's fine.
Right.
So maybe Leslie doesn't fit
your personal idea of what
a candidate's wife should be.
So what?
That's good,
because there shouldn't be
just one idea anyway.
That's right.
If you want to bake a pie,
that's great.
If you want to have a career,
that's great too.
Do both or neither.
It doesn't matter.
Just don't judge what
someone else has decided to do.
I mean, we're all just trying
to find the right path for us
as individuals on this Earth.
I'd say that's 50/50
boos and cheers.
Yeah, that seems about right.
Let Ben speak!
He just spoke.
Oh. Sorry.
I-I just got here.
I had a broken bike chain.
My bad.
So I guess we are celebrating
that you trusted me
and I let you down.
Great.
I change my house locks
every 16 days.
That key has been useless
since the second Tuesday
after I gave it to you.
What matters is that I trust you
and admire you as a person.
I will be sorry
to see you leave this town
for many reasons...
not the least of which
is that you created a puzzle
that even I couldn't solve.
And boy, oh, boy,
did you love Andy.
"Woof, woof."
It really is embarrassing.
Oh, my God.
I totally know where the key is.
How'd you remember?
"Woof, woof."
Bark.
Why here?
Because this tree
reminds me of you.
It's strong and quiet
and always here when you need it...
or whatever.
I have always felt a
certain kinship with April,
and this is proof
that I was correct...
not the nice things
she said about me,
the fact that I buried
a large amount of gold
under that same tree years ago.
I've since moved it.
Or have I?
- Elise.
- Oh...
What did I do wrong now?
No, actually,
we at the I.O.W.
loved what you said
in your speech.
Really?
But what we loved even more
was how you, Ben,
gave Leslie a platform
in which to speak her mind.
Congratulations, Ben Wyatt.
You are this year's I.O.W.
Woman of the Year.
Son of a bitch.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com