Oh, man, my delts
are blasted.
A chart for how much
protein powder to scoop
for a 180-pound
man with no fat
Protein powder, huh?
You cut it with water?
Why don't you
just take estrogen?
Here
There you go, boys See how
Papa takes care of you
people thought biceps
were all that.
They'd flex them all
night at the discotheque
all about core, huh?
Yeah
Core's critical
There are four tenets of Pilates
that I live my life by.
One, lengthen
Two, elongate
Listen, guys. I think we all want
to know the same thing, right?
Who's the strongest?
There's only one
way to solve that
Thigh curl contest
All right,
here we go, everybody
May the manliest man win
Go
Feast on this, Lewis
I love the burn
The burn is where I live
Come on, Gabe. You can't
handle his hamstrings.
You're getting hypno-thized
Speed set. One
One, two
Here, this is for your elbows
For your elbows
Thank you
You're welcome.
Five, six...
- Seven
Quick phone call for you guys
Keep going. Eight.
Nine
Hello?
- Ten.
We got it?
Very funny, Jim
Yeah, Jim
Way to mock us for
perfecting our bodies
Everyone, conference room
Now.
All right
Easy there, Grandpa
Okay, you don't
need my help?
Here, here, just
Morning
Hey
Somebody left in such a hurry
this morning that she forgot
these
Oh
You know, the only thing more
delicious than your feet
is the feast that I am going
to prepare for everyone.
Andy if you're going to
hang out for a while
Uh.
What's this?
This dumb
new rule Robert made
He just wants
visitors to sign in
Is this Robert's
attempt to embarrass me?
No, of course not
It's just... I think it's like
if we make an exception for you
then we have to make an
exception for the water guy
and then it's like, "Where
does it end?' So, just...
Why is it when other people spend
all their time at tee office,
they're rewarded for it
and when I do it,
"It's a little much"?
Is it because I'm not
an employee anymore?
Because that's
what it feels like
All right
enjoy the Illinois game
Good, we have a deal?
Thanks, Janet
Thanks so much, Earl.
Wow. A simultaneous sale
And they said it couldn't be done.
Boom. Screw them
A lot going on, guys
What's happening?
The Binghamton
branch closed last night
and all their
clients are up for grabs
That was a fine branch
Things are really bad under
Robert California I guess
It's like a festival of poo
Hey, come on, language
Yeah, and we're not interested
in your sour grapes, okay?
Jim, tell him where he
can stick his grapes.
In the fridge
No, Jim.
The butt, in his butt
Sorry, man,
I can't focus on zingers
There's too many
potential clients.
You two better
watch yourselves
Yeah, the Syracuse
branch can't be happy
you're taking
New York clients
Robert, why did
Binghamton close?
Can everyone just
Please
saturnalia last night
in celebration of the
finalization of my divorce
of Australian reds
and, how should I say this
Colombian whites.
Wait, what is this
about Binghamton?
The branch closed, forever
Closing the Binghamton branch never
occurred to me before today.
Or, I guess, last night
But, in vino veritas,
as they say
I'm not going to start
doubting my drunken self now
I got your voice
mail from last night
Wonderful
And the answer is yes
yes, yes, yes,
and never
Pam, when's the last time
you lived so intensely
that your brain, literally,
couldn't hold the memories in?
It was the summer
Apparently,
I left a phone message
for Nellie last night, and I
need you to find out what I said
Um, I am a little busy
Yes
Of course
Why don't you list the things that
would keep you from helping me?
Yeah. I can make you a list
Let's do it now
What's number one?
Why don't I help you now?
Okay There we go
Who the hell are Jim Halpert
and Dwight Schrute?
Jim, Dwight,
what are your last names?
And you are?
Harry Jannerone,
Dunder Mifflin Syracuse
What the hell's all this?
Cherries jubilee
over home-made gelato
You live well down here in PA I
want to talk to you guys right now
And Lloyd Gross, too
Which one's that guy?
The salesmen have
a commission cap,
but we figured
out a way around it
Lloyd Gross is a fictional
salesman we invented to
How do I put this? Steal from the
company, embezzle, to commit fraud
Okay, it sounds sketchy but
it helps us get more money.
Yes
Pam made a drawing
of Lloyd.
He is a blend of
all the salesmen
There he is
That's Lloyd.
Me?
Yeah, you
Where do you get off
crossing state lines?
Now, we're actually closer to
Binghamton than you are
kemo sabe
I like to think Lloyd Gross
is a no-nonsense guy
who doesn't back
down from anybody
and he calls
people "kemo sabe.'
They're New York
we're New York.
State line is
the dividing line
That's the way
it's always been
There's actually not a rule
that says that. It's true
It's true. There's no rule. You
can check the employee handbook
Can I check
the employee handbook, Lloyd?
Does it say anything about me
choking a man with my bare hands?
No
Wait, no? Are you kidding me?
You told me there was a rule.
So many people by now
Stay out of my state It's in your
best interest to stay out of my state
I've seen guys
like you, big guys
who like to push
the little guys around
Lloyd Gross eats bullies
like you for breakfast
Stay out of New York, Lloyd
Text from the old wife
I'm going to take that.
How about this, why don't
we just ask Robert?
Can we all agree that maybe
the CEO should decide this?
Robert's here?
Look at us,
bickering like school girls
looking around the room for
things to hit each other with
were doing that
Chair, lamp, plant,
table leg Jim's leg
Where's the Advil, Jim? I think
I've hit my limit on the Tylenol...
Sorry, not Jim
Andrew, what do we have
to do to get rid of you?
Hire you back and send
Erin back to Florida?
Message received
loud and clear
Just have to get
the caramelized sugar
off the pan
before it dries
Oh, for God's sake
Robert California what a
surprise you're here in Scranton
Harry
So, why would you
close Binghamton down
without a transition plan
in place?
How do you mean?
No, no, no, kid, stay there
Do your dishes. Go ahead
Harry, there is a time
for every decision
predetermined
many years ago
There's no benefit
in questioning why
this particular
decision seems
so poorly timed
Okay, what are you deciding?
We get a say.
Listen Robert, I don't have time.
There's a big client in play
Prestige Direct Mail Solutions
used to be Binghamton's
Don't listen to him.
Nope I want it. It's mine
Prestige is ours
Okay, they're responsible
for half of the junk ma
on the eastern seaboard
We get them.
We already put
a call in to them, Robert
We need you to
make a decision
Make a decision.
I have decided
Neither of you are
to have any contact
with either Prestige
or any other Binghamton client
until I've figured out
how to divide things up
As Solomon once said
There's some bizarre energy
in this place today.
Robert going off the rails,
making some funky decisions
Like why is nobody
going to call on Prestige?
That is a huge client
They could give
their business to
the first person to
walk in the door.
Could be any idiot.
Any idiot at all.
Shaping a company is in a sense,
similar to training a geisha.
You have to mold
not merely the physical form
but also the character
The two must harmonize
Are they still there?
They want a decision
who gets the big client
They can wait
I'll still be talking about
geishas long past their bedtime
You know, I trained as one
Is it just me or is our
boss a freaking weirdo?
I'm going to get some air
Jim, you know what would
be really dastardly?
If we snuck out of here
and got to the client first
He's running
Damn it
What... What is this
supposed to be?
It's a monkey
Jim, get real.
This is not a monkey
It's got a hula skirt
and a blue nose.
Hold on. Hold on
Is this him?
What?
Is that him?
It's him! Do something Get out!
Go!
What? What am I
going to do? I don't
Go slash his tires
Go dent his hood!
That's it?
That's great.
That's like a 5-second delay
Dwight
Go
Does this thing have turbo?
Nitrous? Hit the NOS
NOS? You mean like
in Fast & Furious?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, I
definitely have NOS
Hit the NOS.
Are you sure?
Yes. We got it! Go! Brace yourself.
Three, two, one
Here we go
Hello Andy Bernard
to see the CEO
Oh. Do you have
an appointment?
No, I do not
Okay. I think I can
squeeze you in
Seriously?
Because I could just
be anyone. I thought
I was going to
have to convince you
He's really not that busy
Is there someone
here to see me?
Yes. This man
Come on in
So, what do you make of
this Robert California guy?
What does a guy like that
do on an average weeknight
I'll tell you what he does
Hello.
Hello, my clucking hens
Got room for
another in the roost?
Huh? Don't worry I won't lay an egg
Robert sent me to
take over if Pam fails
If?
Crunching numbers all day
Math is for boys
Did someone say "girl talk?'
Sometimes I wonder if I
have ovaries in my scrotum
because I am
great at girl talk
Have you guys been watching
any good Korean soap operas?
I'm pretty deep into
Hee-Jung Cinderella Girl.
Although, I definitely fast-forward
through the Yung Tae storylines
Do you think I'd like that? Or is it
important to have an Asian fetish?
I think you're going to need
to have an Asian fetish. Yeah
It'll be
upsetting if you don't
I'm a former paper executive I know
the product. I know the margins
25% on your costs
Why haven't I heard of you?
You got any references?
No. I'm a rogue
Uh-huh.
Which is the best part
That means you will
be my first customer
and your business will get
100% of my attention.
Now, I have written down
my personal phone number
You call this any time
Every salesman I've ever met has
given me his personal phone number
Of course they have,
which is why I'm giving you
a key to my house
Whatever you need, any time night
or day, you just stop on by.
You want me to drive to
your house if I need paper?
Maybe you just want
someone to talk to,
maybe you need a place to
crash for a couple of days
My wireless password
is "eat, pray, love.'
Easy to remember
Ready? Go, go, go
You all right?
Yeah.
Dwight, what are you doing?
Shh
Go! Go! Take the stairs, now
What are you talking about?
Just run! Take the stairs! I don't
even know where the stairs are
I'll stall him. Go
What are you doing?
I'm going to activate
the seismic fail-safe
We'll be stuck
between floors for hours
Oh
My pants fell down
What?
I don't have a belt!
Hello, sir, good day. Dwight K.
Schrute Dunder Mifflin Scranton
Forgive my pants
they fell down.
An appointment with Mr. Ramish,
please Right now is fine.
No, no, no. I was here first Dwight K.
Schrute Dunder Mifflin Scranton.
Hi, guys. What's going on?
Mr. Ramish, Harry Jannerone
Dunder Mifflin Syracuse.
I was here first. Sorry
about this mix-up Okay.
I already made an appointment
with your secretary
Let me stop you
all right here
I've already picked
a new paper supplier
Wait, it's not
DM Utica, is it?
No, no, it's not Dunder Mifflin at all,
actually. It's Big Red Paper Company
Big Red Paper Company?
Mmm-hmm
Yes, yes, yes
Get me a cup of coffee
Me too
Or do you also have
a monopoly on thirst?
All right, guys, it didn't
work out for any of us,
so we're still
on the same team
Let me get these
No
Let him get his own
He's got Syracuse money
You know your partner's got a lot
of attitude, but I like that.
How long you guys
been dating?
Jim couldn't land me
in a thousand years.
But you're saying
there's a chance.
Shut up
Hey
Excellent. Excellent
Though troubling that your
first instinct is thievery.
What do you want from me?
Now we get to the bottom of Nellie's,
"Yes, yes, yes, yes, never.'
Hello, Nell, it's Mum.
Do keep your chin up. It can't
possibly be as bad as you describe.
Oh, yes, it can
This is MasterCard.
You are over the limit.
Send the minimum payment
of $448 by Monday,
or we will be forced to
send it to collections.
Shopaholic
Sounds like it.
Yeah
Hi, sis. Is your boss
still hitting on you?
This is Annie
from Second Nests.
I'm sorry, but the Romanian
orphanage felt more comfortable
with a two-person nuclear
family than a single mother,
so we're going to hold out for that.
Okay, that's enough
No, no, no Pam, we need to
get to the bottom of this
No. No.
Come on. Come on
Robert, okay... So, I deleted
them all They're all deleted.
Pam, you've
completely bungled this
Ah
Hey
Can I do it, Pam? Can I pull
off a gold Arabian sandal?
Um
Yes. Definitely.
With your hair, certainly
You dropped
your cell phone
Oh, gosh.
Yep
Thank you. I'm so stupid
No. My goodness
you just
You have a lot going on
with Robert and everything
Oh, God,
Pam, don't get me started
No, I will not
You've just got me started
Robert is a filthy beast
Don't you get the feeling
every time he looks at you,
he's just thinking of 15
different ways to do you?
Well
The man talks of
nothing but sex.
Sometimes he talks about
flesh and bacchanals.
Oh, yeah
what he left on my
phone last night
No. Don't. Just put
it out of your mind
Pam, what is your address?
I'm going to send you a pair
of these gold harem shoes
Oh. No, you don't
Yes
Come on, a little
gold Arabian slipper
Things are looking up
I have MasterCard
right where I want them
and I have a new friend
A friend
At work
Erin
There's a call
for you on line 1
Who is it?
He says, "Salvation.'
No last name.
Yeah, hello
You once put me on a list
of the losers in the office
This loser just got
your biggest client
to give him all
their business
So, hire me back,
that business is yours.
Don't, and I will
find another buyer
You're blackmailing me
It's just business
some ineffectual, privileged
effete, soft-penised debutant
You want to start a street
fight with me, bring it on,
but you're going to be
surprised by how ugly it gets
You don't even know my real
name I'm the * Lizard King
Whoa
Well, I gave him a chance
Andy Bernard?
You got a minute?
I'm in the middle
of a piano lesson
I wanted to see if could
interest you in an investment
Dunder Mifflin
Now, why would I want that?
It's worth half what
it was three years ago
Exactly
And you know better than anyone
that with the right management
it could be worth twice what
you would pay for it today
Why don't you come in?
So, what would you do if you
weren't selling paper?
Oh, man,
I'd have to sell beets
probably submit
them for competition
What?
Yeah, I know it
sounds stupid,
but nationals has always kind
of been a dream of mine.
How have we never
talked about this before?
Wait, you don't even
care about nationals
Nothing?
I've always wanted to
own a bike shop, but
What about you?
I'd like to sell one
big thing, you know?
Like a plane
One sale. I'm out
That sounds lovely
Anyway, Robert's going to run
this company into the ground
so we won't be doing
this in six months.