Today is the test paunch day
for the inaugural Sabre store.
And I, Dwight Schrute, am in
charge of the entire operation.
If I can prove myself today and the
store is a hit with the media,
and Nellie sees this,
the vice presidency is mine
Hey, are you
holding this chair?
Because I feel like
I'm going to fall off
Yeah. Yes. Yes I'm not wearing
the right shoes for this
We went
over this, okay?
Your tiny fingers
make the best knots
Hey, strangers. I'm so stoked
for the Sabre store opening
Hey, my name's Tabitha I'm camped
out in front of the Sabre store
so I can be first in line
for the new Pyramid.
Psst
It's me, Erin. Dwight had
me pretend to be a hipster
to create hype
and it's working
There's already people
camped out behind me
NELLIE
Test launch day, people.
Now, I would like to fill you in
on a little secret about me
To inspire you today
Now I know you probably all think
I'm this patrician goddess
But here's the truth
I was born in the little
working-class town of Basildon
and until the age of 32
I talked like this
Which was
bloody horrendous, innit?
No, lower than
What's lower than dirt?
Loam. Magma. Mantle
Outer core. Inner core.
Yeah, thank you. Loam.
Bloody loam I came from
when I auditioned
for the Spice Girls
get a callback
Which Spice Girl?
The black one
Okay
Now think about my
journey here today
and let it inspire
your journey.
Okay Nellie, thank you
Thank you so much
Yep. Yep
Today is press day, and press is
going to make or break this store
And for a tech company press can
only mean one thing, bloggers.
Dossier on bloggers
Bloggers are gross Bloggers are obese.
Bloggers have halitosis
You're going to love them
Ryan is going to be
the main event today
He is the pitchman
who is going to give
the feisty yet
profound speech
worthy of a world's fair.
Ryan, you ready to do this?
When people see
this presentation,
they're going to
♪ in their pants
Come on, man.
- Come on
Okay
Seriously disgusting
Cathy, you will be the hot
girl who talks to bloggers
Ugh! Kill me
It was my idea
Packer, you will be the sexual
predator who has come to prey
on the trendy teenage girls who
are obsessed with the Pyramid
Uh...
- Ah
That is excellent
I don't see what
that gets us,
but I'm a team player
Perfect casting, right?
Schrute's out to get me,
but I'm playing the long game
As soon as he messes up I swoop
in like a sexual predator.
Of wonder and enthusiasm
as if at the end of E.T., candy
poured out of the screen.
Do you understand?
Goose pimples
Speaking of pimples let's
release the bloggers!
Morning, everyone
Oh, Andy, guess what
happened to me this morning
Don't care. Tell me later
Listen, it's important.
You've got to hear this
What do you got?
Oh, my God
Do you have a black eye?
Yes, I do, Phyllis
I woke up at 4:00 a.m
by accident
in time for
the paper to be delivered
Guess what?
It's not a kid on a bike
It's a man in a car
Andy, who punched you?
Hey, I was on the can What's this
about a black guy in the office?
Black eye, Meredith
Will someone please explain
what's going on here?
Since the interesting thing happened
until now so much time has passed
It's like my
life is buffering
Here's what happened Pam and
I were arriving for the day
and there was a gang in the parking
lot, on bikes, on motorcycles
And they just
were hassling Pam.
That's true.
They had weapons.
Weapons.
To talk some sense
into them.
But these were not the kind of
people who use their words.
Punches were going,
and I ducked a few,
landed a couple, and I
was fighting them off.
It was a totally
like, senseless crime
Thank goodness he was there.
- Good job, Andy.
Any of you wouldn't
have done.
Open the gates
There's plenty for
everyone No need to panic
everyone There's plenty
Don't stampede.
No need to stampede, sir
Okay, okay! Hey, hey It's going
to be fine It's going to be fine
There's plenty of Pyramids
Come on,
I was in line before you
So you're
a blogger, right?
Yeah
Blogger
God, stay away
Oh, I always get in
trouble around bloggers
I'm trying to be
a good girl for once
Uh, yeah, I already bought my Pyramid
but I don't want to leave yet.
Since seeing Zooey Deschanel
at the Coachella music festival.
So fun.
How can we feel safe knowing
that there are gangs here?
We should call the police right now
- Yes
No, no, no, no, no, no We don't
need to call the police.
They'll just ask
everybody questions
get up in everyone's
business right, Pam?
Police are a hassle We
settled this on the street
And my eye will heal.
But if the police come
then we will forever stain our
neighborhood as a troubled area
Why would you care what the
police think of our neighborhood?
Because I have
neighborhood pride
Guys, guys
that's so vague
You got to do
the zip plus four
18505-7427
Look, I don't feel safe I think
we should call the police.
Yes Exactly, we
need to feel safe,
which is why Toby is
teaching us self-defense.
Me?
Toby, will you
teach us self-defense?
Yeah. I can't believe
you remembered
I'll go put on my cup
Great
Yes
- Okay.
One of you was Chuck
Yeah, no, it seems
to be going great.
Andy got beat up by
a fifth grade girl?
Look at that guy, he's got
a Sabre phone on him,
he's not even using it
This is a perfect photo
for my daily fail blog.
Uh, I got to go
Okay.
Dwight, what is a fail?
That sounds bad.
No, no, no, it's good
It's really
On the Internet, that's a
really good good thing
Are you trying to
sabotage this entire event?
I'm very sorry
We gave you an Arrowhead
for free for the day.
How hard would it have
been to do this? Hmm?
Hello. Hi, sweetie, it's Jim I'm
calling you from my new Arrowhead
which is why my
voice is crystal clear
and my hand
won't ever get tired
because of
the ergonomic shape
I'm really sorry Is there anything I
can do? Maybe pretend to be Chuck?
You could have
pretended to be Chuck
I begged you to
pretend to be Chuck
But you chose to be yourself and
you can no longer be Chuck.
Surrender the tri-pack
You know what
you have to do
Point it towards
the store, idiot
You know what I mean?
Pick one of these
buttons and just
Damn it. Take over
Oh, hey, hey, hey, you guys
You must be lost
Listen.
Excuse me, sir
The fountain where you can feed the
pigeons is out behind the bank.
Tell your great-grandson
to bring his kid by.
Okay, so long
Here we go.
Erin! Psst! Come on
The elderly suck the life out of
the young Get them out of here
We are closed
Come on
Self-defense is not some
fun boxing match okay?
This is about
escaping with your life
So strike
scream and run
All right,
let's try it
That may have
been my fault.
What the hell, Toby?
Okay, look in a real
crisis situation
you're not going to
have time to think.
Okay?
So just remember IAATG
"It's All About The Groin.'
What if you're being
attacked by a smallish man
who happens to
not have a groin?
I don't think
that's very common
But what if
you're being attacked
by a 4'11" man
who's penis-less
Why are you fixated on this
hypothetical transgendered attacker?
Why don't we
start with the basics?
Show us how to defend
ourself against a baby
and then like
a fifth-grade girl
and then, you know, if we have
time on up to a scary man
The most common scenario is a larger
man attacking a smaller female
So in that scenario
what if the victim
sucker punches
the attacker in the face?
What can the attacker then do
to better protect himself?
It's interesting
that you're drawn
to the point of
view of the attacker
You would like
The Turn of the Table.
Okay? The latest
Chad Flenderman novel
From the point of view of his nemesis, Dr.
Lucifer Woo.
Can I please leave?
I have a rape flute.
All right, well let's try one
simple technique together
Okay, why doesn't
everyone stand?
Okay, so
you're being attacked
you've got your hands up
simple palm strike to the chin
Up to the chin
One, two
Cathy, I would like to introduce
you to Fatty Gruesome
He is a freelancer
for Wired magazine
Patty Grossman
I'm a woman.
But you still work
for Wired, right?
Yes
Good.
Okay. Flirt away
Sabre. It's time
to come home.
Yeah
Yeah. I mean, I think It seemed
like you were a little nervous.
Yeah, no * Sherlock
Can somebody please tell
me something encouraging
about this presentation
before I go out there in front
of a million people and do it?
Okay. I know!
I know, champ
Just calm down
because, listen
when you are out in
front of a those people
Yeah, what?
you just
need to realize
so much rides on this
You have no idea
Dwight
I'm trying to make
him feel important
I wish Kelly were here.
She always knew what to say
Um
Oh, Ryan, you're so smart
You're smarter
than Mark Zuckerberg
and those Google guys
all combined.
You're so ignorant. You barely
know what you're talking about.
It's so ridiculous
You really need to
read a couple of books
What's a book?
Oh, my God
You're so embarrassing
My mom would say
the best stuff though
You can
You can do it, Ryan
And you know that
I'm capable of this?
You're the only one
who can do it, sweetie
What did you think
of the presentation?
I thought
it was great, sweetie
I would just
fix that one
"Fix" means you hate it I knew it!
I need something
to drink!
Jim, get him a water
No, not a water
a sports drink!
I hate everything
in that fridge
Not red! Get me something
yellow or green
from a nearby store
Not red!
Why are you just
standing there?
Go to a nearby store and get him
a yellow or green sports drink.
Now if your attacker is
willing to defile a corpse
you better stop
playing dead right away
and just make it known
that you're alive
Forgive me
for interrupting
had an altercation
with somebody here
some fancy gentleman
with a squeaky voice?
I think you guys might
have the wrong office
That's him.
The guy I hit
What?
You've got to be
kidding me.
Poor Andy
First you got beat up by a gang
and now she kicks your ass
No, Kevin
What about the lady
you hit with a pinecone?
There.
That chubby one
Yesterday?
Wow.
Apologize
Sorry I kicked your ass in front
of your "thin" girlfriend
How about we wait until next
year after you have your kid?
You know what? Tiffany's
going to college
Listen I don't know what you
guys are talking about,
but I guess I' just accept your
apology so we can get on with our day
God bless. A friend of
mine uses your paper
You do good work
Bye-bye.
Bye
So, Toby, I think we should do a
different self-defense seminar
how to protect ourselves
against tiny little girls.
There's no shame in getting
beaten up by a girl
My ex-wife used
to demolish me.
No, there is
shame in it, okay?
We have to draw the
line somewhere.
Oh, my God I think I see
the imprint of a Ring Pop
Oh
Have you seen Erin?
I'm on break
Oh, my God
No, hey, bloggers, where
do you think you're going?
No, you got to stay
for the big presentation
We got this
young whiz kid, Ryan
He's like an even
more handsome Bill Gates
When's the presentation?
It's moments away
Just stay here
Hey, Uncle Lucas
it's your nephew, Ryan
Honestly, I could use a
prescription for Ritalin right now
Well, I know you did
one for Aunt Carol.
So it's different
because it's your wife?
Well, that doesn't
make any sense to me
How are you doing?
Don't talk to me right now
I'm sorry. I know you're my boss
but seriously,
you need to get
the hell out of my face
Your little man is unraveling.
Now go and fix it
Sorry about
kicking you out
It's just we don't want our
brand associated with death
It's okay I'll go to the Costco
and search for handsome men
You're not married yet?
Oh, I was. My husband
was my best friend
He passed away
My best friend
was my boss, Andy
We dated for a while
but since then,
he rejected me and
we're not really friends
Someone rejected you? With
that body and those bazongas?
Forget him
Yeah. Forget him And you
should forget your husband
Well
How long has he
been in the bathroom?
Like 10 minutes
Geez, what's he
doing in there?
Oh, that's my phone
Am I allowed to answer it or
are you going to freak out?
Are there bloggers around?
It's Ryan
"I'm sorry. I lied
I'm not in the bathroom
"I can't do it I need to see my mom
"I'm going home.'
What is the delay here?
Where is Ryan?
Why is he not here?
As brilliant and
creative as he is
he is nothing
compared to this guy
Uh.
What?
That's right. Will you
just give us a second?
You are going to bloody ruin it.
You're going to bloody ruin it
because you're a no-good,
half-assed, cockeyed numpty
Okay. Okay
Jim I'm not doing
the presentation
Look at me. Look at me
Look at this face
This is not
the face of a performer
This is the face of a scary
apparition you see before you die
I'm telling you, if you don't
do this, I don't stand a chance
Please, Jim
Okay, I'll do it
Oh, my God. Okay
Go get into Ryan's costume
and check out his notes.
A costume?
Of course
there's a costume
Oh, this is going
to be great
There's nothing like
some last minute changes
to really energize
a presentation. Huh?
Did you pass out in there?
What is taking so long?
I've been in here
for 20 seconds.
Hurry up! Let me in I want
to watch you get dressed.
Did you find
the eyeliner?
I'm not wearing eyeliner
You are wearing
eyeliner, Jim.
Time, space, gender
There are no rules
anymore.
All boundaries
are breaking down
in the wake of
the infinite future
The only thing that The
only thing that remains...
The only thing
that remains
are the things that have
stood the test of time
Love, values and of
course the Pyramids
The strongest shape
ever constructed.
A shape that fits all other
shapes inside of it.
No, that's
Mmm. It's true
This is the future
because this is the past
I've been through a lot
of issues in my life
I've seen drug addiction
unemployment
I've been in a relationship
that tore my heart apart
without ever being able to
accept that love drove the pain
Yep
When I was 10 years old my
parents took me to Disney world
I was not able to comprehend
the beauty that was before me
This is what the Pyramid
will do for you.
It is the bridge
to the world.
It has the USB port
Wireless will be
available in 2013
You can play anything
from Chuck to Cars 2.
With the Pyramid, you have
the connection to everything
In time and space
Psst
Oh
Sabre. It's time
to come home.
All right.
Thank you so much. Wow
Wow
And good night
Yeah
Okay, this isn't over
Let's stay focused, okay?
We made fun of Andy earlier for
getting beat up by a little girl
but little things
can be dangerous
Whether it's a gremlin
or Chucky the doll,
the key is to
throw it in something
like a fireplace or
a tub of electricity
Okay, good point. Um
Good point? What is a
tub of electricity?
With all due respect
we know what we're
defending against
It's a 12-year-old
female bully.
Great! I think Kelly
should attack Toby
Yeah
Yeah, that's not
a bad idea actually
because I have had
a lot of pent-up aggression
Thanks.
- Good! Go
I don't know whether
this is gonna help
All right, Kelly
We should stay to maybe some
more traditional models.
You think
you're so pretty?
You're not going to be
so pretty come prom-time
Okay, this is what's
called Take that!
pre-violent posture
Take that
Not so pre-violent
anymore
I'm in what's called
the decision point.
Hey, hey, hey
Kelly! Kelly!
Ow
My good eye
Oh, boy
Oh, no, I'm not
laughing at you
I'm laughing at
something that Cece did
on the playground earlier
yesterday, this morning.
You know why I
got hit by girls?
Because I stood up
for others.
Pam and Toby
didn't care that I was
standing up to girls.
You may want to ask yourselves,
where were you when the girls came?
Tough day, yes
But I feel good
I put the office
in their place
took a bunch of painkillers drank half
a bottle of wine took my pants off.
Okay, okay, I will be
the first to admit it.
We could have integrated more
Chuck into the presentation.
Dwight, you're
the vice president
Yeah
Okay! Come on!
Right on
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam
Boom