Oh, yeah
Kevin! As soon as I
heard that wrapper
You really have
to say, "Oh, yeah, '
every time you
eat a candy bar?
I can't help it, Oscar
It's just really good
Oh, yeah
My hands are tied
All right, not bad at all
20 minutes, though
so let's try again
Get it all out
now if you have to
It was a raccoon eating a
hamburger like a person.
You need to stop banging
your pen on your desk,
or it's gonna drive me
insane Okay, got it.
Does anyone have
a first-aid kit?
Check out
this song I wrote.
I'm gonna love you
downstairs tonight
Listen, I say
I mean, he looked
like a little Hamburglar
All right, here we go
Everybody get ready in
three, two Good luck. One
Love letters.
Yes, I love it
What else can be
done with paper?
You can write
a book about chairs
Books. Excellent, Jim
All right, Andy,
please, please, just stop
You can do infinite
things with paper.
Did you hear that?
Infinity. There is an infinity of
things that you can do with paper
Now, who wants
to buy some paper?
Yeah
Very nice
Very nice sales pitch
for our clients that
don't know what paper is
I'm talking about you guys
Who in this room right now
wants to buy some paper?
Let's get high
on our own supply
Andy, you want us
to buy our own paper?
Yes
Robert said that we needed to
double our sales growth to 8%
by the end of the quarter That's
today, and we are $830 short.
And I can't afford
to keep buying paper from us,
so today we need to
sell $830 of paper,
and then next quarter I need to sell
the $2,200 of paper
that's in my garage.
Animals, machines,
vast virtual armies.
All of these things I have
successfully managed.
The only thing I
haven't managed is people
I saw an ad on
the Sabre website
for an open manager position
in their printers division.
I spoke to Robert
California about it,
and he said for me to come by
and see him some time.
So like
a Spanish conquistador,
I have come to Florida to claim
what is rightfully mine.
Dwight Schrute for
Robert California.
Oh. Hello, Mr. Schrute I'll tell him
you're here Can I get you anything at all?
I'm not here to
be given anything
I'm here to take
what is mine
Ooh. I'm glad you're on our
team Here, please have a seat.
Dwight?
What are you doing here?
Gabe. You don't know?
Of course I know
Hmm. Impressive
office you have here
Surrounded by shrubbery
Like a squirrel's office
Corporate says to me "Gabe,
we need you in Scranton."
Scranton says,
"Gabe, go back down
to Florida
You're needed there.'
So Tuesdays and Thursdays
I'm up there.
Mondays, Wednesdays and
Fridays I'm down here
I can think of no better way to
confront my deathly fear of flying
Dwight.
Robert
You made it
Yes
Impressive initiative
I don't know what's worse
the trip or the destination.
Well, let me settle in
And I'll be with you shortly
Very good
Hey, C-SPAN
So my Dad says an accountant
can really help you out
if they're willing to play ball.
Those were his words
Gosh, Andy, you had
a great quarter, okay?
Robert will understand
$800 is a rounding error
So make that error
Andy, no
Hey, I can make that error Oh
Well, it's just I know that making
errors sounds like your kind of thing,
but it's a little more
complicated than that. No, I
It's just I really need
a real accountant on this
What do you say?
Because tonight I have a
trivia contest in Philadelphia
Aw
Any other crunch time
I would love
to stay and cook
the books for you
so you can save face
in front of your CEO
but tonight is
Triviacolypse What?
It's only the biggest night
of trivia of the year
There's a $1,000 prize
I'm committed to my friends
They're committed to me
You know what? Go. Have fun
There's a trivia contest
at a bar in Philadelphia
Stop right there I love it.
I'm in.
It's trivia.
In Philadelphia
But here's the best part
The prize is $1,000
and if we win, we can use
that money to buy paper here
close the gap on our
8% profit increase.
That's a great idea. Yeah
That's a great plan.
Yeah? You like it? All right
All right, good stuff.
I'm so psyched you guys are
into it, 'cause I thought
"This sounds really stupid.'
You just made a good idea
a great idea.
There is one problem
with this plan What?
We'd have to leave work
like, right now to do this
You can reduce
your prices by 10%
or we're gonna be finding a new
source for our morning bagels
All right
Gabe, I always wondered what
it is you did around here
Now I found out
You're the bagel guy
Yeah, but not just bagels
All unwanted problems.
Question What's the most important
appliance in your house?
Meat grinder.
Too slow. It's the toilet
And I am the toilet
of this office
annoying problems
so others can keep
their hands clean,
and just like a toilet I am essential.
You know, Gabe,
you could have gone
with garbage disposal
incinerator, or eraser
And instead
you chose toilet
God bless you
You are an American classic
Dwight, today is not my
day at all, I'm afraid
I'm not going to be
able to meet with you
But I'm leaving you in the
very capable hands of our COO
But I can give you
this pitch in one minute
He's gonna meet
with you later.
No, no, no. I don't
want you to rush it, okay?
Trust me. Meet with Bill
He's a great person to know
I'll dialog with him tonight
CEO to COO What a
difference a letter makes.
Still an important position
Still a chief.
You're really
going to like Bill
He has me toilet
a lot of people for him
Hallway phone.
Gabe Lewis speaking
Gabe, listen to me.
Don't bother Bill with this.
He needs to go put out a fire
on the home front.
Just wait 20 minutes, and then I want
you to listen to Dwight's p\itch.
Make him feel valued.
Make him feel heard.
Your wish is my command
It's a command.
What are you doing here, Andy?
You left us no choice
But this should put
a smile on your face
How would you like to be captain
of the Dunder Mifflin team?
Although I reserve the right
to overrule you What? No.
And you guys thought
this was a good idea?
A fun idea.
There were times on the two and a half
hour drive when I experienced doubt
But that's the thing
about long drives
you know?
You're always going
This is a gay bar
Wait, what?
Everyone in here is gay?
Yes. It's a gay bar so you
guys want to go home now?
No.
No
Awesome
What does this say about you
that you followed me here?
That you think
you're going to win
your sales quota at
a gay bar's trivia night?
It says that I believe
in my staff's intelligence
and that I'm
willing to try anything
Not "anything.'
Good luck
All right, we need to
divide up into teams
but it's winner take all
so no need to divide evenly
We need an A team a backup
team, and a just-have-fun team
So you guys all
know yourselves
Good timers, follow me
Back-ups
Go on, kid. You know
you don't belong here
A team
Okay
All right, everybody,
nice self awareness
Except
Okay
There's a table over here
All right,
first question, everyone.
Ray Charles famously had
this state on his mind.
What is its capital?
Oh, we got this
Let's reverse engineer this
You're a black singer
Where do you go?
Somewhere where
you're a novelty
Alaska
Atlanta.
I know you think that, because
that's where the Olympics were held
My cousins were
actually at those Olympics
Keep talking all you want
How am I supposed to know
what was on his mind?
Ooh! What do blind
people think about?
Okay, dogs, canes signs, manholes,
stairs piano, darkness.
Okay, time's up.
Let's get the boards up.
Atlanta, Georgia is
the correct answer.
What?
Hey, man. Uh
Look, unfortunately,
Bill had to go fight a fire
so, your appointment got
There's no fires
within eight miles of here
Well, it's nine miles away
I'm going to be meeting
with you on his behalf.
What? No, no.
Excuse me, lady
Get anyone from the COO's office
on the phone this instant
This must be
very frustrating
I can see you in
the jungle now
Hey, now, you're not an All-Star of
the NBA, but you did get your game on
when you won the NBA's Sixth Man
of the Year Award in 2011.
Who are you?
Jim, Darryl,
your time to shine
Shawn Marion.
Yes. Shawn Marion
That doesn't sound right I want
to say LaDamien Washington?
Wrong for so many reasons
Well, I know
Elizabeth Taylor's sixth man
was Richard Burton
Is that helpful?
That's it. I'm gonna go watch
the boats on the river
Ron Artest, Kelly
No, it's Lamar Odom
If it had been Ron Artest
it would have
come up on
Dancing with the Stars
when they pan
over his trophy case
when he's at home
with his family
Lamar winning Sixth Man was a big
storyline on Chloe and Lamar.
All right, boards up.
Let's see who got it.
Lamar Odom is what
we were looking for.
Lamar Odom.
Oh, my God
Lamar Odom
Nice. Nicely done
You're my sports guys You're ESPN.
You're ESPN Classic
Ryan is MSNBC.
I'm E! TLC and Oxygen
Chill, man.
This plan is airtight
So it's a very
simple argument
of why I should be put in charge
of southeast printer sales
Nobody has sold more printers
in the northeast than me.
Bottom line, I know
the product I get it.
Well, you got my vote
Oh, my God
Yeah.
Most of all, I believe
that character is destiny
and my character
is one that...
Wait, why are you smiling?
What?
What's with the smile?
You're doing great
So good.
And my character is one
that will never give up
until greatness is on
the horizon behind us
Dwight, that was a fantastic presentation.
Put your hand on my hand
Flush
Ow
Take me to Robert
Ow. He went home.
Take me to his house
It's a condo.
It's long-term
business housing
You know where it is
Lead me there
Ow. Stephanie, help
Listen, you're
a perfectly fine toilet
I'm just an extraordinary
piece of crap. Let's go.
Ow
Excuse me, sir,
on the Dunder Mifflin A team.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah?
I'm sure you're just checking
your Grindr account.
But you can't
check smartphones
during trivia.
It's against the rules.
Okay, I'm turning it off
Okay, you're not
turning it off.
Sir.
Okay, then we're gonna
have to take it away.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, I can't not
have my phone. I'm sorry
All right, guys, after nine
rounds, let's check the scores.
In first place with nine
points, it's Aesop's Foibles.
The Queerenstein
Bears have seven points.
Dunder Mifflin
A team has four points.
All right
The D.M. Backup Team
has three points.
The Einsteins
have eight points.
Ladies Gaga have five points.
Yeah
So our best chance
of hitting our mark
is now in the hands and brains of
Kevin Meredith, Erin and Kelly
Do I like these odds?
My answer is no.
Whoo!
Which one is it? I don't know!
All I know is the building
Robert! Robert California
Robert
Dwight
How nice of Gabe to
show you where I live
Come around, 102
All right, guys, time's up.
Who was the relatively
unknown patent clerk
who discovered
that energy equals
mass times
the speed of light squared?
Looks like everyone gets a
point for Albert Einstein.
Wait, except
for the Einsteins.
That's all right.
Which means
the top three teams
are going to finish it
off in the speed round.
So let's get
everyone some bells.
In third place,
we have the Einsteins.
Oh, yeah
What?
Second place, we have
the Queerenstein Bears.
Yeah
Come on!
And first place
is Aesop's Foibles.
Whoo
Yeah, but they're
going to get clobbered
Ring it in when you know it.
First question.
This man had a fatwa
declared on him when...
Einsteins?
What?
What is it?
I'm just the bell girl
Aesop's?
Salman Rushdie.
Salman Rushdie is correct.
Heading out to sea, sailors.
On a square-rigged
ship, the sail
set furthest
forward is called what?
Princess Ding-Dong
do not hit that bell...
Flying jib
Flying jib is
correct for the Einsteins.
Flying jib. Flying jib
No way
Gentlemen
Give us just a minute. Stew and I
are just finishing up our lesson
Trust me,
one nine-minute bout
is a cardiovascular equivalent of
running uphill for three hours.
I could go to
the gym three times a week
or I can wrestle
Stew once a month
Grab my leg
Yay, Robert
Guys, please help yourself to
some drinks from the fridge.
According to a recent survey,
this is the most common learning
disability among American adolescents.
Boom! ADHD
No.
Wrong.
The answer is dyslexia
That's correct
for the Einsteins.
All right
Whoo! Yeah
Sir, sir. Dial it back. This
isn't Tail Feathers, okay?
Yeah
They haven't really improved
on the Oreo, have they?
No, thank you
Sit down, Dwight
Let me tell you
why I should be
the next manager
with a riddle.
A manager
a salesman, a leader
and a warrior walk
into a restaurant.
The hostess says
"Table for one?"
How is this possible?
You were dining alone
All those people are you
Yes. Exactly. Riddle
number two Who is going...
Your drive, your ambition it would
be wasted on a manager's job.
And Florida,
you don't want to live here
Even I don't
want to live here
It's why I'm always at
my place in Scranton
Florida is America's basement
It's wet. It's filled with mold
strange insects, alligators
Alligators are dinosaurs, Dwight.
You know that, right?
Eh... It's complicated
This medal was
my grandfather's
He received it for acts
of courage for excellence
It's a tribute
one man gives another
a job, Dwight.
But why not let me give you
something even better?
It's a job interview
Not a flea market.
Dwight, the job is
not right for you.
Now, when something
comes along
that is right for you
I'll try you out.
Now get the he
out of my place
Yes
Final round.
Last two teams squaring off.
Ready to play doctor.
Our question is about
health and the human body.
Oh, come on
The standard
American analog scale
has a maximum
capacity of what weight?
Three hundred pounds
Point for the Einsteins.
Here's your final question. Cinephiles,
put on your memory berets.
This 2001 masterpiece
from Gilles Paquet-Brenner
explores the intricate dynamics
of a family in disarray.
Yes
I'm sorry, no.
Over to the Einsteins.
Les Jolies Choses.
- Are you sure?
Marion Cotillard
exposes herself
a number of times
in that film.
The Einsteins win it.
No
Yeah
Come on
Look, I know it's easy to say
tonight was just a fluke,
and maybe it was,
but here's a piece of trivia
A fluke is one of the most
common fish in the sea
So if you go
fishing for a fluke,
chances are you
just might catch one.
Oh, boy.
Welcome to the Stonewall
Alliance Trivia Championship\s!
First prize is $2,500.
Let's just do our thing, collect
our hardware and get the hell home
Whoo
Riboflavin.
Riboflavin?
Michigan.
The President of
the United States
is POTUS.
John Steinbeck wrote
The Grapes of Wrath