Today is the first day
of Sabre's new project
to develop a chain
of retail stores.
Nellie Bertram
Head of Special Projects.
Work starts at 9:00.
Sabre HQ is 30 minutes away
driving the speed limit,
giving everyone 20
minutes to shower,
plus 50 for Jim
to style his hair,
20 for breakfast, 40 for Erin to get
post between her room and the lobby,
90 for Ryan to do
his morning ecstasy.
We're already 20 minutes late
Wake up!
Hey, hey, hey
hey, wake up! Ow
Why are you sleeping
that way?
Oh. I was reading the mattress
tag and I fell asleep.
Stanley! Wake up You've got to
wake up The hotel's on fire!
Stanley, wake up
It's pretzel day
Good morning
Hey, wake up Let's have some fun.
We're in Florida now
Hey, you. I'm so
glad this is happening
door twice last night
Come on in,
the water's fine
Oh, not coo
sleep schedule, so I'm
up and at 'em at 4:15
But no kids, so I honestly didn't
know what to do with myself
And then I thought
of something. Uh
Here is Dwight
What the
Oh, man
What do you think happened?
Looks like Jim got mixed up
with some bad apples.
Oh, no, no, no, no
It wasn't me
at the Alcohol Club."
Puppet
Cool. For your kids?
Yeah. It's weird being away from them.
I've never done this before
Attention Dunder Mifflin
group proceed outside.
The vehicle is waiting
Seats have been assigned
Shotgun goes to Ryan
Congratulations, Ryan
I need to make Nellie
see me as a leader today.
First impressions
get locked in forever
When I first met Pam
she said something
that slightly
rubbed me the wrong way
Since then I've
loved working with Pam
and she's frankly wonderful
but I hate her
I'll have
a bottle of the antacid
Also I want to get
a souvenir for my son
but his mother doesn't
acknowledge my paternity.
Do you have anything for that?
Also I want it to
have a Florida feel
What does he like?
Power
Okay, and this one is, "Huh. Don't
see too many museums around here."
Okay, Twiggy, that's enough
Get in the car.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine, okay?
I'm just stressed
because I care
about this project
And frankly,
the fact that none of you
are vomiting or
diarrheal right now
Who says none of
us are diarrheal?
Are you sure it's stress?
Because I did poison you
Very funny, Jim
Oh, no, I'm serious.
I was thinking for this trip
so what should that be?
And then I thought of it
I'll poison you
What are you going to do? Are
you going to steal my newspaper
or put a cricket in my cereal
or something?
I'm gonna set your face on fire.
That's a good one
Whoa. Stanley,
did you just come back
from burning down
a rival night club?
Laugh it up, Halpert
I'm in Florida for a month without
my family I'm going to enjoy this.
Want to get in?
You can work the iPod
Yes
You're a nice guy, Jim but you
have no idea how to vacation.
Find some Kenny Loggins
Loggins and Messina
Did I say Messina?
Sorry, I couldn't
resist It's so quiet.
It's so peaceful, I've already
written 12 plays today
It's so quiet, one might say
you could hear a pin...
would be cooler
Hey, can you pick up
the pin?
Some of us like to
work in our bare feet
Of course. I will pick up
the pin It is right here
Got it Can we see that?
Did you really find it?
Yes. Right here.
Got it. Dink. Ow
In the trash
Hey, why is it so quiet?
Shouldn't
the phone be ringing?
Uh-oh
Erin set
the phone to voice-mail
Great.
Oh, my God, we're screwed
There
Oh, there we go. Pam?
Yeah
Can you get the phone?
Well, I'm not
the receptionist
Well, you used to be
I know but I can't cover reception
I have a ton of work to do.
Phone's ringing
Will one of you get the phone? I am
freaking out! I know it's for me.
Are you guys kidding me? Stop
flirting and someone get the phone
Answer the phone
Pick up the phone
Andy, you're standing up
You're the closest one to it
Fine
Hello. Dunder Mifflin
Hello, you've reached Dunder Mifflin.
How may I be of service?
How was the drive?
Fantastic
Stanley drives so fast
Life is short. Drive fast leave a
sexy corpse. That's one of my mottos
I would love to
hear the other mottos
Quick query, Halpert
No way
Still queer?
Packer
You can't put me down
Too strong
Yeah, Dwight and Jim
tried to get me fired.
But I landed on my
feet down here in Florida
You see, this cat's got
nine lives and a nine-inch
Say, "So who's
leading this thing anyway?'
So who's leading
this thing anyway?
Psst. Say,
"I can't wait to meet him.'
"Him," you said? Don't think
a woman can be a leader?
L
You poor, simple boy
Expected a man, did you?
Strong, powerful huge whopping penis?
Well, sorry to disappoint
But my huge whopping penis is right
here and I'm not afraid to use it
So stop looking at my breasts
and start looking at my penis.
I'm Nellie Bertram
President of Special Projects
In the next few weeks
we're going to throw
everything you
know about business
out of the window
and do it our own way
Are your minds blown?
So, how did this special
project come about anyway?
Well, I interviewed to be
the manager of your branch
After you decided I
wasn't a good fit...
It was
Ah. Mmm-mmm
It was. I went
on a shopping spree
Very destructive, I bought 1/ pianos
Then I realized, what if
Sabre had a store? Hmm?
So I called Jo old friend,
founder of Sabre and I told her,
and she grabbed me by the
shoulders and she said, "Yes!'
So let's talk about
this Sabre store then
Probably going to
look stupid, right?
Like a big turd with a door
on the front, right?
What do you think
it should look like?
It might be fun if each
store had a different theme
like a beach one,
a winter one, a jungle one
No. Not a big fan of
the winter aesthetic
Well, that was just one idea
It doesn't have to be winter.
Oh, no, it does. It does
It has to be winter
and I reject it
So I drew up a design concept
probably going to be rubbish, right?
Would you like to look at it?
Just so you can laugh at it
Yeah
Let me just get
the projector working
You got to stop with the
antacids It's not the antidote
You didn't poison me
It's just stress.
Okay
What is the antidote?
True love's kiss
Jim, help me
lower this screen
You're a big tall man
You'd be hilarious trying
to do it like a little boy.
Just let go of his balloon
I'll do it.
Something done right,
ask Dwight.
Right, Dwight
Right, Dwight.
Right, Dwight. Right, Dwight
Sorry. Now you'll never be able
to get that out of your head
There we go
Yes, a complete inability
to pass gas, pervert.
Yeah, it's tender, but it can't be
appendicitis. I eat more than enough bacon
Okay, what poison mimics the
symptoms of appendicitis?
You don't know. Hold on
What kind of
poison did you use?
Dwight, I didn't poison you I was kidding
Yeah, I'm going to
need an ambulance
Hold on. I have the address
in my phone Hold on.
Sabre has assigned
Hold on one second
the following positions
in the retail division.
Uh, quick question
Vice President, who is that?
There is no name listed.
Is there not? Maybe I'm just
waiting for someone to wow me
Sir? Sir, where should
we send the ambulance?
Send it to
the freaking moon, idiot
I'll tell you what, though
since my move down to Florida
I've really gotten back
into hunting, big-time.
Hunting's so primal almost sexual
- Totally.
Yeah, I mean
I'd never bang an animal
You can hardly
tell the difference
between a boy or a girl
you know?
But hunting's intense
You talking about hunting?
I'm a master hunter
Did you say "masturbator"?
I'm a decent baiter. My cousin,
Mose, that's a master baiter
Why are you
sitting down like that?
Why is everyone
else standing up?
Okay, team, let's get
back to work Break's over
Wow. Are you that bored?
It's just rum
I'm not bored. I'm a pirate
Is that another motto?
It's whatever you want
Hmm
Or do you only
drink with your kids?
No, let's do it
Woah. That's healthy
I've spent so much of
my life telling myself,
"Please, don't
end up like Stanley.'
And now I'm wondering
if I even have what it takes
We have the Sabre pyramid, right?
We've got a bunch of humans
You guys. Humans, pyramid
Human pyramid. Do you follow?
It's a team-building exercise
You love it. Who's in?
Tallahassee, let's go
Jim, are you in?
Oh, I don't know
Sounds like a hoot. I'm in
All right
What the heck? Let's do it
This is great.
This is going to be great
I feel like I'm
in ancient Egypt.
I'll be on top That's the
most important position
Dude, I think you have appendicitis.
Dwight,
why don't we just hold off
with the human
pyramids for a while?
Everyone stop moving.
Everyone stop wiggling
going to vomit
Dude, don't you yak on me
This shirt is Van Heusen
Oh, stop moving
No one's moving.
Arrest Jim.
He poisoned me
What? No. No
It was not a poisoning
The one thing Pam
made sure I knew,
Florida's pretty loose
with the death penalty
You need an operation
You have appendicitis
Oh! Who called it?
Nothing but net
How long will he be gone?
Two or three days
Don't remember me like this
Remember me as the man
who pulled down the screen
Drama queen, am I right?
Philip, if you're
hearing this memo
that can only mean
one thing, I am dead
You are the rightful heir to Schrute Farms.
Please, you must do one thing
Kill Mose before he kills you
Mose. Hey, it's Dwight
Listen, yeah, I just want
to give you a heads up
That was
an interesting diversion
Should we get
back to the meeting?
Woah. Are those mini pizzas?
Yeah. I figure if
we keep things savory
while Oscar's mouth
is in canker country
bacon-wrapped dates
on deck.
Look at these little mini pizzas.
Does this make me look huge?
Hey, guys
look at me, I'm huge.
Hey, Darryl, good news
your fax went through.
Oh yeah
Up high
Yes, sir. Thanks.
Dunder Mifflin, this is Andy. I put
out some new magazines Check it out
Ah, Dwell.
I'm acting like I like Reception,
and I'm a really good actor
so people are actually buying
that p actually like Reception.
But I mean,
seriously, Reception sucks
Ooh! There's the phone
I just
got out of surgery
What's going on? Fill me in
Well, we broke into groups and the
groups are giving presentations later.
Who's doing the presentations?
Packer's giving one
Jim will probably
give ours, I guess.
Damn it
Let's see
What else have you missed?
Ryan switched his
name tag to his pants
so now it's like
if you wear yours
on your shirt
you're a total dip
But if you switch
you're a copycat
But I think I
figured out a solution
What else? My shoes are...
features the tech support
area Bring in your product,
a bunch of nerdy
virgins fix it on the spot
Huge for building loyalty
Yes, that is
a very good point
Yeah, Todd, decent idea
Obvious, but interesting
Dwight, are you all right?
I'm great. How are you?
Uh.
What's our presentation about?
Dwight, will you go
back to the hospital?
You were there for
like three hours.
I got the surgery.
What else is there to do?
Do 100 jumping jacks
No. I don't feel like it.
You do 100 jumping jacks
ninety-seven, 98, 99
You haven't done
any of the research
You're too slow. You're too small.
Seabiscuit is a stupid name
You guys sound just like
the enemies of Seabiscuit
I'm going to do it
Oh, let him do it
Stanley,
are you listening to music?
Yep
All right, who's ready
for the next presentation?
Oh... What is your topic?
What is our topic? Oh, what
a topic it is. Mmm-hmm
Retail consumer habits
Really? Okay
Retail consumer habits is
The only thing
you need to know
about retail
consumer habits is that
consumers are
mindless lemmings
They just want to
be told what to do
Fast-forward to today and the
retail consumer is independent
well-informed, super smart
Super smart
Okay
Shopping habits are both
seasonal and cyclical
What does this mean?
No, sit down
Seasonal, well, the Christmas shopping
season is certainly a busy one.
Back to school is as well
and in early summer
it seems to slow down a bit
But shopping is also cyclical
The menstrual cycle determines
every choice a woman makes.
You see, during ovulation a woman's
only goal is to get pregnant.
During menses she is sad
that she has failed.
And how does
the woman console herself?
Shopping. Shopping
Just, Jim, could you fetch me
some ice chips?
Thank you. Just gonna take a
brief pause at this point
Thank you
Oh, God
Next slide
Mail call
His name is Oscar,
and he's got some mail
And he better open it or go to
jail, 'cause it's your taxes
His name is Kevin,
and no mail for him
But he got a coupon
for some frozen yogurt
Are those the lyrics?
"Anderson's Three Pillars
of Retail."
Crucial. So important
Next
Are there any questions?
What are the Three
Pillars of Retail?
Convenience
Ingredients.
Service
Burgers.
Building loyalty
Killing royalty
But truth be told
we should really
disregard
Anderson's Three Pillars
He was later
diagnosed with dementia
You know what is important?
Is Dwight's pillars
and there's only one, desire
Do we have a desire
to dominate the retail space?
Not just succeed in it
but to dominate.
And looking around this room
I'm not so sure that we do
But we can get there
And I can lead us there,
and that is all that matters
Very true. Where there's
a will, there's a way.
A passionate night
with Hugh Grant's brother
John Grant
He's older than Hugh
just a little bit uglier.
How did I pull that off?
Sheer force of will
That is very good, Dwight
Thank you very much
Any other questions?
Jim
You are bleeding
through your shirt
Oops
That's embarrassing
Egg on my face
Ah
Hey, having fun?
Yes, I am
as a matter of fact
Oh, I know how it is
I know it's a lot of fun
I don't know how it is.
Andy, this is a lame job
What are you doing here?
Andy, when I was 12 years old we did
a field trip, a lock-in at the zoo.
I was in love with her
But when the sun came up
I knew it wasn't real
because she was ugly
and I had grown tired of her
Reception today
but tomorrow you
won't want to do her
She's a dog
Guys, I don't
like this analogy
Oh, fine
Did you see this?
It's nice
How are you feeling?
Amazing
Just lost four
ounces of appendix
already replaced
it with muscle.
Can I see the wound?
Oh, that's disgusting
That's barely healed.
You're not paying me to heal
You're paying me to kick ass
A few hours ago, your body
was open like a cabinet
That's right
That is amazing
Todd, look at that
Oh, yikes
Incoming
Not so fast
Would you come
in early tomorrow
so we could talk about the
store over breakfast?
A lot to offer.
It would be an honor, ma'am
I'll go ahead and cancel
my post-op checkup right now
the first was to make myself the
clear candidate for Vice President
I achieved that,
no thanks to my appendix
The second was to find a
memorable souvenir for Philip.
For that, I do have
to thank my appendix
Dunder Mifflin, how can I
help you save money on paper?
This is Andrew
Hi, Andrew.
What happened to Erin?
Oh, she's on an assignment in
Florida for a couple weeks.
Oh, good for her.
She's such a sweetheart.
You tell her Donna
Moraski misses her.
Everyone, we have
a very special guest
He turned an idea into a store
into hundreds of stores
of Famous Amos cookies.
Yeah
So I hear
you're all looking to
bake up some dough
in the sales game.
Well, back when I
was regular Amos
What's under the cloth?
We'll get to that
Cookies. I bet you
anything it's cookies
It's cookies
Let me finish my speech first
Oh, we get the gist It's just
success and effort, isn't it?
So just don't be coy.
Make with the cookies
Cookies
Famous, hi
I'm sure you get ideas
for new cookies all the time
But I...
Is it oatmeal with no raisins?
I'm sorry to have
wasted your time
That's okay
Thank you very much