Hey, so this isn't
matching up with this
and I'm not sure
which one is right
Can you just hunt down
the original for me?
Yes, me do
All right
Hey, KevKev, what were you saying
before about the paperwork?
Me do it now.
Go. Stop worry
Kevin, do you feel okay?
Me feel good. Body strong
Sleep big last night
Yeah, I think we should
get him to the hospital.
Yeah, all right, Kev
why don't you come with us?
No, he's fine.
- No, no, guys He's fine.
He's always
been like that
No, he hasn't
I mean, he's gotten worse
over the years, but
He's making a statement
It's an ironic comment
on our expectations of him
A funhouse image of
our model of Kevin.
You keep think that
Me mechanic
not speak English
but he know what me mean
when me say, "Car no go.'
And we best friends
So me think why waste time say
lot word when few word do trick.
Kevin, I appreciate
what you're trying to do
Thank
Here we have
a word code
Same way we have
a dress code.
And what we're
talking about is
basically the speech equivalent
to just wearing underpants
Sometimes words
you no need use
but need need
for talk talk.
But save time.
More success
Does it save time, though? Because
we've been here for about an hour
No me fault
Kevin, at most you're saving
a microscopic amount of time
Many small time
make big time.
What are you going to
do with all this time?
See world
Kevin, you can't possibly save
enough time to see the world
Kevin, are you saying "see
the world' or SeaWorld?
See world Oceans. Fish Jump.
China.
No, see? Right there that's
the problem with your method
because I still don't know if you're
saying SeaWorld or <<see the world.'
And it's taking a lot
of time to explain it
Fine,
fine, I'll talk normally
When me president
they see
They see
This week we are rolling out the
brand new Sabre tablet, the Pyramid.
Why is it
shaped like that?
So you can tell your clients
"Unleash the power of the pyramid
It's huge
How much does it weigh?
Oh, no, no, no
Without the battery pack
and the optional memory
booster, it's barely 3 pounds
How much memory does it
have without the booster?
Fifty L
I'm sorry, "L"?
- Mmm-hmm
How many I to a K?
DWIGHT You're really going
to want the booster.
How on earth are
we supposed to sell
I'll take five
Andy, don't make us
sell this stupid thing
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
This is Dwight's meeting
Thank you. The
I just wanted to pop in
and get your opinions
on ties and tie clips.
Which combo do you think
Robert's going to like more?
What do you think, C-Span?
"C-Span"?
Yeah, C-Span.
Cocker spaniel
Spaniel because of your Spanish
bloodline Cocker because
Is this really the best use
of our collective time?
I am still forming a first
impression with Robert
Once it is formed
we can all relax, okay?
I'm sorry to hijack your meeting,
D-Dub-Dog, had to pull rank
Okay, let's look
at some ties.
Here's how I'm going to
help out from now on.
I'm going to not care
And I'm going to
sit around quietly
waiting for Andy's
inevitable demise
Your friend
Neil Patrick Harris
really made me laugh
the other night.
D Dog, you have a message
Erin, you don't
need to call him that
Andy wants us to, P Dog
It's okay, E Dog
Who called?
Justine. She said
she's coming by later
Your ex-wife?
Wait, I thought
she was a ♪
and you ♪
hated her guts
No, no, no, I like her
Well, I was just
quoting you
I would never say that about her.
I don't know the woman
No, man. We get
along now real well
All right
Can't wait to meet her
I'll introduce you
Yeah, we had a few fights
I suppose
but last night we put
a lot of that to bed.
I can't tell you what I did
with my ex-wife last night
I have to sing it
We took a shower
We were naked
We...
Oh
Hi, Dad. I
Oh, boy.
Hello, Andy
Excellent tie
Would you be requiring a cold
beverage while you're here?
I'd love some coffee
I was looking over your projections
and I think we can do better
Are you factoring in the whole national
economy declining and all that?
Andy, do you know
why I chose you?
I think I can sum it up
with what I think
is your favorite
ice cream flavor
Vanilla?
Vanilla? No
You'll never guess in a million
billion years you'll never guess
You were saying you chose me
There was a reason
Andy, can you inspire?
Do you have that skill set?
Can I inspire?
I don't know
Oh, thank you
Oh, sorry
Yeah, just put it down
Mmm
That is very cold
Yeah, it's old
Why would I
I asked if you
wanted a cold beverage
and you said coffee
Why don't we get Robert a nice, hot,
fresh cup and I will have this.
Andy, you don't
want that.
I've been craving a
freezing cup of old coffee.
Mmm
Sorry
You like her
I do. Yeah
She likes you
You know, we've both been into
each other at different times
and just never
really synced up
Now we're in this weird
dance and now we're...
I'm afraid you've
lost my interest
Let me call you back
I got to go
If the office superstore
was supposed to
put us little suppliers
out of business
why are we still here?
Yeah
This is where we go.
You'd go someplace else That's
not it That's not the answer.
It's a answer.
It's a wrong answer
There are no wrong answers
Take a look
at where you are
Where you once worked in a dying
industry, you now work at its birth
Those superstores
are terrified of us.
Anybody know why?
Wait, they're terrified?
Let me tell you how I buy
something these days
I know what I want, I go on the
Internet and get the best price
Or I don't know what I want and I go
to a small store that can help me
The era of personal service
is back You are back.
You'll find that customers
will pay our higher prices
and then they w
thank us
and we will say to them
"You are welcome."
Thank you
Ooh
Andrew, I chose you for a
reason Lead these people.
Show me the best numbers
this place has ever seen.
Last quarter we saw
4% growth. Double it
You got it
Double.
Done
I'm not kidding.
Neither am I
It's already done
I'm just kidding
It's going to take some time.
Double
Hey
What's up, guys?
Just thought we'd have
a little rap session.
Talk about business.
See how things are going
Why don't you start?
If no one else wants to
I was just thinking about
Robert Man, what a boss.
Just throws down goals
you know?
Anyway, how's the sales
doubling project going?
Yeah, how are we
supposed to do that?
We can't just
press a magic button
Of course not.
There's no magic button
You have to summon that
If we could just double our
sales, we already would have
You're not
making any sense
He brings up
two good points
Do you have any new leads? And new
territories you want us to look into?
Maybe have an in
with a big client
that we could get
our foot in the door?
Dwight, anything?
We could talk about
how fast children grow up
and before you know it
they're out of the house
You know what? We need to get
our heads out of the box
If we did have something
what would it look like?
What would it be?
Tuna
New leads, new
territory to look into
maybe an in with
a big company
that we could get
our foot in the door
Fart
Good sesh
That leg's asleep
Hello
I'm looking for
Darryl Philbin?
Don't
Oh
You must think... No, I'm
not I'm using the fax
This isn't
No, wait.
I'm not supposed to represent
the company, right?
There's usually
an Erin here, so
Okay
Darryl, a girl
Rub a dub, dub, apricot scrub
What's up, darling?
Everybody
this is Justine
Hi, Justine
- Hello.
This is Jim, Oscar
Hi
Everybody
Kevin
Can we go
someplace private?
Follow me.
I got a space
After you I've been thinking
about you all morning
I don't know what you did
I can barely walk today.
D Bone, there you are
Let me guess
Somebody needs a brownie
Lick the spoon?
No. No. That's okay
I just,
I wanted to ask you about
Is this about
the profits?
Because if it is, I just don't see
the point It's so Wall Street.
I know, right? Yeah
Um
How is everything?
Good.
Really, really good
Must be a tough time
to be a family farm.
It is And beets are not immune
I made some inroads in salad but
heirloom tomatoes are pushing back.
What are you going to
do about that?
I don't know,
what do you mean?
Got to be some way you could
double your beet sales
You wanted the job the job
is yours, just do the job.
And I'll do mine
Walnuts?
No
Have you seen this?
Parenting? Yeah.
This is Cece's
favorite magazine
She loves
the pictures of babies
She looks at it when she's on the
potty and she makes the faces
Have you read it?
Has an adult member of your family
read this particular issue?
I flipped through it
So you saw the article
on the importance of
taking frequent walks
while you're pregnant?
Of course, yeah.
- We know that
I will be taking a morning
walk and an afternoon walk.
Would you like to
join me?
That sounds nice
Great
You have a walking buddy
I do
Thanks for
coming in, guys
You don't have to thank us
for coming in It's our job
Well, I never got thanked
for coming into a meeting
and I always wanted to be, so
I<m going to thank people.
What's under the blanket?
This is what's
under the blanket
We don't get it
These are incentives. It's how
we're going to double growth
Now, you're probably all asking
yourselves "Well, how does this work?'
It seems like a basic reward
system where you give us points
and then we redeem
those points for prizes
You're exactly right
and you get a point
Oh.
Uh, is that a vibrator?
20 points
How does one get a point?
I've outlined
the exact parameters
in an email
so check your spam folders
But basically, you do your
job better you get points.
So collect 15 points and redeem
them for this polar bear.
Why is it all kids' stuff and a vibrator?
It's so gross.
There's lots of stuff
John Irving, collected
works 22 points.
Or you can pool your points and redeem
55 for this maternity shirt. Ahem
How about you want us to
work harder, pay us more.
I can't
This points system
is really insulting.
Ooh
I didn't mean to offend you
and I hope you'll forgive me
because I am very very
"sari." 16 points
That's a tablecloth
What if we went all the
way up to 500 points?
That's a crazy
amount of points
But what if?
Well, what do you want?
I don't know.
For such a crazy number
I'd like
something pretty crazy
All right, for 500 points,
I will wear a dress to work
That's pretty good What
about for 1,000 points?
I'll run naked
through the parking lot
with a donut
on my ding dong
Yeah, you like that?
All right
for 5,000 points
I will let you
tattoo whatever you want
on the stern of
the old S.S. Bernard
No
Really?
All right. All right And
you are totally serious?
Swear to God. Hope to die
Now let's get to work.
Wait, but you did say we
can pool our points right?
In that case
let's get to work, guys
- Yeah!
Let's do it, guys
Good
I can have it to you by the
beginning of next week.
All right
thank you very much
Phyllis, Brachen Auto?
Ask for Donald.
Karen's bananas
Okay
T-Bag-Bone
Andrew
DWIGHT
Hold on, one second
Have you noticed a little bit
of a mood shift around here?
No. I haven't
noticed anything
Really? Because I sat next to Stanley
for years and this is nap time.
Open eye nap time. He balances
the phone on his shoulder
and just powers down
Now look at him
You've got to unleash
the power of the pyramid
I don't know what
to tell you, man
Do you think it has something to
do with that incentive program?
Oh, 100% We all want to
see you tattoo your ass
Uh.
I think people thought I was
kidding when I said that.
No. You definitely
weren't kidding.
That came across
loud and clear.
Oh, by the way,
I want to hand this in
120 points?
Yeah. Big sale
Don't worry about it, though I
don't really care about the points
I would like
a point receipt though
Hey, yes this is Jim Halpert
calling for Donald.
Can you hold on for one second?
Thank you very much
Who talked to
Maggie at Kaufman's?
And I'm back
How are you, sir?
I think you can squeeze a couple
more golf games in, right?
Where's Angela?
Angela, these are yours
Hey, Kevin,
what are you doing?
Don't talk to me
Yeah
Hi. Professor Frank
Andy Bernard, class of '95
Hey there, I'm a huge fan of
your management book Management.
Uh, quick question I may
be missing a chapter here:
"De-incentivizing."
What are your strategies?
I'm looking for
a real blow to morale
Uh, why?
Well, um
I guess you could say
I'm in one of those
classic ass-tattoo-incentive
situations.
Took 'em one day
Are you ready?
I like it. I like it
Okay, keep in mind, it's not too
late to choose another prize
and there are some
great new additions
My car.
For 1,000 points
Or best offer
What else you got?
Oh, and then this
was Phyllis' idea.
Oh
Oh!
So nasty, Phyllis
Oh, my God
We were hoping you could
do something like this
So coming out of
his butt is a
Baby
Baby.
Yes
Yeah. No problem
We should think about this Does
anyone have any better ideas?
I like what we have
Yeah, nice try
It's pretty edgy
I just need
a second outside
You getting psyched up?
Yeah.
Andy, nobody really expects
you to go through with this.
Toons, what am I
doing here?
Why did Robert pick me?
Confession, I don't
know what I'm doing
I mean
do you like it?
You having fun?
I'll tell you this everybody
else is having a lot of fun
And you did that
My ass is only so big. I mean
I can't do this every day
But I think it's big enough
to buy you some time
until your next
great idea.
Which, by the way
I can't wait for
No one expects me to go
through with this, right?
Absolutely not
Let's ink my stink
Yeah
My heart belongs to music but
my ass belongs to these people
Whoa
Do your worst
Uh, you can keep your
pants on actually
If you just drop them down
a bit that'd be great.
They are already off
my good sir.
I'd really prefer
they not be down
Well, I think down's better
Sweating pretty heavily down there
Do you think you
could work from this?
We made some
small adjustments
Okay, you want me to
Just those few adjustments Yeah.
All right.
Let's begin
This is where I grin
and bear Ow, ow!
That was just
a cotton swab
Invest in
softer cotton, sir
Ow
Oh
Obviously you can go
the ass tattoo route
and obviously I'm
going to like it.
Draw some blood
Ha-ha!
Why did I choose
Andy to run the office?
Because he's all surface, uncomplicated.
What you see is what you get.
It could be a recipe
for mediocrity, yes.
But then again, it might just
be why people fight for him.
It's a Nard dog
That's my nickity name
I love it. I love it
Pull up your pants
There's something
about an underdog
that really
inspires the unexceptional
Um, what should we
talk about?
Well, we could talk about an
ethical dilemma I'm having.
Oh, yeah, sure
I hope I can help
A coworker of mine is drinking
caffeine while pregnant
and I don't know if I should
call social services about it
Angela, that's
pretty transparently me
Maybe
You know
it's just herbal tea
In mugs with trace
amounts of coffee
Yeah. I think you
should call social services
I already did
You know, maybe we should
just have our own pregnancies
and not pretend like
we're in this together
Fine