Hey, everybody!
It's closing time
You don't gotta go home
but you can't stay here.
Closing time!
Every office needs an
end-of-the-day tradition
Something to tell you
the day's over.
Otherwise, you go home and the
night just feels like more day.
It's weird
Closing time!
W, R, K
One last call
for alcohol so...
No, it's W, R, K
as in kitten?
so finish your
whiskey or beer!
Oh, my boss is
singing Closing Time,
maybe that's
what you're hearing
Come on, Pam
Closing time!
Time for you to go home
to the places you will be from
Let's see Andy has been
manager for 105 days,
which means I've heard
Closing Time 105 times
Still don't know the words
Home and home and home
I know who I want
to take me home!
to take me home
Take me home
You know what? Fine! I try to
start fun traditions for you guys
but if you don't want
to sing, no traditions
Closing time!
Every new beginning...
I never heard that song before and
once I heard it I did not care for it.
But that song means
it's time to go home.
Now, it's my favourite song
Every new beginning comes from
some other beginning's end
Good night
This report is atrocious Who's
your favourite Iron Chef?
You go first
The ticketing software
paints a picture
of a sloppy, careless
error-prone office.
Well, the monitoring software
is a double-edged sword.
Sometimes the
Sorry. Go ahead
Mmm-hmm
Did you need
something from us?
Yes
Your attention
because...
No. That is all
Last night I dreamed
that the number two
was the most valued
number in the world.
The Vice President
had all the power,
athletes fought
for silver medals,
women were considered
the best gender.
And stadiums of fans shouted,
"We're number two!"
As with all my dreams,
I'm guessing
it was about
my fear of immigrants
Last week, an accounting
mistake resulted in
a client getting
their order for free
Ho! That's not good
Chalk that one up to "Tweedle-Dee'
and "Tweedle-Dum" out there
Who are they?
They're both Kevin
Oscar's the
Sex and the City gang,
and Angela, if you can
Andy, sometimes I feel like
you don't know me at all.
I would agree with that
Simply end the mistakes
End the mistakes. Easy
When I come back next week, and this
report shows me "No mistakes, '
we can talk
about names all day
Our favourite names,
silly made-up names
normal names said in a silly voice.
Wouldn't that be nice?
I would like that
End the mistakes
That's all I ask
And you can't have
a favorite Iron Chef
It depends entirely on
the secret ingredient
Sometimes I feel you
don't know food at all
I'm just saying,
with the NBA lockout
I think roller derby's in a
really good place right now.
So, my pitch is, me, Pam
you and someone else
maybe Justine
No. Not Justine
Never Justine
Is that off again?
Oh, yeah.
Okay
Hey, mandatory warehouse
safety meeting today.
We don't really do those
We just sign the thing.
Are you really this lazy?
I'll be there
Hey
Mondays suck
Yeah. Yep
Just trying to
I may have a little solution
to our mistakes problem.
This is a project I've been
working on for quite some time.
And today might be
the day to use it.
What've you got?
Allow me
You're gonna love this
Should've used
a shorter string.
Never mind
I know it by heart
It is a system that holds people
accountable for everyone else's work.
Sounds controversial
Have I not been
worthy of your trust?
a reliable number two?
Do not go there
You're the deuce
I never want to drop
Well, I can make this work
I'll set it up right now.
I just need your go ahead
Go do the voodoo
that you do so we
I will do my voodoo
Mmm-hmm
Hey. I need you to get
the paperwork rolling
on a new
workplace relationship
For you?
Yes, for Gabe
Who are you seeing?
That's great
Whom I am seeing is Val,
from down in the warehouse
I'm not technically
seeing her
but, I've seen
her with the eyes
And there was attraction in
at least one direction, so...
You know, I don't have to do paperwork
unless you're actually dating.
Okay. Well, once this starts
it's gonna be moving fast,
it's gonna be hot and heavy
and I don't want
a bunch of
bureaucratic red tape
wrapped around my jock
you know?
But I mean, well, have
you talked to her?
Yeah. We had a whole
conversation about Mondays
Do you know
her last name yet?
Toby, I'm gonna tell you
her last name tomorrow
because she's gonna be
screaming it tonight.
She's gonna be screaming
her own last name?
Hey, watch it
Good luck, Gabe
Hi, guys
Hi.
I just wanna say that you all have
been doing amazing work, really.
Thank you.
And I'd like to add
that your work has
been a little sloppy
So, Dwight and I
have implemented
a new program that
we like to call...
Dwight?
The Accountability Booster
It registers every time a mistake
has been made in the office,
from a late delivery
to an accounting error
Five strikes in a day
equals a home run
One home run
and you're out
If we as a group make
five mistakes in a day
something bad happens
Like, we block Minesweeper
Or, in this case, an e-mail
gets sent to Robert California
containing the consultant's
report from last year.
Remember the one that recommended
the branch be shut down?
What?
And, as a failsafe, also
every negative e-mail you've ever
written about him to the group
will also be
forwarded to him
What e-mails are
you talking about?
Robert's favorite songs, Creep
by TLC Creep by Radiohead.
You remember that one, Jim?
"There's no way he hasn't
strangled at least one stripper.'
Oscar
"He eats his yogurt like he is
punishing it for disappointing him.'
Kelly
That's not that
bad, actually.
PS, "We should
kill him."
Wait. So, you installed
a doomsday device?
No, it's an
Accountability Booster
Which, when it goes off
it destroys everything
very similar to
a doomsday device
Jim, you're trying to make me sound
like some kind of evil maniac
No, the point is, is that we are
now working in an environment
where we have accountability
to each other
I am confident that you
guys are equal to the task
No, we're not. And you are a
psycho who is ruining our lives
We can't do this, Dwight.
We can't
Smile
Nod. Smile and nod
They're making me out
to be a Bond villain.
I like to think of myself
as a brilliant scientist
who will stop at nothing
to remake the world.
Like
Not Doctor Moreau
someone good
Doctor Frankenstein
Doctor Jekyll, not them
Doctor
Are you sure
this is a good idea?
I mean, the thing about this office
is we make a lot of mistakes
But the device
will change that
Without a safety net
people will improve.
All right, everybody, looks like
we need to be getting to work.
Be extra careful,
double-check everything
Or the Accountability Booster
will get you.
This doomsday device sounds
like a scare tactic to me.
There's an easy way to tell
if this device is a sham,
we just make a mistake
I'll send an order down to shipping
before we've received payment
There's one mistake
Now we only have four strikes
left until a home run.
Dwight's our co-worker
and he worked really hard
on this doomsday
device. So, I...
it's not a doomsday
device! Gosh!
We can do this, you guys
First
Second
it's not a race.
Third
Who knows
what the belt is for?
It's for
protecting my ass
when you suckers lift
more than you can handle.
What's up? I'm Gabe
Corporate. Continue
Don't be nervous
Apparently,
we have a visitor
Gabe, everyone
Hi, Gabe
All right so the support belt.
Now this one is mine
Doesn't get much
use nowadays.
Look at this.
This is enormous
I get the sense that Val
enjoys a good put-down
Considering that's the only
thing I know about her,
I will be milking that hard
It's like a hula-hoop
right?
Mele Kalikimaka
is Hawaii's way
You done?
The Michelin Man called,
he wants his cummerbund back
Remember, we have to get Regal
Escrow their refund by 5:00.
I'm on it
Kevin, maybe I
should handle that.
We really need you to
focus on your project.
Good thinking
Apparently a big client
for this company
needs to know the story
of how paper gets made
Oscar, use a calculator
When the stakes are this high there's
only one computer that I trust
And it's powered by
Thai food and Spanish reds
All right, everybody
you're doing great.
Well, I wouldn't say that. Three
mistakes already is pretty terrible
But I do see
improvement
Meredith kept someone
on hold for 30 minutes,
and now look
she's hard at work
Dwight, question.
No questions
If this doomsday
device goes off
Accountability Booster
If this bad idea goes off
and we all lose our jobs, are
you gonna feel good about that?
I haven't even
considered it
That's how sure I am that this
Accountability Booster is gonna work
Try "Mose-1-2-3-4.'
Dwight would never be that
obvious Try something like...
"Z-6-4-$-8.'
Not that exactly, Jim
something like that
Okay
How about
"Scranton-Strangler-6-6-6"?
Nope
No?
Aw...
Shoot.
You guys are never gonna
shut down the machine, okay?
But I appreciate your energy
and your teamwork
You apply this to
your regular work
you won't even notice
that the device is there
watching you
ready to strike
What's Dwight's
mother's name?
Hedda
No
Once you've read
the packet, sign the back
Hey, Darryl.
I was thinking
maybe while we
read through this
you could grab us
all some coffee?
My treat
Here's a $100 bill
That should cover it
I think.
Don't bring me any of that
caramel soy latte crap, okay?
I want a decaf
frappuccino.
Val?
Actually, Val
why don't you come with?
I'll need the extra hands
to carry them back.
Yeah, sure
Mmm-hmm
Caramel soy latte
No, a decaf frap
Got it
You sent the late notice to
Rinehart and Wolfe, right?
Mmm-hmm. 64620
Nuh-uh.
Yes
588 plus 15%
Oh, no!
- What does this mean?
What does it mean?
- Andy.
Oh
God
That's five strikes
Well
I was saving this for my
retirement which I guess is today
Dwight, we got
five strikes.
Really?
Did the e-ma
go out or...
It goes out automatically
at 5:00 p.m
Well, then there's
gotta be a way to stop it
Well, I would have to enter my
password in order to cancel it.
Okay
Dwight, you may now
enter your password.
No
What?
You don't deserve
to have this branch
Five mistakes in
less than a day?
We did our best
No, you didn't, Phyllis
You complained
the whole time,
you yelled at me you tried
to break into the machine.
What?
You're a real crumb bum
you know that?
Hey, you can't
just change the rules
because you don't
like the outcome.
What about you, Kevin? What
about you and your fake task?
Can you tell me now
where paper comes from?
The man tree
puts its penis
Okay. All right, Andy,
back me up here, please
No
What?
Dwight, be human for once
shut down the machine.
Shut it down
Shut it down.
Shut down the machine
Shut it down
good luck finding
a new job, idiots
I'll make sure to write
you a glowing reference
Glowingly negative
Dwight's car is gone
I bet he went home
Some of us should go there, try
to talk some sense into him.
Get him to stop that e-mail
Pam, you should come with
me. Dwight really likes you,
and your breasts are
enormous, that could help us
Kevin has that lovability
Guys, come on
I'm right here
Jim, I want you to go find Robert.
Just be where he is
in case that e-ma
goes out at 5:00,
you can try to
delete it or something
Okay. Where is he?
He's at some club where you
either eat squash or play squash
I'll try both
Oh
Did you come to
reason with me?
Got you something
And I just really
want to talk to you
Get lost
Well, now hold on
What are you doing?
What does it
look like I'm doing?
Digging a grave
for a horse
Do you need a hand?
Yeah, you need a hand?
If you hit another horse
you've dug too far
I'll see you
next week, Will.
Robert
Jim, what are you
What a surprise
Yeah. Well, you know I just had
a meeting, a squash meeting
Yeah?
You up for a game?
A game? Or a match?
Exactly! Here we go
Let's do it
Are you okay, Kevin?
Where are you going?
In. I'm hungry
Could we come in, too?
Just for some water?
Okay. Take off your shoes
Except you, Kevin
They stay on
Wow, I forgot how
pretty your house is
This is the newest addition,
built by Erasmus Schrute in 1808
It doubled as a tuberculosis
recovery room until 2009.
That's too much doodle
and not enough lab
Yeah, when are they gonna do a
Labradoodle that's just lab?
That's what I'm saying
Hey
You're welcome.
Thanks for the coffee
So, tonight I was thinking,
I'm gonna go to the cemetery
I'm gonna drink
a little wine
and I thought maybe you'd
like to come with me
Are you asking me
on a date?
Yes, I am
Because I don't
date coworkers
it's not personal.
It's a matter of policy
I could quit
Problem solved
Don't quit
Good policy
It's sensible
Smart
All right. Serving
Serving, serving, serving
In the box.
In the box
Why haven't
we heard anything?
It's 4:45 There's
only 15 minutes left
Oh, now you
can do math?
Where were you two hours
ago beautiful mind?
I made a mistake
I'm sorry!
I know how to save
the company, everyone
Just write a petition,
get everyone's signature
including our clients,
march down to Florida
and shove it up your butt
it's not that funny
Pam, you got something
on your shirt.
Oh!
Well, pobody's
nerfect, right?
Did you just have a stroke, Pam?
It's "nobody's perfect.'
Nice stroke, Pam
No, it's a jokey saying
"Pobody's nerfect.'
Like, I can't even
say those words right
I hadn't heard that before
That's funny
Dwight, there's just the small
You know what would go so
great with this cabbage pie?
Milk
Any specific animal?
I'm thinking cow
Don't say cow.
What are you doing?
It's five to 5:00
Just don't talk
about the e-mail, okay?
He's gonna cancel it on his
own I really think he will.
That's insane
Just trust me.
Trust you? Like I trusted
Dwight this morning?
I got this
Thanks for everything
Sive drafely
Wasn't it supposed
to be drive safely?
Is that my phone?
Sounded like mine
No, I think it's mine Let me
just check real quick here
All right
No, it's mine.
You took it out of my bag
Oh. Oops
Yeah
Can I have it?
Yes
Right now?
There you go
Whoa! No! Wait, wait
What the *?
Oh, man
I'm sorry!
Jesus!
Did it break?
No, it's good, thanks.
You sure?
Yeah
What kind of
iPhone is that?
It's the standard one,
the one everyone has
Yeah. I have the one
that nobody has.
Is there anything
interesting?
It depends, Jim.
Do you find one-day-only
JetBlue sales to
Buffalo interesting?
No, I don't
All right
Well, I am sore and
obviously horrible at this
My serve
Dwight stopped the device
Yes
He stopped it
We still have our jobs
They're not my favorite
people in the world
I wouldn't even
call them friends.
They come over here,
eat my pie,
dig the crappiest horse grave
you've ever seen.
God, I'm gonna have to work
with them forever, aren't I?
Just take it easy
Nice and easy
Classic, right?
Ooh
I'm all right.
You all right?
Yeah.
Skinned knee
Yeah
Need a little ice
on that, maybe.
Yeah. That does
not feel good.
Okay. My serve