It feels like it wasn't that long ago
we were here doing this for Halley.
Because it wasn't.
Which reminds me, before we leave,
let's get you a vasectomy.
Ohh, that's sweet, but today's all about you.
So you two ready
to find out the sex of this baby?
- Yeah.
- Absolutely.
Is Halley hoping
for a little brother or a little sister?
Well, she's 9 months old. So unless it
jingles or is in my bra, she doesn't care.
And how about you two?
You know, for the first one,
we really wanted a girl.
But this time around,
we don't have a preference.
Yeah, boy, girl, as long as it's healthy.
[ULTRASOUND HUMMING]
Well, it's a boy.
BOTH:
Oh.
Oh, come on.
You can't really be disappointed.
Hey, I barely know how to be a man myself.
Now I have to teach someone?
As the saying goes,
"Those who can't do, teach."
Don't you want a little version of Howard?
I already have a little version of Howard.
Now I'm having a son?
I'll have to teach him how to play sports...
and watch sports.
And— And— And—
He just ran out of "man" things.
He's in trouble.
It's okay. We're all here to help.
Yes, and this baby will have plenty
of manly role models.
Now, I'm certain that whatever Bernadette
can't teach him, Penny can.
- Oh, she can pee into a bottle.
PENNY: Mm-hm.
Anything with a neck wider than a nickel.
Howie, there's a lot of amazing things
you can teach a son.
Yeah, you do always know
how to pick just the right antacid.
I don't know if I can teach that.
It's just something I was born with.
Come on. You can build things.
You were an astronaut.
That's true.
You know, as a kid, I used to make model
rockets. That'd be pretty cool to do with a son.
Model rockets. Finally.
Something interesting.
What is your preferred mode of recovery?
Sheldon, we're helping our friends.
And we got to model rockets.
It was a tedious road,
but well worth the effort.
- Have you thought of names?
- We finally got to model rockets.
Why are you turning back?
- Where you going?
- Back to the dry cleaner. Look.
They didn't get the stain
out of my Starfleet uniform.
Well, if you didn't make me
wear the green body paint in bed...
you wouldn't have to
get it dry cleaned so much.
No, it's worth it.
[LAPTOP CHIMING]
Hey, wait, it's your mom.
Oh, too bad. She just missed me.
Hey, Beverly.
Oh, hello, Penny.
Leonard just left. He's gonna be
so upset he missed your call.
Why?
Because he—
Yeah, I don't know. How are you?
Did you mean personally or professionally?
Personally? Like, what'd you do last night?
I had Cuban food at the home of a man
with whom I shared unsatisfying intercourse.
Wow. Okay.
And to anticipate your next questions...
roasted pork and sideways missionary.
Sure. Sure. Because you were full.
I haven't looked at all this stuff in years.
Had it. Had it.
Burnt down my garage with it.
I had three model rockets as a kid.
And that was the largest
space program in India.
You have a replica Saturn V?
Yeah, my dad bought it
before he, you know...
abandoned our family.
Lucky duck.
I could never bring myself
to open it without him.
It's silly.
That's not silly.
I always wanted my dad to build
rockets with me, but he wasn't interested.
Yes. Disappointing fathers.
Tell me about it.
I remember for my 16th birthday,
my dad bought me a Mercedes.
Like, a little one. Like, a starter Mercedes.
He had barely handed me the keys
before he had to rush back to work.
I didn't see him again till,
like, pretty late that night.
Anyway...
as angry as I was with him leaving...
building this stuff is probably
what led me to become an engineer.
I suppose, in his own way,
my dad also encouraged me to pursue science.
I mean, he is the one that taught me
that flatulence is combustible.
And also,
polyester gym shorts don't burn.
They melt.
Yeah, I guess I'm an astrophysicist because
as a kid I said I liked to look at the stars.
So my dad sent me to Hawaii
to visit the Keck telescope.
Screw you. My pain is real.
You know what, forget the past.
What do you say
you and me build this rocket.
That sounds like it could be
a real bonding experience for us.
- Right?
- Oh, I see.
You think that's a positive.
So you didn't wanna hang out
with Sheldon and Howard?
No, they were bonding
over their sad childhoods.
And my stupid parents
were always there for me.
What's all this?
I'm just boxing up all the clothes Halley's
outgrown. Guess we won't need them anymore.
Slow down. I'm sure there's some
you could reuse for a boy.
"Daddy's little girl"?
Okay, well, what if we change it to say:
"Daddy's little girl magnet."
Boom, boy shirt.
What about this?
Okay.
Pull off the skirt, slap a lightning bolt
on the front, and you've got Baby Flash.
Oh! Stick a long sleeve under it.
Boom, Baby Sheldon.
- Wow, you're really good at this.
- Oh, please.
This isn't my first time
turning girl clothes into boy clothes.
Why?
You got your sister's hand-me-downs?
Yeah, that.
Oh, I should've brought peanuts.
You can't eat peanuts. You're allergic.
If you die, who's going to drive me home?
I'm not gonna eat them.
It's a thing they do at JPL.
When the Ranger mission had a successful
launch, there were peanuts in the room.
Ever since then,
they have them at every launch.
That sounds like a silly superstition.
It's more of a tradition.
Ohh! I do love a tradition.
Pull over at the next peanut store.
I don't think that's a real thing.
Oh, don't be pedantic.
Any nut store will do.
I don't think we can get peanuts out here.
Oh, well, then this whole day's ruined.
Now that I think about it,
maybe it is more of a superstition.
Whew. That was close.
[CELL PHONE CHIMING]
Oh, hey, Beverly.
You called my phone, not Leonard's.
Actually, I was hoping to speak with you.
Is this a good time?
That depends.
What time is it where you are?
Just after 5.
Ahem. Yeah, that counts. What's up?
Well, I enjoyed
our conversation the other day.
And I was hoping to continue it.
Really?
Yes. You may find this surprising...
but I don't have a lot of
what you would call "girlfriends."
What?
Of course there are my female colleagues...
but they're all Freudians.
So the only boy that I can
dish about is my father. Ha-ha-ha.
Well, I'm here for you.
What do you wanna talk about?
Well, last time, we focused on my life.
If we're going to be real girlfriends,
we should talk about you as well.
Well, if we're gonna be real girlfriends...
we should get a third girl
we can trash behind her back.
Oh, so we'd be catty.
Oh, I like it.
What about Sheldon's fiancé?
She seems a bit dour.
"Dour"? Meow.
All right. Here we go.
L-minus-ten.
- Nine.
- What are you doing?
It's "T-minus."
I was an astronaut. We used "L-minus."
Yeah, but this is a Saturn V. When they
launched those, they said, "T-minus."
It's my rocket. We're doing it my way.
Fine.
I'm not saying I know why your dad left,
but I think I'm getting an idea.
L-minus-ten, night, eight, seven, six—
Because you're kind of bossy.
Five, four, three, two, one.
I remember them going up higher.
Well, that's perfect.
The one thing I thought I could
do with my son. I can't even do that right.
If you wanna see it again, I got it on video.
It's pretty cool in slow motion.
Thank you for your support.
- You're welcome.
- I was being sarcastic.
How dare you?
Sheldon, what am I gonna do?
What do I know about raising a boy?
What do you know about raising a girl?
Oh, my God.
You're right.
Well, I don't know
if that was sarcasm or not.
So either, "You're welcome," or "Hey."
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
Leonard, did you really just text me from the
couch to put extra mustard on your sandwich?
I was worried
you might not check your e-mail.
[CELL PHONE CHIMES]
- I swear to God I will throw this out.
- That one was not me.
Oh, wait. It's just your mom.
My mother's texting you?
Yeah, we've been talking a lot lately.
Why?
Is she sick of talking
to the Magic Mirror on the wall?
No, I thinks she's lonely.
She's been reaching out.
Okay, just be careful.
You think you're getting close to her.
The next thing you know,
you're featured in a book called:
He's Doing It on Purpose:
Raising a Teenage Bed Wetter.
No, it's not like that.
You know, she's been
opening up about her life.
She's been really supportive about mine.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I've been telling her about my job.
She said she was proud of me.
Well, that's great.
She never told me she was proud of me.
Even when I stayed dry for a whole month.
Do you not want me
to be friends with your mom?
Well, let's be clear.
I married you to hurt her.
You're kind of ruining it.
Reason number 13 to feel good:
As a launch, it was bad.
But as an explosion, it was glorious.
Reason 14:
You still have all your fingers.
And boys prefer a dad with fingers.
Thanks for trying, but you're not
gonna be able to cheer me up.
Well, how about this then?
You quit your whining before I give you
something to cry about, young man.
What?
Those are comforting words
my father would often say.
Did it help?
I turned out great. You tell me.
Let's get going.
You gonna be this mopey
all the way home?
I don't know. Maybe.
There any chance you'd be cheered up
by an amazing trigonometry riddle?
Well, if you can't answer that,
there's no way you're gonna get this riddle.
Oh, hey. Hey, what do you think?
Just because it's a boy, I don't think you need
to put a picture of genitals on his shirt.
What? That's a baseball bat
with two little baseballs.
Okay, yeah, now I see it.
So, you know...
I understand why Howard is nervous about
having a son, but are you really upset about it?
No, I'm fine.
It's just, I grew up with a bunch of brothers.
So I thought it'd be nice for Halley
to have a sister. Is that wrong?
Of course it's wrong. You don't know
what this little boy's gonna be like.
Maybe he'll be rough and tumble.
Or maybe he'll be sweet and sensitive.
Or maybe he'll be all those things, like me.
You're rough and tumble?
You bet I am, bitch.
But I'm also sensitive
and regret saying that.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
- Hey.
- Hello.
You got a sec?
Sure, what's up?
Penny's been talking to my mother
like they're best friends.
And it's kind of freaking me out.
Okay.
I am pretty sure they're not best friends.
Because you can only have one best friend.
And Penny has that, and, tsk, it's me.
Oh, really? Is she FaceTiming
with you right now?
She's FaceTiming with my mom.
And believe me,
that is not a face you want to spend time with.
Hm. Well, I have been pretty busy lately.
Maybe I've been neglecting our friendship.
Penny knows I have a complicated relationship
with my mother. She doesn't care.
And with everything going on at the lab and
planning the wedding, I have so little free time.
Penny doesn't know
how manipulative my mother can be.
Did you know there's such a thing as
reverse-reverse-reverse psychology?
Because there is.
She must feel so abandoned.
She's used to me being there all the time.
But now I have my own life,
and she's just gonna have to accept it.
And why is my mom
proud of Penny and not me?
The question is: why is Penny
afraid of me growing as a person?
- I'm good at stuff too.
- I deserve my own life.
- Okay, well, thanks.
- Yeah, good talk.
You know, studies have shown that...
people distracted by emotional issues
are poor drivers.
What about people distracted
by irritating passengers?
That would be hard to test because
irritating is a subjective quality.
Strongly disagree.
Can I drive?
No, you can't drive.
You don't even have a license.
Actually, I do.
Really?
Since when?
Three years ago.
I went on a bit of a license kick.
I'm also a commercial fisherman.
Then why don't you ever drive yourself?
Honestly, I barely passed my test.
And the one time I drove on my own,
I made a U-turn...
got dizzy, threw up and walked home.
You really wanna drive?
It seems like the perfect time.
The roads are straight.
There's no one around.
And you don't seem to care
if you live or die.
Live, Sheldon. I wanna live.
That makes things a little trickier,
but I'll do my best.
[DIAL TONE ON LAPTOP]
Hi, Penn— Oh, hello, Leonard.
Hello, Mother. How are you?
- Fine, and you?
- I'm great.
- Well, it's been lovely catching up.
- No.
Wait, hang on. We need to talk.
Oh, brother.
I wanna know why aren't you proud of me.
Well, isn't the real question
why aren't you proud of yourself?
No, that is a question.
And I ask it a lot.
But let's stick with the one I asked you.
Well, why do you think
I'm not proud of you?
Because you never say it.
But two days into chatting with Penny,
and you can't stop telling her how great she is.
She is great.
Honestly, of all of my children's spouses,
she's the one that I'm most impressed by.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
She's confident. She's thoughtful.
And she never complained about you once.
I know what kind of strength that takes.
So Penny's your favorite.
I suppose she is.
You married well, Leonard.
And for that, I am proud of you.
I don't know what to say.
I'm also proud of how hard
you're trying not to cry.
Thank you.
- Would you like to hang up now?
- Yeah, here it comes.
Your hands are at 10 and 2. Good.
Steady on the gas.
Okay.
Now, you're gonna
wanna slowly switch lanes.
- Why?
- Because there are only two...
and you're not in either of them.
Attaboy. Well done.
Thank you.
The last time I drove,
I was terrified, but this is fun.
You're doing great.
You're a good teacher.
Your son is going to be lucky
to have you as a father.
Thanks.
Do you think I could try going a little faster?
- Go for it, champ.
- Ow.
Sorry. Just ease on the gas and—
Too much. Too much.
Why was I scared of this?
This is exhilarating.
No, it's not. Slow down.
Don't tell me what to do.
You're not my father.
- You know how fast you were going?
- A hundred and twelve.
Let me see your license.
- Okay, here's the plan.
- No.
Fine.
There you go.
You know what, you can just keep it.