Uh, one dumpling left, who wants it?
Maybe you should offer it
to the pregnant lady.
And that would be...?
Me, Sheldon, I'm obviously pregnant.
You never said it to my face,
and the last time I assumed...
a woman was pregnant,
it did not go over well.
Yeah, I'm still mad at you. Ahem.
You were drinking water instead of wine,
what was I supposed to think?
Sheldon's right,
I would never ask a woman...
if she's pregnant unless she tells me
or I see a human being wiggling out of her.
Well, Sheldon, I'm pregnant.
Congratulations. How far along are you?
- About three months.
- Only three?
Good gravy, how many babies are in there?
Okay, let's talk about something that
won't infuriate my pregnant wife.
- I read an interesting fact about elephants—
- Try again.
I've got something.
I'm being interviewed
on public radio this Friday.
- Cool, how come?
- The university's trying to get funding...
for the physics department.
They want me to talk it up.
Really, you?
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
Well, they picked
the right person for the job.
- Thank you.
- I think he bought it.
Hi, I'm Ira Flatow,
and this is Science Friday.
Joining me today is my guest,
physicist Dr. Leonard Hofstadter...
to talk about all the exciting research
they're doing at Caltech.
Thank you for having me. Whoa. Heh.
I never get used to hearing myself
in headphones.
- Is that really how I sound?
- Heh-heh.
It is. It is.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
That is good to know.
I told him his voice was annoying,
he didn't wanna listen.
- Hey.
- You're saying it's not?
Just— Hey.
So it's been five years
since the discovery of the Higgs boson.
What's the next big thing gonna be?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Wow, that's hard
to say, there's so much going on.
We've been collecting tons of data
that could revolutionize...
the way we understand the universe.
For instance,
there's a particle called a squark...
which could prove supersymmetry.
- That is interesting. Have you found it?
- The squark?
- Yes.
- No, no.
Wouldn't that be exciting? Heh.
But we're also looking for the selectron,
the gluino, the neutralino.
- Oh, and have you found—?
- No.
Fun side note,
I went to high school with a girl...
named Theresa Gluino.
But it didn't cost 2 billion dollars
to find her.
She was smoking behind the gym. Heh.
So, what have you found?
Uh, nothing, actually.
Should he be saying that?
Oh, probably not.
Yeah, this is public radio.
Doesn't he realize
dozens of people might hear him?
But I remain confident.
We've got the best equipment...
and the best minds all working on it.
Okay, sounds like he's back on track.
Although, some days I'm like,
"Ugh, we've spent so much money.
Why haven't we found anything?
What are we doing?"
Oh, boy.
There's Leonard.
I bet he's having a rough day. Heh.
- Let's just try to be supportive.
- Supportive?
He publicly maligned
the love of my life, Lady Physics.
You might not wanna mention that
to Lady Fiancée.
- Hey, guys.
RAJESH: Hey. How's it going?
Pff.
What? You got something to say?
I think I just said it.
P-F-F.
Pff.
Look, I was just speaking the truth.
We're scientists,
isn't that what we're supposed to do?
What would you know about the truth?
You thought Phantom Menace was
"Not half bad."
I told you that in confidence.
Okay, calm down, everybody just cool it.
No, let them go. If we get lucky,
maybe one of them will start crying.
Can we just drop this
and have lunch like adults?
- Very well.
- Sure.
- Leonard.
- What?
Pff.
You ready for lunch?
Oh. One second.
Ooh, someone's got a lot
of fancy new lab equipment.
I know, the university's been
throwing money at my study.
With any luck, there'll be a brain disease
with my name on it.
Fingers crossed.
Which is ironic because
if you had Fowler's Palsy...
you wouldn't be able to cross your fingers.
I'm surprised Sheldon's not up here
playing with all your new toys.
Actually, I haven't told him about it.
We've been getting...
so much more funding,
he's been a little sensitive.
So you're just gonna hide
your success from him?
I know. Am I terrible?
No, I do that too.
Howie thought my company retreat
was in Boise.
It was in Tahiti.
That's such a relief.
Part of me was worried
I was being unfair to Sheldon.
Take that part of yourself and hide it away.
Just like last year's bonus check
that I "didn't get."
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Ms. Davis, you wanted to see me?
- Yes, Dr. Hofstadter, come on in.
Should I sit or stand? I'm not used
to being called into the dean's office.
Please sit.
- I have to say, I'm a little nervous.
- You should be.
Look, I know I screwed up,
but it was only one interview.
How much damage could it have caused?
Would you like me to read you
the emails from donors...
asking why they're giving us money
if physics is a dead end?
I didn't say it was a dead end.
I just said that I was worried it might be.
So if I just said I was worried
you might not have a job next week...
how would you feel?
Light-headed
and glad you asked me to sit down.
Okay, just tell me what I can do.
I'm gonna need you to make a statement
saying that you misspoke...
and you're confident
the physics community is close...
to a major breakthrough.
You want me to lie?
Look, Dr. Hofstadter, I'm counting on you.
I think you're the smartest physicist
at this university.
- Really?
- See, lies, they're not that hard.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hi.
- Hello.
Huh. Looks like you've been busy.
Oh, I have.
Uh, dark matter, reconciling gravity
and quantum mechanics, supersymmetry.
I figured out the biggest problems
in physics today.
Wow, you solved them all?
No, I just— I figured out
that they're the biggest problems.
Is this about
what Leonard said on the radio?
Absolutely not.
And I do not want to talk about Leonard.
Can we talk about anything else?
We could talk about my day.
Walked right into that one, didn't I?
Well, since you sort of asked,
I actually had a very good day.
I got some new equipment for my lab.
Well, congratulations.
I got some new equipment too.
I got these markers.
They smell like fruit...
which I did not notice when I bought them.
Don't really care for it.
Here, drink this.
It might help.
- What if it doesn't?
- That's why I brought the bottle.
No one would talk to me in the halls,
they just glared at me.
It's like high school all over again.
Ugh. I would totally do
high school all over again.
- But that doesn't help you.
- No.
I got called into the administration office.
Ooh, look at my bad boy
getting called to the principal.
We don't have a principal,
there's a standing committee...
that oversees the budget.
Ooh, look at my bad boy
answering questions nobody asked.
Look, you said
a few dumb things on the radio.
What's the worst that could happen?
I may get fired.
Well, even if you did,
you could get another job.
Yeah, who wouldn't wanna hire
the physicist who publicly said...
physics is dead.
Well, I wouldn't put that under special skills.
I can fix it. I just need to write
a retraction I don't believe in.
Basically sell out to keep my job.
Great, I'll leave you to it.
Hmm...
Hmm.
Oy.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
LEONARD:
Sheldon, it's me.
- What?
- I know you're mad.
I have to write a statement that says
physics is close to a breakthrough.
Since you actually believe that,
I could really use your help.
- Sorry, I can't.
- Come on, don't be like that.
I can't because I think you were right.
- What?
- Look...
not all science pans out.
We've been hoping supersymmetry
was true for decades...
and finally we built
the Large Hadron Collider...
which is supposed to prove it
by finding these new particles and it hasn't.
And maybe supersymmetry,
our last big idea, is simply wrong.
Well, that sounds awful.
Now I get why everyone hates me.
On the bright side,
after working together for 15 years...
you finally get to hear me say
you were right.
Yeah, you did.
How's it feel?
Given I might be unemployed, bittersweet.
- Read it back to me.
- Hang on.
"Yes, one might question
the 20 billion dollars to build and run...
the Large Hadron Collider,
but on the other hand..."
Okay. Um...
Oh, "On the other hand,
contrary to predictions...
the Collider didn't create
a small black hole...
that devoured the earth
and life as we know it. So...
money well spent."
This is depressing.
Do you have any alcohol around here?
Not surprisingly,
when Penny moved out...
she took every drop. Um...
Oh, but I do have several bottles...
of Romulan ale that I bought at Comic-Con.
Isn't that just vodka with blue dye in it?
First physics, now Romulan ale.
What else would you like to defecate on?
I thought you were coming right back.
I was, but we're both depressed
and decided to drown our sorrows.
In mouthwash?
Man, that is so summer camp.
It's Romulan ale. From Star Trek.
It was briefly legalized during the alliance
between the Romulan Empire...
and the Federation
at the time of the Dominion War.
Aww, now I'm depressed.
The more I told him
about my lab, the pissier he got.
Know what he said to me? He said:
"I hope all your correlations
turn out to be specious."
He said that to your face?
What a dick.
You know, you're a successful woman,
you should be able to brag...
about your accomplishments.
So should you. I mean,
the guys are never shy about bragging.
Tell me about it. Howie texts me
every time his dog levels up in Warcraft.
Has he ever called to tell you
he found three peanuts in one shell?
Because Sheldon has.
We should be able to do that too.
I guess we can brag to each other.
That's a great idea.
Damn right it is, I came up with it.
[CHUCKLES]
That felt good. Heh-heh.
There's so much money in pharmaceuticals,
we don't even wash out our test tubes.
We just throw them out and get new ones.
I just got a brand-new,
state-of-the-art fMRI machine.
Wow, those things are so expensive.
I know. Sometimes I just lie down in there
and take a nap.
It's like a million-dollar bunk bed.
At the office, I have two assistants.
I don't even know their names,
I just call them Thing One and Thing Two.
That's great. I don't have assistants.
Oh. I guess that's one of the benefits
of being in the private sector.
That and all the money I make.
Yeah, you've got that.
I've got my integrity.
Hard to say which is better
without making you feel bad.
Okay, so you guys are upset
because the collider thing...
disproved your theories?
It's worse than that.
It hasn't found anything in years.
We don't know if we're right,
if we're wrong.
We don't know where to go next.
All I know is it looks like
I tongue-kissed Avatar.
Come on, you guys are physicists.
Okay, you're always gonna be physicists.
And sure, sometimes the physics is hard...
but isn't that what makes it boring?
- Hey.
- We're here.
What's going on?
Okay, as far as I can see,
science is dead because Leonard killed it.
And I don't know who the Romulans are,
but those guys know how to party. Heh.
- What do you want us to do?
- You're scientists.
- Cheer them up.
- Cheer them up?
Do you even know what a scientist is?
We don't need to be cheered up.
It just turns out that physics
is exactly like Lost. Started out great...
and turns out just a big old waste of time.
Boo-hoo. You know what you sound like?
Babies.
Two whiny babies.
And there's nothing worse
than being stuck with two whiny babies.
Oh.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna have two babies.
No, no, no, babies are great.
You're lucky to have two babies.
I mean, look at me, I'm all alone.
I'm never gonna have babies.
Because you can't make a baby
watching Netflix with your dog.
Thanks for coming.
I may not make as much money,
but at least I know...
that I'm doing something
that makes people's lives better.
Hey, my work makes people's lives better.
Especially if you have moderate
to severe eczema...
and don't mind a few loose teeth.
You're right, we both do important work.
I map the structures of the brain
and you're trying to convince people...
that itchy hair is a real thing.
It is a real thing.
It happens to be a side effect
of our cholesterol drug.
I'm just saying that my research
may actually change the world forever.
I hope it does,
because I'm gonna see that world...
from a yacht so big
you can land a helicopter on it.
Physics is all we're cut out for.
I mean, If we weren't physicists,
what would we be?
I don't know, popular? Heh.
It's fine, I don't need to be
a theoretical physicist.
There's lots of things
I could use this brain for.
I could be an accountant for the mob.
I could guess people's weight at the fair.
Okay, this is getting silly.
Is it?
One-eighty.
Okay, that is enough.
Your lives are not wasted,
your careers are not at a dead end.
You hit a rough patch.
Instead of feeling sorry for yourselves,
you need to get inspired.
- How?
- I don't know.
When I'm feeling down, I go for a run.
Which is exactly why
I'm not 180 pounds, genius.
- I know where we need to go.
- Are we running there?
Because watching drunk Sheldon run
would be the highlight of my life.
We're going to see Richard Feynman.
Penny, Richard Feynman
is an iconic physicist—
I know who he is, Leonard dressed as him
for Halloween last year.
I had no idea Richard Feynman was dead.
Yeah. Most people don't know
he's actually buried right here in Altadena.
I'm sure they keep a lid on that
to avoid traffic jams.
Oh. Heh-heh. Here he is.
Oh, wow, he's buried with his wife.
We get it, a lady loved you, quit bragging.
Feynman was so cool.
When I was a kid
I'd put on some headphones...
crank up one of his lectures and just...
jam out to knowledge.
This guy knew how to live.
Taught himself musical instruments...
he studied Portuguese
just to give a speech in Brazil.
The only part of me
that's been to Brazil is my bikini line.
Okay.
He did so much.
And here we are,
stuck and letting him down.
You know, Feynman used to say
he didn't do physics for the glory...
or the awards, but just for the fun of it.
He's right.
Physics is only dead
when we stop being excited about it.
Even beyond the grave,
he's imparting wisdom.
Um, I'm the one who remembered it.
Give me the bottle. It might be corny...
but I say we pour one out
for all the science homies...
- ... who came before us.
- I love that.
LEONARD:
Do it.
Here comes some more.
[SHELDON VOMITS]
Eh, we got to see him run.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hi, you wanted to see me?
Yes, I wanted to talk about
the e-mail you sent me last night.
I sent you an e-mail?
You bet you did.
"Hello, shalom and aloha
from the grave of Richard Feynman."
Oh, it's coming back to me.
"Please accept the following retraction:
I know I said physics is dead...
but it is the opposite of dead.
If anything, it is undead, like a zombie.
Speaking of which,
if Richard Feynman came back as a zombie...
I would totally let him bite me."
Any chance that's the end?
"I got bit by a squirrel once.
I had to get rabies shots.
I cried so much.
My mother said, 'Don't be a baby.'
In conclusion, physics is great,
squirrels suck, and someday...
I'm gonna put my mom
in a cheap nursing home.
Yours truly, XOXO
Dr. Leonard Hofstadter."
I can explain.
"P.S.
Can you come pick us up?
The Uber driver won't open the door
because Sheldon is covered in blue vomit."