So, uh, have you found
a band yet for your wedding?
No.
'Cause I'm in a band.
We really rock.
Yeah.
I mean, it's inevitable.
I definitely overhear
some wedding preparation,
but I'm fine with it.
She hears me arranging
my social life,
and we both have to hear
Dwight order deer urine
over the Internet,
so it evens out.
So I got the Save The Date.
Yeah?
Yeah, pretty stationery.
Oh, thanks.
I didn't get mine yet.
Um...
There are a few people
I decided not to invite,
and that might make things
kind of awkward, but...
it's my wedding.
And I don't want anyone there
who has called me a hussy.
Yes, thanks.
Fantastic Sam's.
Adult cut plus.
Comes with a shampoo
and blow-dry.
We're doing I.D. photos today.
Gotta represent.
Uh, on or off?
Off.
Okay.
Oh! What is on your face?
Is that a disguise?
Excuse me.
Clown paint.
I.D. badges are long overdue.
Security in this office park
is a joke.
Last year I came to work with
my spud gun in a duffel bag.
I sat at my desk all day with
a rifle that shoots potatoes
at 60 pounds per square inch.
Can you imagine
if I was deranged?
That's a nice tie.
Thank you.
That is...
Who makes that?
Um, I don't know.
Do you mind if I wear that
for the photo?
Uh, let's, um...
Let's keep our clothes.
It's like child abuse!
I say if Jesus saw that,
he'd freak out!
He'd freak out, Toby,
I mean, on so many levels.
And I'm supposed to work there!
I'm supposed...
What's the dealio?
Just letting Oscar
vent a little.
We would use the break room,
but the photographer's
back there.
What's the problem?
Angela.
There's just a little dispute
over a poster
in their workspace.
Since Christmas.
So what, you're having
a little spat?
I forget.
Are you guys dating?
No.
Michael, can I talk to you
for a second, please? Yes.
Here's how
I usually handle this.
All I do is listen.
These things just have a way
of working themselves out.
It's like if you
write someone a letter
when you're really angry.
They say to keep it in
your drawer for a couple days,
and then you just never
end up sending it.
What do you know about
conflict resolution?
Your answer to everything
is to get divorced, so...
Okay.
Okay, what?
That was a right decision
for me and my marriage.
Well, that's not gonna fly here
because in this office,
it is till death do us part,
assuming that we don't
get downsized.
Uh, Pam, would you get Angela
and meet us in
the conference room, please?
A Mediator's Toolchest.
Okay, well,
before we get started,
you should know that there are
five different styles
of conflict.
My Shaolin Temple style
defeats your Monkey style.
Can we go?
I have a lot of work to do.
No. This is important.
Okay, the first style is
"lose-lose."
What's the next one?
Just hold on, please.
Okay, if we do lose-lose,
neither of you
gets what you want.
Do you understand?
You would both lose.
Now, I need to ask you,
do you want to pursue
a lose-lose negotiation?
Can we just skip
to whatever number five is?
Win-win or whatever?
Win-win is number four,
and number five is
win-win-win.
The important difference here is
with win-win-win,
we all win.
Me too. I win for having
successfully mediated
a conflict at work.
Okay, so this is
the disputed poster.
Now, one at a time,
I want you
to express your feelings
using "I" emotion language
and no judging,
or "you" statements.
I got this poster for Christmas,
and I feel I want
to see it every day.
It makes me feel like the
babies are the true artists,
and God has a really cute
sense of humor.
Come on, seriously.
That?
I don't like looking at it.
It's creepy and in bad taste,
and it's just offensive to me.
It makes me think of the
horrible, frigid stage mothers
who forced the babies into it.
It's kitsch.
It's the opposite of art.
It destroys art.
It destroys souls.
This is so much more offensive
to me than hard-core porno.
Okay, okay, okay!
Oh, my God.
Stop, stop, stop!
Let's see if we can't
just brainstorm
and find some creative
alternatives that are win-win.
Win. Yes. Thank you, Pam.
How about Angela makes
the poster into a t-shirt,
which Oscar wears.
That way he can never see it,
and whenever she looks at Oscar,
she can see it.
Win-win-win.
No. That's... No.
Okay, well, brainstorm.
Own the solution.
How about I leave it up?
How about she takes it down?
How about Angela can keep it up
on Tuesdays and Thursdays. Okay.
That is called a compromise,
and it is style three,
and it is not ideal.
To sum up,
win-win, make the poster
into a t-shirt.
Win-lose,
take the poster down.
Compromise,
Tuesdays and Thursdays.
And the answer is...
make the poster
into a t-shirt.
Win-win.
Win.
Fine.
But...
It is done!
No, you're all good.
Great.
Hey, Angela.
I didn't have your zip code.
Oh, thanks.
It was hand-delivered,
but I did get
a Save The Date after all.
It's not my taste.
You solved it.
Yes.
Well, good.
We can throw that one out.
Are those all the other complaints?
Mm-hmm.
I would like to see those,
please.
I... I can't do that.
You can't do that, huh?
Okay.
Now you and I have a conflict.
I order you
to give me that file.
That...
Okay.
There!
No more conflict.
I had to use win-lose on that.
It was not pretty.
All right.
Is that it?
It's all Dwight's.
Every Friday at 4:00,
I have a standing appointment
with Dwight
for him to file a grievance
against Jim.
I tell him that I'm sending them
to a special file in New York.
That box is the...
Special file in New York.
Oh, God.
All right.
Why do I have to do everything?
Are you sure?
Oh, he's sure.
Just shoot.
This is from Kevin.
He says Stanley uses his
Miracle Whip without asking.
Meredith complains that
everyone talks too loud
in the morning,
and the lights are too bright.
Creed...
Creed is sick of looking
at the redhead all day
and wants a seat facing
the receptionist.
Nice.
You will notice that not one of
these complaints is against me.
Actually,
I have a separate folder
for complaints against Michael.
This is January through March
of this year.
How many of you have at one time
gone to Toby to complain
about another employee?
And did you get what you wanted,
or were you merely listened to,
you forget about your problem,
and you move on?
That is outrageous!
I love this place,
and it pains me to see
all of the negativity
festering...
Okay.
Today we are going to get
everything out of these files
and into the open,
where it can be resolved.
All right, how about
the Phyllis-Angela dispute?
You already did me.
That's what she said.
The thing is, Angela,
you are in here an awful lot.
You have complained
about everybody in the office,
except Dwight, which is odd
because everyone else has
had run-ins with Dwight.
Toby, by the way,
what does "redacted" mean?
There is a file full
of complaints in here
marked "redacted."
Yeah, it just means
whoever complained
came to me later
and withdrew it,
so I took their name off.
Okay.
There were a bunch of complaints
about Dwight
that were put in the redacted
file about six months ago.
Wait!
If someone has
a problem with me,
why would they withdraw it
six months ago?
Um...
Let's move on.
I volunteer.
Did anyone have a problem
with me?
All right, Pamela.
Come on down!
Let's do it.
And... okay.
Just one complaint.
Actually, it has been withdrawn.
So that is no help to us.
Next.
Wait, what did it say?
Uh, "Does she have to plan
her wedding on office time?
Shouldn't she do that
at home?"
Who else?
Why don't we just warm up first?
Warm up emotionally, all right?
I have this kind of big secret
about Angela.
And I've been
really nice to her,
and I haven't told anyone,
and...
What the hell?
Here is a Kelly complaint.
"Ryan never returns
my calls."
Ah.
Join the club.
My voice mail's
real spotty... sometimes.
I didn't file a complaint.
I was just talking.
To your HR representative.
To my friend, I thought.
I want that withdrawn.
Fine, I'll take your name off.
So no one will know.
Making progress.
Yes.
Dwight tried to kiss me.
What?
And I didn't tell anyone
'cause I'm not really sure
how I feel about it.
That is not true.
Redact it. Redact it!
Well, I'm not actually making
a formal complaint.
I just really think
we should talk about it.
Okay, question.
When a name is withdrawn,
does that also apply
to the permanent
misbehavior file in New York?
Sure.
Stanley.
Hey.
A lot of anger under there...
Thanks for ratting me out.
I didn't do it.
I find that hard to believe,
considering you have problems
with every single person
in this entire office
except Bobblehead Joe.
Someone complained
that the men's room
is "whites only."
Stanley, you know
that's not true.
I didn't say that.
Then why is there a picture
of a white man on the door?
Okay, Phyllis.
You complained that Angela
is giving you dirty looks.
And you tried to get off
the party planning committee.
No, I never said any such thing.
Angela and I are close.
And... also, Phyllis,
Stanley says that you
cry too much,
and that bugs him.
Stanley and I are close, too.
- We sit close.
- Okaaay.
Just take it.
I can't believe Angela.
I went against
my better judgment,
and I gave her a Save The Date.
And now it turns out
she complained about me to Toby.
Well, it was redacted.
Look, if she wants an invite,
maybe she's just trying
to be friends.
Don't take her side.
Well, what does Roy think
about everything?
I try not to bother him
about this kind of stuff.
You mean like your thoughts
and feelings?
Yeah.
I know you keep saying
it's your space,
even though
there's no assigned parking,
but I keep forgetting.
Yes, that's the problem.
I guess so.
Okay, well.
All settled, then.
I don't like you.
Okay, Ryan, you told Toby
that Creed has a distinct
old man smell?
I know exactly
what he's talking about.
I sprout mung beans
on a damp paper towel
in my desk drawer.
Very nutritious.
But they smell like death.
All right, Kevin.
You are accused of making
sexually suggestive
remarks to Angela
that made her feel
uncomfortable.
Solution.
Angela, you are to make
sexually suggestive
remarks to Kevin
that will make him
uncomfortable.
I accept your decision.
Hey, you know what, Dwight? Maybe we
should get our photo I.D. taken together.
That doesn't make any sense.
Well, it saves time, you know.
'Cause we could just meet
in the parking lot
every morning.
Walk in together.
Perfect.
Smile.
No.
I never smile if I can help it.
Showing one's teeth
is a submission signal
in primates.
When someone smiles at me,
all I see
is a chimpanzee
begging for its life.
This came out really well.
There you go.
This is humongous.
I am not a security threat.
Oh.
And my middle name is Kurt.
Not Fart.
What did I write?
I have another complaint
for Jim's permanent file.
Talk to Michael.
I gave him the box.
What box?
But I didn't report your
snoring... Wednesdays, tearful.
Tuesdays...
Okay.
Ah... agh... dgh... dah! Dwight.
No, no!
Four years of malfeasance
unreported.
This cannot stand.
Okay. Calm down.
No, you calm down.
Whose side is Toby on?
Whose side are you on?
Hey, hey!
Him or me?
I cannot work with Jim anymore.
Okay.
Either he goes, or I go.
Dwight, stop...
You choose!
One of us is out of here
by the end of today.
Okay.
I am not bluffing!
Okay, yes.
Okay?
Do the right thing here,
Michael.
I have served you loyally
for years.
I deserve this, you know I do!
You know your I.D. says
you're a security threat?
You have till 5:00.
Oh, look, Jim.
There's a sales manager
position open in Stamford.
Want me to call Jan
and tell her you're interested?
I could put in
a good word for you.
'Cause I'll still
be working here.
Trans-fer,
trans-fer... Everybody.
Trans-fer, trans-fer
trans-fer!
Okay, you two,
in the conference room, with me.
Nobody leaves until
we work this out.
Cage match.
Cage matches?
Yeah, they work.
How could they not work?
If they didn't work,
everybody would still
be in the cage.
Okay, so, Dwight,
in your own words.
"Someone replaced all my pens
and pencils with crayons.
I suspect Jim Halpert."
"Everyone has
called me Dwayne all day.
I think Jim Halpert
paid them to."
Yes, five bucks each.
And it was totally worth it.
"This morning I found a bloody
glove in my desk drawer,
"and Jim Halpert
tried to convince me
"I committed murder.
I think he may be
the real murderer."
"Jim Halpert said there was
an abandoned infant
"in the women's room.
"When I went to save the child,
I saw Meredith on the can."
Gad.
"This morning I knocked myself
in the head with the phone."
That actually took a while.
I had to put more and more
nickels into his handset,
till he got used to the weight,
and then I just...
took 'em all out.
"Every time I typed my name
it said Diapers."
Just a simple macro.
You know, these actually
don't sound that funny
one after another.
But he does deserve it, though.
"By the end of the day,
my desk was about two feet
closer to the copier."
Yeah, I just moved it an inch
every time he went
to the bathroom.
And that's how I spent
my entire day that day.
The Japanese have this thing
called shiatsu massage,
where they dig into your body,
very hard.
And it is very painful.
And apparently,
some people throw up.
But the next day
they feel great.
I've never had one.
They sound awful.
Maybe Stamford would be cool.
It's a good market.
Higher volume.
Yeah.
Maybe we should both go.
I have a girlfriend.
Sure, you do, Dwight. Sure.
Hey, there's, like,
300 more of these.
Let's get to them later.
So, you gonna
transfer Jim or not?
Maybe. I haven't decided yet.
Let's get to work.
I want an answer by tomorrow.
Okay... ooh, actually,
tomorrow's not good.
How about later in the week?
Fine.
Good. Okay.
Hey! Wait.
How about a group picture
while you're here?
I can't. I only get reimbursed
for the I.D. photos.
Well, that's, what,
a computer camera, right?
You mean, digital?
Yeah, it'll take, like,
two seconds.
20 bucks.
All right.
Everybody, come on.
Group photo for the newsletter.
You've gotta be kidding.
Come on, everybody.
Come on, let's go.
Creed, Kevin, Oscar,
andale, let's go.
One, two, three.
Smile.
Try to smile.
We resolved a lot today,
everybody.
Think happy thoughts.
Okay, I'm just gonna
take it on three,
whether you smile or not.
One, two, three.
Good. Let's check that out.
Ew, okay, all right.
One more.
We'll take one more.
That'll be another 20.
What?
Angela, I want to talk to
you about something. What?
No, Pam...
I am.
It's about the Save The Date...
Pam, it wasn't her.
What?
I'm the one
who complained about you.
I didn't know that Toby
was gonna write it down.
I was just venting.
You know, it was one day.
And I took it right back.
It was like...
Okay.
Oh, dear.
Okay... we can do this.
Come on, everybody.
All right.
Here we go.
It was really hard getting
a good picture of 15 people.
He would not give me a discount.
And eight tries added up.
One, two...
Didn't say three, did I?
But I'm sort of an expert
at Photoshop.
So it turned out fine
in the end.
When people work together,
there is going to be conflict.
You can't outrun your problems.
Hey, Pam, it's Jim.
Um, I have a doctor's
appointment in the city.
So I probably won't be in
till the late afternoon.
Just thought I'd let ya know.
Okay, bye.
Okay, Jan will see you now.
Oh, thanks.
And that is why the idea
of a cage match
is so universally appealing.
But here's the thing
about cage matches.
Sometimes you have
to open the cage.
And that is something that Toby
will never understand.