Happy Halloween, everyone.
Oh, that's great.
Hey.
Happy Halloween.
Jan called.
O... kay.
I know why she's calling.
It's the end of the month,
and I was supposed
to let somebody go
by the end of the month.
And somehow I'm supposed
to put on a costume and smile.
Okay.
Jan Levinson's office.
Hey, Sherri,
Michael Scott returning.
Oh, she's in a meeting.
She just wanted the name
of the employee you let go.
Well, I'm gonna wait 'til
the end of the day.
Because the book said it's best
to wait 'til the end of the day.
I just need the name of who
you're planning to let go.
I.. don't... know... yet.
I will have to call her back.
I know she wanted the name.
Okay, Sherri?
Yeah?
If you were getting fired,
how would you wanna be told
so that you could
still be friends
with the person firing you?
Jan wants the name as soon
as possible, Michael.
Thanks.
Mmm-hmm.
I'll call her back.
Wish I could fire Sherri.
Hey, I'm still here.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
No?
Okay.
Bye.
Hanging up now.
I mean, you hear
about layoffs in the news,
but when you actually have
to do it yourself,
it is heavy stuff.
It's...
I mean, these are people's lives
you're talking about.
You wanted me?
Yes.
Papier-mâché?
Yesh.
Hmm.
Um, Pam I have
to let somebody go today.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
Why did you put it off
until Halloween?
Because it's very scary stuff.
Well, I think it's gonna put
a damper on the party a little.
You're worried about the party?
There's a man's
life at stake here.
So it's a man?
No.
Or a woman.
A human life.
If you had to guess,
who would it be,
based on their job performance?
And who do you think
deserves to be fired?
Who would that be?
I just answer the phone.
And sometimes you just let
it go to voice mail.
Your costume is fantastic.
I know.
I sent away for it
in July from a catalog.
Oh, no.
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
Aah.
Okay.
Oh, man.
Okay, I have to fire somebody.
What is that?
What are you supposed to be?
I'm a three-hole punch
version of Jim.
'Cause he can have me
either way.
Plain white Jim,
or three-hole punch.
- That's great.
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, well, look.
What about me?
What are you?
A monk?
I am a Sith Lord.
Oh, big deal.
Three round pieces of paper
taped to his shirt.
This cost me $129.
Ass.
Hey, you guys excited
about the party?
It's gonna be fun.
Yeah.
Oh, look at you.
Showing your colors.
Bet you wish you wore
a dress every day.
What are you implying?
All good.
Happy Halloween.
What happened to all those
spooky decorations that we had?
The cobwebs and such?
I don't know.
We put them all up last night.
Well, you know what?
Go buy some more.
I'll approve the overages.
Sound good?
Yeah.
Good.
Oh, yeah, also,
about budget stuff,
um, I need you to find,
like a...
a full employee salary
plus benefits, like 50 grand.
I'm gonna need you to find
50 grand in the numbers.
But we don't keep two cents...
Well, that's not
what I'm saying.
Just, you know, find it.
Pretend that your
jobs depend on it.
Mmm-hm-hmm.
Interesting take on Dorothy.
I love it.
Hey, you know what would
even be better?
Soccer ball and cleats.
Why is that?
Bend It Like Beckham.
Oh, like, the movie
about the Indian girl
who plays soccer?
Yeah.
That would be perfect.
Yeah, I mean, I guess
I could do that.
I don't really play soccer
or anything.
Well, I don't really
have two heads, so.
Wait, what are you again?
Oh, right.
Three-hole punch!
Okay, greatest strength.
Okay, okay.
A doglike obedience
to authority.
Nice.
That doesn't sound good.
Okay, okay.
Um, how 'bout
the ultimate team player?
Dwight is special,
but I don't believe that his
talents are being used
in this office.
So Pam and I have put his résumé
on monster.com, Google,
craigslist.
We're really interested
most in jobs
that take Dwight out of state.
Um, preferably Alaska.
Or India.
He's a gun nut.
Mmm.
Sticks to his guns.
Well, I looked through
all the budgets.
And there is one department...
Yes?
That has three people...
Yeah?
Doing the work that could
be done by two.
This is great.
Oh.
Yeah. Oh.
Who do you think it should be?
Jim, definitely.
No, Jim brings in money.
Phyllis.
Eh.
Stanley. Pam.
Oscar. Meredith.
Kevin. Angela.
It's not a popularity contest.
Although it does make sense
to fire the least popular,
because it has the least
effect on morale.
One of the warehouse guys.
What?
There was someone
left off that list?
Who?
Who is he saying?
You're right.
I didn't even think of him.
No, Michael.
Yeah, that's actually
a really good idea.
No, not me.
Yeah, I could.
Not Dwight.
I'm not saying
that's what he said.
I know that's what he said.
What?
Tell him not Dwight.
That is not a very nice
thing to say about him.
Tell him to stop.
Are you kidding?
Quiet you.
I agree.
He'd land on his feet.
Make him be quiet.
Those aren't chips and dip.
No, I made brownies.
What?
I'm just trying to figure out
why you're sabotaging things.
I made brownies.
And I made cookies.
Same category.
I'm guessing Angela's the one
in the neighborhood
who gives the trick-or-treaters
some toothbrushes.
Pennies.
Walnuts.
Dunder-Mifflin,
this is Pam.
Uh, yeah.
Just one second.
I will transfer you
to our manager, Michael Scott.
Michael Scott here.
Yes, I am regional manager
of this orifice.
Mmm-hmm.
Dwight Schrute is amazing.
Yeah.
No, he is actually the single
greatest employee
of his generation.
Mmm-hmm.
You know what?
I'm gonna tell you what.
You hire Dwight K. Schrute,
and he does not meet, nay,
exceed every one
of your wildest expectations,
well, then you can hold me,
Michael Gary Scott,
personally and financially
responsible.
Okay. Okay.
Okay-kay-kay-kay.
Okay.
Stanley, could you come
with me, please.
No.
As assistant regional manager...
To the...
Look.
I've got some bad news.
You're fired.
You need to pack up
your things and go.
I'm serious, Stanley.
It's over, I'm sorry.
You're fired.
Get your fingers off my phone.
So, how did it go with Stanley?
How... how'd he take it?
He wouldn't listen to me.
Oh, come on.
If you wanna fire him, you're
gonna have to tell him yourself.
I don't wanna fire Stanley.
I never said that.
I'm certainly not going
to do it myself.
Get those big, baleful
eyes staring at me.
Yikes.
Okay, just...
Cumberland Mills?
And how did you get my résumé?
Oh, no, no.
I'm very flattered.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just not sure
that it's my official résumé,
or if it's something that maybe
a satisfied customer
posted online.
What does it say under
martial arts training?
Oh, okay, I'm gonna have
to supplement that.
Could I have your fax number?
Would I ever leave this company?
Look, I'm all about loyalty.
In fact, I feel like
part of what I'm getting
paid for here is my loyalty.
But if there were somewhere else
that valued that loyalty
more highly,
I'm going wherever
they value loyalty the most.
Oh, hey.
Oh, your dress is stuck
in the back.
Oh.
So you got the fax?
So why didn't you add it
to the res...
What do you mean?
Of course martial arts training
is relevant.
Oh, excuse me.
I know about a billion Asians
that would beg to differ.
Uh, yeah, I get
a little frustrated
when I'm dealing
with incompetence.
Well, you know what?
You can go to hell too.
And I will see you there...
burning.
Fine. Okay, wait.
So you'll let me know
when you've made a decis...
Jim is really talented.
And he should be the one who's
getting a better job offer.
Like, for real.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you should go for that job.
Um, it's in Maryland.
Yeah.
But, I mean, look at the salary.
And it's definitely a step up.
And a challenge.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know what?
Maybe...
Maybe I will.
Jim...
This is called leveraging
an offer.
Michael, can I talk to you
for a moment? Oh, God.
I just thought you should know
that I was just offered
a job with better pay,
better benefits and a better
title at Cumberland Mills.
Fantastic.
And I turned it down.
What? That would've
solved all my problems.
Out of loyalty
to this company...
Oh, you idiot.
So I was hoping to be made
assistant regional manager.
If you left,
I wouldn't have to fire anybody.
But then you wouldn't
have me here.
Big deal, oh, it would've
worked out so well.
Can you get it back?
It's in Maryland.
You can call.
Can you call 'em?
I can't... I... I suppose I... no.
They never really made me
an offer anyway.
Why are you torturing me?
God.
Honestly, I don't think that
Michael has the slightest clue
of who he's going to fire.
I think he keeps hoping that
someone's going to volunteer.
Uh, or be run over
by a bus before the deadline.
But in the end,
really what's going to happen is
it's gonna be the first
person to give him
a dirty look in the hall.
And therein lies the true
essence of his charisma.
Can I speak to you a minute?
Um... yes.
Michael, I really
didn't mean to...
Help me.
I'm sorry?
I want you to role
play firing me.
I want you to fire me,
and I will take it.
Oh, you want me to be you? Yes.
I want you to be me,
and I will be Creed.
Oh, are you firing Creed?
No, no.
No, that's just first... thing.
Can't... in head.
We should switch seats
in order to...
Yes, that's a good idea.
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry,
but I have to let you go.
And it's purely budgetary.
It's not personal...
I'm gonna kill myself!
Wow.
I'm going to kill myself!
And it's your fault!
That's an overreaction.
Corporate is really
breathing down my neck.
And they're saying
this has to be done
by the end of the month.
Is this you? Are you being you,
or is this Creed?
I... this is Creed.
Okay. I'm improvising,
so just try to keep up.
And I'm very angry.
Hold that thought.
Creed?
Michael Scott here. I'm gonna
kill you for firing me.
Toby? Mmm-hmm?
I really have to take this,
Creed, so it was really worth...
Get off, get off.
No, no.
Just, just... yeah.
What happened?
It wasn't me.
Oh.
That was, like, crazy.
I know.
'Cause I was...
Uh, hey, Creed?
Huh?
Could I talk to you
for a second?
You are great.
Very ambitious.
And I feel like you want more
than this little office
has to offer.
And I understand that you'd
wanna just spread your wings
and fly the coop.
We're gonna have to...
You... you want something better.
No, I don't.
I wanna stay right here.
No, you wanna leave.
No, I wanna stay here.
Why are you making this so hard?
I think there's
a misunderstanding, Michael.
I think you're right.
Can I go?
No, of course, you can't go.
We haven't even started
this horrible process of...
Okay, Creed,
I need to let somebody go today.
They told me I need
to let somebody go.
And as much as I think
you're a great guy,
and I like you,
you're... you're, good-bye.
Let's fight it.
Hmm?
Let's call Jan,
and fight this thing together
like the old days.
What old days?
What are you talking about?
Did you start the paperwork yet?
It's right here
on the desk, yeah.
You don't have to do this,
Michael.
I can't...
Undo it!
I can't change anything.
No, you have the power
to undo it.
You undo it.
Michael, undo it.
Yeah, I went hunting once.
Shot the deer in the leg.
Had to kill it with a shovel.
Took about an hour.
Why do you ask?
I have to fire someone today.
Okay?
Fine.
Fire someone else.
Fire Devon, he's terrible.
I am so much better
at my job than Devon.
Okay, well,
I already picked you.
And you know that.
So, unless I just
go through with this,
you're always gonna look at me
as the guy who almost fired you.
No, no, no, no, no.
I will forget so fast.
You will be my savior.
You're the guy who
gave me my life back.
Thank you.
I knew you'd see my way,
Michael, God bless you.
You're a fine man.
Don't...
Listen, you will not regret
this either.
Devon's terrible.
No one's gonna miss him.
Good, good, good.
Devon, could I talk
to you for a sec?
Creed's an idiot. You know that.
Well, he...
No, no, no, no, no.
You had it right the first time.
Well, maybe I did.
Exactly.
You gotta go with you gut, man.
Huh. Well...
No, I can't...
No.
I can't go back.
I would look like an idiot.
That's why I'm being fired?
No.
So you might not look
like an idiot? No.
It was all
the stuff that I said.
It was the business downturn,
the cutbacks, and, and...
This is unbelievable!
I just hope that you
and I can remain friends.
Devon, wait... please.
Look, look.
In addition to severance,
and everything,
I want to give you
this gift certificate
to Chili's.
From me.
Okay? No hard feelings.
Kevin, Jim, Pam, Kelly,
Toby, Oscar, Meredith,
Phyllis, Stanley, or the temp.
If any of you wanna meet me
for a drink,
I'm gonna be at Poor Richard's.
And the rest of you
can go to hell.
What about the Halloween party?
Oh, hey, Jim.
Wait, stop.
Um, I'm sorry
for pushing you
toward Cumberland.
Seriously, if you left here,
I would blow my brains out.
Come on.
That's just a figure
of speech, you know?
Blow your brains out?
Come on.
All it really means
is that we're friends.
I mean, who else
is she gonna talk to
if I'm gone, right?
I mean, if she left I wouldn't
blow my brains out.
Of course, I would take
that job in Maryland.
Because it's double the pay,
and soft shell crab just happens
to be my favorite food.
I love Halloween.
You, know it's just...
it's just fun.
Every year, it's just fun.
Last Halloween,
I came as Janet Jackson's boob.
It was topical.
People got a big kick out of it.
The year before that,
I came as Monica Lewinsky.
And I wore a stained dress.
The year before that,
I also came as Monica Lewinsky.
And before that,
I was O.J.
It was pretty funny.
Oh, I wish you were here
last year.
Trick or treat!
Hey!
How you doin'? Wow!
You guys look great.
I'm a bumblebee.
You look great.
And you're a princess?
A fairy princess.
You're very...
I'm a lion.
You're a lion.
Wow, I want to hear your...
Oh, okay, that's all yours.
That's all yours.
Grab it, grab it.
You know what?
You guys are getting
all of these.