Kevin Malone, you're next.
Spit that out.
Spit... okay, come on.
Let's go.
You look cute today, Dwight.
Thanks, girl.
So, yesterday, Dwight found
half a joint
in the parking lot.
Which is unfortunate,
because, as it turns out,
Dwight finding drugs
is more dangerous
than most people using drugs.
Let's go over
some of the symptoms
of marijuana use, shall we?
You tell me
who this sounds like.
Slow moving.
Inattentive.
Dull.
Constantly snacking.
Shows a lack of motivation.
Hey.
I like the people
I work with generally.
With four exceptions.
But someone committed a crime.
And I did not become
a Lackawanna County
Volunteer Sheriff's Deputy
to make friends.
And by the way, I haven't.
I enjoy the tangy zip
of Miracle Whip.
Jim does the best impressions.
Sometimes he'll look up at me
from his desk
and he'll just be someone else.
Like, he'll go, um...
That was supposed to be Phyllis.
I can't do it as good as he can.
And the guys are saying,
"Chug chug chug."
But I'm so small
and all I'd eaten that day
was one of those
Auntie M pretzels
from the food court.
So I said, "Is it okay
if I sip it?"
And they said no.
But Ryan seemed cool either way.
Stop!
This is not Kelly Kapur
story hour.
Illegal drugs were consumed
on company property, okay?
Your ass is on the line, Mister!
My ass is on the line.
Now, I'm gonna ask you again.
What time did you
go home last night?
6:00.
I didn't know that you were
at a party Saturday night.
I go to a lot of parties.
Okay, I'm gonna need
to search your car.
Give me your keys.
I am not giving you my keys.
Don't make me
do this the hard way.
What's the hard way?
I go down to the police station
on my lunch break.
I tell a police officer...
I know several.
What I suspect
you may have in your car.
He requests a hearing
from a judge
and obtains a search warrant.
Once he has said warrant,
he will drive over here
and make you give him
the keys to your car.
And you will have to obey him.
Yeah, let's do it that way.
Ryan, is he bugging you?
Dwight, dude,
you gotta take
a chill pill, man.
It was one joint
in the parking lot, you know?
You're totally harshing
the office mellow.
I can't stop this investigation.
It is my job.
Whoa, you are a volunteer.
I volunteered for this job.
And that's not the same.
It is my duty...
Volunteer duty,
to investigate the crime scene.
I have six more
interviews to go.
And then I will reveal
what I know.
Narc!
If you are attempting
to compliment me,
you have done a very good job.
I wasn't attempting
to compliment you.
Well, you have.
Because being a narc is one of
the hardest jobs
that you can have.
Okay.
And I am very proud
of being a narc.
Why don't you just cool it?
Cool it, Dwight, please?
God.
Dude, where's my office?
I totally lost it!
'Cause I was half-baked!
Smoking doobies!
Doobie Brothers.
I was smoking doobies
with my brothers.
Peace out!
Seacrest.
Well, your office is behind you.
Thanks.
Mmmunchies.
Who wants some munchies?
I don't think Michael's
ever done drugs.
I don't know if anyone's
ever offered him any.
Oscar visited Mexico
when he was five
to attend his
great grandmother's funeral.
What does that mean
to a United States
law enforcement officer?
He's a potential drug mule.
Have you ever taken any
illegal drugs?
No, I have not.
Do you think it's possible
that maybe
you could have had
some drugs in your system
without you knowing about it?
What are you implying?
Have you ever...
pooped a balloon?
Okay, I'm done with this.
He sure left in a hurry.
I don't wanna blow this.
This is what all
good law enforcement officers
dream of.
The chance to solve
an actual crime.
Do you know what this is?
Yes, it's marijuana.
How do you know that?
It's labeled.
Dammit.
That is Northern Lights
Cannabis Indica.
No.
It's marijuana.
I'm just saying
that you can't be sure
that it wasn't you.
That's ridiculous.
Of course it wasn't me.
Marijuana is a memory loss drug.
So maybe you just
don't remember.
I would remember.
Well, how could you
of it just erased your memory?
That's not how it works.
Now, how do you know
how it works?
Knock it off, okay?
I am interviewing you.
No, you said that
I'd be conducting the interview
when I walked in here.
Now, exactly how much pot
did you smoke?
So, Pam told me you do
a great Stanley impression.
I'd love to hear it.
Oh, um...
Why do you keep CC'ing me
on things
that have nothing to do with me?
Why do you...
Oh.
Is that supposed to be me?
Oh, hey, Stanley.
I was just doing an impression.
I do not think that is funny.
He does everyone in the office.
Hmm.
I do not think that is funny.
Jinx.
Buy me a coke.
No no no!
No talking.
Jim is not allowed to talk
until after he buys me a coke.
Those are the rules of jinx.
And they are
unflinchingly rigid.
Sold out!
That has never happened
in the history of jinx!
Sorry, that's not my problem.
I know you're innocent.
But I can't look like
I'm treating you
any differently.
I understand.
Where were you yesterday
after work?
Uh-oh.
Who's he calling?
Rattin' somebody out.
Narc.
Narc!
Kevin.
That is so good, Michael.
Remember the narc bit?
I will let them know.
Uh-oh.
Who's in trouble?
Attention, everyone!
Drug testers are coming
in a couple hours
to test everyone's urine.
Wha...
What?
What are you talking about?
Company policy.
If drugs are found
on the premises,
there is automatic drug testing
conducted within 24 hours.
Is that true, Toby?
Uh, when you sign
your job application
you agree to comply
with random drug testing.
Two nights ago I went
to an Alicia Keys concert
at Montage Mountain
Performing Arts Center.
I scored these
great aisle seats.
Anyway, after the opening act,
this beautiful girl
sits down next to me.
And I never get to meet girls
with lip rings.
And she had one.
I don't know exactly
how this happened,
but one of her friends
started passing around
some stuff.
And they said that it
was clove cigarettes.
And I'm sure that
it was clove cigarettes.
Everybody in the aisle
was doing it.
Okay, attention, everyone.
The drug testing
has been cancelled.
Instead, I will be going around
to each of you and doing
a visual inspection.
No, you can't do that.
I can do that.
It is my office.
No, you cannot.
It has to be official.
And it has to be urine.
Uh... all right.
Kevin, what prescription drugs
are you taking
besides Rogaine?
I'm not taking Rogaine.
Angela, what about you?
I don't take
any prescription drugs.
You're not... on anything?
Good.
So, the first time
we went out to dinner,
it was like, whatever, fine.
But I was so nervous.
So this time,
I want it to be special.
So I bought a new dress!
One of those kinds
that's kind of low cut
at the top to show some things
but not everything.
I mean, not everything, Jim.
I promise.
Hey, you guys.
What's going on?
Oh, we're just having
the best conversation.
Oh, okay... well,
Michael wants to see everyone
in the conference room.
But you know what?
We have a few minutes.
So you guys should definitely
finish up your conversation.
Cool, thanks.
So I was looking so hot...
It has come to my attention
that some people here
think the use of drugs
is something to laugh about.
We don't feel that way.
No, not at all.
You were the one joking around
calling Dwight a narc.
No.
Uh, no.
That was a test.
I was testing you.
And you all failed.
Miserably.
When I said
that Dwight was a narc,
how many of you defended him?
How many of you said,
"Hey, you know what?
"He's right.
"What he's doing
is protecting this office
from the evils of drugs"?
Thank you, Michael.
I am ridiculously
anti-drug.
I am so anti-drug that I am
above suspicion
in any way
that involved suspicion...
or testing of any kind.
Drugs ruin lives, people.
Drugs destroy careers.
Take Cheech and Chong.
Everybody knows that
Cheech and Chong are funny.
But just imagine
how funny they would be
if they didn't smoke pot.
I want everybody
to take a look to their left.
Now I want everybody
to take a look to their right.
One of those people will be dead
from drug use at some point
in their lives.
This year, more people
will use cocaine
than will read a book
to their children.
Where did you get these facts?
Are these facts scaring you?
Or are they not?
They are not.
Do you think
that smoking drugs is cool?
that doing alcohol is cool?
No, I don't.
I have a glass of red wine
with dinner
about once a week
for the antioxidants.
Okay, enough.
Enough.
Enough!
I have written down a list
of illegal drugs.
Take a gander.
How many of these
are you familiar with?
Hookah is not
an illegal drug, Michael.
Yes, it is.
No, it's not.
It's a type of pipe.
You can fill it with tobacco,
often mixed with fruit, or...
Okay, you know what, Toby?
Pam, could you take this down?
In addition to Toby's urine
being tested,
I would like to test
his blood and his hair.
You can't do that.
I can test anyone randomly.
And I have chosen you randomly.
That's not random.
Okay, enie, meanie, miney, moe.
Is random.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna need a volunteer
to select one of these words.
And tell us of something...
tragic that happened
in either their lives
or the lives of a loved one.
Yeah, Pam.
I know that Jim
has an amazing story
about a relative of his
who got caught up
in the world of drugs.
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Jim, it's okay.
You can...
This would be a good place
to let it out, Jim.
These are people you can trust.
These are people
who care about you.
It's okay.
Just... we will
not judge you.
We are here to not judge you.
Oh, he's doing it.
Okay.
It's okay.
Oh.
Okay, are you sure?
That looked like
it was gonna be good.
All right.
Okay, well...
Wow!
He really pulled out
the big guns.
Fake crying.
Did not expect that.
The point I'm trying to make
with all of this, people,
is that I hate drugs.
I hate them.
And based upon what I have seen,
you all don't quite hate 'em
as much as I do.
So you are going
to have a drug test.
And I am not.
No, you will be tested.
Yes, I... no,
will not be.
No, you will be.
That is the law
according to the rules.
Okay.
Well, Dwight, just know...
that I've been very busy today.
And I've got a lot
of work to do.
And I wasn't planning
on going to the bathroom.
And I don't even know
if anything's
gonna come out, okay?
So, good.
Thank you.
Hi, Linda.
Dwight Schrute.
Assistant Regional Manager.
You might remember
testing my urine
a few years back
when I was applying
to be a Volunteer
Sheriff's Deputy.
We test a lot of urine.
Mine was green.
Oh, right.
How are you?
I'm all better.
So I need you to do some work
on the St. Andrew's account.
I need your urine.
I need some filing done.
What kind of filing?
That... just forget it.
Just the urine.
That goes directly
to the tester.
Just...
I need your urine.
Like, in a cup?
Yes, in a cup.
We're not animals, Dwight.
For what purpose?
It's none of your business.
Then I refuse.
Okay, all right.
Just...
I went to
an Alicia Keys concert.
Over the weekend.
And I think I may have
gotten high accidentally
by a girl with a lip ring.
Are you serious?
I need clean urine for the lady.
But that's illegal.
Don't think of it that way.
It's like...
Urine goes all over the place,
you know?
There's no controlling it.
It just...
Not my urine.
A cup could find its way
under the urine.
It might be an accident.
Were you forced to do drugs
at this concert?
Is something wrong?
Look, just...
Just fill up the cup.
Do you want to
give Michael your urine?
I want him to have
all the urine he needs.
You're not gonna get
my permission on this.
I know that.
Don't you think I know that?
Yeah, we do testing
all over the country.
Cool.
Hey, are you guys hiring?
You wanna work
at the urinalysis lab?
Yeah, maybe.
My father's name
was Dwight Schrute.
My grandfather's name
His father's name?
Dwiged Schrued.
Amish.
I loved my father very much.
Every morning
he'd wake up at dawn
and make us biscuits with gravy.
When I was little, my dad and I
played a lot of games together.
My dad cheated a lot,
but I never busted him on it.
I would have, except I didn't
know about it.
He didn't tell me
'til years later.
I was shocked when I found out.
What?
Did you wanna tell me something?
You look like
you wanna tell me something.
You look like you have something
really important to say
and you just can't
for some reason.
Come on, you can tell me.
Jim, you can tell me anything.
I'd like a magazine.
We just need urine, sir.
I'd still like one.
Dwight.
Well...
I passed the test, thanks to you
and your untainted pee.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
What's wrong?
Where's your costume?
It's a uniform.
And I turned it in today
when I tendered my resignation.
Why? What...
I took an oath
when I was sworn in.
And I broke that oath today.
Here.
Just buy it from me.
I haven't talked
to you in hours,
and it's been weird.
And I really wanna know
what the hell's going on
with Dwight.
Hi.
Hey.
How much time do you have left
on your break?
10 minutes.
Since you did such a good job
with the investigation,
I decided to pull a few strings,
call in a few favors.
And I've decided to make you
Official Security Supervisor
of the branch.
Really?
Yes, sir.
That's fantastic.
'Cause I've always felt
that the security here sucked.
So you wanna...
"Dwight K. Schrute,
"I hereby declare you
an honorary volunteer corporal
in charge of assisting
all activity security."
Good, okay?
Here's your badge.
Thank you, Michael.
Very nice.
Great.
Can I have a gun?
No.
I don't have a gun.
Okay.
I'll have to bring in
my bow staff.
I don't think so.
Don't.
Good.
Thank you, Michael.
No... oh...
I need to go over
some details with you.
First of all...
All right, well...
Thank you.
How many orange traffic cones
do you have?
Two.
Oh... God.
Wow, what a terrible day
to not be able to talk.
Dwight was literally carrying
around his own urine
and dressed like
one of the Village People.
Why does he do the things
that he does for Michael?
I just don't get it.
What is he getting
out of that relationship?