Should you really be
sitting in Sheldon's spot?
He's in Texas.
He'll never know.
I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Yeah, he has
a very sensitive butt.
Well, it's true.
Once I saw him sit on a bunch
of loose change and add it up.
Have you heard from Howard?
I did.
His talk at NASA went great.
Sheldon didn't heckle him?
No, in fact, he was
so well-behaved,
Howie bought him
a Buzz Aldrin bobble head
and astronaut ice cream.
Hey, guys.
Oh, hi. - Hi, Stuart.
Hey, Stuart!
How's it going?
Good.
Sheldon's out of town,
so we can do whatever we want.
We even ordered from
the Thai place he doesn't like.
Oh, how is it?
Disgusting. Do not tell him.
What do you guys want
to do tonight?
I don't know.
Well, I told Howie
if I wasn't busy,
I'd spend the night
at his mom's.
So for God's sake,
think of something.
Stuart?
Are you okay?
No, I don't feel so...
Oh, Stuart?
Stuart?
Oh, my God,
you guys need to do something!
Stuart?
Calling 911.
Well, it's too late.
What do you mean it's too late?
He's been murdered
by someone in this room.
Oh, my God.
Oh, come on!
Welcome to another classic
Koothrappali
murder mystery dinner.
I'm leaving.
You can't leave.
You're a suspect in
the mysterious murder
of Stuart Bloom.
I didn't know his
last name was Bloom.
Yeah, it's Bloom.
Are you really gonna
lie on the floor
and pretend
to be dead all night?
What do you think
I was gonna do at home?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x18 ♪
The Mommy Observation
Original Air Date on March 13, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Are you gonna make us pretend
to be a bunch of lame characters
with silly accents?
"Lame characters
with silly ac..."
What kind of actress are you?
You're right, I'm sorry.
It... sounds like fun.
Thank you.
That kind of actress.
This sucks!
Come on, guys.
Raj put a lot of
effort into this.
And that's great.
It's not sad, it's great.
I think it might be fun
to be someone else tonight.
Actually, you're all just
gonna be yourselves.
Oh... ugh.
All right,
if I'm doing this,
I'm playing to win,
so just to be clear:
If we're ourselves, that means
one of us killed Stuart?
Very good, Bernadette.
You are a regular
Byomkesh Bakshi.
What is that, like,
the Indian Sherlock Holmes?
Or is Sherlock Holmes
the English Byomkesh Bakshi?
According to Wikipedia,
Sherlock Holmes came first.
Great, everyone's
a Byomkesh Bakshi.
Now... here are
some secret facts
about each of you,
including whether
you are the murderer.
Throughout the game, feel free
to ask each other questions
to uncover clues.
Got it. Hey...
who's the murderer?
Any question but that.
Sorry. Hey...
who's not the murderer?
Bernadette, can you not stand
so close to me?
What do you care? You're dead.
Suit yourself.
But I can kind of...
see up your skirt.
Thank you
for my bobble head.
Thank you for not making fun
of me during my speech.
It wasn't easy. Was it Buzz?
We can't show up to
your mom's empty-handed.
We should bring something.
I already am.
I'm bringing
the gift of knowledge.
Oh, boy.
Despite what her Bible says,
recent archeological
studies indicate
that although camels are
referenced in the Old Testament,
they didn't exist
in the Middle East
until hundreds of years later.
I was gonna say we pick up
a cake or a pie.
But an insult to her faith
is always thoughtful.
So, what happens next?
I can't tell you that.
But perhaps the killer dropped
a fun and imaginative clue
somewhere in the apartment.
Ooh, I'm gonna check the fridge,
and see if there are
any clues inside a beer.
Hey, I-I found something.
It looks like a little man
with a briefcase.
Oh, no, no.
That's Clarence Darrow.
It's from a game Sheldon made up
called Chutes and Lawyers.
You slide down a chute
and then work your way back up
through the appellate system.
Well, unlike that,
my games are much more fun.
Okay, can I ask you something?
Why do you like making us
do this stuff?
Well, I guess
it goes back to
when I was a fat kid in India,
and didn't have any friends.
I didn't know you were fat.
Yeah, I was...
I was 200 pounds by the time
I was in middle school.
Kids were mean.
Cows may be sacred there,
but it doesn't help
if you look like one.
Anyway, I was pretty lonely,
so I had to make up
my own stories and games,
and I promised myself
if I ever made
any friends that...
that I would play
those games with them.
That is so sweet.
I've seen old pictures of you.
You were never a fat kid.
No, I was svelte as a gazelle.
A gazelle blessed with a flair
for storytelling.
Hey, what about this?
It looks like a receipt.
What's it for?
For a cup of coffee.
But it's dated
20 years from now.
From the future?!
How fun and imaginative.
So one of us came back
from the future
to murder Stuart?
Correct.
Does the gazelle with a flair
for storytelling
know he's just ripping off
Terminator?
Does the smart-ass know
that Terminator was actually
ripped off from an Outer Limits
script called
Demon With a Glass Hand,
by Harlan Ellison?
Oh, does the gazelle know that
according to Harlan Ellison,
it was not ripped off
from Demon With a Glass Hand,
but was ripped off from another
Outer Limits script
he wrote called The Soldier?
I'm gonna need
another clue.
Okay...
give me
the flowers and pie.
But if we show up
and you're holding them,
she'll think
they're only from you.
They are only from me.
You said the gift
of you was enough.
Yes... but now
that I've seen
what the gift of me
with flowers and pie looks like,
there's no going back.
Boy, I can't wait to see
the look on her face...
We're leaving right now.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What? Sheldon, tell me
what's going on!
I saw my mommy with a naked man
and she was trying
to be a mommy again.
You ready to talk about it?
I'm not nearly drunk enough.
Okay.
Do you have any idea
what it's like to see
your mother ravaging someone?
Does a brisket count?
I'm sorry, buddy, that's rough.
But didn't she know
we were coming?
No.
I wanted to surprise her.
What am I supposed to say to
her after something like this?
Well, did she see you
in the window?
No.
Then don't say anything.
I have to.
How can we ever hope to have
a healthy relationship
if I don't tell her
how disappointed I am,
and that I'll never forgive her?
Well, don't do it on the phone.
No, I'm just going
to tell her I'm coming
so she can give that Good
Time Charlie the heave-ho.
That's some tough talk.
I may need to cut you off.
Yeah, maybe you better.
I took a pretty big sip.
Look, she's a grown woman.
And-and your dad's been
gone a long time.
Maybe this is
none of your business.
I beg to differ.
I used to live in
those genitals.
And if someone wants
to move into my old room,
I should at least get a vote.
Okay, murder suspects,
Leonard has found the time
machine the killer must've used.
You're all inside it,
and we hurtle
through the very fabric of time.
And welcome
to 20 years in the future.
Hey, you guys
just time-traveled.
Stop looking so bored.
Well, my beer isn't flat
and my rack's not saggy.
So far, the future's great.
Hey, can I go to the bathroom?
Fine, just try not
to look too alive.
That's my jam.
So one of us went back
in time to kill Stuart?
But why?
Perhaps this will help.
Here are some facts
about yourselves in the future
that might contain a clue.
Hey, I-I won
the Nobel Prize in physiology.
Then I used the money to buy
Stuart's comic book store,
and close it down so Sheldon
would pay attention to me.
Not the worst idea.
Hey, I'm a famous actress
living in London.
Hmm! I'm a professor at Stanford.
Hmm!
So I guess you two are
making it work long distance.
Oh, no.
In this game,
as your careers both took off,
you drifted apart.
Kind of like how future me
lost touch with you guys
after I became boy toy
for the wrinkled,
but still flexible, Madonna.
What does
your card say, Bernadette?
Eh, eh, eh, hang on.
Do-do you think
we'd really drift apart
if we both became successful?
Of course not.
If I became a famous actress
and had to move,
you would just come with me.
But if I get a chance
to be a tenured professor,
I might not have that much
choice in where I end up.
Yeah, but if I become
a successful actress,
we wouldn't need the money.
Well, you don't go
into science for the money.
Speak for yourself.
Last month,
my company both invented
and cured
Restless Eye Syndrome.
Ka-ching,
ya blinky chumps.
So, wait, if my career
took me somewhere else,
you might not go?
Well...
He started it.
Okay, okay, guys--
new back stories.
Uh, Penny and Leonard,
you two lovebirds are
super successful
and living in New York.
Uh, you're an actress,
you're a professor
and you have
three beautiful kids.
Great.
Really? You think I'm putting
this body through three kids?
Okay, let's do this.
Good luck.
You...
Aren't you gonna come with me?
While you confront your mother
about her sex life?
I'd rather go back to that bar
in ass-less chaps.
Mother?
Mother.
Shelly!
I'm so glad you're here!
I saw you having naked sex.
What are you talking about?
Earlier, I came here
to surprise you.
I looked in the window
and I saw you with a man.
Oh, Shelly, I'm so sorry.
Come in.
Um...
Maybe we should sit down
and talk about this.
Can you recommend a surface
you haven't had coitus on?
That's not funny.
Maybe we should sit
at the table.
Well, I'm sure that, uh,
you...
have a lot of questions.
Who was he?
His name is Ron.
I met him at my prayer group.
How long have you been
involved with him?
A few months.
And of those few months,
how long have you been
a demented sex pervert?
That is no way
to speak to your mother.
Perhaps not.
But it is a way to speak
to a woman who quoted the Bible
to me my whole life,
and then desecrates
one of Ethan Allen's
finest sofas.
I will give you one opportunity,
young man, to apologize.
Or what?
Or I will send you to your room.
That's ridiculous.
I am a grown man.
I am a professional scientist.
And I currently occupy
the moral high ground.
Go to your room.
But I occupy
the moral high ground.
Go to your room.
But I'm
a professional scientist.
Go... to your room!
I'm a grown man.
Can we please get back
to the game?
I-I-In a minute.
I-I-I don't understand
why any success
you have in acting
is more important
than any I have in science.
Okay, if you do
something cool in science,
you might change the world.
If I become
a famous actress...
I'm not gonna tell you
why movie stars are the best.
They just are.
I'm surprised you guys never
talked about this stuff.
Like you and Sheldon have
everything figured out?
Actually,
our relationship agreement
covers a wide array
of scenarios,
including career changes,
financial instability,
intelligent dog uprising...
FYI, we plan on selling out
the human race hard.
In 20 years, who knows
what'll happen with any of us?
I think you and Leonard
will be together.
You do?
Yeah.
I think you're
the best couple I know.
Aw.
That's so sweet.
What the hell?!
Excuse me?
Ah-da-da-da-da!
Let the dead man talk.
So, why do you think that?
Uh, well, I feel like
you guys make each
other better.
Penny brought Leonard
out of his shell.
And it seems like Leonard
makes Penny think more
deeply about the world.
I don't know.
Together, you two kind of
make one awesome person.
Aw, Stuart.
Now I feel bad
for murdering you.
Oh, come on!
Penny did it! I win!
Suck it, jackasses!
Hey, can I come in?
Apparently any man
is welcome in this house.
Why not you?
I thought you were waiting
in the car.
That was an hour ago, Sheldon.
A Jew sits in front of a house
in Texas that long,
"For Sale" signs
start to go up.
I take it things didn't
go smoothly with your mom.
No.
I'm not sure how we're going
to get past this.
You know, I...
I sort of went
through something
like this myself.
Howard, we've all seen
your mother naked.
That woman needs to learn
how to tie a robe.
I'm talking about when
my mom started seeing someone
a couple years
after my dad left.
I didn't know she did.
Yeah, she was dating this guy,
and I was kind of a jerk
to her about it.
What did you do?
Well, let's just say
it was the most vicious
bar mitzvah speech in
the history of Temple Beth El.
Anyway, she broke up with him.
And she's basically
been alone ever since.
She never said it,
but I always felt
I was the reason why.
I'm sorry.
Although,
based on your story,
you absolutely
were the reason why.
All I'm saying is
you might not want
to get in the way
of your mom's happiness.
You may have a point.
I love my mother.
Even if she fornicates
like a demonic weasel.
And the healing begins.
Hello.
Are you ready to discuss
this calmly, like adults?
I am.
Shelly, I'm sorry that
you saw what you saw.
I know that this
is hard for you.
I think what most upsets me
about it, Mother,
is the hypocrisy.
Doesn't this contradict
all the religious rules you've
been espousing your whole life?
You're right, it does,
and it's something
that I'm struggling
with these days.
Then why are you doing it?
Because I'm not
perfect, Shelly.
And that man's booty is.
Well, this is confusing for me.
But I don't want to stand
in the way of your happiness.
So...
I'll condemn you internally
while maintaining
an outward appearance
of acceptance.
That is very Christian of you.
Mother, if you're going
to conduct your life
in this fashion,
then I should let you know
that the world has changed
since you were a young woman.
You know,
it's not all shock hops,
soda jerks
and segregation anymore.
How old do you think I am?
My point is that you're going
to need to be careful.
You used to be protected
by your pre-Enlightenment
mythology,
but now you're going
to need a stronger friend
named latex.
Are you having the
sex talk with me?
Well, someone has to.
Oh, dear Lord!
Yeah, well...
No, don't look to Him.
He's mad at you right now.
Oh, come on, don't pout.
I'm sorry I ruined your game.
I'm not pouting, I'm brooding.
Which is how sexy men pout.
It actually was kind of fun.
You're just saying that.
Yeah.
I liked the time travel element.
Thank you.
I thought it was inspired.
It was. By Terminator.
Well, I hope 20 years from now,
we really are all still together
and still friends.
Definitely.
Of course.
Well, hey, how about this?
Whether we're friends,
not friends,
scattered around the world,
no matter what,
let's all promise to meet
in front of this building
exactly 20 years
from tonight at 8:00 p.m.
and have dinner
like we always do.
Aw! I love it.
Okay?
Putting it
in my phone right now.
Yeah, me, too.
My phone doesn't
have a calendar.
It's all right, I'll just
write it on my hand.
And it's done.
Yup, we're all in.
All right, I'll see you guys
in 20 years.
I knew it.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man