Almost there.
You're doing great.
Thanks for lifting my spirits.
Next time, try lifting the box.
Please hurry.
I don't need
a treadmill!
The doctor says
you need to get exercise!
I get plenty
of exercise!
Crushing my will to live
isn't exercise!
If she isn't gonna use it,
then why are we doing this?
She'll use it.
All I need is to rig it
with a fishing pole
and a HoneyBaked Ham.
All right.
Now what?
We set it up
in Howie's old room.
Do you know how to set it up?
Please,
I'm an MIT-trained engineer.
I think I can handle...
Ma, look out!
I told you this
thing would kill me!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x23 ♪
The Gorilla Dissolution
Original Air Date on May 8, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
So she's gonna be laid up
for at least six weeks.
Poor Mrs. Wolowitz.
Should we do something
for her?
I know. Let's go see
the new Spider-Man movie.
Sheldon, we're talking
about your friend's mother.
She got hurt.
I thought that subject
had run its course,
so I changed it.
It's called reading
the room, Amy.
Hi.
Hey, how were things on the set?
Uh, pretty good, actually.
So the movie's not
as bad as you thought?
Oh, no, it is,
but I decided,
instead of complaining about it,
I'm just gonna go in every day
and give it my all.
Good for you.
Thanks.
There's no reason why
I shouldn't be
the best bisexual go-go dancer
slowly transforming
into a killer gorilla
anyone's ever seen.
I don't know.
The bisexual gorilla
go-go dancer in Schindler's List
is tough to beat.
Ah, very good.
Because a gorilla go-go dancer
of any sexual preference
would be out of place in a film
about the Holocaust.
It only gets funnier
when you explain it, Sheldon.
I know.
Okay, she's all settled
in the guest room.
Maybe we should get
one of those machines
to help her up the stairs.
You mean a forklift?
Howie...
I'm sorry.
I just can't deal
with this right now.
Taking care of your own mother?
How can you say that?
Bernie, she's gonna be off
her feet for six to eight weeks.
Are you prepared
to feed her, wash her
and take her to the toilet?
I would do it for my mother.
Yeah, of course
you would--
you're a loving person.
I'm what my people
would call a putz.
Look, I'm not crazy
about the idea,
but what other
choice do we have?
We get a nurse.
Preferably someone
from a Third World country
who's used to suffering
and unpleasant smells.
You'd hire a
total stranger
to take care of the
woman who raised you?
That's so cruel.
Not if we pay them well
and let them listen
to the music of their homeland.
I need to tinkle!
Sounds like a job
for a loving person.
Would you like me
to play some Polish music
while you carry her
to the toilet?
You are a putz.
As advertised.
Thanks for coming
with me.
Thanks for inviting me
after everyone else said no.
Aren't you gonna get
3-D glasses?
I brought my own.
No sense in risking
bridge-of-nose herpes.
Is that a real thing?
Well, until they invent
nose condoms,
I'm not finding out.
Emily! Hey!
Oh, hey, Raj.
Uh, this is my friend, Sheldon.
Sheldon, this is Emily.
Oh, yes, you're
the dermatologist.
I went for a walk yesterday
without sunscreen.
Do you see anything
on my forehead
that I should be
concerned about?
Um, you know what?
I better go.
My movie's about
to start.
Are you here alone?
No, not really.
What do you mean,
"not really"?
Hey, should we get
our seats?
Yeah.
It was nice seeing you.
Um, I'll call you later.
Yeah, okay.
That was awkward, right?
Uh-huh.
Is it because
she's dating you
but was out with
that other fellow?
Yes.
Good. I thought she saw
something on my forehead.
And... action.
Please don't shut me out.
Go away.
Just go away.
I swear, I will find a way
to turn you back.
What gave you
the right
to mix my DNA with that
of a killer gorilla?
I was trying
to save your life.
Life? What life?
Look at me! I'm a monster!
And now I have blood on my
hands, or paws. I don't know.
You can't give up.
I love you.
I love you, too.
But I'm afraid
I love killing more.
Like, one day, I might
actually try and kill you!
And... cut.
All right.
All right, let's set up
for the next scene.
Actually, you know what?
Can we do one more?
I think I could do it better.
Let's just move on.
No one cares.
Well,  I care.
I mean, look,
if we're gonna do this,
why not try and make it
something
we're actually proud of?
Look, sweetie,
this movie is garbage,
but you should be happy
about that,
'cause if it was a good movie,
you wouldn't be in it.
Whoa, whoa, hang on.
There's no need
to insult her.
And who are you?
I'm her boyfriend.
Isn't she too hot for you?
A little, yeah.
Well, boyfriend, get off my set.
You can't do that.
He's with me.
You know what? You can get off
my set, too. You're fired.
What? You can't fire me.
I'm the star.
I'm the girl that goes bananas.
It says so on the poster.
Yeah, but we just shot the last
scene where we see your face.
So from now own, the star of
the movie is whoever wears this.
Hey, if you're
gonna fire her,
then you have to
fire me, too.
Wow, that fell apart
really fast.
Thanks for skipping
the movie.
I couldn't sit in that theater
for two hours
wondering about Emily
and that guy.
Oh, quite all right.
After my forehead
melanoma scare,
I've learned not to sweat
the small stuff.
Well, sorry,
I don't have all the ingredients
to make chai tea.
You don't have
to make me anything.
No, I do.
You're upset about Emily
and you're Indian.
I need to make you
chai tea.
Now, I have all the ingredients
except cardamom seeds.
Do you happen
to have any on you?
Sorry, I left them in my turban.
Oh, I'll make
English breakfast tea.
They destroyed
your culture.
That's close enough.
You know, I'm curious,
why are you so upset about
seeing Emily with another man?
Wouldn't you be upset if you saw
Amy out with someone else?
Can't happen.
We have an ironclad
relationship agreement
which precludes her
from physical contact
with anyone other than me.
But you don't have sex
with her, either.
Slick, huh?
To be truthful, Emily and I
haven't dated that long,
and we never agreed to be
exclusive to each other.
Have you had intercourse?
No.
Well, stick to your guns.
There will be a lot of pressure.
I'm hungry again!
It's like the world's
fattest cuckoo clock.
You know, you're
always talking about
having a baby someday.
This is exactly what
it's gonna be like.
No, it's not.
Come on. The constant
fussing, eating, pooping,
burping, drooling.
We're even waiting
for the day
when she can finally
walk on her own.
Maybe you're right.
Anything she finds on the floor
goes right in her mouth.
I'm just telling you now,
if we do have kids,
don't expect me
to do all the work.
Hey, I'm a very paternal person.
I'd be excellent
at taking care of a baby.
I'm still hungry!
I'm coming, you big baby!
You know, the only thing worse
than doing a movie
where they glue monkey hair
to your ass
is getting fired from a movie
where they glue monkey hair
to your ass.
Forget it, man,
it's crap.
You just move on
to the next thing.
Yeah, well, it's easy
for you to say.
You used to be famous.
Hey. I just lost
a job for you.
You're right, I'm sorry,
you're famous.
Penny, it's not
about being famous.
It's about the art.
It's about the passion
we have for our craft.
I have an audition
for Sharknado 2!
If I book this,
I am totally gonna
pay you back
for this beer.
God, what am I
doing with my life?
You having second thoughts
about acting?
You were on set, you
saw what it was like.
Yeah, but it's not
always that bad.
Oh, really?
What about when you did, uh,
Anne Frank at that
cute little theater?
It was over a bowling alley.
Yeah, but...
there was ample parking.
Are you done?
And you were so good
in the TV commercial.
It was for hemorrhoid cream.
And I got itchy and swollen
just watching you.
Leonard, you are really
not cheering me up.
Come on.
How can you be sad
when you're going home
with all five-foot-six of this?
Hmm. You think you're
five-foot-six, that's funny.
I don't understand it.
I'm a nice guy,
I have a great job,
I'm well-educated,
come from a good family...
Why don't women
want to be with me?
An interesting
question.
Well...
good night.
What?
Don't send me home.
I can't be alone
right now.
That's your problem.
You can't be alone.
What do you mean?
How many women have
you had dates with?
Eleven.
How many of
those women
did you think would become
your perfect companion?
Eleven.
Wait.
Do I count the 200-pound
Sailor Moon girl
that Howard and I had
a threesome with at Comic Con?
Sure.
I'll stick with 11.
She liked Howard better.
Well, now do you
see the problem?
Maybe.
I... I don't know.
You... It's late,
I-I should...
I should go.
Look,
I-I do get what you're saying.
Instead of desperately clinging
to any woman
who will go out with me,
I need to work on
my fear of being alone.
I was trying to suggest
chemical castration, but...
...it's my bedtime,
so whatever gets you
out the door.
Good night.
Howie, I'm back!
Shh-shh-shh,
I just got her to sleep.
Sorry.
What took you so long?
The grocery store
is a few blocks away.
They only had
regular yogurt.
I had to go to
a different store
to get the extra-fat
kind your mom likes.
Then why do I smell coffee
on your breath?
So what?
After two days of
taking care of her,
excuse me for stopping
to get a mocha.
A mocha?
Well, it must be nice
to be queen.
Queen?
I've been killing
myself here!
Well, whose fault is that?
I wanted to get a nurse,
but you were all,
"I'm nice.
I want to take care of people."
I'm glad I got that mocha.
And you know what
else I'm glad about?
I bought you a brownie
and I ate it in the car!
Howard!
Thanks a lot.
Now I have to go
rub her belly again.
Hey.
Thanks for letting me come over.
Of course.
Please, come in.
I just wanted to say
how sorry I am about tonight,
and...
I want to make sure
that we're okay.
Uh, look, you and I haven't made
any commitments to each other.
I know.
I just felt like
I needed to explain.
The guy I was with
did my last tattoo,
and he's been asking
me out for months.
I finally said yes
just to get it over with.
It's okay.
Really?
Well, I mean, yeah,
it freaked me out a little,
but that's my issue, not yours.
Wow.
If I saw you out
with another woman,
I'd be pretty upset.
Thank you.
Not just for being upset,
but for believing
that could happen.
Just so you know,
I'm not seeing anyone else.
Well, me, neither.
Okay.
Please.
So, uh... you...
you have tattoos?
Yeah.
I don't.
I have a hole
in my belly button
that may or may not
have been a piercing.
That's cool.
It's a piercing.
So, uh...
how many tattoos?
One on my shoulder,
one not on my shoulder
and one really not
on my shoulder.
It's, uh...
been a long time since
I've seen a girl's...
really not her shoulder.
Well...
how about you show
me your piercing
and I show you
my tattoos?
But, uh, before
I take my shirt off,
I just need like ten minutes
to do some crunches.
Oh, my God.
What a day.
Can I get you anything?
No.
I need to start making
some smart decisions.
With your career?
With my life.
Like what?
I don't know.
We could get married.
Come on, be serious.
I am.
Why?
Because I'm
a-a "smart decision"?
Well, yeah.
So I'm like a bran muffin.
What...
No, that's not what I'm saying.
No, it's exactly
what you're saying.
I'm the boring thing
you're choosing
because I'm good for you.
What does it matter?
The point is, I'm choosing you.
Well, it matters a lot!
I don't want to be
a bran muffin.
I-I want to be
a... Cinnabon, you know?
A strawberry Pop-Tart.
Something you're excited about
even though it could
give you diabetes.
Sweetie, you can be
any pastry you want.
No, no. No, it's too late.
I-I'm your
bran muffin.
Probably fat-free
and good for your colon.
You know what? Forget it.
I never should've brought it up.
You know I want to marry you,
but you're
only doing this
because you got fired
and you're feeling
sorry for yourself.
Okay, it may look that way,
but getting fired
from that movie was the best
thing that could have happened
to me, okay?
I finally realize
I don't need to be famous
or have some big career
to be happy.
Then what do you need?
You, you stupid Pop-Tart!
Oh.
Then I guess I'm in.
Really?
You "guess you're in"?
Not like, "I guess I'm in."
Like "I guess... I'm in!"
Okay.
Cool.
So is that it?
Are... are we engaged?
Yeah, I think so.
All right.
What's wrong?
I'm not sure.
Just... feels
a little anticlimactic.
Yeah, it kind of does, huh?
Oh, I know.
This might help.
Where did you get a ring?
I've...
had it for a couple years,
not important.
Penny...
will you marry me?
Oh, my God, yes.
This would have been
so much more romantic
if you didn't have
monkey hair on your finger.
How you feeling?
Last night was
a little rough,
but I think we're
gonna get through this.
I'm proud of us.
Me, too.
Where's my pancakes?!
Coming, Mrs. Wolowitz!
You were right.
Welcome to Team Putz.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man