- Hey, hey hey!
It's the best day of the year.
Happy Cinco de Mayo!
- I don't think you're allowed
to wear a poncho
to work, Hitchcock.
- Let's fiesta!
[band playing
"The Mexican Hat Song']
- Oh, you got a band.
♪
- Stop, stop!
No trumpets!
Not today!
My head is killing me!
- Hit the tequila
a little early, huh?
- I'm not hung over, Hitchcock.
I've got a tension headache.
I've got
the Lieutenant's exam tonight.
I'm stress-eating like crazy.
I had ten hard-boiled
egg yolks this morning.
- Gross.
- You're having a high-grade
pre-test freak out.
I've been there.
March 13, 2001.
AP Calc test—
- Ames, I hate to cut you off,
but we all know where
this story's going.
- Oh, yeah? You know
that I crapped my pants
in the middle of the test?
- Oh my God, no, I thought
you were just gonna say
you got a B+ or something.
- More like a BM.
- Noice.
- Come on, now Terry's worried
about his test and his bowels!
- What you need, Sergeant, is
to distract yourself.
NPR has a riveting
six hour interview
with Eileen Moon Myers.
- Nobody knows who that is.
- Nobody knows the Associate
Principal Cellist in the
New York Philharmonic?
[snorts] Okay.
- Wait! I've got it!
I know how to distract Terry.
Captain, remember how you
cancelled the last Halloween
heist because there was that
emergency gas line explosion
and you said we had
to "help out"?
- Yes,
I also remember you
refusing to believe
the explosion was real.
- Go back to acting school,
buddy.
You're way overselling
the pain here.
No one's buying it!
Well, it's not like I
was the only
one who thought
it was fake.
- And the Oscar goes to...
Trent!
- You said that we should
reschedule the heist for
another day, so why not today?
To help distract Terry?
- Yes! And I would love to
defend my crown after I
destroyed you all last year.
- Well, I mean, the proposal
was all part of my plan.
- All I remember is you
bowing to me on your knees.
- Yeah, I was asking you
to marry me.
- Well, you look like a fool.
- Neither of you won
because Jake swapped out
the real championship
cummerbund—
- Belt.
- For the treacly proposal one.
- What? I thought
everyone loved that
I used the heist
to do the proposal.
- You are wrong—everyone hated
it—but it helped me win.
During your engagement
celebration, I snuck back
and found the
original cummerbund.
- Belt.
- It's hanging up in
my living room at home.
- I never thought I'd say
this, but enough foreplay!
Are we heisting or not?
- Yes!
- Of course!
- Wait, I will only do this
under one condition.
Sergeant Jeffords agrees that
this will help his nerves.
- Yeah, I mean, I would like to
take my mind off the test.
And maybe I'll win this year!
- Ah, the heist
is already working.
Sergeant Jeffords has
recovered his sense of humor.
[laughter]
- Hey!
- All right,
but for real, though.
Are we doing this?
- We're doing this!
- Heist!
- It's a Cinco de Mayo heist!
- A Cinco de Mayo heist
makes just as much sense
as Halloween!
Let's do it!
[upbeat music]
♪
- Welcome one and all
to the first ever Cinco de Mayo
Halloween Heist 6!
We're still working
on the title.
- No need, I love it!
- Thank you, Charles.
Now, before we go any further,
we should probably choose
an item to steal.
Does anyone have
anything valuable on them?
Maybe some jewelry?
- I have a medical alert
bracelet that tells people
my name and address, in
case I have a brain collapse.
- Perfect, this year's champion
will be whoever's in possession
of Scully's very upsetting
bracelet at midnight tonight.
- I take my test at 6:30.
- You know what, Terry?
You're kind of making
this a nightmare.
Maybe you just
shouldn't participate.
- So this really isn't about
helping out Sergeant Jeffords?
- What?
- I guess I'm out.
- But—no, no, no, no, come on.
Of course I'm 100%
in support of Terry.
In fact, I'm going to
team up with him.
- [laughs]
Let's do this!
- You are so easily
manipulated.
Now you're stuck with
Sergeant Dumb Dumb.
- Damn it.
- Hey.
- Santiago,
shall we join forces?
- Ooh, smart, teaming up
with the reigning champ.
- Again with this nonsense?
I'm the reigning champ.
The only thing you won
last heist was a lifetime of
mediocre heterosexual
intercourse with Jake.
- [gasps]
How dare you.
No one thinks you won
last year.
- Wow, really thought the "how
dare you" was going to be
linked to his mean
sex comment, but okay.
- Right, sorry.
I'll have you know
Jake and I wear each other out
every single night.
- Good lord, overcompensating.
You know what?
Maybe we just shouldn't
talk about this at work.
- I'm texting Kevin
to bring the cummerbund.
You'll see who the real winner
is, you braggy breeders.
- A lot of infighting.
Not too late to ditch
Amy and team up with
this pussycat burglar.
- Please, Boyle,
your only value was
you had a doppelganger
which no longer matters
since Bill died in
that accident.
- RIP, Bill.
- So sad.
- I can still be useful
without Bill!
No hole's too tight
for these tiny tips.
[groaning]
For stealing stuff!
- [sighs]
- Well, fine.
Looks like I'll just team up
with my friend Rosa.
- I'm out.
Five heists was enough.
We've exhausted every
possibility of this thing.
Literally nothing new
can happen.
It's boring.
You can have a long lunch
with me instead.
- Ooh, lunch?
The devil's breakfast.
- Well, forget it.
- Okay, I won't call it that!
I just want to be
included in something!
- Okay, that whole lunch thing
was clearly a ploy.
But even still, I'm not
worried about losing to Boyle.
- No one is.
He's a joke.
All right, let's
get this thing going.
Scully will be locked
in the supply closet
with his bracelet.
- Can I lie down on the floor?
- Uh, yeah.
You can do whatever you want.
And you're already on the
ground.
With Hitchcock.
And you both have pillows.
- Best day ever!
- There.
Now they're locked in.
Arrange your affairs.
The heist begins
in five minutes.
- Five minutes? But this whole
thing was so last second!
I don't even have
any plans or supplies!
I have so many
plans and supplies.
I even have a victory banner
that unfurls with
a voice command.
I can't say what,
but it's so cool.
- I thought this was
a spur-of-the-moment fun way
to distract me from freaking
out about my exam!
- Well, it wasn't exactly
hard to predict, Sarge.
Your catchphrase is
"Terry hates tests."
- It's true.
Terry hates tests!
- But the point is,
I planned everything,
starting with
Scully's bracelet.
It had to be the prize
because I have prepared
the greatest reveal
in heist history.
Allow me to introduce you to...
Other Scully.
- Hi, I'm Earl,
Norm's twin brother.
- [mimicking explosion]
- Why's Scully never mentioned
he had a twin before?
- Because no one talks about
their siblings with coworkers.
- I've told you about
my brother Lawrence.
- Nope, and I don't want to
learn about him
and I already forgot his name.
Now let's go.
It's time to heist!
- No movement yet.
So here's our plan.
After watching everyone coo
over your maudlin proposal,
I've decided we should
employ a similar diversion.
- Smart, I'm in.
- You will tell Jake
you are pregnant
with his child.
- What? I'm not pregnant.
- Here is a positive
pregnancy test
and a sonogram of your fetus.
Congratulations.
It's a girl.
- Feels a little mean
to play with Jake's feelings
like that, sir.
- You're right, it is mean.
Too bad.
As your mentor,
I command you to do it.
- Wow, okay.
Perhaps we should
discuss some other options.
- There's no time, look.
Peralta's going
for the bracelet!
- How'd he get him
free so quickly?
- See ya later, losers!
- Not so fast!
[taser crackling]
- [grunting]
What the hell was that?
- That Fitbit I gave
you at Christmas?
I modified it into a taser.
- What? Do you even want
me to get into shape?
- Yeah, but not as
much as I want to win.
Buzz buzz, bitch.
- I've got Scully.
Come on, let's go.
[taser crackling]
- [muffled shout]
No! Nooo!
- Yes.
- Fake heist went perfectly.
- So did the real heist.
- Why is your face
twitching like that?
- Oh, Amy tased me a bunch.
I bit my own tongue.
It was awesome. Was it hard
to get through the door?
- No. I'm strong as hell.
The hard part was getting this
bracelet off Scully's wrist.
How can you even feel your
hand with this thing so tight?
- You're supposed
to feel your hand?
- Well, that's terrifying.
Now if you'll excuse
me I'm going to hide
the old bracelet and
win me this heist.
- Don't you mean
win us this heist?
- Oh, Terrence,
unfortunately I do not.
- What the hell?
- Sorry, Sarge.
It had to be this way.
- Why?
- The banner only has
my name on it.
It's really all about the
banner.
It unfurls by
a voice command.
But I promise that I will
mention
both you and Earl Scully
in my victory speech.
- Wait, Earl's here?
- Yeah. He helped us
with the heist.
- I told that son of a bitch
never to show his face in
New York again!
- Why are you running
towards the glass?
[glass shatters]
- You're a dead man, Earl!
- That's not great.
- You're a dead man, Jake!
- Uh, that's much worse.
- Squirt more lube
and help me yank.
- Ugh, you know
that fun braggy recap
we do at the end of each win?
Can we leave this part out?
- [grunts] Yes.
We'll make up a cooler thing.
But for now,
we lube and yank.
Wrap your legs around him
to anchor yourself.
- Yep. Here we go.
[grunting, screaming]
- Earl? Earl!
- Norm?
Norm?
- What the—
- I'm so happy your
friend invited me to—
- I told you
what would happen
if I ever saw
you again, Earl.
- What is going on?
What am I looking at?
- Scully has a twin
brother named Earl.
Jake brought him
here to trick you.
- Thank you
for the ride, Terrence.
Apparently they don't
get along very well.
- We did get along.
We were inseparable,
until Earl slept
with my wife.
- It's not my fault she wanted
to have sex with a stud
instead of a dud.
- Stud? Your face looks it's
been kicked in by a horse!
- Well, your mouth
looks like a butthole!
- Your whole body
looks like a butthole.
- And you look identical.
- [grunting]
- [gurgling]
- Should we help Scully?
- I'm not touching this.
[grunting]
- [screams]
- There's nowhere to run, Earl!
- Well, that was
a real mind eff.
Good-bye.
- Just so you know,
Jake has the bracelet
in his pocket.
- Why would you tell them that?
We're a team!
- You locked me up.
- Yeah, but they
didn't know that!
- There's no bracelet
in his pocket!
- What? There should be.
Where'd it go?
- Shalom, partner.
- Dope.
- And you thought
Shlomo Ben-Yisrael
wouldn't come through.
- No, I said the name
and the costume
were offensive,
bordering on actionable.
- Well, it worked.
Jake brought in Scully's twin
just like I planned when
I connected them on Facebook,
but he had no idea
they hated each other.
And when everyone
was fighting,
they were too distracted
to notice old Shlomo.
They all underestimated me,
Rosa, but today,
they will learn the error
of their ways, for today,
I will prove that nobody
gets the best of Charles Boyle.
- I doused your beard
in chloroform.
- Really? I find that
very hard to beli—
[triumphant music]
♪
- Where's this goin'?
- All the way to Trenton.
Take your time.
- Aah, perfect.
- What? What happened?
You know where the bracelet is?
- No. Kevin has arrived
with proof that I am
the only two-time
winner of the heist.
- Here's your cummerbund,
Raymond.
- We don't have
time for this, sir!
I'm gonna go search
the first floor.
- And I will search
the second floor.
We are an inseparable team.
That was a devious fib.
I'm betraying her
even as we speak.
- Hey, Kev.
- Diaz and I are covertly
working together.
She snuck up through the vents.
This is a major reveal.
I feel like you're
not appreciating it.
- I don't like these heists,
or what they bring out in you.
- Oh, clam it, Kevin.
- "Clam it"?
Cheddar, perhaps
we should leave.
- No, Cheddar stays.
He still has
an important role to play.
Give me Mr. Hootsworth.
No one would ever think of
looking for the bracelet
in Cheddar's
favorite chew toy.
- Or do you mean
Jake's favorite chew toy?
[chuckles]
Well, thank God no one
was around to hear that.
Ah! There you are.
I've been looking all over.
Woah. That's a lot of yolks.
Are you stress eating again
or is this just a
small Terry snack?
- I'm stress eating, Jake!
My snack yolks
are in that bowl.
- Oh. Well,
stop eating eggs
and come help me
with the heist!
- I'm not helping you.
- Why not?
Ugh, is this because
I once betrayed you?
- Yes! It was
our last interaction.
- And it was a huge mistake
and I now realize that
our friendship
is way more important
than any stupid banner.
Look, the bracelet
is in Cheddar's chew toy.
I know because I bugged
Holt's cummerbund.
- You did?
- Yes! I figured he would
bring it in to show off.
Now let's do this!
- I don't know.
- Look, Sarge,
I'm sorry, okay?
I can't undo the past,
but come on.
Would you rather
win the heist with me or sit
around swallowing eggs like
Birdo from "Super Mario 2"?
- Birdo doesn't eat eggs.
Birdo spits them!
- Oh, my God, you got
that reference, Terry?
We're the perfect team!
Come on, Sarge, please?
- Fine, I'll help.
- Ah! Wonderful.
But, before you fully commit,
I should probably
give you the heads-up.
My plan is very elaborate and
you might get a little messy.
- I'm in.
It's the heist, baby!
Now let me know how
we get that chew toy.
- All right!
Okay.
First, I infiltrate Holt's
office and continue
our argument about
who won last year's heist.
- How many cummerbunds are
you holding right now? Zero!
It's one bund to none, son!
Tell him, Kevin.
- I'm leaving.
- It doesn't matter—
- As Holt argues with me
I will be covertly
releasing more water
into Cheddar's bowl.
Then we sit back
and wait for...
[Cheddar whimpers]
- Potty time again?
- What if he takes
him downstairs?
- He won't.
I spent a lot of time
making clandestine searches
on Holt's computer.
Now all of his targeted ads
direct him straight to...
- The Puppy PeePee Pad.
Intriguing.
- He bought one
and put it out
on the roof next
to Gina's golden statue.
And, because he believes
that Cheddar deserves
to pee in privacy like any
other self-respecting adult,
he will leave Cheddar outside
alone to do his business.
- Notify me when you're done,
via bark.
- While Holt guards the door,
you'll be swapping out
Mr. Hootsworth for this.
- That all sounds great,
but how do I get onto the roof
without Holt noticing?
- Oh, Sarge.
You'll already be out there...
In a perfect golden disguise.
- The plan worked! I got it!
- Oh my God, you
look like an Oscar. Ooh!
We should take a picture where
it looks like I'm holding you.
- Jake.
- You're right.
There's no time.
We'll do it later.
- No, we won't!
Help me get this paint off!
- Okay, put your hands out and
I'll squirt you with
a little makeup remover.
Hi-ya!
- No!
You're betraying me again?
Why?
- Because of the banner!
- But I thought you said our
friendship was more important!
- Yeah, that was
obviously a lie.
The banner was very expensive!
I don't have
a lot of money, Sarge.
All right, bye.
Don't make a lot of noise.
- Howdy. I just got back
from lunch with Charles,
who is not here.
I am real glad
I skipped the heist.
Say, who is winning?
- I don't know, but I know
that I am not winning.
- Interesting,
it is also not me.
- Uh, why are you guys
acting so weird?
- Gah, weird?
Would a person who is acting
weird laugh like this?
A huh-huh huh-ha, carefree!
- Yes.
- Jake!
- Oh, Terry, you ripped
yourself free.
- Yeah, maybe you
should try cuffing me
to a stronger metal
next time.
- Yeah, I don't know the
relative strength of metals.
- What's going on?
Why does Terry
look like an Oscar?
- Doesn't he?
- He has the bracelet!
We grabbed Mr. Hootsworth
from Cheddar and
swapped it for a fake!
- Wow, Terry, my betrayals
were all in good fun,
but this really hurts.
- Cheddar,
bring me Mr. Hootsworth.
It's an updated model.
The bowtie is Turkish blue
instead of Egyptian blue.
How could you not
have noticed this?
- Because he's a dog.
And at the end of the day a dog
is no match for Jake Peralta.
- Well yours is a fake, too.
Turkish blue bowtie.
- Oh, come on!
The one time
I say out loud
I'm smarter than a dog?
- If I have a fake
and you have a fake,
who took the real bracelet?
- I did.
- Kevin?
- I swapped out Mr. Hootsworth
for a fake
while you were arguing
with Peralta.
- How many cummerbunds are you
holding right now? Zero!
It's one bund to none, son!
- You betrayed me?
But why?
- I can't have more of
these trophies in our home.
The cummerbund was already in
the living room.
What's next,
a rusty medical bracelet
suspended above our bed?
- Yes! Now hand it over.
- I don't have it.
I gave it to Amy.
- [gasps]
- Santiago.
- You betrayed me as well?
- You betrayed me first.
You were working with Rosa
this whole time.
- That wasn't real.
I was always gonna
stab her in the back.
- You were?
What kind of person treats
another human being
like that?
- You tricked me, Rosa!
And then you shipped
me to New Jersey!
- First of all, grow up.
Second of all, how'd you
get back here so fast?
- If you get a box wet enough,
it's very easy to
bust out of it.
- No one ask any follow-ups!
- I knew I couldn't
trust you, Rosa.
That's why I was going to
double-cross you with Bill.
That's right,
he didn't really die.
- Hey, guys, you really thought
I'd miss this year's heist?
No way, I'm part of the squad.
- No.
- Not true.
- Okay, this is official
getting hard to track.
Who has the bracelet now?
- Santiago.
- Yeah! And none of you
are getting it!
- We'll see about that.
[taser crackling]
- [groans]
What the hell?
- Remember that very
fancy Swiss pen I got you
for Christmas,
the one that you keep in
your pocket at all times?
It's a taser, bro.
[beeping]
- Uuugh!
I'll take that. Amy,
do not make me tase you again.
- No, no, no, no, don't!
I'm pregnant!
- What?
- I just found out.
It's a girl.
- Oh, my God!
- Oh my God, it's happening!
Quick, someone get a reaction
video of me becoming an uncle!
- She's making it up.
The pregnancy scam was my idea.
- No.
No, no, no, no, Amy.
Wait, is that true? Did you
just lie to me about our baby?
- Yeah, did you lie to
us about our baby?
- You tased me!
- You tased me first!
- Enough!
Terry's had enough of this.
This was supposed to be
just a fun game but it's turned
you all into terrible people.
Betraying your husband, putting
your friend in the mail.
Jake and Amy, did you guys
buy each other any gifts
this year that weren't tasers?
- No.
- You all pretended that
this was all about
helping me with my test.
But none of you cared one bit!
You know what?
You all suck!
[beeping]
- Oh no, my voice command.
Terry, look out!
- [groans]
- Okay. I know that was bad,
but let's not jump to
any conclusions about
whose fault it was.
all: ♪ Jacob Peralta,
Jacob Peralta ♪
♪ This was all
his clever plan ♪
- Wow, what
a fun improvised song.
all: ♪ This was all
his clever plan ♪
- His eyes aren't focusing and
he hasn't referred to himself
in the third person in minutes.
He's clearly concussed.
- Guys, this is bad.
The Lieutenant's exam
is in 30 minutes.
- Okay, look, let's just
get him to One Police Plaza
and hopefully he'll
wake up on the way.
Charles, help me pick him up.
- Copy that.
He's too heavy.
We can't do this.
- God! How does he lift weights
and also lift his arms?
This is impossible.
We'll never get him there.
- So you guys need
help moving a body?
Thank God old Bill's
part of the squad.
I mean, assuming,
I am part of the squad.
- Yes, sure.
- Totally.
- Oh, yes, finally.
I have somewhere to live.
- What?
- Meet me in the alley next to
my shopping cart.
It's the one with all the cans.
- Seems like his plan is
just to put Terry in
the shopping cart.
- Correct.
We'll take it!
[driving mariachi music]
♪
- Room 410 is this way!
Okay, we got him here with
one minute to spare.
- Yes! I knew we could make it.
All right, Sarge.
You ready to
go in there and ace this thing?
- Yeah, I can't believe it,
I'm gonna be a pilot!
- Okay, well, that's not great.
- There's no way he can take
the test in that condition!
- You're right. Amy,
you're going to have to
crawl inside
his shirt and operate
his arms for him.
It's a Ratatouille situation.
- On it.
- No. It's over. We have to go
in there and tell them
that he won't be making it.
- So that's it then.
Rosa, you should probably go
in first since
this is mostly your fault.
- Dude.
- All right, fine, I'll do it,
jeez.
- Wait. Where is everyone?
Where are all the desks?
- What is happening?
What's happening is...
You all suck!
[beeping]
all: ♪ You all are losers,
you all are losers ♪
♪ And Terry Jeffords
is the best! ♪
♪ You are all losers,
you are all losers ♪
♪ And Terry Jeffords
is the best ♪
- Son of a bitch stole my song.
- Wait, Terry has the bracelet?
- That's right.
Me and my teammate Terry won.
We fooled you all.
- You didn't do [bleep]!
- Okay, well, neither did
Jordan's teammates,
but they still got rings.
All right, fine.
Just tell us how you did it.
- Well, first, for my plan
to work, it had to happen
on a day when I could
control everything.
I couldn't let it
be Halloween.
- You faked the gas explosion!
- Yeah, stupid actors
almost blew it.
- What was with
that moaning, Trent?
I thought you studied at
the Lee Strasberg Institute!
- It doesn't mean anything.
They just take your money!
- Oh, that is a huge relief.
I felt so bad about poking
that guy's wound to make
sure it was real.
- You should still
feel bad about that.
- No, it was all fake.
I'm totally absolved.
Continue with your story,
Sarge.
- I knew you'd suggest a heist
as a distraction from
my Lieutenant exam, then all
I had to do was sit back
and watch as everyone
took things way too far.
- But how'd you know we'd
get so out of hand?
- I spent the last six months
sowing the seeds of conflict.
- Man, I am so sick of Jake
saying he is the only
two-time Halloween
heist winner.
both: I'm the only two-time
Halloween heist winner.
- I can't believe
everyone says you're
not helpful during
the Halloween heist.
Just because they all think
your fingers are too big.
- We'll show them.
- Thanks for inviting
me over for dinner.
Boy, that's hung in a real
prominent place, isn't it?
- Not for long.
I was manipulated?
- Sorry, Kevin.
- Don't apologize to him,
Terry.
It's his first heist.
He needs to learn.
Keep going.
- Well, after I got everyone
acting like maniacs, all I had
to do was make you feel bad
by "knocking myself out."
- The banner.
But how did you learn
my voice command?
- I didn't have to.
I sold you the damn thing!
- No.
I want it to unfurl when I say,
"You all suck."
[through voice distortion app]
- Absolutely.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
- The pleasure was all mine.
[click]
That's gonna work.
I spent $1,800 on that thing!
- You did?
- Amy, stop interrupting.
Terry's doing his big speech.
- Anyway, once
my fake concussion was
on display, I created
the perfect distraction
for my partner
to do his job.
- Cheddar,
you duplicitous bitch.
- I've been training
Cheddar for months.
- Wow, what a fun
improvised song!
- When I swapped
the Hootsworths,
I put a magnetic collar
on him!
From there, Cheddar
followed us all the way
to One Police Plaza,
where he hand-delivered
the bracelet to me
right outside this room.
- But, wait, what about
the Lieutenant's exam?
Aren't you supposed to
be taking it right now?
- Hell no, I took
that thing weeks ago.
And I passed!
I'm already a lieutenant!
- You are?
- That's incredible!
- Lieutenant Jeffords!
- This is amazing.
- I'm so proud of you, Terry.
- All right.
You've overstepped now, Bill.
- Yeah, it's weird
you're here, Bill.
- To Terry Jeffords,
the ultimate human being
slash genius.
Nice work... Lieutenant.
all: Yeah!
- Thanks, squad!
- Also the next heist will be
at Halloween,
so you'll only be champion
for six months.
This is half a win at best.
- Sounds about right, yeah.
- Yeah.
- Pretty garbage.
- Hey, Scully, so you
and Earl made up?
- Yup.
Hitchcock helped us realize
we shouldn't fight just
because we're so different.
- Yeah. To our differences!
[mugs clink]
[together]
Oh, dang it!
[simultaneous farts]
[together]
Ooh, double dang it.
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- Terry, what you did
today was awesome
and I just wanted to say I'm
sorry if I took things too far.
- Are you kidding me?
I was just guilting you
as a tactic.
I love how crazy
the heist gets.
- Okay, good, 'cause what I
really wanted to say
is next heist I'm gonna drown
you in your own blood.
- Oh, yeah? Well, then I'm
gonna rip your arms off
and beat you to
death with 'em.
- Oh!
- I'm going to slice your
Achilles' tendons, peel off
your fingernails, and stick
knitting needles in your eyes.
both: Oh, damn.
- Raymond, you were right.
These heists are fun.
- Fremulon.
- Not a doctor.
Shh.