- Hey, what's up?
I came as fast as I could.
- Title of your sex tape.
Nailed it.
So have you ever heard of a guy
named Bruno Rojas?
- Yeah, big guy
in the Colombian cartel, right?
- He was, until he got shot
in the chest yesterday
by his top lieutenant.
Apparently, the bullet went
straight through his nipple.
- Whoa.
Nature's bull's-eye.
- Oh, my God, I love the way
your brain works.
Anyway, he's in a coma now,
and Captain Holt thinks
if I'm here when he wakes up,
I can get him to talk.
- So what'd you call me for?
- Because I need a partner.
- What about them?
- Oh, we're not here for work.
I brought Scully in because
he needs some medical tests.
- Yeah, I'm here all the time.
I'm kind of the mayor
of this place.
Cheryl, baby,
you got a fresh bag for me?
- Saving you the biggest one,
Scully.
- You're too good to me.
Anyway, I'll see you guys
around.
Dan, Dan, the enema man.
- Well, guess it's kind of nice
to see Scully in his element.
- Whoo!
- Jake, I can't stay here
with you.
I have so much on my plate
at work.
- Yeah, so do I.
I mean, I've been pulling
double shifts nonstop,
but we haven't really gotten
to hang out in almost a month.
Our anniversary is coming up,
and we don't even have
anything planned.
- I know, but we talked
about this.
We're gonna take a trip
as soon as we have time.
I promise.
- Just like you promised
we would see
the "Bumblebee" movie?
- I didn't promise that.
I believe what I said was,
"Isn't that a kids' movie?"
- Yeah, and I believe
what I said was,
"It's for teens."
Look, I get that you can't
take any time off from work,
but this is a loophole.
It's still work.
You know,
we can hang out here
and chat and catch up
and laugh,
and technically,
we'll be doing our jobs.
I call it a "casecation."
♪ Casecation,
all I ever wanted ♪
- Ooh.
- ♪ Casecation,
had to get away ♪
- Babe, this is so sweet,
but do you honestly think
that Holt's gonna let me
just hang out here
with you indefinitely?
- Yes. Just tell him
I need supervision.
I've spent the last six years
building up a reputation
as an irresponsible goof
for this very moment.
- That is ridiculous.
Holt respects you.
- Does he, though?
- Hello, you've reached
the office of Raymond Holt.
I can come to the phone
right now.
- Hey, sir, I'm just here
at the hospital with Jake,
and I think he could use some—
- Oversight?
Agreed.
- So?
- ♪ Casecation
♪ All I ever wanted
- Prepare to be romanced.
Voilà.
- Bienvenue à Paris.
- Bonjour, madame. Fromage?
- Don't worry,
Charles is leaving
in a second.
- I am?
- Yeah, you were just
helping me set up.
- Fine. Enjoy your weird
anniversary
with just the couple,
you selfish jerks.
- Thank you for your help!
So what do you think?
- I love it.
It's really romantic.
- Aww.
- I mean, except
for the comatose body
in the middle of the room.
- Oh, yeah, just pretend
he's part of Paris.
Imagine we're on a walking tour
of the Louvre,
and he's a statue.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Shall we, ma chérie?
I asked the lady at the store
what her favorite cheeses were,
and those were all
super expensive,
so I got us a budget-conscious
selection of local cheddars.
- So, a full year of marriage.
What was your favorite part?
- Are you asking me
to do a marriage highlight reel
countdown
à la "NBA Inside Stuff"?
- I mean, that's not exactly
what I was—
- Number five!
Ahmad Rashad.
It's my best impression.
Number five was the time
that we accidentally got
our contact lenses switched.
I got to see the world
through your eyes.
- But our prescriptions
are different,
and the world was so blurry.
- Yeah, it was crazy.
I thought I was having
a stroke.
Okay, your turn.
- Number four!
- Oh, is an old witch
introducing this highlight?
- That was exactly
what you sounded like.
- No.
- Yes.
- Agree to disagree.
- Fine.
Number four was
when we played laser tag
and we shot all those
little kids.
- Oh, yeah. We really messed up
little Mason's birthday party.
- Mm-hmm.
- Deservedly so.
He was a jerk.
- Ugh.
- Okay, what should
number three be?
Ooh, I know.
It was that time we shared
an UberPool with Michael Caine.
- Oh!
- I mean, obviously,
Michael Caine
was shooting a movie in London
at that time, and also,
why would Michael Caine be
in an UberPool?
- But it was still so cool.
- It really was.
We shared a car with Alfred.
- We did!
Okay, number two.
This might be
my favorite moment
of our entire time as a couple:
January 6th.
- Eddie Redmayne's birthday.
- Why do you know that?
- 'Cause he was weird
in "Jupiter Ascending."
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm just a fan.
- Yeah, that's not what
I'm talking about.
- Okay.
- It was the coldest night
of the year,
and you put socks on my feet
while I slept.
You never even took credit
for it.
- But now I'm getting credit
for that
and for not taking credit.
That's double credit, you fool.
- You two are just the cutest.
I can't wait for number one!
- Oh, it's Ahmad Rashad.
- I'm Pam.
I'm from next door.
I was listening
to the two of you talk
and just had to get a look.
You're both very attractive.
- Aren't they?
- Boyle, go home!
- Oh, Pam can stay but not me?
- Yeah, because
she's a patient here.
I'm assuming,
because of your gown.
- I am.
I have a twisted bowel.
I have a tube; I have a bag.
Do you want to see?
- Oh, no, no, no.
But thank you, Pam.
- Let me know
if you smell anything.
I don't even notice it anymore.
- Well, I'm pretty sure
I actually already
smell something.
- No, you'll know.
- Oh.
- Do you two have kids?
Mixed race babies are always
so adorable.
- Oh, you said words.
- Yeah, we don't have kids yet,
but we're gonna start trying
soon.
- I just have the one,
my Bobby.
He was such a cute little kid,
until he discovered his wiener.
- Pam, there you are.
It's time for your IV.
You're playing music in here?
You can't do that.
- Why not, Nurse Janet?
Is it gonna distract
the doctors?
- Yes, that's exactly
what it'll do.
- Okay, fine,
I'll turn it off immediately.
- Are we the bad guys here?
- Yeah, it seems very likely.
Hey, by the way,
we don't have to pretend
we're undercover here.
The hospital staff knows
we're cops.
- Oh, I wasn't
setting up cover.
Was I?
- Well, just the kids thing.
Saying that we were gonna
start trying soon.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean right away.
I just meant
in the near future.
- Oh.
Okay.
Cool, cool, cool,
cool, cool, cool.
Cool, cool, cool, cool,
except for that there's
one little problem there,
which is that I don't know
that I totally know
that I for sure
want to have kids,
so...
- You don't?
- No.
Do you?
- Uh-huh.
- Oh.
- I don't understand.
I thought we were
on the same page about kids.
We talked about this.
- We did?
- Aw, look at these pictures
my brother sent of Matthew.
- Mm.
- We should do this someday.
What do you think?
- Are you kidding me?
Of course.
I was talking about going
to the water park.
You were talking about
having kids?
- Yeah! I said, "Do you think
we can afford it?"
And you said, "We'll start
saving right away."
- So let me get this straight.
All that water park money
I've been saving,
you want to spend it
on kids now?
- Yeah. Why would you want
to spend that much money
on a water park?
- Look, I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say here.
I just—
I never wanted children.
- Well, I always have.
- All right,
so how do we handle this?
- I mean, there's only one
thing to do when two people
have diametrically opposing
views on a subject.
- Talk about it lovingly
and decide how to move forward?
- Structured debate.
- Oh. Fun.
- High school format.
Modified Lincoln-Douglas.
Let's take one hour apart
for research and prep. Yeah.
- Great, I'll just do
a Lincoln-Douglas.
- I'd be careful if I were you.
Relationships are like bowels.
Once you get them twisted,
they can never untwist.
- Pam, you're in here again.
- That's all you prepped?
- Yeah,
I just searched my heart
and then wrote down
how I was feeling.
- I'm gonna eat you alive,
you dumb son of a bitch.
- Cool. And then
we'll have kids together?
- Yeah. It's gonna be great.
Okay, the topic today
is whether or not
we should have children.
I will be taking
the affirmative.
You will be taking
the negative.
Each round will be
individually scored
by our judge, Captain Holt.
- Do you need to hear
my credentials?
Debate moderator license
D as in delta, 8-1-0—
- I believe you.
- Y as in Yankee, 4-1.
J as in Juliet,
J as in Juliet, 6.
- Great.
- I have a variety of timers.
Do you prefer a buzz or a ding?
- Don't care.
- Ding.
- Okay.
Peralta, you can present
the first argument
from your, uh...
Scribbled list of feelings.
- I'll have you know
that I have some
data-driven arguments as well.
According to a study I read,
people with kids
were less likely to report that
they were happy in their lives
than people without kids.
Now, call me crazy, but being
happy tends to make me feel,
uh, pretty happy.
- Where did you read
this study?
- Well, it wasn't
something I read
so much as told about.
- And who told you about it?
- Hitchcock.
- Hitchcock?
- Yeah.
- That seems like
a pretty intellectual thing
for him to mention.
What was the context?
- He had invested in a NuvaRing
competitor called Vag-a-Plug
and was practicing
his sales pitch on me.
- This is your first argument?
Your opening statement?
- Point to Amy.
- All right, fine.
Forget the study.
I just don't want to lose
what we already have.
- Ask anyone with children
and they'll tell you
children bring meaning and love
into your life.
Yes, there may be some moments
that you lose,
but there will also be
new moments.
Take the water park.
I would never go with you,
but you know who would?
Your kid.
- Point to Amy.
- That's not your call to make,
Peralta.
Point to Amy.
- Okay, fine.
New subject: work.
We both work way too much.
Why bother having kids
if you never get
to spend time with them?
I mean, I love my job,
and I know you love yours,
and I don't think it's fair
for either of us
to have to sacrifice that.
- Do you know why I want to
become lieutenant so badly?
- To prove your worth to
your hyper judgmental parents.
- Yes, obviously that.
But also, the higher your rank,
the more control
over your hours.
Plenty of people
have jobs and kids, Jake,
and they find a way.
- This has become more about
your employment status.
As your supervisor, I feel
I have a conflict of interest
and should abstain
from judging.
- Okay, so do we both
get a point?
- No. Kevin has been
on the phone all this time.
He's also a licensed
debate moderator.
- License number
J as in Juliet, 2-5-9...
- This means nothing to me.
- H as in hotel.
Z as in Zulu.
- Oh, thank God he stopped.
- 3-6-9.
Point to Amy.
- Okay, fine.
You want to know why I really
don't want to have children?
I had a crappy dad.
I know what happens
when you mess up as a parent.
It's not great.
And this may come as a shock
to you, but...
I kind of have some dad issues
with certain people.
- Holt.
- Me.
- Raymond.
- Yeah, but not just him.
It's every male authority
figure from my entire life.
- Hey, Jake, can you move
"Legends of the Fall"
from new releases into drama?
- You got it, Dad.
Craig was only six weeks older
than me.
- Since this has become
about me,
I'm gonna have to abstain
from this round as well,
but Kevin is still standing by.
- Actually, I feel as though
your personal relationship
with Peralta
affects me too.
Luckily, I had Gail
standing by as well.
- Oh, my God,
you guys know Gail?
- Who's Gail?
- Vice president
of the Debaters Club.
- This is a very big deal.
- Do you need to hear
my credentials?
License number
U as in uniform, 7—
- No!
No more credentials, please.
I don't want to have
a structured debate.
It's an idiotic way
to decide something.
- What?
- How dare you?
- Is he insane?
- Raymond, Kevin,
I'll be reporting this.
- Okay, look.
Amy, I'm scared, okay?
I'm scared that
we're gonna have a child
and I won't be able
to handle it,
I'm scared that
I'm not gonna be a good father,
and I'm scared that I'll make
a mistake I can't take back.
- Jake, I get it.
I'm scared too.
- Every other big decision
I've made in my life
I was sure about:
becoming a cop,
asking you to marry me,
buying those Jordan 1s
for $500.
- Wait, you spent $500
on sneakers?
- Yeah, they were so cool,
and if I had never worn them,
they would have kept
their value.
- So they lost their value?
- Yes, all of it.
I stepped in a puddle
as soon as I left the store.
But this isn't about
the Jordans.
This is about the fact
that I don't want to bring
a human being into this world
unless I'm 100% sure that
I'm ready to take care of it.
Okay?
- Too emotional.
Point to Amy.
- Okay, Gail is clearly biased.
I think we need
a new moderator.
- Bob Templeman here.
- What? How many people
are on this phone call?
- Hey, so Holt went to go
smooth things over with Gail.
He thinks we may
just have to pay
the Debaters Guild
a small fine.
- Cool. And as you can see,
Pam is here.
She has some thoughts.
- I was saying to Jake,
before Bobby,
I didn't think I wanted
to have kids either.
But he's the best thing
that ever happened to me.
- Hey, Pam, could you give us
a minute?
- Oh, of course.
I'm gonna call my friend JoAnn.
She's been waiting for
a big update on all of this.
- Great.
- I'm sorry.
The debate was a bad idea.
I just...
I felt ambushed by the fact
that you didn't want kids,
and I thought I could fix it
with logic.
- I mean,
what if I had won the debate?
- Jake, I'm trying so hard
to be nice,
but I don't know how to respond
to that.
- Cold-blooded but fair.
- I get it.
You're scared.
I can't change that.
- Yeah, but that doesn't mean
I'll never change
how I feel about it.
I mean, I used to be scared
of sushi,
and now it's my favorite food.
I got tuna sashimi
from a pharmacy the other day.
- You shouldn't have.
- Yeah, it was very warm.
I got so sick.
Look, can we just press pause
on this conversation?
I mean, let's enjoy our lives
for a little bit,
and then maybe the next time
it comes up,
I'll feel differently, okay?
- No.
- What?
- I need an answer
from you now.
Like right this minute?
- You can take a day or a week,
or maybe a month.
- That's not a lot of time,
Ames.
I mean, that doesn't seem
totally fair.
- Well, now you know
how I feel.
Women don't have the luxury
of waiting till we're 60
and then changing our minds
and getting remarried
and having a baby
with some dumb 28-year-old.
- Oh, come on.
There's no way
I'm gonna be rich enough
that a 28-year-old
is gonna want to be with me.
Did that help?
Look, I don't understand
what the big deal is.
You're still young.
We have plenty of time.
- I know, but I don't want
to wait around for two years
and then have you decide
you don't want kids,
'cause I don't want
to start over at 38.
- Start over?
Like, with someone else?
- ♪ Casecation,
all I ever wanted ♪
♪ Casecation, had to get away
♪ Casecation
♪ The vibe in here
is really weird ♪
- I think they're having
a fight.
- No, it's not a fight,
it's just a devastatingly sad
conversation
about whether or not
we should have kids
or just start over,
so you were totally wrong,
Rosa.
- What? You got married
without talking about
if you want children?
- Yeah, and we also got married
without discussing
whether or not we like
water parks.
A lot of new stuff has come up,
okay, Terry?
- Why are you guys here?
- A CI came in.
There's a lot of chatter that
whoever tried to kill Rojas
is coming to finish the job.
- At the hospital?
- Yeah.
Holt wanted extra manpower
here.
- Okay, why don't you two
lock down the nurses' station
while Amy and I
secure the room?
- Actually,
I'd rather be with Rosa.
- Uh-oh.
- Damn, Jake.
Thanks a lot, Sarge.
- You told me to sing!
- Yeah, but what was all this?
- That's just Terry
being Terry.
- Okay, from this vantage
we can see the elevator
and the stairs.
No one should be able to get
to Rojas without us noticing.
- Cool.
- Hey, look, um...
I don't want you to get caught
in the middle of this stuff
between me and Jake.
I don't want you
to choose sides.
- Already chose. I'm with you.
- Really?
I didn't know you wanted kids.
- I don't know
if I'll ever want kids,
but you should have them.
They're so cute.
It's up.
- Aw, it is up.
- Anyway, do you want me
to talk to Jake?
I'm a pretty good bully.
- Thanks, but no.
I've got this covered.
I left him alone with Terry.
That guy is
a walking advertisement
for the joys of fatherhood.
- Do not do it.
- What?
Don't you love your girls?
- So much.
You should have seen Cagney
this morning
with her little braids in.
- Oh.
- But they are a ton of work,
man.
If you are not totally,
100% sure you want them,
you won't survive.
- Is it really that hard?
- Yes.
I never get any sleep.
I'm always sick.
I never get to watch anything
I want on TV.
I still haven't finished
"Breaking Bad,"
but I can recite "Moana"
from memory?
"Maui, shape-shifter,
demigod of the wind and sea.
I am Moana."
Why do I know that?
- I don't want to watch
kids' movies.
I want to watch movies
for adults.
Adults and teens.
- And they are getting
so manipulative.
Yesterday,
Cagney pretended to be hurt,
I went in to help her,
and Lacey snuck in the kitchen
and stole two cookies.
- Oh, my God.
Your children are monsters.
- Hey, those are my kids, man.
Back off.
- Right.
- And the crazy part is,
I really do want to go
to the water park,
but I can't give that to him
because it's the only card
I hold.
- Mm.
Elevator.
- Excuse me, NYPD.
Can I see your ID?
- Amy, behind the wheelchair.
- NYPD! Stop!
- Diaz for Jeffords.
- This is Terry.
- I think we got our guy.
Colombian man,
unarmed,
but he tried to run
as soon as we identified
ourselves.
And he's got a picture of Rojas
on his phone.
- We'll be right there.
- No one in or out
of this hallway.
Why do you think that guy
is unarmed?
- Who knows? Maybe he was
trying to smother Rojas
or unplug his life support.
- Or maybe he's a distraction,
and someone else is going
for the cookie jar.
- What?
- Hi, Pam.
- Hi, Jake.
Don't come any closer,
or I'll blow us both up!
- I'm sorry.
You weren't supposed
to be here.
This wasn't part of the plan.
- It's okay, Pam.
No need to panic.
We're just talking.
Look, I'm just gonna
put this away.
No, Terry,
don't open that, please.
- What's going on in there?
- There is a woman in here
with an explosive device.
- What? You okay?
- Yep. Everyone is fine.
I just need you to evacuate
this entire floor,
call ESU and the bomb squad
right away,
and jam all cellular
and Wi-Fi signals.
- On it.
- Okay, Pam, so we're just
gonna stay calm here
and talk this thing through
as friends.
- This isn't supposed to be
happening.
The man said that I'd be able
to sneak in here unnoticed.
- What man?
Who asked you to do this?
- I didn't get his name,
but he was very attractive.
Antonio Banderas could play him
in a movie.
What has he been doing lately?
You know what?
He should be on "Outlander."
- Okay, Pam,
I'm gonna cut you off,
but it's not because
I'm not interested.
- I'm sorry, I'm nervous.
I get chatty
when I get nervous.
- This man who gave you
the bomb,
did he happen to mention
whether or not it's on a timer
or if there's
a remote detonator?
- I don't know.
I'm terrible with electronics.
I wish my son Bobby were here.
He taught me how to iPad.
- Okay, I also know
how to iPad,
so maybe I could take a look.
- Stay where you are!
The man told me
that when I got the bomb set,
I should text him
with this phone
and if anything went wrong,
I should push this button.
- No, no, no, no!
You don't want to do that.
- Yes, I do.
I have to.
- Well, there's only one thing
to do when two people
have diametrically opposing
opinions on a subject.
Structured debate.
- What?
- Yeah, I just learned
about it.
All right, I will argue
the negative:
I don't want to blow up.
And you can argue
the affirmative:
you do want to blow up,
which I have to say, Pam,
is a very tough stance to take.
- I don't want to blow up,
but the man said
he'd give me $500,000.
This is so Bobby can take care
of my granddaughter.
That girl means the world
to me.
- Fine, fine.
Point to Pam.
But if you care about her
so much,
how can you just
blow yourself up?
You'll never get to see her
again.
- Well, at least I know
she'll be financially
well taken care of.
- Sure, but is this really how
you want her to remember you?
As a murderer?
- I'd rather be remembered
as a woman who blew up
a mobster to help her family
rather than a librarian
whose bowels are tied up
like a sailor's knot!
- Okay, that's a very strong
argument.
Very strong.
But you're forgetting
one thing.
You're not just gonna be
killing a mobster.
You're also gonna be
killing me.
- He said the blast would only
hurt people in the room.
You could just walk right out
of here.
- Pam, you know
I can't do that.
Now, please,
just give me the bomb.
- And then what?
Bobby doesn't get any money
and I go to jail?
I can't go to jail.
Every roommate I've ever had
has hated me.
In college, I had a roommate
named Mary-Ellen,
and she was dating the brother
of Steve Guttenberg—
- Pam, what are we talking
about here?
- I'm sorry.
I'm really nervous.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I know it probably feels like
you don't have a lot of options
right now.
In fact, this whole situation
probably feels like—
like a twisted bowel,
but it's not.
There's still one end
of this bowel that's open.
- Which end?
- The butt end.
- I'm listening.
- Okay, if you hand me
that bomb right now,
nothing bad will have happened,
and that'll be because of you,
because you cooperated.
Also, I'm sure a judge
would understand
how you got into
this situation.
I mean, you were asked
to do this
by an Antonio Banderas type.
Who could say no to that?
And even if you do go
to prison,
it is gonna be
such a fancy prison.
- With a lot of crafts?
- Yes, with tons of crafts.
Pam, listen to me.
Let's untwist this bowel
together.
Let's clear everything out.
- Okay.
You did great, Pam.
Thank you.
- Now that it's out
of my hands,
I can see it really is a bomb.
- Yes. Yes, it is.
- Oh, my God, get some help!
- Okay.
- You okay?
- Hey.
Yeah, I'm okay.
- Really surprised by Pam.
I did not see that coming.
- Right?
You should have seen
the look on my face
when I saw it was her.
- Your jaw just dropped.
- Oh, she's right there.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good-bye, Pam.
Good luck with everything.
Kind of liked her in the end.
- Yeah.
So did they defuse the bomb?
- Yeah, one of 'em.
Oh, you didn't hear?
There was a second bomb.
Ya butt.
Ya butt is da bomb.
- Aww.
On our anniversary.
Speaking of which,
I requested next week off
so we can take
an actual vacation...
to the water park.
- I've never been more in love
with you in my entire life.
And hey, I've been thinking,
and I do want to have kids.
With you.
- You're not scared anymore?
- Oh, no, I am so scared.
Maybe even more so than before,
but I was scared in there
with Pam too,
and you know, I didn't panic
or mess anything up there.
If anything, I was sharper.
I was a freakin' debate genius.
- Debate genius?
Oh, that's very hot.
- Oh, that's an added bonus.
Okay, keep that energy up.
But the point that I was
actually trying to make is,
maybe it's a good thing
that I'm scared of fatherhood.
You know? Maybe it'll turn me
into a freakin' dad genius.
But we don't have to start
trying right away, right?
I mean, I don't know
that I'm all the way there yet.
- No, of course not.
Whenever we're both ready.
- How do you know when that is?
- I guess we'll just
have to have another one
of these really fun,
casual conversations.
- Cool. Love that.
Can't wait.
Can we go home now?
- Yes, please.
Maybe we can grab
some Thai food
and brainstorm baby names?
- Ooh, I like that.
- Now, I am a fan of the show
"American Gladiators."
How do you feel about the name
Blaze Peralta?
- Not great.
- What about Laser?
- No.
- Nitro?
- Viper?
- No.
- Atlas?
- Ooh, I do love atlases.
- Mm, common ground.
- Fremulon.
- Not a doctor.
- Shh.