♪ Men. ♪
ALAN:
Fade in.
Exterior—night.
A dark, desolate prairie.
A lone cowboy sits
on a sturdy horse,
gazing up at the moon.
Suddenly, a flash of light
appears in the sky,
and a burning meteor
plummets to the Earth.
(typing)
(sighs)
Fade in.
Exterior— night.
New York City, Hell's Kitchen.
A lone cop sits
in a patrol car,
gazing up at the moon.
Suddenly, a flash of light
appears in the sky,
and a flaming meteor
plummets to the Earth.
All right.
Now we're cooking.
Alan?
Mia?
I thought that was you.
What a nice surprise.
Uh, didn't you move back
to New York with your husband?
We did, but then we split
up, and I came back here.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
I mean, not that you moved
back here,
but that it didn't work out.
So, how's Charlie doing?
Oh, he's fine.
Uh, actually,
he's engaged,
if you can believe that.
You're kidding.
No, no, she moved in
and everything.
Good for him.
Hmm!
So, where are
you living now?
What do you mean?
You know,
since Charlie's fiancée
moved in, I assumed...
You look great, Alan.
Thank you— you, too.
Please give Charlie my best.
Uh, will do.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
(typing)
Fade in.
Interior— coffee shop.
Night.
An unconventionally
handsome man
pounds away
at his lonely laptop,
writing the summer blockbuster
that will lift him
from poverty and put him
in a home of his own.
A beautiful woman
crosses to him.
Their eyes meet.
Suddenly, a flash of light
appears in the sky,
and a flaming meteor
plummets to the Earth.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
But I was looking forward
to having dinner with you.
All right, I'll see you later.
Yeah... love you, too.
(smacks lips)
"Love you, too."
Alan?
Yeah?
Smack your kid
for me.
Should we really risk
more brain damage?
Thanks for sticking
up for me, Dad.
Oh, hey.
You'll never guess
who I ran into.
Kobe Bryant?
No.
Lauren Conrad?
Sean "P. Diddy"
Combs?
What is wrong with you?
No, I ran into Mia
at the coffee shop.
You're kidding.
No, uh, apparently,
she's single again
and, uh, living in L.A.
What's wrong
with you?
So...
Mia.
How did she look?
Oh, better than ever.
Damn.
What did she say?
Uh, she said to
give you her best.
That's it?
Pretty much.
How did she say it?
What do you mean?
I mean, was it perfunctory
or was there subtext?
"Perfunctory."
That could be my rap name.
MC Perfunctory.
I don't know.
Um...
but I-I mentioned
that you were engaged,
and, uh, she seemed happy
for you.
You told her I was engaged?
Why the hell would you do that?
Because you are,
in fact, engaged.
And she seemed happy
about that?
Yeah, she said,
"Good for him."
How did she say it?
Was it perfunctory?
Or were there subtitles?
I'm leaving.
And yet the memory of him
lingers on.
Hey, Uncle Charlie.
Yeah?
Love you. (smacks lips)
To think I fought
for shared custody.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
so... so back to Mia.
Oh, don't tell me
you're still carrying
a torch for her.
No, I'm not carrying
Why, do you think
she's carrying a torch for me?
Charlie, you are engaged
to a wonderful woman.
Just forget about Mia.
I had forgotten about her.
I had forgotten
about her face...
her eyes...
her lips, her legs.
Oh, God, those legs.
You're the one
who brought her up.
Sorry.
Look, I'm the last one
to tell you
you can't have feelings
for an old girlfriend.
I mean, I myself still have very
strong feelings for Melissa.
Who's Melissa?
My receptionist.
Oh, right.
The one that caught you
in bed with her mom.
Uh, you're
leaving out a lot
of extenuating
circumstances, but...
yes, she caught me
rubbing against her mother.
And you want to compare
that freak show
to what Mia and I had?
I almost married her.
All I'm saying is,
you can acknowledge
your feelings for Mia
while still moving forward
with Chelsea.
That's exactly what
I intend to do.
Good.
It is good.
You're thinking about sex
with Mia, aren't you?
with Melissa, aren't you?
Trying to, but her mom
keeps popping in.
♪ Men. ♪
(sportscast plays on TV)
Okay, okay.
I'm just going to
come out and say it.
Baseball was better
with steroids.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, this guy
is leading the league
with 11 home runs.
Back in Sammy Sosa's day,
that was a slow weekend.
Mm-hmm.
Call me crazy, but...
I think people would
pay real money
to see a meat-covered
robot hit a ball 750 feet.
Mmm...
Okay, well...
Sportscenter is over.
Time for sex.
Charlie, please,
this report's due tomorrow.
All right.
I guess our relationship
is getting to that mature,
evolved stage they talk about.
Guess so.
Terrific.
I hope I die soon.
What?
Love you.
(toilet seat clanging)
(loud splashing)
Remember when you used
to close the door
and tried to hit the porcelain
so I didn't have
to hear you pee?
Yeah, way back when we used
to have sex after Sportscenter.
(phone ringing)
(loud splashing continues)
Hello?
Uh, hang on.
Charlie, there's a woman
named Mia on the phone.
(thudding, urine splashing)
Ow!
(groans)
Should I take a message?
No, no, no.
(toilet flushing)
Hello.
Oh, hey, Mia.
What a surprise.
Yeah, Alan mentioned
he ran into you.
Old friend.
Yes, yes, you heard correctly.
I am engaged.
Thank you.
Yes, that was her.
Oh, she's terrific.
And how are you?
Oh, I'm sorry
to hear that.
Well, there's plenty
more fish in the sea.
And I'm sure you'll
get out there
in that old dating pond
and catch something.
You know, a-a-a fish,
not a disease.
Anyway, thanks for
the good wishes.
Bye-bye.
Okay, well, good night.
Old friend, huh?
Yeah.
She heard I was engaged
and wanted to
congratulate me.
Sweet kid.
Is this the woman
you almost married in Vegas
a few years ago?
Charlie?
I'm thinking.
Charlie.
Who told you
about that?
Your brother.
Oh, really?
Did he tell you his
last girlfriend
caught him in bed
with her mother?
Yes, he did.
What a dirtbag, huh?
So, were you ever going
to tell me about Mia?
What's the point?
Have you told me about every guy
you've ever been with?
Actually, I have.
My boyfriend
in high school,
two guys in college
and the man I married.
That's it— four?
Back in your day, that
was a slow weekend, right?
It's not a competition, Chels.
So, why do you
think this Mia
is calling you
in the middle of the night?
Honey, it was
perfectly innocent.
She just called
to congratulate me
on our engagement.
No, she didn't.
She called to see
if you're happy.
She wants to know
if you're still available.
Really, you think so?
I mean...
Yes, I think so.
The question is:
are you happy?
Are you available?
Oh, come on, Chels.
What kind of
question is that?
No, I'm not available, and
I'm certainly not happy.
You know what I mean.
I hope so.
Yep.
I'm a happy
and lucky man.
Happy, happy, happy.
Lucky, lucky, lucky.
And wet.
I'm kind of wet.
♪ Men. ♪
What you writing?
A screenplay.
Cool.
Hey, I got a great idea for
a movie if you want it.
Thanks— I'm okay.
What is it?
Okay. So there's this
guy who's in an accident
on the highway, where he hits
like a moose or something.
And he loses
control of his car
and crashes into a truck
full of toxic waste.
And when he wakes
up in the hospital,
he's part car
and part animal.
Car-nimal.
Um... thanks, but I think
I'll stick with my idea.
Fine— what's your idea?
You really interested?
Sure.
Well, it's, uh...
it's about a man,
uh, who's at a crossroads
in his life,
uh, coming to terms
with, uh, loss
and... and mortality.
Huh.
You know what you
could call it?
What?
Boring.
Thank you.
Rated G... A-Y.
(doorbell rings)
Hey, Charlie.
Hey, Herb.
I'm here to pick up Jake.
Oh, come on in.
Jake, time to get the
hell out of my house!
So, how's it going?
Oh, pretty good.
Baby's coming any day now.
Judith's got that
glow of motherhood.
Gangway, I gotta
freakin' pee again.
Yeah, she's radiant.
Hey, Herb.
Jake's just finishing breakfast.
Or he could be starting lunch.
It's a fine line.
Well, he is a growing boy.
He's a growing
pain in my ass.
He says that with love.
No, I say it with a dull,
throbbing pain in my ass.
JUDITH:
Uh-oh.
What's the matter?
My water just broke.
Are you sure?
(yelling)
Yes, I'm sure.
I ain't cleaning that up.
♪ Men.
♪ Men
Boy, this brings back
memories, huh?
Shut up.
Slipping in Judith's
amniotic fluid.
Guess this'll be
pretty funny someday.
It's pretty funny
right now, Herb.
Hello?
A little help here!
Ding! Ding! Ding!
Hold your horses, I'm...
Dr. Harper?
Melissa, what are
you doing here?
I work here.
I had to find another job
after... You know.
For the last time, I did not
have sex with your mother!
Excuse me, I'm having
a baby here!
Yeah, and I think
I broke my ankle.
Quit whining, Herb!
Her doctor's
on his way.
The contractions are
about eight minutes apart.
Oh, well, let's
get you to prenatal.
I'll sign you in and have
an orderly take you upstairs.
No. No, No, no.
I'm the father.
I'll do it.
Bad idea, Herb.
I'm here, Judith.
Everything's okay.
Oh.
JUDITH:
Oh!
Whoa!
God.
My arm!
I'm coming, Judith!
Stay down, champ.
It's not your night.
Oh, my freaking God!
Now, you're not
breathing.
You got to
remember to breathe.
Good, good, good.
Okay. Now, you're only
two minutes apart.
So we're in the
homestretch here.
Great.
Boy...
It seems like just yesterday
we were at this same hospital
waiting for little Jake
to arrive.
Uh-huh.
I guess after pushing out
his enormous head,
this one will feel like spitting
a watermelon seed.
(moaning)
So anyway, I really
love my fiancée,
but I can't get this
other girl out of my mind.
I mean, she told my brother
to give me her best.
And let me tell ya,
her best
could curl your hair
and make your ass whistle.
Is that what
you're here for?
A whistling ass?
No-no, no.
There's a baby
and some broken bones.
Not important.
The thing is,
I know you can't expect
to keep the passion
of a new relationship
going forever,
but I kind of miss it.
Maybe it's just
that the grass
always looks greener,
you know?
You see this cooler?
Yeah.
It's carrying two light beers,
a half a ham sandwich
and my thumb.
So you'll excuse
me if I lack
a certain degree of interest
in your romantic dilemma.
You got beer?
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Now, focus on me.
Remember your breathing.
One, two, one,
two, one...
Dr. Harper?
Melissa.
I miss you.
Oh, I miss you, too.
Can we talk?
Of course.
Alan!
You're fine.
Just keep breathing.
Hey, Charlie!
Look at me.
I'm half man,
half machine.
Kind of like
Jake's movie idea.
Car-nimal!
It's okay, dude.
I'm going to hang here
for a while.
I love that guy!
What the hell
did they give you?
Oh, the good stuff.
You could pull out
every one of my teeth,
I wouldn't even notice.
They didn't, did they?
You're fine.
Okay, then.
Guess we should get going.
You drive, okay?
I'm pretty buzzed.
What about Judith?
No, let's not bring her.
She's a downer.
No argument,
but there is the baby.
Oh, my God... the baby!
Judith needs me.
I must go to her.
I'm coming, Judith!
I'm coming!
Hey, Charlie,
how'd you get here so quick?
Oh, I tried to forget you.
To hate you.
But I couldn't.
Really?
Most people don't have
that problem.
Beer and chips.
This is turning out okay.
Did you see where
my friend went?
He went hobbling down the hall,
mumbling about some Judith.
I better go warn
the villagers.
Good luck to you.
Thanks.
Oh, and hey.
Good luck to you, too.
(moaning, screaming)
Oh... God!
Oh... oh...
Oh...
Oh, there you are.
You seen Herb?
No, I haven't seen Herb!
Huh.
Chips?
No, I don't want any chips!
Okay.
I don't think
you're supposed to have beer.
Get out of here!
No problem.
Wait! Don't leave me!
I need someone to coach me
through my contractions.
All right.
(screaming)
Uh...
Way to go.
HERB:
Judith!
I'm coming!
See, I love Chelsea,
but you know, there
was a time I loved Mia.
(screaming
and panting)
Breathe.
All right, you're fully dilated.
I think it's time
to have this baby.
Okay, well...
good luck.
Don't you dare leave me!
(Judith screaming)
Judith, I'm here! Oh!
Whoopsie.
Think I broke my nose.
Three cheers for Demerol.
Hip-hip!
Hooray!
♪ Men. ♪
ALAN:
Interior— hospital
delivery room.
Day.
An unconventionally handsome
man looks down upon the baby
that might be his,
but which he can never claim.
Suddenly, a flash of light
appears in the sky
and a flaming meteor plummets
to the Earth.
See, that's me
holding the baby.
That's me and
the doctor.
That's me, Judith
and the baby.
Who's that?
Oh, that's just a guy who got
his thumb sewn back on.
I can't get over
how into this baby you are.
It was amazing.
The miracle of birth.
If Judith hadn't been there,
it would've been perfect.
So you're not against maybe
having one of your own someday?
I don't see why not.
Turns out, I like babies.
And as you know, I'm a longtime
fan of intercourse.
I know.
I got to get back to work.
Okay, I'll see you tonight.
Love you.
Love you, too.
Bye, Alan.
Bye.
How's the screenplay coming?
Great.
Still on page one?
Yeah, but now it really sizzles.
MIA:
Hi, Charlie.
Mia.
ALAN:
To be continued...