♪ Men. ♪
(woman coughing)
(woman honking nose)
Chelsea?
(congested):
Yeah?
You okay?
I think I'm coming down
with a cold.
(nose honking)
That doesn't sound
like a cold,
it sounds like quitting
time in Bedrock.
Do I feel hot to you?
Let me see.
Stop it.
You're supposed
to feel my head.
Yeah, but those babies are
my frame of reference.
(coughing)
Maybe I should go home.
Well, if you think that's
the right thing to do.
Charlie, it's the middle
of the night and I'm sick.
I'm not going home.
Then why'd you
say you were?
I was testing you.
Yeah, well, I knew that
and I was testing you.
I think we both
did very well.
(coughing)
Tell you what,
you get a good
night's sleep.
I'm sure you'll feel better
in the morning.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go crash on the couch,
let you have the whole bed
to yourself.
Really? You're gonna
leave me here alone?
No, no, I just thought you might
want your own space.
You know, when dogs are sick,
they hide till
they feel better.
Probably why they're
man's best friend.
Could you please stay?
Pretty please?
How can I say no?
(under breath):
Seriously, how?
Spoon?
Try and stop me.
(coughing and clearing throat)
So what, you're just
gonna swallow that?
Go to sleep.
What are you doing?
Come on, you know what
happens when we spoon.
I'm sick.
Obviously, so am I.
All right, fine.
Go ahead.
This is another
test, isn't it?
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Men. ♪
TV ANNOUNCER: Coming up next on
Turner Classic Movies:
The Bridges of Madison County.
I am not gonna cry.
Hey.
What are you doing up?
Watching a Clint Eastwood movie.
Chelsea's sick.
She was coughing and sneezing
all over the place.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I had to wait till she
finally fell asleep
so I could get the
hell outta there
without pissin'
her off.
How considerate.
What do you want
from me?
I'm not a big
phlegm fan.
(movie plays indistinctly)
This isn't a Clint Eastwood
movie.
Yes, it is.
Even Clint Eastwood
doesn't think
this is a Clint Eastwood movie.
Well, tough, I like it.
Sure, you do.
You're a giant fruit basket.
I'll never apologize
for my feminine side.
Boy, I hope she gets better
soon.
This sick stuff is not
what I signed on for.
You're kidding, right?
This is exactly
what you signed on for.
(broadcast stops)
You told Chelsea you loved her,
you gave her an engagement ring.
This is what it's all about.
Being there for her,
no matter what.
For richer or poorer,
better or worse,
in sickness and in health.
Call me crazy,
but I prefer richer,
better and health.
Well, regardless, this could
be a real opportunity for you.
Opportunity for what,
a massive infection?
An opportunity to show her
that she can depend on you.
That you're not just there
for the good times.
Okay, I hear that.
But tell me one thing.
Yeah?
What's in it for me?
Watch Clint and Meryl.
(broadcast resumes)
Learn how to love.
I'll take my chances
in the snot locker.
I will not cry.
♪ Men. ♪
CHELSEA (weakly):
Charlie?
You awake?
(sighs)
Boy, I hope not.
I feel awful.
Really?
You look swell.
I should go home.
No, no, no, no.
I am not falling
for that again.
You stay right here, let
me take care of you.
You mean it?
Oh, man, do I have
to mean it, too?
Just kiddin'.
Can I make you some
tea or something?
Yes, please.
Comin' up.
With honey?
Sure.
And maybe an English muffin.
No problem.
Toasted crispy.
Right.
And let the butter melt
into all the nooks and crannies
before you put the jam on.
Anything else?
Can I have a hug?
Try and stop me.
Nice necklace.
Thanks.
Buy it for yourself?
No, a girl gave it to me.
Really?
She must like you.
Yeah, she's nuts for me.
Well, is she cute?
I guess.
You, uh, you don't seem
very happy about it.
I'm not.
Why? What's the problem?
She's nine.
Nine?
Where would you meet a
nine-year-old girl?
We're in the same math class.
Is, uh, is she one of those
advanced students?
Sadly, no.
But she does help me
with my homework.
Hey, Berta, Chelsea's
not feeling well.
Could you make her some tea
and an English muffin?
Sure, I could.
But you won't.
Is that what you're saying?
Where are the
muffins?
In the fridge.
As always.
Don't condescend to me.
He does it to me all the time.
It's very irritating.
No one's talking to you.
See? Like that.
That wasn't condescending.
But that was, right?
Right...
Boy, as soon as I get my
license, I am so outta here.
Sure. You can drive your
girlfriend to Gymboree.
At least I have a girlfriend.
(mocking):
So what's the deal?
Does, uh, Chelsea have a cold?
I'm not sure.
Cold, flu, something disgusting.
Maybe she has an STD.
What?
It means "sexually
transmitted disease."
I know what STD's are.
Your uncle helped invent them.
You know, they can be prevented
by using a condom.
I know we could've prevented you
Now we gotta use a hammer.
I don't understand.
Go get me a hammer,
and I'll show you.
Okay.
You must be so proud.
JAKE:
Ball peen
or claw hammer?
Do me a favor,
when he comes back, just do it.
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, here we go.
Room service.
Chelsea?
Honey?
CHELSEA (congested):
Don't come in.
Wasn't even tempted.
I got your tea and muffins.
I have diarrhea.
I can't eat now.
I may never eat again.
Would you mind going
to the drugstore for me?
For you, I'd go to the ends
of the earth.
(under breath): Coming back's
a whole other question.
What?
I said, "What do you need?"
Well, I need Pepto,
and we're almost
out of tissues,
and I need some
decongestant,
some cough syrup,
something for canker sores,
and wet wipes.
For your hands?
No.
Got it.
And I'm probably gonna
need some tampons.
(under breath):
Oh, great.
There's gonna be blood, too.
You're really
being wonderful
about all this,
Charlie.
Oh, it's nothing.
It's what a guy does
when he loves somebody.
Should've known.
The second you give 'em a ring,
they fall out of warranty.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Russell?
Mm-hmm?
What's good
for canker sores?
You got canker
sores?
No, my girlfriend.
What do you recommend?
Tennis shoes.
Excuse me?
Put 'em on and run away.
There's a lot of
broads out there.
Find a clean one.
I-I can't run away.
I'm kind of engaged to her.
Oh, Charlie, no.
Yup. I bit the bullet.
You bit the big one.
Hey, just because you blew
three marriages doesn't mean
I can't make this work.
(laughs)
You're a funny guy, Charlie.
And that's not just
the Oxycontin talking.
Here you go.
Cank-B-Gone.
What else?
Uh, let's see.
Cough syrup.
Regular or codeine?
Don't you need a
prescription for codeine?
What are you, a cop?
Here.
I'll give you the kid stuff.
What else?
Uh, tissues,
throat lozenges,
decongestant,
Pepto, wet wipes.
Geez, where'd you find this one?
A hospital parking lot?
Come on, Russell, help me out.
Okay. Okay, here you go.
A dam for every river.
A plug for every jug.
Oh, right, I almost forgot.
She also needs tampons.
Oh, lucky you.
(laughing)
What size?
How should I know?
Is there some kind
of a condom-tampon
conversion chart?
No, but that's an amusing idea.
Actually, it's not
about size, per se.
It's more about flow.
Okay, see, that's a piece
of information
I could have gone the rest
of my life without knowing.
Here you go.
Here's a variety pack.
This'll handle anything
from a little drizzle
to a monsoon.
Listen, is it too late to change
my mind about the codeine?
The first one's free.
♪ Men. ♪
(coughing)
Okay, got all your stuff.
Took you long enough.
Whoa!
Whoa! I just went shopping
for wet wipes and tampons.
I'm allowed to take my time.
I'm sorry. Are you mad at me?
No. No.
Why would I be mad at you?
'Cause I'm sick,
and you have to take care of me.
Are you kidding me?
I love taking care of you.
I just... love...
it.
Yeah, I can see that.
Listen, could you go over
to my place
and get me some clean clothes
and feed Sir Lancelot?
Who?
My cat.
He's not gonna feed himself,
Charlie.
Are you sure?
Maybe you've got mice.
And you're probably gonna have
to change the litter box, too.
Change it into what?
You got to scoop out the poop
and put in fresh litter.
Oh, this just keeps
getting better and better.
Charlie?
Yeah?
I love you.
Great.
Aren't you gonna say it back?
I'm gonna go pan for cat turds.
If that doesn't say
"I love you,"
nothing does.
I promise, I'm wearing it.
Wait a sec.
Okay, I sent you a picture.
Now what's the answer
to number four?
Oh, yeah. That's what I had.
What you doing, Alan?
My taxes. I promised myself
I wouldn't wait
till the last minute this year.
Yeah, and you promised me
you'd only stay here
for a few days,
so your word means nothing.
Come on, you're driving me
to Chelsea's.
Why don't you drive yourself?
Because I just chugged
a half a bottle of codeine,
and this bourbon might make me
a bit of a threat on the road.
Ah, good call.
♪ Men. ♪
Here, kitty, kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Okay, I got
her clean clothes.
Great.
Now I just got
to feed the damn cat.
Come on, Sir Lancelot.
Come out and eat your kibble.
(cat yowling)
Oh!
Son of a bitch!
I'm pretty sure
if you just put the food out,
he'll find it and eat it
when he's hungry.
Really? You'd think
if he was that smart,
he'd just crap in the toilet
instead of a litter box.
Oh, uh, did you change
the litter yet?
No. I was actually gonna
offer you $20 to do it.
I'll take it.
Deal...
Ha, ha. I would have
done it for ten.
Ha, ha. I would have given you
a thousand.
Whoa. Big cat.
You know what I just realized,
Alan?
Cough syrup and hard liquor
don't mix?
No, they're
delightful.
I'm thinking that
sooner or later,
Chelsea's gonna want
to move in with me.
Yeah, if you marry her,
that's a chance you take.
And she's probably gonna
want to bring Sir Craps-a-lot.
You never know.
He might want
to get his own place.
I'm guessing he will
before you will.
Oh, Lord.
This cat's been eating more
than kibble.
This turd's got feathers.
You know, there's a real chance
that someday,
without any kind
of warning whatsoever,
Chelsea will up and decide
to get sick again.
And we're on the air
with codeine and bourbon.
Go ahead, caller.
I'm just saying, I don't think
I can go through it again.
I'm not cut out
to be a caregiver.
Well, you might not think so,
but you're doing it.
I mean, you, Charlie Harper,
are unselfishly taking care
of the woman you love.
Maybe so, but...
it's getting harder and harder
to love her.
You don't mean that.
Oh, Alan,
if you'd seen and heard
the things I have
in the last 24 hours, it'd turn
you gayer than a French horn.
Excuse me,
but I have witnessed childbirth.
I saw my son's enormous head
poke out
of what used to be one
of my very favorite places.
Thanks for the image.
I'll never be able to watch
the kid pull on a sweater again.
Trust me. If you hang in there
and show Chelsea
that you'll stick by her
even when she's not at her best,
she will love you more deeply
and intensely
than you ever
could have imagined.
And you know this how?
How else? Chick flicks.
Oh.
This is not a kitty cat.
This is a mountain lion.
Look.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
♪ Men. ♪
You need some more
orange juice?
No, thank you.
It was so nice of you
to bring some up
without me even asking.
Don't tell Charlie.
It's taken a long time
to train him not
to expect anything from me.
Yeah.
He really is crazy
about you, you know.
You think?
Are you kidding?
Charlie doesn't
go near sick women.
I mean, physically sick.
Around here,
one sneeze will get you cab fare
and a complimentary travel mug.
I have noticed
he's trying very hard.
Just remember,
when it comes to nurturing,
Charlie's like a dog
playing the piano.
You can't fault him
if he hits a few bum notes.
You just got
to applaud
the effort and hope he doesn't
whiz all over the keys.
I understand.
Thanks, Berta.
Just so we're clear,
this ain't no hotel.
You need more towels,
you get 'em yourself.
Sorry about that.
You really can't expect much
from her.
I won't.
Here. I got you
clean clothes and underwear.
The cat's fed,
and the litter box is turd free.
Thank you, Charlie.
You have been so wonderful
through all of this.
I have, haven't I?
I just want you to know
I am definitely
gonna make it up to you.
Chelsea, to be honest,
that's the only thing
that's kept me going.
Uh-oh.
Uh-oh, what?
(retching)
(splattering)
Oh, Charlie, I'm so sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
At least it's not wicker.
Excuse me a sec.
(loud retching
and splattering)
♪ Men. ♪
(coughing)
(loud nose blowing)
Okay, I am going to go
to the pharmacy
and get your
medicine.
If you get it from Russell,
count the pills.
Will do.
Hope you feel better.
Thanks.
Charlie, you don't mind
Sir Lancelot being here, do you?
No, not at all.
I love cats.
Good.
(coughing)
(door closes)
(scratching at door)
Don't scratch the door,
Sir Lancelot!
Did you clean my litter box?
Oh, come on. I've been sick.
Fine. I'll just use
your facilities.
Not in the tub this time, okay?
Your house, your rules.
(panting)
(sighs)
I'm not gonna make it.
(coughing)
Yes, you are.