Would you like
the last sausage?
Oh, how about
we split it?
Okay.
Meet you in the middle.
Oh.
Okay.
Sexy.
CHARLIE:
Aw.
Nothing says love like
a little morning pork.
Oh, hey.
You're home early.
How was Vegas?
(sighs)
Never again.
Oh, you lost?
No, Alan.
I won so much freaking money
that I'm embarrassed to go back.
All right... well, uh,
you remember Melissa?
Of course he
remembers me, Alan.
He deflowered me,
then dumped me.
No offense, sweetheart,
but your flower
had been plucked and potted
long before I met you.
Okay, okay, look.
Look, we're all adults here.
This doesn't have
to be awkward, you know.
I mean, sure... Melissa
is my receptionist,
and sure, she was with you,
and sure, that ended badly,
but, uh ...
Okay, I guess this does have
to be awkward.
Honey, shouldn't we
be getting ready for work?
Yes, yes, let's do that.
You want to shower together?
Oh, great, great.
Uh, let me just, uh,
start without you.
There's a couple of things
I'd like to prewash.
There's a mental image
I didn't need.
Charlie, I need to talk to you.
I'm sorry I was a jerk.
I'm happy for you and Alan,
and I will kick myself
for the rest of my life
for losing someone
as special as you.
No, silly, it's about
something else.
Oh, good, 'cause evenl
didn't believe that.
Alan's birthday
is next Saturday.
Really?
I don't think so.
Yeppers. He's gonna be 40.
Wow, that is so weird.
My baby brother's gonna be 40.
How old are you?
39.
That's what makes it so weird.
Anyway, I think
we should have a party for him.
Why?
Because it's an
important birthday,
and he deserves a big party
with all his friends
and loved ones.
All right... all right,
let's break this down.
You want him
to get what he deserves.
You want it to be
with his friends and loved ones,
and you want it to be big.
Uh-huh.
Pick one.
Come on, Charlie.
Don't be such a pooper.
If it's gonna be a fun party,
I need your help.
You want it to be fun?
Don't invite Alan.
Charlie...
Okay.
Okay, you know who would love
to help you out with this?
Our mom.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Nothing she likes better
than extending herself
for other people.
Good idea.
I'll give her a call.
You do that.
Wait till she hears Alan's 40.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Charlie.
Wake up.
I need to talk to you.
CHARLIE:
Don't move.
Don't blink.
Maybe she'll think you're dead
and leave.
I know you can hear me, Charlie.
She's bluffing.
Just stay still.
(nasally):
Okay, don't panic.
You've experienced
oxygen deprivation before.
I can't breathe, Mom.
Oh, good, you're awake.
What can I do for you?
I received a very unsettling
message on my answering machine,
and I would like you
to explain it to me.
Okay, look.
Sometimes the liquor
makes me say hateful things.
No, this message was from
some woman named Melissa.
Alan's receptionist.
Really?
From the sound of her voice,
I'd guess she earns her living
baking cookies in a hollow tree.
Anyway, she's somehow gotten it
into her head
that Alan is turning 40
on Saturday.
Yeah, so?
Is she insane?
Running around telling people
my son is 40?
I know.
She's a bad person.
That's not all.
She wants me to help
with a party.
Where in God's name
could she have gotten
such an idea?
Beats me.
Maybe the fact
that you're his mother
confused the poor girl.
(toilet flushing)
Oh, you're up.
You've been cleaning
in there this whole time?
Sure, let's say I was cleaning.
Hey, Uncle Charlie,
if you're going out today,
can I pull your car out
of the garage?
No, I don't want you pulling
my car out of the garage.
Okay, I won't.
From now on.
Hey, what's, uh...
what's going on up here?
Oh, terrific.
This meeting of the worst club
in the history of the world
can now come to order.
Madam President,
you have the floor.
Oh, I get it.
Sorry to interrupt.
Go back to what you
were planning...
uh, uh doing,
uh, whatever.
(chuckling)
Oh, uh, apropos
of nothing,
uh, I like red velvet cake
and close-up magic.
Oh, crap.
Now we have
to throw him a party.
Who?
Your father.
Why?
It's his birthday.
Oh.
Can I bring a date?
You got a date?
That depends.
On what?
Can I borrow your car?
You don't got a date.
♪ Men.
You know, we don't have
to go out to dinner
just 'cause
it's my birthday.
Don't be silly.
This is a very special night.
How many times do you turn 40?
In my family, three or four.
Well, the first time
is the one that counts.
Okay.
So... so, it's
just us, right?
Of course, it's just us.
Who else would it be?
I don't know.
My friends, family.
A close-up magician.
Oh, darn, what gave it away?
Well, when I left the house,
Jake was taking a shower,
uh, Charlie had on long pants,
and Berta said she had
to quit early
because she was going
to some loser's birthday party.
Oh, good, I had her down
as a "maybe."
Promise you'll act surprised.
♪ Men.
ALAN:
Oh!
Oh, my God,
what a surprise!
I don't know these people.
We have a private room.
Sorry.
(chuckling)
We got a private room.
Go back to your dinner.
Ooh, gazpacho.
This is so nice.
(loudly):
A private, intimate dinner
for just the two of us.
Oh, my God, you guys!
There's nobody here.
I don't understand it.
I told them
to be here an hour ago.
Yeah, well, what
are you gonna do?
My family are a bunch
of thoughtless,
selfish butt-wipes.
Surprise.
♪ Men.
MELISSA:
Evelyn, smile.
That's a keeper.
Listen, darling, are you going
to be cutting the cake soon?
Because, actually,
I have a real party to go to.
You can't go.
We haven't even done
the speeches yet.
Oh, of course.
Were we supposed
to write speeches?
For what?
For Alan.
Let him write
his own speech.
(glass clinking)
Uh, can I have
your attention, please?
I want to thank you
all for coming
to celebrate this
wonderful occasion.
I thought
it was Alan's birthday.
And now it's time
to say a few words
about the guest of honor.
I can think of a few words.
(chuckling)
Not only is he
a terrific doctor
and fantastic boss,
he is also good
and kind and smart
and funny... and...
a really swell kisser.
I can still hear you.
WOMAN:
Sorry I'm late.
I was burning a fatty
with one of the busboys
in the parking lot.
How are you?
Everyone, this is
my mother, Shelly.
Mom, this is Alan's
mother, Evelyn, and...
Sweetie, save your breath,
because I'm way too toasted
to remember a lot of names.
(giggling)
Ooh, bread.
All right, well, uh,
now that we're all here,
why don't we take turns
saying something
about Alan and how much
he means to us.
Okay, Jake, you
want to start?
No, I got to go make room
for cake.
Uh, Berta, why don't you
get the ball rolling?
Sure.
What the hell?
Zippy, I got to tell you,
when you first moved in,
I didn't really care for you.
(chuckling)
You were a persnickety,
self-righteous,
smug son of a bitch.
And now
here we are, six years later.
Thank you.
Hear, hear.
Oh, okay.
Anyone else?
SHELLY:
Okay.
I'll go.
I have pictures of myself
dressed in a forest ranger
uniform,
and I have absolutely no memory
of ever working
as a forest ranger.
Thank you.
All righty.
Uh, who's next?
Evelyn?
Me?
Isn't it enough
I carried him
for seven and
a half months?
You'd be surprised
how many women
opt for the full nine.
Come on, Evelyn, you
have to say something.
Oh, fine.
Alan, darling.
You were always
the good son.
Of course, your brother
didn't set the bar very high.
Hear, hear.
Wait a minute.
Charlie, do you want
to say anything?
Uh, all right.
(clears throat)
Alan, you're my little brother.
And I know
over the years
I've tormented you.
I've embarrassed you in public.
I've tied you
to streetlights, car bumpers,
the occasional angry animal...
Oh, remember that Fourth of July
when I used your ass
as a launch pad
for my bottle rockets?
(chuckles)
Anyway, I guess
what I'm trying to say is...
thanks for the memories.
That's it?
That's all you
have to say?
I suppose I could talk
about his bed-wetting.
You people are horrible.
No. Honey, it's okay.
No-no-no-no,
it's not okay.
You should be ashamed
of yourselves.
This is a warm
and wonderful human being
and he deserves more,
especially from his family.
I don't even know why you
guys showed up tonight.
Well, I can't speak
for anybody else,
but I'm getting overtime.
Come on, Alan.
We're leaving.
Really? Before the cake?
You don't need people
who don't appreciate you.
Uh, well, no, but I do
kind of need Charlie's house.
No, you don't.
You'll come live with me
and Mom. Right, Mom?
You know, I did spend a summer
in Yosemite doing shrooms,
so maybe I wasn't
an official forest ranger.
Let's go.
Mom, we're leaving.
Okay.
I'm sorry. This is
the best bread I ever had.
Who likes magic?
I shaved for this?
♪ Men. ♪
Berta?
Who's asking?
What's wrong?
Too much celebrating last night.
I didn't notice you
drinking at Alan's party.
No, afterward.
With the magician at his place.
You went back to his place?
Well, technically, his van.
Well, why didn't you
just stay home?
If I stay home,
you don't pay me.
So you just came in
to lie on my couch?
Tough times, Charlie.
Some people are living
in their vans.
(phone ringing)
Oh, make it stop!
Hello?
Hi, Mom.
Alan? Nah, he didn't come home.
You're right.
We were funny.
He just overreacted.
I'm sure
he'll come back eventually.
He always does.
You should've named him
"Herpes."
Yeah, I wish I'd thought
of it last night, too.
Talk to you later.
So what are we going
to do today?
Aren't you going
to ask about your dad?
What about him?
Were we not at the same party
last night?
Did you not notice
when you finally came out
of the toilet
that your father was gone?
You know,
now that you mention it...
Herpes, Jr.
Oh.
Look who's back.
I'm not back.
I just came to get my stuff.
You're really going
to milk this thing, huh?
I'm not milking anything,
Charlie.
There is no milk.
I'm moving in with Melissa
and her mother.
Sounds like milk to me.
I need to be someplace
where I'm appreciated,
someplace where
I'm nurtured and loved.
(mooing)
You're not taking me
seriously, are you?
Oh, come on, Alan.
You ain't going anywhere.
You know it. I know it.
The seagulls out there
crapping on my deck know it.
"You think he'll be back?"
"Oh, yeah."
No, no. This is it.
This is where I cut the cord!
Oh, man.
I think David Copperfield
slipped me a roofie.
♪ Men. ♪
I really appreciate you
taking me in like this.
Yeah, we love you, Alan.
We want you here.
You're a good man,
and you have a beautiful soul.
It is beautiful, isn't it?
God forbid my family
should notice.
Oh, damn, I knew
I'd forget something!
What'd you forget?
My son.
Well, that's no problem.
We'll just move Mom's
hydroponic equipment
out of the garage
and make a bedroom for him.
"Hydroponic equipment"?
I'm a bit
of a horticulturist.
A little herb garden.
Ah, okay.
Well, uh, uh,
just a heads-up,
I love my son and everything,
but he hasn't quite gotten
to "beautiful soul" yet.
He's more "methane cloud."
He's still one
of God's flowers.
All he needs is a little love,
ultraviolet light, potassium
and he'll grow
into some righteous chronic.
♪ Men. ♪
(snoring lightly)
Quitting time.
(TV playing music)
What are you doing here?
I'm watching TV.
Why didn't you go
with your dad?
Dad was here?
Yeah, he came by
to get his stuff
and I figured that included you.
I'm not stuff, Uncle Charlie.
I'm a human being.
Don't flatter yourself.
And turn off the TV.
I'm taking you
back to your mom's.
Mom and Herb are in Mexico.
For how long?
I don't know.
Turn off the TV.
I'm taking you to Mexico.
Can I drive?
♪ Men. ♪
You all comfy, cozy?
Uh-huh.
Mom made you
some hot chocolate.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, and it's got
those little marshmallows.
I love those.
Good. I'm going
to the market.
What would you
like for dinner?
Oh, gosh, I don't know.
What do you want?
I want to please you.
Really?
No one's ever said that
to me before.
Get used to it.
(sobs)
I'll try.
Now, what can I get you?
Um, well...
you know the macaroni
that's shaped like
the little wagon wheels?
I do.
I like that with melted cheese.
You got it.
Oh, and maybe a couple of those
bottled wine spritzers?
Okeydoke.
(door closes)
♪ I'm getting mac
and spritzers ♪
♪ I'm getting
mac and spritzers. ♪
Here you go, bright eyes.
I made you some banana bread.
Aw, really?
Mm-hmm.
Banana bread?
Oh, thank you.
Wow, it's still warm.
Mmm, right out of the oven.
Mmm. Oh, that's, uh,
that's very unusual.
Uh, I'm tasting bananas
and, uh, what is that, nutmeg?
Nope.
Mmm, that's good.
You know what?
You might want to just start
with half a piece.
I can't believe it.
Believe what?
I think I miss him.
Miss who?
Your father.
Oh.
What about you?
What about me what?
Do you miss him?
Who?
Your father.
Why? Where is he?
♪ Men. ♪
Honey, they didn't have
any spritzers, so I got you
7Up and sangria.
♪ Nights in white satin
♪ Never reaching the end
♪ Letters I've written...
Alan?
Oh, hey, baby.
Have you tried
your mom's banana bread?
♪ Men. ♪
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
I'm back.
I'm shocked.
Hey, Alan?
Yeah?
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
I told you he'd be back.
Who?