♪ Men. ♪
I know you hate it when
I review the game tapes,
but that was one for
the highlight reel.
"The highlight reel"?
Yeah, you know,
"best of" moments
for deathbed reflections.
Only in your memory, right?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I got rid of the camcorder
like I promised.
Good.
It's a shame.
The camera
really loves you.
Shut up, Charlie.
I'm not just saying that.
Even from unflattering angles,
you light up the screen.
Oh, I hate you.
That's too bad,
'cause I love you.
Really?
Um... actually,
yes.
Yes, I do.
I love you, Chelsea.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Thank you.
(door closes)
No, no, thank you.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Morning.
Always got to make a comment,
don't you?
Oh, my.
Fitful night's sleep
on Alcohol Island?
Keep it up, funny man.
You're going to be homeless,
wearing a tube top
and turning tricks
on Santa Monica Boulevard.
Wow.
What crawled in your keister
and built a nest?
You want to know?
You really want to know?
I've fallen in love
with Chelsea.
Oh. Well, why are you so upset?
Love is a beautiful thing.
Beautiful thing, my ass.
And we're back
in your keister.
Last night, in bed,
I told her I loved her.
And you know what she said?
Uh... "I'm still not going
to let you do that"?
She said, "Thank you."
Ooh, that's an ice cube
to the man sack.
I don't get it.
I've gone the whole nine yards
for this relationship.
I gave her her own drawer
in my bedroom.
I stopped smoking cigars
after sex.
I even started seeing a shrink
so I can be more sensitive,
and I still can't get a freaking
"I love you."
But you've obviously
become more sensitive.
For what I've spent on therapy,
I could get a couple
of very expensive hookers
who will say anything I want.
There's that sensitivity again.
Look at the bright side.
What's the bright side?
Well, when women do tell you
they love you,
it usually ends with them
tossing a lit road flare
through your bedroom window.
That happened one time.
Why can't you just be grateful
for what you've got?
What do I got?
Oh, a woman who may not proclaim
her love for you,
but who doesn't try
to set you on fire
while you're sleeping.
One time.
Okay.
A woman who may not
proclaim her love for you,
but who doesn't steal
your Mercedes
while you're passed out
in the backseat
and drive it
into the Pacific Ocean.
Another isolated incident.
I believe I've made my point.
I'm sorry, Alan.
But not being drowned or burned
by the woman I love
is not enough for me.
I want more.
Oh, sure.
Reach for the stars.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Charlie,
how's it going?
Boy, you really blew it
this time.
Did I now? How so?
I've fallen in love
with Chelsea.
Ooh, my bad.
Damn right, your bad.
There were plenty of medications
that would've turned me
into a happy little potato,
but would you prescribe them?
No!
You said I had to get in touch
with my feelings
and express them
to the people I care about.
Sorry, I must've been drunk.
No. No, it's too late
for excuses.
I'm sensing something happened
with Chelsea.
Oh, you're good.
There's no sliding anything
past you.
Hey,
last night I dreamt
I was a giant hot dog
jumping through a doughnut
that looked like my mother.
What do you suppose that means?
All right, Charlie,
you've made your point.
Now, tell me what happened.
We can go back to the doughnut
dream later.
It wasn't a real dream.
I was being sarcastic.
Oh, I know, but the fact
that you chose
that particular imagery
is a little troubling.
Now, what happened
with Chelsea?
I told her I loved her,
and you know what she said?
This process isn't really about
me guessing, Charlie.
She said, "Thank you."
Interesting.
How did that make you feel?
No, no, no, no, no!
No more feelings.
We tried it your way.
Now, just take out
your little prescription pad
and start scribbling.
You don't need medication,
Charlie.
You're actually making
tremendous progress.
Are you not listening
to a thing I say?
I drift in and out.
Look, the fact that
you're upset about this
tells me you've come
a long way from the guy
who first walked
into this office.
The guy who first walked
into this office
was a happy-go-lucky,
fully-functioning man whore
and I want him back.
I'm guessing
you don't mean that.
Oh, now you're guessing?
A minute ago it was, "That's not
how the process works."
A minute ago, it didn't.
So are you still seeing Chelsea?
Well, of course
I'm still seeing her,
but now the relationship's
totally screwed.
Why is that?
She knows I love her.
The whole balance of power
is completely out of whack.
Huh.
Okay, I really don't like it
when you give me the "huh."
Huh.
Now, you're just
screwing with me, right?
There's no sliding
anything past you.
So let's talk about
this whole balance of power
issue of yours.
What about it?
Why do you look at relationships
as a power struggle?
'Cause that's what they are.
Is that how you saw
your parents' relationship,
as a power struggle?
Oh, there was no struggle.
My father sat very quietly
while my mother
sucked the life out of him.
I see, and you're terrified
of that happening to you.
No, I'm looking forward to it.
In fact,
I'm thinking about having
a nozzle attached to my heart
to make the sucking
more convenient.
Let me ask you something.
What would it take for you feel
that things were back in balance
with Chelsea?
Simple. She has to tell me
she loves me.
Even if she doesn't feel it?
It's even better if she
doesn't feel it.
'Cause that means
she's only saying it
'cause she's afraid to lose me.
Wow.
"Wow"?
What's "wow"?
Kind of like "huh,"
but with a "wuh" and an "ow."
Charlie, I would suggest
that you forget about
getting the "I love you" back
and focus more
on what it feels like
to give love,
maybe for the first time
in your life.
You know, I can get the drugs
without you.
I've got a nephew
in junior high.
Do what you got to do.
Now, let's get back to that
mom-shaped doughnut of yours.
♪ Men. ♪
So you really told her
you loved her?
Yeah.
Were you loaded?
No.
Were you trying to get her to do
something kinky?
No.
Did she catch you doing
something kinky
to somebody else?
No.
By yourself?
Then I don't get it.
What was your angle?
My angle was I love her.
Huh.
Why does everybody go "huh"?
What's with the "huh"?
We always knew
this day would come.
What day?
The day you stopped manipulating
and conning women.
The day you dropped your guard
and let an honest emotion
into your heart.
Well, that's a good day, right?
If you don't mind being
some broad's prison bitch.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
I can't keep seeing her,
'cause the relationship's
completely out of balance,
and I can't stop seeing her
because I love her.
I feel for you.
I once loved a guy,
didn't love me back.
What did you do?
90 days in County.
Plus anger management classes,
which by the way, are a total
freaking waste of time.
(music playing on TV)
Hey.
Have you ever been in love?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Alan.
ALAN
Ocupado!
I got it! I got it!
I know how to restore
the balance of power
with Chelsea.
Excuse me!
What part of "ocupado"
don't you understand?
The "ocu" or the "pado"?
I understood it all.
I was just hoping
you were shaving.
Well, I'm not!
And as you well know,
this is an uphill battle for me,
even in the best
of circumstances.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
but this is important.
I'm going to get an "I love you"
from Chelsea.
If you let me finish,
you'll get one from me.
Check this out.
Oh, Charlie, this is so sudden.
If you wait a few minutes,
I'll have a gift for you.
I'm going to marry Chelsea.
Are you serious?
Serious enough to ignore
what's going on
right in front of me.
Well, congratulations...
I guess.
Thank you.
Let's see her not say
"I love you" now.
Let's see what marriage
does to his bowels.
♪ Men. ♪
How's your salmon?
Delicious.
And this is such
a romantic restaurant.
I'm glad you like it.
Have you been here before?
No.
Yes.
Well, a couple times.
A lot.
I know you've dated other women.
Why would you lie?
Survival instinct.
Same reason I don't drink
in the bathtub anymore.
What else have you lied
to me about?
I don't know.
What else haven't you believed?
You're awful.
Awful good, right?
Yeah.
Excuse me,
I have to powder my nose.
Okay, who's lying now?
(quietly):
Bobby.
Is everything all right,
Mr. Harper?
Yeah, terrific. Listen,
my date's in the ladies' room
and I need you
to do something for me.
Not a problem.
I'll have the valet bring
your car around to the alley.
I'll open the men's restroom
window so you can shimmy out.
And I'll have a cab standing by
to take the lady home
along with the customary
chocolate soufflé to go.
No, no, no,
I'm not breaking up with her.
I'm going to ask her
to marry me.
I think we need
to get some coffee in you.
I'm not drunk.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
As always.
All I need you to do is bring
a bottle of champagne,
pour a glass for her
and a glass for me,
then distract her so I can slip
the ring into her glass.
Oh, how charmingly original.
You've seen that before?
Never.
Here she comes.
Go get the champagne.
I'll keep the bathroom
window open just in case.
Charlie, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
Okay.
The other day
when you said you loved me,
I didn't really respond.
Yes, you did.
You said, "Thank you."
You were very courteous.
It's not that I don't have
strong feelings for you,
it's just that
taking that extra step
is really hard for me.
Well, don't worry about it.
I'm sure you'll take that step
when it's appropriate.
Oh, look, champagne.
Ooh, is it a special occasion?
Every night with you
is a special occasion.
I'm going to miss you, sir.
(mouthing words)
Oh, dear.
I hope I'm not having
a massive coronary.
Oh, my God,
are you all right?
I'm not sure.
Yes, I'm fine.
(sotto voce):
The one waiter in L.A.
who's not an actor.
What?
Nothing. Nothing.
A toast.
To saying what we feel.
What the hell
did I just swallow?
A one-bedroom condo.
What?
I put a diamond ring
in your champagne glass.
Why?
What do you mean "why?"
I was going to propose
and I had no idea you'd chug it
like a Jell-O shot.
That was a ring
I just swallowed?
Who drinks champagne like that?
I was thirsty.
Stop yelling at me!
How in God's name could you
swallow it so easily?
Hey, that's one of the things
you love about me!
Problem?
No problem. Go away.
Car's outside, window's open.
Let's go.
Where?
The emergency room.
Why?
Because I have a ring
in my stomach!
Oh, don't worry about that.
You'll be fine.
How do you know?
When Jake was little,
he swallowed
a handful of nickels.
Nothing bad happened.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
He still shoots one out
every now and then.
Bets me heads or tails.
Just between you and me,
I'm not even sure
they're the same nickels.
Trust me.
A couple cups of coffee
in the morning,
problem solved.
I suppose you're right.
So, what do you say?
What do I say about what?
I asked you to marry me.
No, you didn't.
Well, I was about to
until you ruined the moment.
I ruined the moment?
Okay. Okay, there's no sense
in assigning blame.
The point is, I'm proposing.
You want to marry me.
Yes. I love you.
Oh... I don't know what to say.
Say you love me
and you'll marry me.
Gee, Charlie, you're kind
of putting me on the spot here.
Yeah, well, that's kind of built
into the whole proposal concept.
Oh, come on, just say it
so we can be even.
"Even"?
Is that what this is about?
Some kind of power thing?
N-no, no, no.
I meant so that
we could be even... closer.
Right.
Okay, that was lame.
But don't blame me,
blame my shrink.
What?
If I was properly medicated,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
Boy, this keeps getting
more and more romantic.
Look, do you love me or not?
I guess so.
No guessing.
That's not how
the process works.
All right, I love you.
Oh, great! Great, good.
That's all I wanted.
But I won't marry you.
What? Oh, yeah, right.
That's okay, no biggie.
I just got out of a marriage.
I'm not ready to do it again.
That's fine.
I understand.
I'm not saying "no,"
I'm just saying "not now."
Hey, "not now" is
my favorite time for a wedding.
The important thing
is that we love each other.
Right.
Equally.
Yes.
Fifty-fifty.
If it means that much to you.
Come on, say it again.
"I love you."
No.
Why not?
I want to see the ring first.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Berta?
Where do we keep
the spaghetti strainer thingie?
It's called a "colander."
What do you need it for?
It's not for me.
It's for Chelsea.
Okay, what kind
of Martha Stewart freak show
you got going up there?
Trust me, you don't need
the details.
I don't want the details.
I just need to know
whether to wash it
or throw it away
when you're done.
Oh, I think you'll want
to throw it away.
Morning.
Hey, Alan.
Congratulate me.
I'm kind of engaged.
So she said "yes"?
Not exactly.
You gave her the ring, right?
Yep.
Well, what did she say?
(gagging)
You had to be there.
Okay.
So, have you set a date?
For what?
The wedding.
What wedding?
Nobody's getting married.
I'm just engaged.
When do we get to see
this rock?
Well, Chelsea just finished
her second cup of coffee,
so I'd guess...
15, 20 minutes.
Anybody understand
what that was all about?
I think Chelsea
swallowed some nickels.
♪ Men. ♪
Chelsea?
CHELSEA:
Yeah?
You've been in
there for awhile.
How's it going?
Just fine.
You need any help?
I brought Alan's
little poop stool.
Go away!
All right, all right.
But just remember,
when you hear
a metallic clink, stop.
I think I can
handle it.
I'm just saying, it's not
on my homeowner's policy yet,
so if you flush it
by mistake, I'm screwed.
Charlie, I swear
if you don't walk away
from that door,
I will eat
a block of cheese
and you will never
see that ring again!
Okay, I'm walking.
Good.
Love you.
Don't push it,
Charlie!
Right back at you.
(clinking)
Oh, Charlie,
it's beautiful.