♪ Men. ♪
And how are you
this morning, Danny?
Well, I didn't sleep
very well last night, Alan.
I had nightmares.
Nightmares. Nightmares.
I dreamed I ate
a five-pound marshmallow.
A five-pound
marshmallow?
Yeah, and when I woke up,
my pillow was gone.
Pillow was gone.
Pillow. T-Tillow.
Pil... tillow. Pftil...
Alan?
Yeah?
You're starting to scare
the crap out of me.
Oh, oh, this?
This is, uh,
just a new hobby.
Charlie, say hello
to Danny O'Day.
Howdy-do, Charlie.
That's not a hobby.
That's a cry for help.
Oh, come on, Charlie,
play along.
So, Charlie, how did you
sleep last night?
With a woman, Alan.
Something you need to do
before this gets out of hand.
Wow.
He's got a stick
where I've got your hand.
Did you ask him
if he wants to go
to the movies with us?
No.
Why not?
Because he's a ticking time bomb
and we don't want to be
in the car with him
when he goes off.
Come on,
he's breaking my heart.
Staying home all alone
on a Friday night.
Don't worry.
You know how they say
you can be alone
but not lonely?
Yeah.
Well, Alan's kind
of the opposite.
He's always lonely
but he's never alone.
He's going through a tough time.
Your brother should
be surrounded
by friends and family.
My brother should be surrounded
by a SWAT team.
Please? For me?
Chelsea, we agreed that you only
get one of those a month.
Are you sure you want
to waste it on Alan?
Thanks for letting me
tag along with you.
This is really sweet.
We're thrilled
you could join us.
Right, Charlie?
Yippee skippy.
So have we picked a movie yet?
Nope. Would you
like to see
La Poubelle et le Fromage
at the Nuart?
Would I?
Who you calling
"wood eye"?
Big ears.
Now, Danny,
watch your mouth.
Why? Yours is the one
that's moving.
(Chelsea and Alan laugh)
Yippee skippy.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Men. ♪
(woman and man speaking French
on movie screen)
If she goes back to him
after what he's done,
I will never
forgive her.
She loves him.
What choice
does she have?
Oh, she can return
to her husband,
the cheese maker.
Listen, I'm going
to hit the head.
Let me know if any
kind of a plot
ever kicks in.
He's not coming
back, is he?
They sell beer
in the lobby?
Yes.
No.
♪ Men. ♪
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
(mimics rooster call)
You're up early
for a Saturday morning.
Hence the cock-a-doodle-doo.
(knocking)
ALAN:
Chelsea, it's 7:30.
We got to get
a move on.
Oh, God, that's right.
I forgot.
Give me a few minutes
to get dressed.
No problem.
I'll wait for
you downstairs.
What's going on?
Your brother and I are going
to the farmers market.
Since when?
We made plans
last night.
Last night when?
In the movie theater,
while you were sitting
in the lobby drinking.
Well, I wasn't going to go
sit in the car
with that scary dummy.
I like mustard,
and pickles,
and ketchup,
and mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise.
You and me need to talk.
Howdy-do, Charlie.
Get that ugly thing
out of my face.
That's what she said.
Oh, Danny.
Danny, you're horrible.
My hand to God, Alan,
I will wrap
that dummy with meat
and throw him in the ocean.
Don't forget
the mayonnaise.
Ow!
I'm okay.
Why are you taking Chelsea
to that farmers thing?
Is there a problem?
Yeah, there's a problem!
You're ruining my Saturday.
I'm sorry.
Did you have plans for the day?
Damn right I had plans.
First, I was going
to have sex with Chelsea.
And then...
Well, then I was going
to go back to sleep.
Well, you can still
go back to sleep.
Yeah, but without sex,
it's a restless sleep.
Fine, fine,
I'll just go by myself.
No, no,
if you go without her now,
then I'm the bad guy.
So what do you want me to do?
In the future,
I want you to try to be
more sensitive and considerate
to other people's needs.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to join Chelsea
in the shower and try
to knock out a quick one.
Oh, Danny...
Sometimes he can
be such a pig.
Well, you know what
happens to pigs.
They get slaught...
Danny, don't say it.
Don't even think it.
ered.
♪ Men. ♪
(sportscast playing on TV)
What are you looking at?
Nothin'.
Oh, hey! Hey.
What are you doing here?
I thought you were
spending the weekend
with your mom and Herb.
Yeah, I was supposed to,
but Mom's got
all those pregnancy
hormones going.
What did you do?
One little fat joke.
Took it badly, eh?
Well, here I am.
Where's Dad?
He went out
with Chelsea.
You mean like a date?
No, no, not a date.
Good, 'cause
that'd be weird.
Yeah.
I saw something like that
on Jerry Springer once.
Two brothers, one girl—
it got ugly.
I'm sure it did.
So what's Dad's dummy
doing here?
He pissed off his mother.
Oh.
Hey, I did that, too.
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, please take this
kettle corn away from me.
I can feel it going
right to my behind.
Oh, stop it.
I wish my tush
was as small as yours.
Okay, first of all,
you have a perfect heinie.
And secondly, if you're
worried about firmness,
the secret is
isometric glute crunches.
Really?
Yeah, you can do
them anywhere, anytime.
I'm doing them
right now. See?
Mailbox open, mailbox closed.
Mailbox open,
mailbox closed.
Come on, try it with me.
BOTH:
Mailbox open, mailbox closed.
Mailbox open,
mailbox closed.
Mailbox open, mailbox...
You know, just once
I'd like to walk in this room
and not be freaked out.
Alan was just showing
me his butt exercises.
Have him show you the one where
he sticks his head up there.
That's my favorite.
Stop it.
Now, go away,
we're making dinner.
It's kind of like a Kegel
exercise, isn't it?
Exactly.
Except with the tush,
not the hoo-ha.
What up, homes?
What are you doing?
Enjoying the sunset,
waiting on dinner.
You're staying for dinner?
I wasn't gonna,
but your lovely fiancée
and her new gal pal insisted.
Yeah, I've got to put
a stop to that.
What are you, nuts?
This is the perfect
setup for you.
How do you figure?
Do you like
to go shopping?
No.
Zippy does.
Do you like to watch
chick flicks?
No.
Zippy does.
Do you like
to talk for hours
about your feelings?
No.
Zippy do.
Oh, right.
He digs the trench,
you lay the pipe.
How could I not see this?
Alan's not the competition.
He's her gay friend.
There you go.
Your life is perfect.
It is, isn't it?
Yeah. Now, be an
angel and get me
another beer.
Absolutely.
(door opens)
(door closes)
Jiminy, I'm drunk.
♪ Men. ♪
(TV playing)
Oh, I hate
to do this to you.
Uh, but using the existing "S"
in the top row,
with R-E before it
and I-Z-I-N-G after it,
hitting two triple word scores,
and it's a bingo.
"Resizing."
120 points.
Oh, my God.
You play for
blood, don't you?
Let me tell you something,
Chelsea.
When it comes to Scrabble,
nice guys finish
with a rack full of tiles.
(turns off TV)
(yawns)
CHELSEA:
What do you mean
it's not a word?
ALAN:
I mean it's not a
word. Try again.
Hmm.
Charlie horny.
Another glass of wine?
I would love one.
(giggles) Now?
But Alan and I are
playing Scrabble.
(chuckling):
Well, I'm playing Scrabble.
I don't know whatshe'sdoing.
I'm improving,
is what I'm doing.
I want a rematch.
Good night, Alan.
But I just poured wine.
Oh, thanks.
And thanks for being such
a good friend to Chelsea.
You don't have
to thank me.
I like her, and we've got
a lot in common.
Yeah, whatever—
just keep it up,
and I'll try
to do the same.
Kind of ruined the night.
He's using you.
(chuckling)
I know, but what
am I going to do?
You could... kill him.
Now, Danny,
I-I could never do that.
Don't worry, Alan.
I can do it for you.
♪ Men. ♪
Morning.
Hope you're hungry—
I made pancakes.
Oh, I'm starving.
Can I help?
Uh, sure, slice
up some bananas
and warm up the syrup.
I'm on it.
Sleep well?
Yeah.
I mean, when your brother
finally let me go to sleep.
(forced chuckling)
Can I tell you a little secret?
Sure.
He's the best lover
I've ever had.
Oh, isn't that nice.
Yeah, it's great,
but sometimes he doesn't know
when to quit.
Have you tried pepper spray?
No.
But every once in a while,
I actually have
to give him a little smack
on the top of his head.
Yeah, I have the same problem
with Jake
when he eats spaghetti.
I mean, obviously not
the same problem.
Jake's head is
usually over here.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not complaining,
but it can be exhausting.
I can imagine.
Have you given Charlie
enough attaboys?
Attaboys?
You know,
like when you're training a dog.
If you don't give them
a lot of hugs
and a treat every now and then,
they're gonna chew up your rug.
I mean, not your rug.
Hey, how are those
bananas coming?
Morning.
How'd you sleep?
Good.
When you finally let me.
Hush.
Alan's making pancakes.
Can I pour you
some coffee?
I would love that.
Good morning,
Mrs. Butterworth.
(forced chuckling)
Ooh.
Lakers-Spurs today.
Charlie, you promised we'd go
to the Van Gogh exhibit.
I did?
Yes.
Wow, I don't remember that.
You got to quit hitting me
on the head so much.
Yeah, I have heard that exhibit
is supposed to be terrific.
I've been dying
to see it.
Really?
Then why don't we all go?
I can't. I promised Jake
we'd do something.
Bring him along.
What 14-year-old boy
doesn't love a fine art museum?
I think
that's a great idea, Alan.
You and Jake come with us.
Well, if you don't think
we'd be intruding.
No. No, not at all.
Okay, great.
Well, save me some pancakes.
I'm going to jump
in the shower and get ready.
Hurry! I want to get to the
museum before it's too crowded.
All right,
here's the deal.
You're gonna have to go
to the museum without me.
Why?
I am about
to get an acute case
of intestinal distress.
What?
You know...
the flapjack two-step.
But there's nothing wrong
with my pancakes.
No, they're delightful.
But the Lakers are playing
the Spurs,
and I'm not gonna miss it.
So what? So you're just gonna
use me to entertain your fiancée
while you stay home
and watch a basketball game?
Good. We're on the same page.
Hey, did you ever stop to think
that maybe
I've got plans of my own?
That I've got a life?
That I'm not always
at your beck and call?
No.
♪ Men. ♪
(sportscast playing)
You know, Berta, I thought
when Alan moved in here
I was being punished.
You and me both.
But come to find out,
it was a blessing.
With him in my life,
I think
I can actually make my
relationship with Chelsea work.
So you're really gonna go
through with this marriage?
Absolutely. I'm ready
for the whole shebang.
Kids, too?
Well, it's certainly
in the cards.
Of course, I'd have
to talk it over
with Chelsea
and Alan first.
Wow, marriage and kids.
I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
What can I say, Berta?
He completes me.
(chuckles)
♪ Men. ♪
(cell phone chimes)
One second.
(laughs)
He's hilarious.
Who?
Your brother.
L-O-L.
(cell phone chimes)
Let me just tell him
we'll talk tomorrow.
(laughing)
He is out of control.
What now?
Hang on.
"Don't let him
chew up the rug."
What does that mean?
Nothing.
Why would I
chew up a rug?
Not a rug, my...
never mind.
Okay, where were we?
We were just about...
(cell phone chimes)
I'm sure he just wants
to say "good night."
(cell phone chimes)
I'm sorry. Let me just
make sure he's okay.
Is he okay?
Yeah.
Good, good.
Hey, I'm thirsty.
Are you thirsty?
No.
Be right back.
Hurry.
Don't worry.
This won't take but a minute.
Oh, Charlie...
Your penis is no match
for my technology.
Okay.
I know what you're doing,
now quit it.
What I'm doing?
Whatever do you mean?
You're text-blocking me.
Hey, I can't help it
if Chelsea finds me
witty and urbane.
Keep it up and she's going
to find you bloody and homeless.
You don't scare me, Charlie.
You need me to keep
Chelsea off your back.
That may be true,
but I don't need
him!
Wait, just let
him go, Charlie.
This is just between you and me.
Not anymore.
Don't you dare hurt him!
Well, now,
that's entirely up to you.
His tiny, wooden head
is in your hands.
Charlie?
ALAN:
Danny!
(thudding)
ALAN: Just let him go!
CHARLIE: No!
Charlie?
(both grunting)
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing.
♪ Men. ♪
That's no way for
a grown man to behave!
CHARLIE:
He started it!
CHELSEA: I don't care
who started it!
You're the older brother.
You set the example.
Really?
Then maybe I
should move out...
Boy, they're really
going at it.
Yeah. I'm glad
we never fight.
Me, too, Danny.
'Cause you don't ever
want to make me angry.
I-I-I know, Danny.
Seriously.
♪ Men. ♪