♪ Men...
♪ Mmm... mmm
Morning.
Mmm. Morning.
Charlie, please don't
start anything.
Too late. I woke
up started.
I have to get to work.
Okay, I've got
a job for you.
We'll finish this tonight.
I may have to finish this
myself.
Knock yourself out.
It's no fun
if you have permission.
So, Charlie, I was thinking
maybe tonight
we could stay at my place.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Charlie?
I'm sorry,
did you say something?
I said maybe tonight
we could stay at my place.
You want to play on my face?
Stay at my place.
Oh.
What about it?
I've been coming here
for the past three weeks,
and it's like an hour drive
for me to get to work.
Well, I'd be happy
to spring for a cab.
It's not the drive, you idiot.
You just said it was the drive.
What I mean is if we're gonna
see each other
on a regular basis, there should
be some give and take.
Based on last night,
we're pretty even Steven
in the give-and-take department.
And if I recall correctly,
you're up one "take."
Hey, of the two of us,
I'm the one with tennis elbow.
So what about tonight?
I'd love to, but it might be
a little tricky.
Why?
(softly):
Oh, I knew she'd ask me that.
I'm starting
to get the feeling
that you only want to see
at your place
and at your convenience.
No, of course not.
Well, then fine, you'll stay
at my place tonight.
Sounds great.
Lookin' forward to it.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Doesn't matter, just as long
as you and I are together.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Why would you even ask me that?
I'm guessing he either robbed
a liquor store
or killed a drifter.
Do I need to call your mother
and ask her?
If you want to, but you know
how she pushes your buttons.
I'll take that chance.
Fine, I don't care.
All right, all right!
I got thrown off the school bus.
You got the spine
of a gummy bear.
Why were you thrown off the bus?
Well, actually,
it's a funny story.
Amuse me.
Have you ever heard of this
thing called mooning?
Yeah. Yeah, it rings a bell.
The bus was going past the
girls' track team
and a bunch of us thought
it'd be funny to moon them.
(chuckling)
See, she gets it.
Berta.
Sorry. I'm just
remembering my prom.
(sighs)
So what happened?
Well, I was working near the
high school that night,
and I thought it would be fun
to drive the backhoe...
No. Not you.
Him.
Well. Excuse me for sharing.
What happened?
Well, it sounds like
Berta had quite a prom.
You're skating
on thin ice, Jake.
Boy, that's something
we haven't done in a
long time— skating.
Jake!
Mom grounded me
for two weeks.
Why didn't your mother
tell me about this?
I promised I'd tell you.
What can I say?
She believed me.
So how about a movie?
A little father-son bonding.
No, no. No movies.
Skating?
No skating.
Fine.
Also no TV, no video games,
no cell phones, and no iPods—
Couldn't you just smack me with
a belt and get it over with?
Get out of here.
I'm bored.
♪ Men...
Oh, man.
What's the matter?
Did you know that Culver City
is all the way down
near the airport?
Yes.
That's gotta be like 45 minutes
from here.
If there's no traffic.
Traffic?
Is this Culver City place
popular?
Not particularly, but there are
other people with cars
living lives completely
separate from your own.
Oh, right.
I hate those people.
"So what's in Culver City?"
he asked,
knowing the only possible
answer.
Can you believe she wants me
to schlep all the way
over to her place just so we can
spend the night together?
Aw, you poor guy.
You have to drive 45
minutes to get laid.
And 45 minutes to get back.
That's 90 minutes
behind the wheel
for 20, 30 minutes behind...
Well, I don't need
to draw you a map.
You're breaking my heart.
And it's not just that.
She said there's
only street parking.
Which means trees.
And trees have that, you know,
toxic syrup
that drips out of them
and gets all over your car.
Sap.
If I make that drive, I am.
Wait a minute,
wait a minute.
You always said
that it was better to go
to the woman's house so that
you could make a quick getaway.
Yeah, for one-nighters
that's fine.
But this girl, I care about.
We've been seeing each other
for almost a month.
And yet you just found out
where she lives.
There's a difference between
caring and stalking, Alan.
Hey, Dad, I need my laptop.
What for?
Homework.
What homework?
Um... Damn, you're good.
♪ Men...
Thanks for driving all the
way over here, Charlie.
Are you kidding?
I would've walked here
if I had to.
Probably would've been faster
with the traffic.
Good night.
(car door slams)
What are you doing?
I heard a car door.
Your Mercedes is fine, Charlie.
I know, I know.
Just double-checking.
(alarm chirps)
Probably gonna get sap
all over the car cover.
Isn't that what it's for?
You don't get it.
That's fine.
No TV in the bedroom, huh?
It's in the living room.
You just got the one?
How many do I need?
Well, you've got three rooms
and a bath, so... four.
If you want to go watch
television instead of cuddling,
that's up to you.
No, no, I'd much rather cuddle.
At my house,
we could do both.
You know, cuddling
and Sportscenter.
Good night, Charlie.
Sweet dreams.
(sighs)
What now?
Nothing. I'm just
used to sleeping
on the other side of the bed.
Yeah, so?
So I usually sleep
on my left side,
which faces me towards
the edge of the mattress.
But here, I'm facing the back
of your head—which is fine;
there are certainly times
when I enjoy seeing it
from that angle—
but, you know,
when I'm trying to sleep,
it's a little disconcerting.
Well, I'm sorry,
but this is my side.
But you sleep on the other side
at my house.
Because it's your house;
this is my house.
But I'm a guest.
And I'm the guest
at your house.
That's different.
How?
Give me a minute.
Good night, Charlie.
Boy, you're being
pretty inflexible.
Oh, you think
I'm inflexible.
Well, not physically,
but you got to admit
in this regard,
you're a little stubborn.
Good night, Charlie.
Okay. Good night.
How about this?
If we switch sides
and an armed intruder came in,
I could leap up
and protect you.
But this way,
you're pretty much guaranteed
to catch the first bullet.
What if he comes
through the window?
Oh, great.
Now I'm never
gonna get to sleep.
ALAN:
Jake?
(TV turns off)
You'd better not
be watching TV.
(sighs)
Ah.
Maybe he's upstairs.
(doorknob rattling)
Uh-oh.
(subtle clattering outside)
(clattering continues)
(dog barks)
(car approaching)
(sighs deeply)
It's like trying to sleep
in the freaking jungle.
(cat snarls)
(screams)
What's going on?
Nothing, nothing.
I was going to the bathroom,
and I stepped on a cat.
You don't have to sneak out.
If you want to leave, leave.
Whoa, I'd say someone woke up
on the wrong side of the bed.
But I don't want
to revisit that topic.
Good-bye, Charlie.
Gee, you sound kind of angry.
Why would I
be angry?
Just because I drive
to Malibu every night
for a month,
and you won't stay even one
night with me?
Well, that and, you know,
possibly crippling your cat.
Go home, Charlie.
Are you sure?
I'm begging you.
Okay, if that's what you want.
So tomorrow at my place?
You make love like a woman,
but you throw like a man.
♪ Men...
Jake?
(yells)
Why are you sleeping out here?
I was, um... camping?
Okay, well, as long
as you're not watching TV.
Oh!
Stupid birds.
Hey, how'd it go last night?
I couldn't do it, Alan.
I tried, but I couldn't.
Oh, well, that happens
to all men occasionally.
Especially when you get
to be our age.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about how
I'm so set in my ways,
I couldn't spend one night
in a strange house.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about.
I mean, there was a time
when I could sleep anywhere:
couches, floors, witness boxes,
police cars, jail cells.
That's not sleeping.
That's passing out.
I'm not gonna argue
semantics with you.
The point is I was really
uncomfortable over there.
Even if I could have gotten
to sleep,
the morning would have been
a disaster.
How so?
Think about it.
After I had my morning coffee,
where would I go
to do my business?
Oh, right, you always want
to have home-field advantage
for that.
She's got one of those
wooden toilet seats.
It would've been like sitting
on Pinocchio's mouth.
You ever wonder about people
who can poop in a gas station?
What is wrong with them?
What about Porta-Potties?
Those aren't people.
Those are animals.
I'd rather go in the trunk
of my car.
I have.
You've gone in the trunk
of your car?
No, yours.
That was you?
I convinced myself a coyote
had gotten in there.
(playing "Smoke On the Water"
amateurishly)
What the hell
are you doing?
Playing "Smoke On the Water."
With your tongue?
Pretty cool, huh?
No, that is not cool.
It's disgusting.
Alan, get in here!
What now?
Your kid's licking my piano.
Jake, don't lick
your uncle's piano.
I'm bored.
Go read a book.
I don't want to read a book.
Then go lick a book.
How long is this
whole grounding thing
gonna go on for?
Two weeks.
Two weeks?
Charlie, he stuck his ass out
a bus window
at the girls' track team.
That's what
you're punishing him for?
When you were his age,
you mooned the girls' choir.
No, when I was his age,
you pantsed me
in front of the girls' choir.
Oh, right.
Well, either way,
you made the yearbook.
Berta, I'm leaving.
Hang on!
Where you going?
I talked Chelsea
into giving me another chance
to spend the night at her place.
Here's your overnight bag.
Thank you.
All that's for one night?
One night and one morning
business meeting with Pinocchio.
I got your flip-flops
for the shower,
your personal bath towel,
hand towel and washcloth,
your hand soap, face soap
and shampoo.
Great.
One handheld TV,
your goose-down pillow,
Egyptian cotton
pillowcase and sheets
and a ziplock baggie
of your special blend
French roast coffee.
Terrific.
One jar of seedless raspberry
jam, a mild laxative
and one roll of quilted toilet
paper with lanolin.
Okay.
Culver City, here I come.
He ain't gonna make it.
Not a chance.
You know, I have never once seen
him eat seedless raspberry jam.
That's because you've never
applied a thin layer
to your hindquarters.
♪ Men...
I'm so glad you decided
this was important
to you, Charlie.
Well, you're important to me.
What are you doing?
I brought my sheets.
You wanna grab the other side?
What's wrong
with my sheets?
Nothing, nothing.
But mine are better.
Egyptian cotton.
Like, eight-million
thread count.
And good news.
I solved the wrong-side-
of-the-bed situation.
Okay...
I'll just sleep
with my head down there.
That way, I'm facing
the right way.
But then your feet
will be in my face.
Way ahead of you.
Peppermint foot lotion.
You'll think you're sleepin'
in Candyland.
Oh, before I forget.
Toilet paper?
Don't get your hopes up,
but I'm gonna make the effort.
♪ Men...
Hey, Jake?
You out here?
Seen my kid?
(TV blasting)
What the hell?
Can I have some privacy, please?
Get out of the tub.
Out of the tub.
Fine.
You're unbelievable.
Is TV that important to you?
Do you really
have to ask?
Go to your room.
Fine, but check out Uncle
Charlie's toilet seat.
It heats up.
Just go!
Can I have this
raspberry jam?
Don't touch the jam!
Oh...
Toasty.
If only I could poop at night.
Maybe I'll just pee
girly style.
♪ Men...
Charlie...
(gasps)
What?
This isn't working for me.
My feet too minty?
It's not your feet.
Well, it is your feet,
but it's also the sheets,
the pillows, the towels, the TV,
the electric toothbrush.
It's not a toothbrush.
It's an ultrasonic dental
appliance.
It's probably got more
vibrations per minute
than that plastic egg
you keep in your nightstand.
That's right.
I do have one of those.
Go home.
But I want to spend
the night here.
No, no, I made a mistake.
From now on,
we'll stay at your place.
Oh, okay.
Your call.
I'm nothing if not flexible.
(cat yowls)
You really should put a bell
on that thing.
♪ Men...
Hello, Mr. Bed.
I'll be with you
in a minute
after I pay my respects
to Professor Toilet.
Hello.