Check it out.
They got cars that run
on vegetable oil now.
How about that.
You know what would be cool?
A Hummer that runs
on French fry grease.
Uh-huh.
We could be energy independent
and still smash through crap.
Sounds great.
Plus, the new car smell
is French fries.
Okay, I'm only gonna
say this one more time.
You don't get your license
for two more years
and you're not
getting a Hummer.
You know, you say you
want me to open up to you,
but what's the point?
(chuckling)
Yeah, I always loved
Paris in the springtime.
Oh, you're lucky.
I only got to do her
once, on Halloween.
Hi.
Oh, hey, Alan.
Andy, this is
my brother Alan.
Alan, Andy.
Hello.
Hey, Andy.
Pull up a chair.
We're just telling
war stories.
Oh, great.
The sponge?
Yeah.
So, uh, how do you
guys know each other?
Well, Andy and I—
Can I have a cigar?
Sure, help yourself.
Thank you.
Anyway, Andy and I
have known each other—
Maybe I'll take one for
now and one for later.
Anyway, before
he moved to New York,
Andy and I were
partners in crime.
There weren't
that many actual crimes.
Unless you count
the ones against nature.
Alan, this is a great man.
ANDY:
No, no,
Albert Einstein
was a great man.
I just drink, gamble and hump.
But I'm great at it.
Andy once managed to hitchhike
from Vegas to L.A.,
wearing no pants.
Hey, anybody can
use their thumb.
This right here,
this is the brother
I never had.
Oh, well,
how nice for you.
I don't mean it that way.
You're my brother.
Well, thank you.
I just like him better.
Got it.
*Andy is the one guy
in the world
that can match me drink for
drink and broad for broad.
In fact, the one time I thought
I drank him under the table,
it turned out he had
a broad under there.
Right, Andy?
CHARLIE:
Andy?
Don't screw
with me, dude.
Who's your favorite brother now?
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Men.
♪ Oh, oh-oh. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
So, he died right out there
in the chair, huh?
Yep.
(clicks tongue)
Remind me
to flip that cushion.
You should've seen it, Berta.
The paramedics zipped him up
in a big plastic bag.
Is that so?
It looked like
one of those things
the delivery guys
use to keep pizza hot.
I wonder if they
got him to the morgue
in 30 minutes or less.
Not funny, Jake.
Maybe it is funny and
you just didn't get it.
Eat.
So, uh, did you know him?
Andy? Sure.
Before he moved to New York,
he and Charlie
were just like brothers.
Yeah, I heard that part.
How's Charlie taking it?
He's pretty shook up.
Well, you can understand why.
Somebody your age,
living the same
dumbass lifestyle you live
keels over and dies.
It's gotta give you pause.
You're right about that.
Actually, I'm surprised
that Charlie didn't go first.
Excuse me.
I'm standing right here.
But for how long?
Did you get that one?
I'll see you later.
Where you going?
Where do you think?
My best friend just died.
I got a lot of things
to take care of.
You're handling
the funeral?
I'm sure Andy
would like that.
The hell with Andy.
I'm going to the hospital
to get every damn
medical test known to man.
Good one.
You're not getting
any of these, are you?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Hey, how'd the tests go?
I won't know
for a couple of days.
All right, I'm outta here.
How about you, Charlie?
Wait, I got something
for you.
It's a gift certificate for a
week at a spa in Palm Springs.
Well, I'll be.
Thank you, Charlie.
I just wanted you
to know that I love you
and appreciate that you've
always been there for me.
Great, see you in a week.
Look at you.
The minute you start thinking
about your mortality,
you realize how much you care
about the people around you.
Yeah, and I need to
start showing it.
Well, little gifts are always
a nice way to express
your feelings.
I know.
Could be as simple
as a cashmere robe
or as extravagant
as a new car.
Yeah, I suppose it could.
Excuse me, I got something
really cool for Jake.
Doesn't even
have to be new!
"Certified pre-owned"
is still very thoughtful!
(knocking on door)
Hey, what are
you doing?
I was trying to research cars,
but you wouldn't believe
what comes up
when you Google "Hummer."
Actually, I would.
Here, I got you something
I think you're
really gonna like.
Is it a sandwich?
Why would I gift wrap
a sandwich?
'Cause you want me
to be surprised?
Just open it.
You know what's
a great sandwich?
The Monte Cristo.
'Cause it has ham and cheese
and it's fried.
Open the damn box.
Whoa,
don't get your period.
Oh, wow, a mini
video camera.
Pretty cool, huh?
Is this 'cause
you think you're dying?
No, no.
I just wanted to do
something nice for you.
Before you die.
Do you want the camera or not?
Yeah, I want it.
Then just say thank you.
Thank you. Geez.
You need to relax.
You'll give yourself
a heart attack.
I'll work on it.
Have a sandwich.
That always relaxes me.
All right,
one more gift to give.
Oh, yeah?
Saving the best for last?
I don't know about the best,
but it's sure the hardest.
Any way I can make it easier?
Yeah.
Call Mom and tell her
I'm on my way over.
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, Charlie, what
a beautiful watch!
Do you really like it?
Are you kidding?
It's gorgeous!
And the best part is
now I don't have to wear
my good one every day.
Anyway, you're
probably wondering
why I bought it for you.
Well, I just
assumed you love me
and did it out of the
goodness of your heart.
I'm kidding.
Why, dear?
Okay, I deserve that.
But the truth is
I do love you
and despite our
many differences,
I'm glad you're my mother.
You didn't drive over
here drunk, did you?
I'm not drunk.
I just...
I've been thinking a lot
about how fleeting life is,
and that none of us really knows
how long we're gonna be here.
Did you find another
lump on your pee-pee?
No, Mom, my pee-pee's fine.
I don't know how "worn down
to a nub" can be fine,
but all right.
My point is,
I don't want to be
angry with you anymore.
I want us to be friends.
I was always
your friend, Charlie.
You were just too
self-involved to see it.
Okay, I got to go.
Where you off to?
I have to pick out
a casket for a friend of mine.
Oh, I'm... I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, what
are you gonna do.
Don't cheap out.
It's one thing to
do it with a watch,
but a casket is forever.
♪ Men. ♪
CHARLIE:
So young.
I can't believe it.
Yeah...
Who'd have thought smoking,
drinking and whoring
could kill you?
You realize that could just
as easily be me in there.
Yeah.
Don't even
think that.
It is a nice
casket, though.
Should be.
It cost me ten grand.
Ten grand? Wow.
What can I say?
I take care of
the people I love.
Could've taken care of me
with a freakin' robe.
Kind of a light turnout.
You'd probably get more
people with an open bar.
Hey, make sure there's
an open bar at mine.
Oh, now I'm your
funeral planner?
Don't you want a friend
or someone you really
care about in charge of that?
No, you do it.
MINISTER:
Good afternoon and welcome.
(somberly):
We are here
to celebrate the life
and mourn the passing
of Andrew Donald Patterson.
How do we measure
a man's life?
Geez, this guy's a load.
Don't get a guy
like this for me.
I want someone with
a little bit ofgravitas.
I'll see if James Earl
Jones is available.
That would be nice.
"... a time to die,
"a time to reap,
"a time to sow,
"a time to mourn...
JAMES EARL JONES:
"... a time to heal.
a time for every
purpose under heaven."
And so we say goodbye
to Charles Francis Harper.
Devoted son,
loving brother,
caring uncle.
Bon vivant and world-class
connoisseur of the booty.
Nice turnout.
Yeah, man.
Standing room only.
Goes to show you, give
the people what they want.
You mean the
open bar, right?
Sure.
Thanks for coming,
by the way.
Well, you came to mine.
Yeah, but you're dead.
Charlie, take a
look in the box.
That's not
a tanning booth.
Oh, yeah.
So, listen, as long as you're
here— what's Heaven like?
It's unbelievable.
It's paradise.
Like your house.
Before your brother
moved in.
Oh, that was good.
You can drink all you want
and there's no hangover.
Endless supply of women,
each one more beautiful
than the last,
and, Charlie, get this:
they believe everything
you tell 'em.
Everything?
It's Heaven, dude.
Wow.
Well, save me a good seat.
I wish I could, but that's
not where they sent me.
Oh...
Then how do you know
what Heaven's like?
They make us look at
a video every day,
while they're putting
lube on the pitchfork.
Well, at least
you get lube.
Only on the little prong.
JAMES EARL JONES:
To be completely honest,
I didn't know Charlie Harper,
but any man who,
with his dying breath,
would set aside $25,000
and a first-class air ticket,
so I could deliver
his eulogy...
is aces in my book!
That being said, uh...
there are many people here today
who did know Charlie,
and perhaps some of them
would like to stand up
and say a few words.
Ooh! Ooh!
I want to say something.
Uh... Hello, everybody.
Hello, James Earl Jones.
Um... hey, bro.
Don't get up.
What can I say
about Charlie?
Uh, so many words
come to mind—
so few that you can say
in church.
But we'll give it a shot.
Um... Charlie was
a man of love.
Um, he loved his friends;
he loved his family;
but, most of all,
he loved his penis...
the only part of him that
ever had an actual job.
Well, anyway...
this was a man so full of love
that it practically
oozed out of him,
at which point, of course,
he would see a doctor.
But I kid the deceased
whoremonger.
(chuckling)
Anyway...
since he never
made out a will,
I hope you will all join me
for a wake-slash-luau
at my Malibu beach house!
(applause)
He got my house?
He got everything
you had.
Everything?
Well, not the
diseased liver
and the swollen prostate.
Oh, look, your
old girlfriends
are saying their
final goodbye.
(spits)
That's not very
respectful.
Just FYI— spit is
the Devil's lube.
Listen, would you mind
recording my answering
machine message for me?
That'll be an extra $500.
That's okay.
I'm rich now.
Well, what do you want:
"This is CNN"
or "Luke, I am
your father"?
So, Charlie, it's been
great catching up
but I gotta go.
Already?
Can't you stay awhile?
No. It's pitchfork time.
If you're late,
you don't get the spit.
And, believe me, Charlie,
you want the spit.
I want the spit!
♪ Men. ♪
Harper.
Charlie Harper.
It was in
a few days ago.
I peed in a cup;
you took my blood
and slipped a camera
up the heart of darkness.
You know,
the doctor said my results
would be ready today.
Fine.
Have him get back to me.
He's avoiding
my calls, Alan.
I'm gonna die.
No. No you're not.
I can feel it.
You might as well just drive
into that tree
and kill us both.
Sure.
(monotone):
I don't want to go on
living without you.
What's the point
of it all?
Yeah, I'm rich, charming,
classically handsome.
I've laid more pipe than a guy
who has sex with pipes.
But what have I done
with my life?
A few stupid jingles;
some kids' songs—
nothing that really matters.
(monotone):
Now, now, you're being
too hard on yourself.
I've got no wife,
I've got no children...
I'm going leave this world
the way I came in...
By Cesarean section?
Alone.
Oh, for God sakes,
Charlie,
I am tired of
listening to this.
There has always been
one person in your life
who's been there for you and
loved you unconditionally.
You mean...?
You're right.
How could I
have missed it?
It's been in front
of me the whole time!
Well, you know,
sometimes you can't see
the forest for the trees,
even when the forest
is in your own backyard.
Or guest room.
Rose?
Yep, the one and only.
I know, I know.
It's been awhile.
I was thinking,
if you're not too busy,
maybe we can get together,
have a drink or something?
Well, great!
So, do you want to meet,
or should I pick you up?
(horn beeping)
(mouthing)
Okay, I'll meet you
back at my place.
Huh. Small world.
Yeah. Teeny-tiny.
♪ Men. ♪
Here you go.
Thank you, Charlie.
You comfy?
Oh, very.
Good.
(sighs)
So, Rose...
Charlie...
Haven't seen you
in awhile.
Can't say the same.
Right, uh, sure.
Sorry about your friend.
Yeah, yeah, it was a
real wake-up call for me.
Mm. I can imagine.
Makes you stop and wonder
what's important in your life.
Who's important
in your life.
I've always known
who's important in my life.
You have, haven't you.
You know how I feel
about you, right?
Tell me anyway.
Oh, okay.
Well, as you know, we've
had our ups and downs.
I told you that was
my medication.
I was talking about
our relationship.
Oh. Yes.
That's had
ups and downs, too.
Continue.
Well, uh, I'm thinking,
we're not getting any younger.
You know, there was a time
when I did think
I was getting younger
but it turns out that
that was my medication.
Sure.
I also thought
that I was getting smaller.
(clears throat)
Anyway, uh, it struck me
that life is... short,
and maybe the time has come
for you and I to start
thinking about
our future.
What about it?
(sighs heavily)
Well...
I know this is kind
of sudden, but...
Rose...
Yes, Charlie?
(phone rings)
Would you do me
the honor of...
I'm sorry.
Let me just
get rid of this.
Oh, it's my doctor.
Hey, Doc.
What's the word?
No liver damage
whatsoever?
What about my heart?
Well, that's terrific!
Lungs are good, too?
So I don't have to
give up cigars?
No, no, no,
I won't overdo it.
Just when I drink.
Speaking of which—
how's the plumbing?
Does that include
the prostate?
(quietly):
Yes.
All right, well, uh,
thanks for getting
back to me so soon.
And, again, I'm sorry
for all the name calling
when you slipped
your finger up there.
Oh, boy, this is awkward.
♪ Men. ♪
Look at him—
he's gonna live forever.
Nah, it's just gonna
seem like forever.
He smokes, he drinks, he parties
like there's no tomorrow.
Me?
I have Mexican food
and a couple of beers
and I'm farting blood.
Yeah, boo-hoo.
You just said Mexican food
and I grew a third butt cheek.
Life isn't fair,
is it, Berta?
If it were,
you'd be cleaning my toilets
and I'd have
my own talk show.
A talk show?
Why not?
I'm personable.
Well, at least he has
a clean bill of health.
I'm happy for that.
Me, too.
I don't care if I never
inherit this house.
Uh, uh... excuse me?
Oh, you ain't seen
his new will, huh?
Uh, what new will?
Never mind.
But in case tragedy strikes,
be prepared to clear your crap
out of here in 48 hours.
Son of a bitch.