all this time
without a jockstrap.
I don't like it.
It feels like I'm flossing
my butt crack.
Based on what I'm paying
your dentist,
you know nothing about flossing.
Think of it as
a bra for your balls.
Oh, now I want one.
What size are you?
How should I know?
I think they have one
of those measuring things.
You know, like at
the shoe store.
Length, width.
He's kidding, right?
Yes, he's joking,
Don't do that.
Here, "teen."
Think you can fit
your junk into that?
I'll make it fit.
Let's just go.
No, no, put it on
over your pants.
We'll take a look.
The heck you will.
Charlie, you're
embarrassing him.
Of course I am.
That's why I came.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Excuse me.
Charlie Harper?
Where? He owes
me money.
Miss Pasternak?
Jake! Wow, look at you.
Look how much you've grown.
I reached puberty.
Oh, right, Miss Pasternak,
fifth grade,
Woodward Avenue
Elementary School.
Oh, yeah,
Miss Pasternak!
Miss Pasternak.
So, are you still
teaching?
No. No, I'm not.
How are you, Charlie?
Good, good. Nice to
see you. Long time.
You look terrific.
Guess who's wearing a jock.
Oh, how nice.
Well, it's great to see you all.
Good-bye.
Bye, Miss Pasternak.
Dodged a bullet there.
I'll say.
She was kind of shook up
after I broke it off with her.
Kind of shook up?
She went bananas
and bit the gym teacher.
Where?
In the gym.
You miserable
son of a bitch!
I gave you my heart,
I gave you my soul,
I gave you my body and
you just threw me aside
like I was some
piece of garbage!
Yeah, my bad.
So, what's new?
Oh, you want to catch up?
Yeah, sure, let's catch up.
Let's see, um, well, okay,
after you dumped me,
I had a nervous breakdown.
Well, it sure looks
like you bounced back.
And then after my breakdown,
I got fired and blackballed
from teaching.
Oh... bummer.
So, what are you up to now?
I'll tell you what
I'm up to now.
I lost my house, I'm
living in a cheap motel,
and my new career is giving
lap dances to strangers
while I'm swinging by my crotch
on a pole eight times a night.
Have you considered
an athletic supporter?
Okay, well,
thanks for the update.
Nice seeing you.
(hushed):
Move, move, move.
You ruined my life,
Charlie Harper!
Righto. Bye.
We didn't pay for
the jockstrap.
Just keep walking.
How can you live with yourself,
you horrible evil man?
He drinks.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
We're making an apple
and sugar mixture...
What are you watching?
The Food Network.
I'm learning how
to prepare a
cinnamon-apple cobbler.
Tired of being at the mercy
of the dealers, huh?
What?
Nothing, nothing.
Listen, I think
I owe you an apology.
For what?
You know, this morning
in the drugstore?
Oh, yeah, the jockstrap jokes.
You shou be sorry.
No, not the jockstrap jokes.
Those were funny.
I stand by those.
I meant the run-in
with your old teacher.
You probably shouldn't
have seen that.
I've seen worse.
Remember the Pilates
instructor who threw
the lit road flare
through your bedroom window?
Yeah.
That was awesome.
That's one word
for it.
Oh, and remember
the dental hygienist
who shot your ass up
full of Novocain?
I do.
That was so funny.
You kept falling off the toilet.
Yeah, good times.
What do you do
that gets these women
so pissed off at you?
It's hard to say exactly.
I guess when a guy
has an intimate relationship...
Oh, remember the girl
from the tanning salon
who tried to shoot you
with a bow and arrow?
Yeah, Jake.
My point is, I was wrong in
the way I treated those women,
and you should learn a lesson
from my mistakes.
You mean like keep
a fire extinguisher by your bed?
Sure, that's one lesson.
And whenever a dental hygienist
drops a quarter,
never bend over to pick it up?
Yeah, that, too.
And never go
to a Halloween party
with a girl dressed
as Robin Hood?
The thing is, Jake,
you wouldn't have to learn
any of these lessons
if you always treated women
better in the first place.
I'm confused.
If I don't have to learn them,
why are you bothering me
with them?
I don't know.
I'm sorry to take up
your valuable time.
What the heck
was that all about?
♪ Men. ♪
Hey. Guess what?
Turns out my kid's
jockstrap is too small.
Good news, eh?
Yeah, terrific.
Alan, let me
ask you something.
Do you think I'm a horrible,
evil person?
Yes.
What? You are.
Thanks a lot.
Well, you know, not
intentionally evil.
I mean, you know,
is a tornado evil
when it picks up a mobile home
and flings it
into an orphanage?
Is a shark evil
when it eats some poor
schmuck on a boogie board?
Is a flesh-eating virus evil
when it attacks...?
I get it, I get it, I get it.
I'm a malevolent force
of nature.
Pretty much.
Is this about what happened
with Jake's old teacher today?
She said that I ruined her life.
Well, she did choose
to sleep with you.
How much of a life
could she have had
in the first place?
Don't try
to make me feel better.
Because of me, the woman
lost her teaching career,
and now she's dancing
in this skeevy club in Van Nuys
and living
in some fleabag motel.
How do you know
what club she works at?
The clubs have Web sites,
the Web sites have pictures.
It's not rocket science.
Her dancing name
is Desiree Bush.
Certainly more colorful
than Delores Pasternak.
And presidential to boot.
I gotta tell you,
I'm feeling a little guilty.
Does that surprise you?
No, what surprises me
is the liquor isn't helping.
It just beads up on the guilt
and rolls right off it.
Oh, come on,
this can't be the first woman
who had a nervous breakdown,
lost her job and wound up
taking her clothes off
for horny strangers
because of you.
Of course not.
But it's never
bothered me before.
Well, maybe
you're finally
developing
a conscience.
At long last realizing that
your actions have consequences
for other people.
Don't talk down to me,
Jiminy Cricket.
Sorry.
But you're right.
I do need to take responsibility
for the damage I've caused.
Where you going?
Where else? Strip club.
Wait up. I'll drive.
♪ Men. ♪
("Cherry Pie" playing)
Good Lord,
she's quite the gymnast.
I know. I never understood
why this isn't in the Olympics
and synchronized diving is.
Hey, honey, when's
Miss Bush come out?
Whenever Ben Franklin comes out.
I mean Desiree Bush.
She's around here somewhere.
Thank you.
How come she's not taking
her clothes off?
Because this is
a bikini club.
What's a bikini club?
Hard liquor, no nipples.
Man, I could've stayed home
and seen no nipples.
Hey, there she is.
Miss Pasternak.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I just wanted to talk to you.
Yeah, well, I'm working,
so unless you want
a private dance,
I got no time.
I don't need a dance.
Then you get lost.
No, no, wait, wait, wait.
Alan needs a dance.
Oh, no, I don't, I-I...
I'm buying.
Do you mind if I take
my belt off?
So anyway,
I just wanted to tell you
that I'm really sorry
for the way that I ended it,
and if there's
anything I can do
to make it right,
just let me now.
(groans deeply)
What can you do for me, Charlie?
Well, maybe I can help you
get back on your feet.
Oh, oh, not yet, not yet.
Are you gonna get me
my house back?
Are you gonna do that?
Ooh, doggies!
Well, no.
My parents have disowned me.
Are you gonna fix
that relationship?
I'm not real good with parents.
Uh, excuse me, I've gotta,
I've gotta readjust.
I'm playing ring toss
with my car keys.
What then? Are you gonna get me
my teacher's license back?
I wish I could.
Okay, I'm all set.
We can continue.
Alan, this doesn't concern you.
At this point, it kinda does.
Come on,
hop on Pop.
Thank you!
What if there was a way
for you to go back to teaching
that didn't require a license?
What are you talking about?
Private tutoring
for a special-needs child.
Oh, oh, Charlie,
don't drag him into this.
Why not?
She's a good teacher,
and if his grades go any lower,
we'll have to start renting him
out as a speed bump.
Tutoring?
Yeah, I don't know.
I'll match
what you're making here.
Is it okay with you, Alan?
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
Okay, it's a deal.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Now come on, teach.
I'll buy you a drink
and we'll toast your new career.
(laughs):
Great.
Uh, uh... O-O-Okay.
I'll, uh, I'll catch up
with you guys later.
Where's my belt?
♪ Men. ♪
Let me get this straight.
She was his fifth grade teacher,
and then she became a stripper
because you dumped her,
and now she's his tutor
because you felt guilty?
Pretty much.
And you approved?
He caught me at a weak moment.
Well, who am I to judge?
I almost traded one of my kids
for a riding lawn mower.
I'm sorry, but
I'm still confused.
Oh, boy.
Hm. Okay, um...
let's look at it this way.
How about if you
make $40 a dance.
If you want to find out
how much you can earn per hour,
you have to solve
fortimes 40,
X being the number of dances
you can do in an hour.
What about tips?
That's a variable.
Oh. I get it—
so the money
you kick back to
the house is...
The constant!
Good for you.
That's a good start.
Yeah, it was.
You make learning fun.
(laughs):
Where you going?
Take a shower.
Guys, we're done!
Hey. So, how'd it go?
Oh, a little slow.
He's not exactly
the quicker picker upper.
Well, that's why he needs you.
He's kind of an idiot.
Yeah, uh,
I wasn't gonna say anything,
but wow.
So, we'll see you
tomorrow, then?
Great. Hey...
Charlie, thank you.
For what?
Well, you've given me back
something I lost
a long time ago.
I gave it back?
How did I give it back?
My self-respect.
Oh, sure, that you can get back.
And you haven't even tried
to hit on me.
No. And I don't intend to.
I just want to see you
get your life together again.
Boy, I've hated you
for so many years.
I'm starting to think
maybe I was wrong.
No, no, no, you're were right—
this is new for me.
Well, I like this Charlie.
He's got a big heart.
Thank you.
Desiree, wait.
Instead of going
back to that motel,
why don't you stay here?
No strings— just until
you can get a real apartment.
Where would I sleep?
You can have the guest room.
Well, where would Alan sleep?
If there was any justice,
at the bottom of a ravine.
♪ Men. ♪
I can't believe
you gave her my room.
I can't believe you're
still calling it your room.
How long is this
gonna last?
Just until she gets
back on her feet.
Oh, please,
that's a load of crap.
That's what I said to you
six years ago.
You've been here six years?
I'll just go make up the couch.
(quietly):
Story of my life.
No boner goes unpunished.
♪ Men. ♪
(door opens)
Charlie.
Huh?
I was lying in bed alone,
and I had an epiphany.
Okay.
It suddenly became clear to me
why you came back into my life.
Why?
The Lord sent you.
The Lord?
Yes. He sent you to save me
from my sinful ways.
He did?
Yes.
I really don't think
he'd send me.
I'm more of a recruiter
for the other side.
It's not for us to
question his will.
Come, come, let's
pray together.
Now?
Yes, now, while the
spirit is with us.
Can I pee first?
There'll be plenty of
time to pee in Heaven.
There's peeing in Heaven?
Shh!
Weird, us both being on our
knees at the same time, huh?
Shh!
I'm just saying.
♪ Men. ♪
Morning.
How'd everybody sleep?
Fine.
Lousy.
So, listen...
we might have a little
problem with Miss Pasternak.
Oh, Charlie, you didn't.
No, I didn't. Why do you
always believe the worst of me?
Because you're a horrible,
evil person.
I thought we established that.
I'll tell you
what happened.
Last night, I was upstairs,
sleeping alone,
minding my own business...
Good morning, sinners.
Oh, what a glorious day
to bask in the forgiveness
of our Lord.
Uh-oh.
Jake, I have wonderful news.
From now on,
as part of each lesson,
we're gonna spend time
casting demons out of you.
It's the Devil
that's making him stupid.
I told you it
wasn't my fault.
Uh, uh, Miss Pasternak,
while I'm thrilled
that you're helping Jake
with his schoolwork,
I'm not sure an exorcism
is really called for.
Do you want your son
to go to hell, Alan?
Depends.
Do they have
a college prep program?
Eternal damnation is
no laughing matter.
I know—
I've been married twice.
(laughs)
You think you have to wear
a jockstrap in hell?
Yes, but not your own.
Anyway,
I just came down to tell you all
it's time to get dressed
for church.
Uh, uh, gee,
uh, thanks for the invite,
but, uh, Sunday is
kind of our "me" day.
Sunday's not a "me" day,
it's a "he" day.
And he will strike down the
blasphemers and the disbelievers
with fury
and blood-soaked vengeance!
So, chop-chop, washy-washy.
I've said it before,
and I'll say it again:
Boy, can I pick 'em.
♪ Men. ♪
CONGREGATION:
♪ Bringing in the sheaves
♪ Bringing in
the sheaves ♪
♪ We shall come rejoicing
♪ Bringing in the sheaves
♪ Bringing in the sheaves,
bringing in... ♪
Dad?
What?
I promise I'll work
really hard in school
if you can just
get rid of her.
A little religion
isn't gonna kill you.
Oh, really?
What's your definition
of "blood-soaked vengeance"?
♪ Bringing in the sheaves
♪ Bringing in the sheaves,
bringing in the sheaves ♪
♪ We shall come rejoicing
Why you looking
at me like that?
I just don't want to miss it
when you burst into flames.
♪ Bringing in the sheaves
♪ We shall come rejoicing...
Isn't this a beautiful
little church, Charlie?
Oh, yeah, it's great.
Listen, I thought maybe
after the service,
you and I could
drive around
and look for
a nice apartment for you.
Oh, God doesn't want us
to separate, Charlie.
He brought you
back into my life
so that we could be
together for all eternity.
Um, are those
his words or yours?
He speaks through me.
Oh, okay.
Um, to whom
am I talking now?
(music ends)
Oh, oh.
It's time for the
special blessing.
Come on, everyone,
let's go.
Right behind you.
(organ playing)
Come on, come
on, come on.
Blessing time,
blessing time.
Come on.
Is this the kind of church
where they hand out
those little crackers?
Shh!
I'm hungry.
Relax.
It's just us.
Oh.
Why is your hair all wet?
They tried to drown me.
No, they didn't.
He managed
to get himself baptized.
How'd that happen?
People were lining up.
I thought there was food.
Even after
they took your clothes
and gave you
a white robe?
I figured maybe
we were getting ribs.
So where's Berta?
She took a shine
to the organ player
and stayed for
the senior potluck brunch.
So there was food.
I knew I wasn't crazy.
Aren't you at all
concerned about
what happened to Miss Pasternak?
Of course I'm concerned.
I tried to hide, didn't I?
After she realized
that you had dumped
her yet again,
she had a little
bit of a meltdown.
There was more to melt?
She was dripping through the
cone when she left the house.
She grabbed all the bills
out of the collection plate
and started grinding
on the minister.
Okay. No harm, no foul.
How do you figure?
That's how
we found her, right?
Dry-humping
for dollars.
What happened to all your guilt
about ruining her life?
Oh, I still got it.
I'm just learning
to live with it.
You're unbelievable.
Oh, come on.
I tried to do
the right thing.
My intentions
were good.
That's the funny thing
about you.
Doesn't seem to matter
what your intentions are.
Good, bad or indifferent,
everyone around you
ends up suffering.
So it's not my
fault, right?
Right.
Come on, I'll
buy you a drink.
I'm really not in the mood.
Oh, relax.
It's all over.
Nothing to
worry about.