(both panting)
Oh, man.
That was intense.
I need some fluids.
I must have been down a quart.
Guess that makes you
up a quart, huh?
Hey.
You know what would be good
right now?
A pudding cup.
I got some in the fridge.
You want one?
(sobbing)
Um...
You have a bad experience
with pudding?
What are we doing, charlie?
Well, you're crying,
and my best guess
Is i'm about to apologize
for something.
Every time i come over,
it's the same routine.
We have chinese takeout.
Then we have sex.
Then we roll over
and go to sleep.
Which is why
i suggested the pudding.
You know, mix it up
a little.
Besides, what about all
the wonderful talking
And joking and, you know,
sharing we do?
Sharing?
What do we share, charlie?
Well, uh, we share
chinese takeout.
And, uh... Hey,
the other night,
We watched the laker game
together.
You watched it over my shoulder
while we were having sex.
Oh, come on. It was overtime.
What kind of relationship
is this?
We don't go anywhere.
We don't do anything.
Where do you want to go?
What do you want to do?
I can get laker tickets.
I don't want to go
to a basketball game!
I want to know who you are.
I want you to know who i am.
I know who you are.
You do?
Okay, what's my middle name?
Your middle name.
Okay.
I know this.
Sunburned boobs...
What?
Hang on. Hang on.
Sunburned boobs...
Red boobs, red breasts.
Robin.
Little memory trick.
My middle name is christine.
Not a very good trick.
Who's my best friend?
Where do i work?
What's my cat's name?
What's my favorite movie?
What kind of music do i like?
What religion was i raised in?
And do i have any
brothers and sisters?
Okay, i'd like to start
with the cat.
I'm gonna go with...
Fluffy.
Drop dead.
Snowball?
Mr. Mittens?
Tiger?
Whiskers, puss-Puss?
(door slamming)
Oh, come on.
What's my middle name?
Francis.
No, it's not.
Yes, it is!
Show-Off.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
Oh, chelsea, come on.
How much do i need
to know about you
Other than i'm
crazy about you?
It's not
that you don't know.
It's that you don't care.
I do care.
I just don't pay
close attention.
Good-Bye, charlie.
I mean, i pay attention,
but i don't test well.
Damn.
What did you do, bring out
the handcuffs too early?
Apparently, i don't know
her middle name.
It's christine.
How do you know?
She told me.
Why did she tell you?
I asked her.
Why did you ask?
How else do you get
to know a person?
Go away.
If a woman stormed out
on me after sex,
Would you go away?
That's beside
the point.
So, what happened?
I don't know.
We were having a nice night.
Little lo mein, little sex.
Then the crying started.
Oh, yeah.
Been there, done that.
No, she was crying.
She wants more
out of our relationship.
More what?
I'm not sure.
I know it's not pudding.
Well, what did she say?
She said i don't know
her well enough.
You tell me:
what's more important to know?
Her cat's name
or which of her body parts
You can't sneak up on?
Well, i'm not sure
One necessarily precludes
the other.
Yeah, well,
i've never been mule-Kicked
For not knowing a cat's name.
It doesn't matter.
There's more
where she came from.
Speaking of which...
Where does she come from?
I don't know,
and i don't care.
Davenport, iowa.
Bite me.
Want to know her cat's name?
No.
It's mandu.
Mandu?
Yeah, you know, cat mandu.
It's cute, huh?
Why was i thinking puss-Puss?
Because that's what
you're always thinking.
♪ Men.
What happened to all
the pudding cups?
I guess your uncle ate them.
All of them?
There were two 12-Packs.
Have something else.
No cookies?
What the hell is
going on around here?
Hey, watch your mouth.
I am watching it.
It's empty.
I need dessert.
Son of a bitch.
Jake!
Frozen peas?
What am i gonna do
with frozen peas?
Well, if you want dessert,
have an apple.
Not funny, dad.
♪ Men.
You sure i can't interest you
in a pudding cup?
Thanks.
I'm okay.
How about
a chocolate chunk cookie?
No, thank you.
Did you quit drinking?
God, no.
Why?
You seem to be experimenting
With a new sugar
delivery system.
Anything bothering you lately?
Well, there is this one thing,
But i don't know if it's medical
or psychological.
Tell me.
Lately, i've passed up
A couple of opportunities
to get some strange.
Strange?
Um...
Women with whom i have not
previously been acquainted.
Oh, right, strange.
Charming.
Go on.
Anyway, i was wondering if
there's something wrong with me.
Because you passed up
meaningless sex with strangers?
Exactly.
That's not like me.
Hey, you know, i bet "strange"
comes from "stranger."
I wouldn't be surprised.
So, what else is going on
with your life?
Not much.
I've been gaining a little
weight for some reason.
Maybe 'cause i haven't
been sleeping well.
Yeah, that's probably it.
Oh, and this one girl i've been
seeing pretty regularly
Decided to dump me.
Huh.
"huh," what?
Oh, nothing, it's just...
Sometimes i feel
like i'm stealing your money.
So, tell me about this woman.
Chelsea?
Not much to tell.
She's beautiful,
sexy, smart, independent.
Sometimes when she laughs,
She makes a little
snorting noise.
It's really cute.
Kind of like...
(giggling, snorting)
Not as cute when i do it.
Sounds like quite a catch.
She's okay.
Why did she dump you?
Who can understand
a woman's mind?
Yeah, we're pretty
little puzzles, ain't we?
So, it's not just me.
Anyway, for some reason,
She suddenly became dissatisfied
with our relationship.
Well, describe the relationship.
It was great.
She'd come over
a couple times a week.
Either she'd bring food
or i'd have something delivered.
We'd have sex, then eat.
Then, maybe have sex again,
depending on what was on tv.
And she became dissatisfied
with that?
I know, right?
Ooh.
Butterscotch.
So, how did you feel
about losing her?
What do you mean?
What do i mean?
Come on, charlie.
Dr. Seuss could diagnose this.
You're stuffing yourself
with crap
To suppress
your negative feelings.
No, i'm pretty sure
that's why i drink.
You have a choice here.
You can dig down
and confront your feelings
So they won't be controlling
your behavior,
Or you can keep eating pudding
and cookies
Until you have more chins
than a chinese phone book.
Hmm.
No, what else you got?
Do you have a better idea?
What if i could
get chelsea back?
That would only be
a temporary solution.
So?
That's what people said
about bourbon,
And we've been together
for almost 30 years.
Okay, you're right.
Go get chelsea back, and all
your problems will be solved.
I'm sensing sarcasm.
Oh, good, we're finally
making progress.
♪ Men.
Here you go.
What are you
drinking?
Chocolate caramel
frappuccino
With whipped cream
and sprinkles.
My nephew turned
me on to it.
You want some?
No, thanks, i had a hot fudge
sundae for breakfast.
Ooh, that sounds good.
(slurping)
Ah.
You look nice.
I've got to get back
to work, charlie.
What do you want?
I just wanted to see you.
See how you're doing.
I'm fine.
Good.
And how's your
family back in...
Davenport, iowa?
I'm from champaign, illinois.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Bastard set me up.
What?
Nothing, nothing.
I miss you.
I miss you, too,
but it doesn't matter.
Our relationship
wasn't going anywhere,
And you are incapable
of change.
It's not that i'm incapable.
I've just been unwilling.
Thanks for clearing that up.
No, no, no,
wait, wait, wait.
I've been seeing a shrink.
Really?
Yeah, and i'm making
a lot of progress
Confronting my— what do you
call them?-- Personal issues.
Well, i'm glad to hear it.
(tapping):
come.
Sit.
And check this out:
the shrink's a woman.
A real ballbuster.
I can't get away
with anything.
Ballbuster?
In a good way.
You know, a buster
of emotional balls.
You should meet her.
Are you suggesting we go
to couples counseling?
Um...
Sure.
I mean, i want to work
on our relationship,
And what better way
than couples counseling?
You're serious.
Well, of course
i'm serious.
What, you think i'd blurt
out something like that
In the spur of the moment
in a desperate attempt
To keep you from leaving?
It occurred to me.
Well, clearly, you don't know
me as well as you should.
All right.
Couples counseling.
Wow, i'm impressed, charlie.
(chuckling):
me, too.
Okay, i got to run.
Let me know
when our appointment is.
Sure thing.
Bye-Bye.
Oh, god, what have i done?
♪ Men.
Davenport, iowa?
Oh.
Uh, did i say davenport, iowa?
I meant champaign, illinois.
Okay.
That's one for you.
Thank you. (chuckles)
Ow!
And that's one for me.
Now, i need
some advice.
Oh, and just a friendly
heads-Up.
You screw with me again,
it's gonna cost you some teeth.
I'm listening.
Wait a minute.
What's this about?
Oh, he bought some stuff
with his own money,
And he doesn't want you
eating it.
Huh.
You've been to couples
counseling, right?
Yeah, why?
I'm going with chelsea,
And i need to know
what i'm getting into.
Oh, you're gonna love it.
I am?
Absolutely.
Once a week, you sit on a couch
with your significant other
While she snips off
your testicles,
Reaches up
inside your chest cavity
And goes like this...
To your heart.
That doesn't sound very good.
Oh, it's horrible.
But it's worth it
Because you're paying
a stranger to watch
While your life goes
down the toilet.
Along with your money
and your house and your car
And every last shred
of your self-Respect!
You know, maybe you're not
the right guy to ask.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, i'm the
perfect guy to ask.
When judith
and i started,
We were just a couple
with a few problems.
When we finished,
i came to live on your couch!
God bless couples counseling!
That better not be one
of my pudding cups.
Nope.
♪ Men.
(sighs)
Hi, charlie.
Come on in.
Shouldn't we wait for chelsea?
She's already here.
Really?
That seems a little ambushy.
Hi, sweetie.
You're late.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry.
But... (clears throat)
I have a good excuse.
Happy first day
of counseling.
You brought a present?
Yeah.
Isn't that the protocol?
No.
So...
You don't want
this bottle of champagne?
Bastard got me again.
Well, why don't we get started.
Hold on. Hold on.
Does the name "mandu"
ring any kind of a bell?
What?
I'm gonna kill him.
Well, why don't we start out
with why we're here
And what our goals are.
Chelsea, would you like
to go first?
Sure.
I want to know
if my relationship
With charlie
can be more than...
Sex, tv, and chinese food.
It can.
Right, doc?
Of course it can.
Thank you.
Well, this is good.
This is progress.
I have to say this has
been a very good session.
Where do you think you're going?
Nowhere.
Just...
Stretching my legs.
Charlie, before you got here,
chelsea mentioned
That she feels you've fallen
into a rut.
A rut?
We're not in a rut.
When's the last time
we did something new?
(sighs)
Hello?
Great... And what else?
Uh...
He's got nothing.
Excuse me, but if
this is gonna work,
You can't jump all over me
while i'm thinking.
I'm sorry. Go ahead.
Thank you.
I got nothing.
Okay, might i make a suggestion?
Would you be willing
to commit to chelsea
That maybe once a week,
twice a month,
You do something together
Completely outside
your comfort zone?
Done. No problem.
So, we could go
to the ballet,
The opera,
visit my parents,
Hang out
with my brother,
Go hiking
with my friends?
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I was thinking more like
renting a chick flick
And ordering italian.
This is hopeless.
No, no, no, no,
there's hope.
There's always hope.
Keep hope alive.
I can do those things.
Come.
Sit.
Charlie, has it ever
occurred to you
That you might enjoy
doing new things
And meeting new people?
I know i'm supposed
to say yes, but...
Every fiber of my body
is screaming, "no!"
All right, then i have to ask.
Given that you and chelsea
are such different people,
Why do you want to be
in this relationship?
Well...
'cause i'm crazy about her.
'cause, when i'm
with somebody else,
I'm thinking of her.
Not that i've been
with anybody else.
Tell her, doc.
He passed up strange.
See, that's got
to mean something,
Considering how i used to,
you know, live for strange.
First time
in the sack,
She was the strange.
Charlie, can i give you
my opinion as your therapist?
Sure.
Shut up.
Oh, god, i wish i could.
Chelsea, look.
I know i'm not perfect.
(chuckles)
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
That was probably
unprofessional.
Anyway,
You need to know
That you mean
everything to me,
And i'll do whatever it
takes to make this work.
You really mean that?
I do.
Thank you, charlie.
Well, this has been
very helpful.
Sit down, charlie.
We're not done?
Not even close.
Oh, boy.
What else could we possibly
have to talk about?
Well, there's always your mother
And the fact
that your relationship issues
Are linked to your anger
towards her,
As well as fear
of your latent homosexuality.
It was kind of
a rhetorical question.
♪ Men.
Alan:
charlie?
Yeah.
How was couples
counseling?
You really want to know?
Sure.
Tell me everything.
Oh!
Ow!
Why?
Why would you do that?
You know, i've been asking
myself the same thing,
And the only thing
i can come up with is:
It's really, really funny.
Go ahead.
Yuk it up.
Those were among the worst
50 minutes of my entire life.
I told you.
Didn't i tell you?
Yep.
You told me.
I bet you left with your gonads
in a guppy bag.
I didn't get a bag.
Going back next week?
Uh-Huh.
$180 an hour?
$240.
Ooh.
Licensed.
(chuckling)
You two kids
will patch things up in no time.
Hey, just because counseling
didn't help your relationships
Doesn't mean it won't help mine.
Right, right.
Keep drinking
that old kool-Aid.
Looking for something?
Don't screw with me, kid.
Now, hand over the pudding
or you'll be sorry.
Have an apple.
Little turd called my bluff.
(laughing)
(loud smack)
Alan:
ow!
♪ Men.