I really appreciate you
getting up so early
and driving me to work.
I owe you one.
You owed me one
when I didn't smother
you in your crib.
Well, then,
I owe you two.
My car will be out of the shop
in a couple of days.
There was a terrible knock
in the engine.
Like a... like a...
(imitating knocking)
I kept saying, "Come in,"
but nobody did.
(chuckling)
Ooh, carpool lane—
that's us.
We could...
Shut up.
Right.
It's 7:00.
Where are all these
damn people going?
I know, right?
I deal with that every day.
Very frustrating.
Sometimes I dream about buying
a cabin in the woods
and just getting away...
I said shut up.
Yes, you did.
The people going that way
should just switch jobs
with the people
going this way,
and everybody can leave their
freaking cars in the garage.
(chuckles)
You know, that's a...
that's a hell of an idea.
Right on.
Don't patronize me.
Sorry.
Wait a minute.
How are you getting back
to Malibu?
Uh, I...
I was, uh...
I was hoping...
No.
Charlie.
Take the bus.
There's no bus
from Tarzana to Malibu.
Then, take a series
of buses.
And don't get stuck on having
to end up in Malibu.
Charlie, come on. It...
it's just for
a couple of days.
That's what Mom said
when she brought you home
from the hospital.
(chuckling)
Good one.
(imitating Stan Laurel):
You're a very funny man, Ollie.
You certainly are.
It's Laurel and Hardy.
Boy, they used to...
they used to get
in some wacky jams, huh?
(laughing)
What about, uh...
uh, Abbott and Costello?
(imitating Costello):
"Hey, Abbott!"
Or, uh... or, uh,
Martin and Lewis?
(imitating Jerry Lewis):
"Hey, lady, with the flavin'
and the mavin' and the wow."
Three Stooges?
(imitating Curly)
"Nyuck, nyuck, nyuck, nyuck."
(laughing)
ALAN:
Whoa, what...
why are we stopping?
(punches landing)
Ow! Ow! Ow!
"Oh, a wise guy"... ow!
Okay, I don't mind
the good-natured
brotherly punching,
but you did not have
to twist my nipples.
You're lucky I
didn't rip them off
and feed them to you.
Um, you know, if you...
if you really have to go
to the bathroom, there's, uh...
there's one right
down the hallway.
What's wrong with the one
in your office?
Uh, it's not really for guests.
Neither is my house.
Um, you know, I think
we're out of paper towels.
I'll wipe my hands on you.
Get out of the way.
Morning, Dr. Harper.
Morning, Melissa.
Hello, Melissa.
You rat bastard.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
Good to know.
Hi, I'm Charlie,
Alan's brother.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Thought you had to tinkle.
Go away.
So, how long you been working
for my baby brother?
About six months.
Wow, he's been
keeping you a secret
for six months?
Charlie, can I talk to you
for a minute?
There's no reason
to thank me
for the ride again, Alan.
Mi Mercedes, su Mercedes.
It's what brothers do
when one is vastly more
fortunate than the other.
Seriously, we need to talk.
Excuse us.
Charlie, she is the best
receptionist I have ever had.
I'm hoping to say the same.
Come on, Charlie, please
do not crap where I work.
Hey, you crap where I live.
So tell me about her.
There's nothing to tell.
She's a...
she's a terrific employee.
She does my scheduling,
my books.
My patients love her.
She keeps the whole operation
running like clockwork,
and she does it all
for crappy pay and no benefits.
So you're not hitting that?
No, I'm not hitting that.
And even if I
were hitting that,
I wouldn't use the phrase,
"hitting that."
It's a violent image
for a beautiful act.
Yeah, yeah...
so the coast is clear?
No, the coast is not clear.
The coast is foggy
and strewn with
dangerously pointy rocks.
Can I get either of you
a cup of coffee?
Sure.
No.
No for both of us.
Please leave.
All right.
Bye, Melissa.
Bye, Charlie.
Hope I see you again.
Oh, you'll see me tonight
when I come back
to pick up your boss.
Oh, oh, no, Charlie, Charlie,
you don't have to make
that long drive.
I'll take the bus.
I thought there were no buses.
If I have to, I'll charter one.
Why don't I just give you
a ride home?
Oh, that
is so sweet of you.
You got a real gem here, Alan.
Tell you what,
when you get him home,
there will be a cold margarita
waiting for you out on my deck.
Which overlooks the ocean.
On the beach.
In Malibu.
That sounds wonderful.
It's really not:
it's chilly, damp,
and covered with pelican poop.
That's why he'll never win
the Malibu slogan contest.
(laughing)
See you tonight, Melissa.
Bye, Charlie.
Have a great day, bro.
I hate you.
I hate you, too.
Gee, your brother
is really cute.
As a bug.
Bathroom?
Oh, let me give you the key.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
You are a doll.
You are cute.
She's actually a doll.
I wonder if she's
anatomically correct.
♪ Men.
(Melissa giggling loudly)
Yeah.
Who's the Smurf?
The Smurf is my receptionist.
You're letting Charlie hit that?
Okay, look, first of all,
that is a very ugly phrase.
And second of all,
I'm not letting him.
I mean, short of drugging him
and dumping him in the woods,
what can I do?
Yeah.
He is like an Alabama bloodhound
once he gets a whiff.
(Melissa giggling)
Now it's just a matter
of waiting until it blows up
in my face.
And after it blows up
in my face,
it will then circle around
and bite me in the ass.
That's me.
No face, no ass.
Well, that's what you get
when you mix work
and personal.
Which is why me and Charlie
have always kept everything
strictly professional.
Yeah, yeah, I've often wondered
about that.
When I first started
to work here,
I laid down the law:
looky, no touchy.
Yipes.
All right, I'll
make you another,
but you got to promise
not to chug this one.
Promise!
What a fun gal.
Charlie, do you know
how hard it is
to find a decent
receptionist?
Well, kudos, bro,
you did a great job.
Thank you, and I-I really
don't want to lose her.
Why would you lose her?
Oh, gee, I don't know.
Maybe because my brother intends
to defile and discard her
like a warm melon.
A warm melon?
Nothing.
Anyway, my point is
that you're gonna leave her
with bad memories
that can only be erased
by removing herself
from anything that reminds her
of you— like me.
Is that what you're
worried about, Bunky?
Yes, that's
what I'm worried about.
What did you think
I was worried about?
What else
would I be worried about?
Well, let's see.
Your receding hairline,
your semi-literate son,
your budding man-boobs.
But that's just off
the top of my head.
Charlie, please,
I am begging you.
Look, I understand
your concerns,
but it's not like that.
I think Melissa is terrific.
You always think
they're terrific.
They're terrific before.
They're terrific during.
It's the after
when the crying
and the quitting start.
Why is it always about you?
Aren't I entitled
to some happiness?
You've had your share
of happiness.
You've had your
share of happiness,
my share,
everybody's share.
You've sucked the marrow
of happiness from the...
bones of...
Oh, just leave her alone,
won't you?
Alan, you don't
have to worry.
You're thinking about
the old Charlie,
the old-hump-'em-
and-dump-'em,
one-track-mind Charlie.
Oh, oh, right,
uh, the old Charlie
from way back this morning.
I'm serious.
I honestly want to start
building a relationship.
Really?
Yeah.
Get to know someone,
let her get to know me,
have something in common
before we jump into bed.
Wow, I'm impressed.
That I'm growing up?
No, that you can
so easily lie to my face.
You'll see.
It's gonna be different
with Melissa.
I'm gonna take my time,
form a friendship,
bond emotionally,
and then and only then,
take it to the next level.
(box springs squeaking)
MELISSA:
Oh, Charlie!
You schmuck.
♪ Men.
Morning, Dr. Harper.
Morning.
I like
your jammies.
Thank you, I,
uh, I like your...
thank you.
Guess you're kind of surprised
to see me, huh?
Yeah, shocked.
Well, I hope you know
it is not the kind of thing
I usually do—
you know, hop into bed
with a fella zippity-quick.
It's really none of my business.
Well, I don't.
But Charlie is
so sweet and special.
Yep, he's a treasure.
Yeah, and this works out
well for you.
Really? Uh, how do you figure?
Since your car is
still in the shop,
we can carpool
to and from work.
I see.
So, so you'll be coming back?
Oh, yeah.
Charlie asked me
to stay the weekend.
No kidding.
Yeppers.
We really made a connection...
and it is not just physical.
Although the physical part
is amazing.
Again, none of my business.
It is like I have known him
all my life.
I know the feeling.
You get over it.
Hey, baby.
Hey yourself.
Mmm.
Do I smell toast?
You do.
Would you like a slice?
I can put butter
and jelly on it.
Oh, déjà vu.
(yelps)
Stop it.
You're terrible.
Whoo!
(giggles, clears throat)
Sorry, Dr. Harper.
That's okay.
I wasn't even listening.
I'm going to take a shower.
Hit the road in
about 20 minutes?
I thought you were going
to call in sick.
Shush.
He's kidding.
It's okay.
20 minutes is fine.
Great.
(sighs)
Alan, you know me
as a cynical man,
but in just one night
that little pixie has melted
this cold, lonely heart.
You don't say.
You may not believe me,
but there is something
going on here,
and I really want to thank you
for bringing her into my life.
I may not believe you?
You know what?
Fine. Think what you want.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to go play
"Paul Bunyan takes a shower
in Tiny Town."
♪ Men.
Sorry we're
running late.
That's all right.
Shower lasted a bit longer
than I planned.
Yeah, well, uh,
that happens.
I got to tell you, I am just
crazy about your brother.
Swell.
Hope it works out.
How is a guy like that
still single?
Well, he's always been a bit
of a butterfly, you know,
fluttering through life,
hard to pin down.
And being a fall-down drunk
is kind of a speed bump
for some of the ladies.
(laughing):
You're such a jokester,
Dr. Harper.
(chuckles)
Either that
or put a gun in my mouth.
Oh, listen, on the
way home tonight,
we have to swing
by my apartment
so I can get some clothes
for the weekend.
Mm-hmm.
And I'm gonna need a little
extra time for lunch today.
I want to buy some
sexy lingerie... for you know.
I do.
Can I pick you
up anything?
Yeah, yeah, um,
ear plugs would be nice,
um, and that gun
I mentioned.
Nothing special.
I'm only going to use it
just the once.
(giggling)
Oh.
♪ Men.
(doorbell rings)
Hi, Jake.
Hey, got to hit
the crapper.
You must be Judith.
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
I'm Melissa,
Dr. Harper's receptionist.
We talk on the phone
all the time.
Oh, right, Melissa.
It's so nice
to finally meet you.
Alan!
Oh, oh, hey, hey, hi, uh, hi,
Judith, this is Melissa.
Melissa, Judith.
It's not what it looks like.
Charlie's doing her, not me.
And, uh,
where is Charlie anyway?
Taking a nap.
He says I drain him.
Isn't that adorable?
Adorable, disturbing, whatever.
Uh, thanks, I've got this.
Your brother
and your receptionist?
(sighs)
What do you want from me?
Th-The Volvo's in the shop,
he twisted my nipples
and peed in my office.
What?
I'm not thrilled
about this either,
but what can I do?
You could think
about the effect
these shenanigans have
on your adolescent son.
Okay, you know
what, Judith?
I have enough problems.
If you're not comfortable
leaving Jake here
for the weekend,
then take him home.
Nice try, Alan.
♪ Men.
You think Uncle Charlie
and Melissa
are coming down for lunch?
I doubt it.
Can I have their chicken?
Knock yourself out.
You know how you always say
I can ask you anything?
Yeah?
Is them being together
weird for you?
No, no.
Well, you're a better man
than I.
How so?
Well, you remember
when Uncle Charlie
was hittin' my
fifth grade teacher?
Okay...
can we please stop
calling it "hittin'"?
Well, I got another word,
but I don't think
you're going to like it.
Fine, fine,
then I, uh, I do remember
when he was... hitting
your fifth grade teacher.
That kind of bugged me.
Well, I'm, I'm sorry.
I mean, don't you think
there should be boundaries?
I do think that.
But I thought you
said it's not weird
that he's hittin'
your receptionist.
Ah, uh, w... uh, well, pal, um,
the thing is, um, Daddy lied.
Oh, then it is weird for you?
Yes, yes, it is weird for me.
Are you jealous?
Uh, no, no.
'Cause I was a little bit
jealous about Miss Pasternak.
She had a rockin' bod.
Eat your chicken.
♪ Men.
Melissa?
We, uh, need to get a move on.
A lot of traffic
what with the rain and all.
CHARLIE:
We need a minute, Alan.
Oh, God.
What can they do in a minute
that they didn't do all weekend?
MELISSA:
You are just
a selfish son of a bitch
and you can go
right to hell!
(sobbing)
Sorry, Dr. Harper.
I'll be in the car.
Well...
that could have gone better.
I knew it.
I thought it might take longer
than 48 hours, but I knew it.
Hey, hey, hey.
A little sensitivity
would be appreciated.
I'm hurting here.
I'm sure a lot of that
is friction burn.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where does that come from?
(scoffing):
Where does it come from?
It comes from
a long history
of you using my life
as a specimen cup.
Excuse me, but you're still
talking about the old Charlie.
This Charlie was hoping
to have a relationship
of substance and depth.
By locking a stranger
in your room and hittin' it
for two days straight?
Okay, mea culpa.
Change is hard.
And now that I'm hearing it,
I agree with you.
"Hittin' it" is an ugly term.
Don't change the subject.
What happened?
Nothing.
(gargles, spits)
I just said to her that maybe
we should slow things down,
see other people.
Wait, y-y-you said this
after the two days?
How could I know beforehand?
I thought you'd be happy.
You didn't want me to go out
with her in the first place.
Yes, but it's no longer
the first place.
It's the last place.
What can I tell you, Alan?
I made a mistake.
I rushed to love.
No, no,
your mistake was
you rushed to love
my receptionist,
the woman who I depend upon
to run my business.
Oh, she's a good kid.
She'll get over it.
(horn honking repeatedly)
You hear that? You hear that?
Does that sound like a woman
who's getting over it?
Well, Alan,
the wounds are fresh.
You're going to need
to be patient.
Why should I have to be patient?
Well, you have to work with her.
(horn honking)
And it sounds like
you'd better get going.
Sure you don't want
to come back to my office
and hump my fax machine?
Wow.
You still have a fax machine?
You're despicable.
Alan, wait.
What?
Let me make it up to you.
How could you possibly
make it up to me?
Well, I'm guessing
she won't be inclined
to bring you back here tonight.
So why don't you take a cab
and I'll pay for it?
Thanks.
That makes up for everything.
I'm talking cab, not Town Car.
(sighing):
Oh, man.
Break-ups are so hard.
Ow.
Huh.
I do have
a little friction burn.
♪ Men.
That miserable son of a bitch.
Might want to extend your
brake zone on the wet roads.
I'm so stupid.
No, no, no, no,
you are not stupid.
You're, you're a dear,
sweet, remarkably bright...
Truck, truck—
watch out for the truck.
Watch out for the truck.
(shrieking)
I want a raise.
Sure, sure.
And health insurance.
That's a given.
I-I can't believe
you don't have it already.
And a paid vacation.
Well, now, hang on a second.
There's only so mu...
(shrieking):
Two weeks, two weeks, two weeks!
♪ Men.