ReEncoded By Dr. XJ | PSA
www.PSArips.com
(crowd cheering,
whistle blowing over TV)
It seems to me
that it would be more fair
if everybody on both
basketball teams
was the same height.
That's how it
seems to you, huh?
Yeah, like in boxing.
Heavyweights
fight heavyweights.
Lightweights
fight lightweights.
So, in your world,
everybody on a basketball team
would be, say, 6'5",
and they'd only
play other teams
that were 6'5".
Exactly.
That way, no one would have
an unfair advantage.
Huh.
That's very interesting.
You really think so?
No, but it's less likely
to start a fight
than "That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard."
And yet,
you said it anyway.
Listen, I've got to talk
to you about something.
Okay, "dumb" was a
poor choice of words.
It's not about that.
Can it wait till halftime?
No.
(mutes TV)
I've got to go
to a funeral this weekend.
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
Who died?
My ex-mother-in-law.
That couldn't wait
till halftime?
Charlie.
I'm just saying she'll
still be dead at halftime.
I was very close to her
and I want to pay my respects,
so I'm going to Santa Barbara,
and I'll be spending the weekend
with my ex-husband.
Oh, okay.
(TV audio resumes)
ANNOUNCER:
They certainly are very...
Define "with."
Well, everyone's staying
at his parents' house.
All right... well, do you
want me to come with you?
No.
Great.
ANNOUNCER:
But, once again, Barry,
most of...
Why not?
Do you want to come?
Hell, no.
That's what I figured.
Look, I just want
to be up-front with you.
I was married to Alex
for eight years,
and I just don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
I wouldn't have had any idea
if you hadn't felt
the need to tell me.
Yeah, well,
I don't want us
to have any secrets
from each other.
Oh, I agree.
We definitely should
not have secrets.
Right.
You know, from this
point forward.
ANNOUNCER:
had control of the ball
and lost the...
What kind of guy is this Alex?
He's a good guy.
We just got married
too young
and wanted
different things.
He wanted something
different than your things?
'Cause your things
are terrific.
Thank you.
ANNOUNCER:
Some golden opportunities
to score.
He didn't go gay
on you, did he?
No.
Rats.
Are you jealous?
No, no.
Of course not.
I mean, maybe a little.
You know, in the sense
that his mother's dead.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
I miss you, too, honey.
How was the funeral?
Yeah, I guess
they're all pretty sad.
Probably why they don't
call them fun-erals.
(chuckling)
Yeah, that was lame.
So, where are you now,
at the house?
And where is your ex-husband?
And where is his room
in relationship to yours?
Hey, hey, it's got nothing
to do with jealousy.
I just know, based on a lifetime
of experience,
that penises do not observe
a traditional mourning period.
Forget it, you are not
driving my car
until you get
a learner's permit.
Not even in the driveway?
Not anywhere.
What if you have
a heart attack?
Can I drive you
to the hospital?
No, call an ambulance.
Fine.
If they don't get
here in time,
can I have your car?
Hey.
There's my posse.
What are we doing
tonight, boys?
Think big. It's my treat.
Drunk?
Probably.
Where is Chelsea?
She had to go out of town.
Oh, so your girlfriend's
gone for a couple of days.
Now, suddenly, you
have time for us?
Yeah.
You ever think that maybe Jake
and I already have plans?
That our lives go on
even when you're not around?
That we don't just pop
into existence
the moment you need us?
I'm free.
Me, too.
I'm just making a point.
So, what's it going to be?
A movie, bowling?
Putt-putt, Nevada cathouse?
I vote for cathouse.
Do you even know
what a cathouse is?
Not firsthand.
That's why I voted for it.
A movie would be fine.
All right, a movie it is.
What's out that's good?
There's a new pirate movie.
It's rated "Arr!"
You guys have no sense of humor.
♪ Men.
Can we go to
that new theater
with the reserved seats
and the jumbo kosher hot dogs?
You just finished
dinner.
That doesn't mean
I finished eating.
Hey, Charlie.
Wanda...
what are you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood,
and I'm drunk and horny.
New plan.
♪ Men.
Have I met
this one before?
I doubt it.
She looks familiar.
Blond, busty, and bombed?
Around here, that's familiar.
I thought Uncle Charlie
liked Chelsea.
He does.
Well, then, what's he doing
with Wanda?
Well, buddy, it's like this.
Uh, despite his many
admirable qualities,
your Uncle Charlie is,
at heart, a sleazeball.
That's what I figured.
I just wanted a second opinion.
Hang on.
I'll grab another bottle.
Broad is part camel.
Except the humps
aren't on her back.
Oh, come on.
That was funnier
than "Rated arr!"
(sighs)
Look, I know you're upset,
but I'll take you
to the movies
some other time.
This has nothing to do
with the movie.
Then what's the problem?
The problem
is you're a sleazeball.
Really? How so?
Oh, please.
You're in a committed
relationship
with a wonderful woman,
and the minute
her back is turned,
you're out gallivanting.
Gallivanting?
Screwing around.
Then, why don't you just say,
"Screwing around"?
Hey, as we speak, Chelsea is
doing the same thing I'm doing.
Oh, really?
She's pouring liquor
down the throat
of an inebriated party girl?
Inebriated?
Drunk.
Geez, who are you
showing off for?
At this moment,
Chelsea is in the same house
as her ex-husband.
Why?
His mother died.
Oh, my apologies.
Clearly, anything you do
at this point is justified.
No, it's not.
I was being disingenuous.
What?
Sarcastic.
You know, this is why Mom
gets pissed off at you so much.
Look.
Charlie, do what you want.
If you can live with yourself,
more power to you.
If I could live with myself,
we'd be having this conversation
by telephone.
See, him I understand.
Charlie, bed, now, come.
Succinct, ain't she?
Does "succinct" mean
what I think it means?
I highly doubt it.
Hello?
Right here, baby.
(loud thudding)
Are you okay?
Yeah, why?
Never mind. (clears throat)
Come on.
Let's get you
into bed.
(sighs)
Thank you.
Hey, you remember
when we were in Vegas
and I talked that cute waitress
into joining us?
Yeah, I do.
I saw her last week
at the Hard Rock.
No kidding.
She gained a lot of weight.
Is that so?
Yeah, we were lucky.
We nailed her right before
she quit smoking.
Listen, Wanda, uh...
She does smell better, though.
I'm sure, but listen...
Like Fritos.
You know what?
I got to...
check on something.
Well, is it okay
if I start without you?
Top drawer, nightstand—
take your pick.
Ooh.
Careful.
The big one's
a flashlight.
That was fast.
I'm guessing.
You're right.
I'm a sleazeball.
Don't tell me you actually
had a moral epiphany.
Uh, "epiphany"
means...
Don't bother.
I don't know what
you call it,
but I've got a gorgeous,
willing girl in my bed,
and I'm just
not interested.
Maybe you're a gay sleazeball.
I'll tell you
what's going on.
You care about Chelsea
too much
to cheapen
your relationship
with a meaningless
one-night stand.
You're right.
I do care about Chelsea.
I'm crazy about her.
Boy, that sucks.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Oh, hey, Chelsea,
we were just...
Give me that.
Hey, baby,
what's going on?
He did?
At his own mother's funeral?
Her ex-husband put
the moves on her.
What a sleazeball.
No, no, no,
don't blame yourself.
You were right
to go to the funeral.
Tonight?
(stammering):
I'd love to see you tonight,
but... isn't it a little late
to drive all the way
from Santa Barbara?
Oh, you're already on the road.
Oh, that close?
Wonderful.
Drive safe.
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap.
Crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap...
Remember when I was little and
every time someone said "crap",
they had to put a dollar
in the swear jar?
I do.
Whatever happened
to all that money?
Wanda, I don't want you
to take this the wrong way,
but you got to get the hell
out of here.
Come on. Chop-chop.
Wanda?
(smacks lips)
Wanda...!
(snores)
Oh, darn.
*Men. ♪
♪ Men.
So the car's
a time machine?
Yeah, it's called
a DeLorean.
They don't make 'em
anymore.
CHARLIE:
Crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, crap, crap, crap, crap.
Help. I need help.
Oh, my God, w-what happened?
What's wrong?
Wanda passed out
and Chelsea's on her way over.
Interesting story
about the DeLorean.
It was built by a man named
John DeLorean.
Are you not listening to me?
I've got an emergency here.
A dead girl in your bed
is an emergency.
A passed-out girl
is a dinner date.
I still don't understand why
it's called Back to the Future.
Because they're stuck
in the past,
and they have to get back...
Home.
Oh, for God's sake, come on!
My girlfriend's on her way over,
and I've got a half-naked broad
upstairs!
Half-naked. I'm your man.
Sit down.
Have you tried
waking her up?
Well, of course
I've tried waking her up.
This is not my first
drunk bimbo!
So, what do you expect us to do?
I expect you to help me get her
dressed and drive her home.
Enough talk.
Let's get to it.
I said, sit down.
Where does she live?
I have no idea.
So, how am I supposed
to drive her home?
Oh, come on. Do I have to think
of everything? Just help me!
(sighs)
All right.
Wow.
Oh, and I'm a sleazeball?
You're-You're misreading
my-my "wow."
I meant "Wow, what
a predicament."
Yeah, right.
You hold her up.
I'll put her dress on.
Okay.
She's very fit.
(grunts)
Hold her arms up.
Really soft skin.
Uh-huh.
Hmm. Smells nice, too.
Okay, why don't you just put
a chloroform-soaked handkerchief
over her face and throw her
in the back of your panel van?
Sounds like a waste
of chloroform, doesn't it?
Okay, you get her head;
I'll get her feet.
Why do you get her feet?
What difference does it make?
I like feet.
Just get her head.
Okay, on three.
One, two, three.
Three. Oh! Oh! Oh!
Goodness. Aah.
(panting)
Slowly, slowly.
Slowly, my ass. Come on.
Let's get her out of here.
Charlie. Charlie...!
Oh!
(thudding)
Goodness gracious,
these are real.
♪ Men.
Slowly. Slowly.
(doorbell rings)
Quickly. Quickly.
Hi, baby.
Come on in.
Oh, Charlie, you were
so right about Alex.
Alex?
Oh, yeah. Alex.
What a sleazeball.
Can I get you something
to drink?
No. I just want to get
in bed and hold you.
Oh, boy, does that sound good.
Let me just say
good night to Jake.
Okay. I'll meet you upstairs.
You know what?
Why don't you come
say good night, too?
Why?
Well, you're my girlfriend,
and he's my nephew,
and... isn't that enough?
Hey, Jake...
Might want to
hang back a sec.
I just ripped off
an air biscuit.
What?
I farted.
Sorry. I get the fancy words
from my dad.
Anyway, Chelsea and I just
wanted to say good night.
Okay.
He keeps his feelings
bottled up.
Everything else he shoots
into the atmosphere.
Hi, Chelsea.
Hi, Alan.
Uh, sorry to hear
about your ex-mother-in-law.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, hey, Jake.
I could really use
your help.
With what?
I'm taking out the... Whew!
I'm taking out the trash.
What are you talking about?
The trash.
I'm taking it out,
and I could use your help
carrying it.
Oh. So now you want my help?
Yes, now I want your help.
What about the 20 bucks
you owe me?
Charlie?
Here.
Is the trash still out
where you can see it?
Never mind.
Just go help your father.
Fine.
Nice seeing you, Chelsea.
Good night.
I could have said 50,
couldn't I?
Could have said a hundred.
Can we please go
to bed now?
Beds are for amateurs.
Oh, Charlie.
(sniffing)
What if Jake comes back?
We'll breathe
through our mouths.
She really does
look familiar.
Terrific. Just don't drop her.
I can't wait to tell my friends
about this.
You're not telling anybody
What's the point of doing it
if I can't tell anybody?
You've got 20 bucks
and a memory. Now shut up.
Okay, we've got
to get her in the car.
You want me to pull it around?
No, I don't want you
to pull it around!
Okay, well, then, you pull it
around, I'll stay here with her.
But be very careful.
CHELSEA:
Come on, let's
finish this upstairs.
Move, move, move!
Chelsea, wait.
What?
I'm so happy you're back.
Hey.
Oh, hey, Alan.
Is the trash out?
Uh, almost.
Almost ain't
gonna cut it.
Did you at least
clean out my room?
Yes, I did.
Good. Good.
Okay, well, good night.
Uh, Charlie, can I talk
to you for a sec?
About what?
Um... uh, recycling.
I'm not quite sure
what to do with the...
big jugs.
Oh. Honey, why don't you go up
and get comfortable,
and I'll be right there?
Hurry.
I will.
Okay, first you need to separate
the plastic from the glass.
Then when you get
to the newspaper...
What the hell is your problem?
She's in Jake's room.
What am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
Here's my credit card.
Take her to a hotel
or something.
Okay. Chain motel
or someplace nicer?
What?
You know, uh, room
service, ocean view.
That way when she
regains consciousness,
she won't feel so cheap.
Plus, in the
nicer places,
you have a free
continental breakfast.
Assorted pastries, coffee,
freshly squeezed orange juice...
I know what
a continental breakfast is!
Just get her the hell
out of here!
Okay, fine.
Oh, Charlie?
What?
I'm a little low on gas.
Use the card!
Right, right, right.
Charlie?
What?
I'm really happy you're trying
to make it work with Chelsea.
Go!
What the hell are you doing?
You said I could have a memory.
This is it.
Give me the phone.
Oh, good idea.
I can't get us both
in the frame.
Can you make it look like
we're talking to each other?
Forget the picture.
We have to bring the car around.
Shouldn't someone
stay here with Wanda?
Yeah, but it shouldn't be you.
Give me the keys.
You said I could
pull it around.
I changed my mind.
Okay. I'll tell Mom about Wanda.
One ding, one scratch,
and you're dead.
Dude, mellow out.
You'll give yourself
a heart attack.
(sighs)
Hey, look!
It's me!
I'm glad you came back.
I don't like it
when you're gone.
when I'm gone, either.
Oh. Here they are.
Funny story.
♪ Men.
Why do you get
to take her feet?
Because I'm in charge
of this operation,
and I like feet.
Hey.
I guess we don't have
to take her to a hotel, huh?
No, we don't.
Quick, get in the car.
Where are we going?
Anywhere we want. We've got
Uncle Charlie's credit card.