This is waht they call slightly irregular?
- Fran! Fran!
- Yeah, honey.
- Does it show yet?
- Wait a second.
What are you talking about? Does what show?
That I'll be sixteen next week.
Oh, oh, honey.
Gee, I felt just like my mother
when I told her I lost my virgin...
airline tickets.
What, did they give you another one?
Oh, no honey.
When you loose that ticket,
it's non-refundable.
Unless you get engaged to Prince Charles
and then it miraculously reappears.
Oh Maggie, we gotta plan something
special for your sweet sixteen.
You know with my panache
and your father's checkbook
we could...
we could be two chicks ***.
Well, dad hasn't said
anything about my party,
all he does is pinch my cheek
and call me his almost-grown-up little girl.
With this lame grin.
Aww.
There she is,
my almost-grown-up little girl!
I can't believe how big
you've gotten already.
You know, it only seems like yesterday
I was putting you on Mr. Potty.
Dad, you're making me vomit.
Do you remember our favorite game?
Here comes Mr. Snake.
Ooh! Hello.
That's funny. That was my ex-boyfriend
Danny's favorite game, too.
You know, dad, for Tiffany's sweet 16,
her dad flew all of her
friends to South Africa
and even got Whitney Houston to sing.
Ok, if Maggie gets a sweet
16, I'd like a bar mitzvah.
Brighton, you're not Jewish.
You know, a sizable
donation to Temple Emmanuel
could take care of that.
Let's go, Grace.
Well, Margaret, how does this
sound for your sweet sixteen?
Very famous,
exquisitely decorated,
visited by royalty...
♪♪
Oh, they make a shrimp-scampi
made out of scrod, mwah.
Miss Fine, what royalty would you see at **.
Oh, well, excuse me,
at my cousin ** wedding,
the ballroom right next door,
Prince Matchabelli convention.
Who looks stupid now?
Margaret, I have booked the
solarium at the Guggenheim Museum.
Gloria Vanderbilt just
had a big party there.
♪♪
I think I might be able
to pull a few strings.
You like **, hmm?
Let's just hope he's in town.
Oh, Fran, what are the odds of
me dying in my sleep tonight?
Not good enough.
My party is gonna be so boring and stuffy.
All my friends are gonna hate it.
Oh, don't worry sweetie,
no one will come.
♪ she was working in a bridal
shop in Flushing, Queens ♪
♪ til her boyfriend kicked her out ♪
♪ in one of those crushing scenes ♪
♪ what was she to do,
where was she to go? ♪
♪ she was out on her fanny ♪
♪ so over the bridge from
Flushing to the Sheffield's door ♪
♪ she was there to sell make
up but the father saw more ♪
♪ she had style, she had
flair, she was there ♪
♪ that's how she became the nanny ♪
♪ who would have guessed
that the girl we described ♪
♪ was just exactly what
the doctor prescribed? ♪
♪ now, the father finds her
beguiling, watch out C.C. ♪
♪ and the kids are actually
smiling, such joie de vivre ♪
♪ she's the lady in red when
everybody else is wearing tan ♪
♪ the flashy girl From flushing,
the nanny named Fran ♪
- created, synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Well, what did they say?
The sweet 16 is all set at the Guggenheim.
The curator and I were
in the same sorority.
Delta Felta Guy?
C.C., you are amazing.
I don't know how you do it!
Oh, Maxwell, stop!
You know I adore the children
like they were my very own...
especially...
you know, the big one.
Ok, now remember, honey.
Be strong. We got to stick together.
He can't say no to both of us. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Ok.
Mr. Sheffield,
- we have something that we want to tell you.
- Mm-hmm.
We who?
Well, m... oh, boy. I
taught that kid too well.
Now don't get offended, I don't
want to hurt your feelings.
You don't like the new
curtains in your room.
Fine. We'll replace them.
All right.
Now what?
Well, there is one other thing,
you know, besides the wallpaper.
Maggie hates the Guggenheim.
You're going to have to cancel. Bye.
W... wait! What are you talking about?
The Guggenheim's a perfect
place for the party.
Just picture it...
Margaret coming down that grand foyer,
long white gloves,
pink satin gown.
While Cathy adores a minuet,
a ballet russe, and crêpe suzette,
our Patty likes to rock 'n' roll.
So you're saying I have to
come up with another idea.
Oh, well, you're so close!
Actually, I have to come
up with another idea.
She wants me to take over from here.
Maxwell, I bent over
backwards to get the museum.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time.
All right, Miss Fine.
Let's just cut to the chase, shall we?
Where have you already decided
to have my daughter's party?
Tantuh Frieda's.
What on earth is a tantuh frito?
Not frito. Frieda.
My father's sister owns
a nightclub in Queens.
Oh, well, that sounds...
dreadful, Miss Fine!
No. Actually, it's gorgeous.
It used to be a restaurant,
but it went out of business.
Whose bright idea it was
to open up a Tony Roma's
in a hasidic neighborhood I'll never know!
Oh, boy, does this bring back memories.
I used to hang out at this bar,
wear really short skirts and big,
teased-up hair and way too much makeup on.
Ah, well. Times change.
I would have given anything
to have my sweet 16 party here.
Why?
I mean, why didn't you?
Because my mother wouldn't let me.
She and Frieda had a big fight,
and they haven't talked since 1979.
That must be awful.
It's destroying them.
They both gained 40 pounds,
and they can't even rub
it in each other's faces.
Hello!
Watch this.
Health inspector!
Just one moment!
Here you go.
Franny! It's you!
Hi! Hi, aunt Frieda.
Mmm mmm mmmwah!
Oh, you must be Maggie.
You're too thin.
So how's your father?
Oh, he's great. So's ma.
Oh. She's still alive?
Be nice.
Maggie, you know, Aunt
Frieda's a celebrity.
She once sang on Merv Griffin's Show.
Don't embarrass me.
Twice.
Now I work here.
When you're a woman alone,
you got to earn a living.
Frieda buried four husbands.
The perpetual care alone
is enough to choke a horse.
At least I got them all in one plot,
so holy days... I'm in, I'm out.
So talk to me.
You like?
Uh, Fran, let's not completely
rule out the Guggenheim, ok?
Oh, honey, honey, I think
I can help you visualize.
I once worked here one
summer when I was 15.
Shh! I'll lose my license.
Frieda, if you didn't lose your license
for water bugs, I could double as bouncers.
[disco music plays] Oh, now I get it!
This is like one of those discos!
My party can be retro.
Hey, Fran, maybe we can even dress
up like they did in the olden days.
- Yeah!
- Did you save your stuff?
No, when I transferred from
the Pinta to the Santa Maria,
they lost my luggage.
Here. Here's a menu so you can plan.
Oh!
Aw, you don't have the Tony
Manera Marinara no more?
No.
Now it's the Ed Marinaro Marinara.
Damn butterflies!
Fran, if your mother and
your aunt don't get along,
won't she be upset you're
planning a party here?
Oh, honey, your sweet 16 has
nothing to do with my mother.
What could she possibly be upset about?
Let me go, I want to die!
Ma!
No! You are not my daughter!
Well, then who gave me these
thighs so I can shoot them?
How could you do this to me?
Ma, you have nothing to do with this.
I have nothing to do with my
daughter's boss' daughter's sweet 16?
Fran, if you have the party
at Frieda's, I am not going!
Good, ma, 'cause you are not invited!
Not invited?
You hear this, morty?
I'm not invited!
Your sister got me blackballed
like she did at Hadassah!
Ma, Frieda didn't get you blackballed.
They threw you out of Hadassah
because you donated cakes with
half the frosting licked off.
I felt lightheaded in the car.
She has turned you against me.
I don't want to know from that woman.
Is she bigger than me?
Ma!
This isn't about you and Frieda.
It's about Maggie.
It's her party, and it's all about her.
- Fran...
- Butt out, honey.
Now this stupid fight has
already ruined my graduation
because I couldn't have it at Frieda's.
And it was still lovely.
We had it al dente.
That means outdoors.
Fran, that sounds sort of nice.
Oh, yeah?
We had it on Grandma Yetta's
roof of her old building.
Middle of June. 114 degrees.
People stayed all night.
That's because they were stuck to the tar!
Fran, I really want my party at Frieda's,
but not if it's gonna come
between you and your mom.
Huh?
Oh, I feel terrible. I'm being so selfish.
Yeah, well.
You're only 16 once.
Never mind me.
Have the party wherever you want.
Oh, ma,
you're just saying that to
try and make me feel guilty.
I'm not trying to make you feel anything.
Feel this. Is this a lump here?
Did you pick up Miss Margaret's
present for Mr. Sheffield?
No, I spent the entire day
driving around Greenwich, Connecticut,
looking for that damn jewelry store.
Oh, did I say Greenwich, Connecticut?
I meant Greenwich Village.
That's 10 minutes away, you boob!
Well, you'd better hurry before they close.
Oh, this is ridiculous!
I don't know why that
stupid store doesn't deliver!
Oh.
They do.
Oh, dear. I wonder if I can catch her.
Oh, Miss Babcock.
♪ Miss Babcock ♪
Oh, Niles, I'm gonna have to tell Mr.
Sheffield I'm backing out of the party.
It's turning out to be a real disaster.
Oh, what's the matter, can't get
the 10-foot hero through the door?
You know, Niles, if you're
not part of the solution,
you're my mother.
Nah, I'm just gonna have to bite
the bullet and tell him the truth.
Miss Fine!
Oh! Uh...
burnt down?
Aunt Frieda, what are we
gonna do about Maggie's party?
Well, I guess I'll just have
to see if Mr. Sheffield...
Damn call waiting. So loud.
I want the truth, and you
have exactly five seconds.
Maggie wants to have it at Aunt Frieda's,
and Aunt Frieda said ma can't come,
and ma said if I have it there,
she'll never talk to me again.
Oh you're growing your
hair long. It's very sexy.
Miss Fine!
All right. All right!
If you'll just remain calm,
I will answer all of your questions.
How did your mother get mixed
up in his daughter's sweet 16?
I said I would answer all of his questions.
All right.
If we can't have the party there,
then what do you propose we do?
Hmm?
Well, I was thinking about the Guggenheim.
It's gone! I just canceled it!
What did you do that for?
It sounded so lovely with the grand foyer,
long white gloves, pink satin gowns.
What are you looking for?
The murder confession I
wrote the night I hired you.
Margaret has her heart
set on tantuh fajita,
so you better bloody well make it happen!
[Doorbell rings] Hello.
Wow!
Get a load of this joint.
If I knew it was so fancy, I would
have slipped on the stairs outside.
Aunt Frieda, you're
late. Where have you been?
I wanted to talk to you
before she gets here.
Who?
Hi!
Her.
What is she doing here?
She invited me!
You're not welcome here!
Fine! I'm leaving!
Block them. They're getting away!
Noooooo!
Cake!
See the nice frosting?
And it's chocolate, not
yellow on the inside.
Come on, Frieda. Come on, ma.
Come to the couch.
Sit down.
Sit...
Sit down. That's good, girls.
No! No treats until I tell you.
First we're going to talk.
You want to talk? Fine.
I'll be the bigger person.
Drop dead.
Cook for me, and I will.
Your father was the
first bulimic in flushing.
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoo ooh ooh ooh ooh!
Ooh!
I want to find out how
this whole feud got started.
Well, it was, uh...
- Lots of things.
- Plenty of stuff.
You know, I don't believe you two yentas.
You don't even remember.
What happened? You were both so close!
Do you remember at that wedding
when your *** wiglet caught on
fire from Uncle Zev's cigar?
Who was the one that poured
the celery dish on your head?
It was an emergency.
Anybody would have done the same.
And do you remember at
little Irvie's bar mitzvah
when there was only one
end cut of prime rib left,
who took the middle?
I know how she loves it,
and it didn't mean that much to me.
Oh, Frieda, she's right.
Have the party with my blessing.
And you'll come and you'll dance.
Oh, you lost so much weight!
Aw, now, you see?
This is the way it should be,
hugging, not trying to screw each
other out of Grandma Fine's pearls.
She took my mother's pearls?
I have to sleep with her son!
Whoa there!
Chocolate sauce!
Well, Miss Fine, you certainly seem
to have outdone yourself this time.
Thank you.
So what are your plans for later,
going to raffle off a Ford Granada?
Very funny.
Why don't you just admit
that this place is fabulous?
What's that on the bar?
Where?
Milk dud.
Oh, gee, I hope Aunt Frieda took the
vending machines out of the bathrooms.
What vending machines?
Daddy, can I have a dollar?
- You can buy balloons in the bathroom.
- Honey, honey, go boogie.
So who does your hair?
I wish I could get that heighth.
Oh, please. I wish I had your voice.
I swear, I close my eyes,
it's Julie Budd.
- Oh, wait, Frieda!
- What?
You're giving everyone a
show they didn't pay for.
Ma, didn't you see? Why
didn't you say something?
Oh...
Now I remember.
That's what started all this.
We were at Irwin and Cookie's 25th.
I'm on the dance floor doing the alley cat
with my tush hanging out
for the whole world to see,
and she didn't say one word!
What do you want from me?
I'm oblivious sometimes.
Sometimes?
You are so focused on your rear.
Meanwhile, you got two
watermelons for sale up front!
What?
You're jealous 'cause I worked on Broadway.
And who could forget your big line?
Goobers or raisinettes?
Oh, good, Frieda. Calm down.
What... what... no, no!
Ma, ma, please, think of... no! No!
Are you two nuts?
You're trying to start a food fight?
Food fight!
Miss Fine.
♪ Oh, Miss Fine ♪
Oh, I see you found the camera.
Miss Fine...
What happened?
Why do you always think something happened?
Lovely party.
I am gone two seconds and Bedlam erupts!
Maxwell.
She started it, sir.
I wanted this to be perfect,
a-and just look what you've done!
Go ahead! Go ahead, look at this mess!
Oh, I know.
Bad nanny. Bad nanny!
I'm sorry, Mr. Sheffield.
Oh, save it, Miss Fine.
It's not me you should be apologizing to.
It's Margaret. She's the one
whose party you've ruined!
Fran, we were all having
such a wonderful time!
Who's the idiot who turned on the lights?
Do you know, Mr. Sheffield?
No, I... I went to get the camera.
Aunt Frieda, hit the breaker.
Oh, Fran, all my friends say
this is the best party ever.
Thank you so much for being so cool.
And dad,
well, thanks for paying for it.
I... now, Miss Fine...
Miss... Miss Fine!
Remember who signs your check.
Oh Mr. Sheffield,
I'm not gonna hit you with this.
Fake out!
Friends?
All right. Friends.
Come here!
- created, synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -