The tea in Nepal is very hot.
"But the coffee in Peru
is much hotter."
Last week,
I finally became permanent
manager of Dunder Mifflin,
Scranton!
My first project,
increase security.
I got these doors
from a jewelry store
that had recently
gone out of business.
Now they're protecting
America's real treasure, papefl
Every morning, I e-mail
the day's security codes.
Something that's
been really missing
from my life has been
writing secret codes.
It's not the KGB,
but it's a start.
The tea in Nepal is very hot.
But the coffee in Peru
is far hotter.
Close.
This is Tuesday, right?
The coffee in Paraguay
is far hotter?
Colder.
The coffee in Paraguay
is colder?
No, I meant you
were getting colder.
The correct response is, "The
coffee in Peru is much hotter."
Ah. "Much," okay.
But that's three wrongs, so
I've got to give you the steam.
No. Unless you want
me to break protocol.
No, no. Give me the steam.
It's just harmless
steam to panic intruders.
I'd like to get harmful steam,
but the prices are absurd.
Break protocol!
Oh, I'm saving
a fortune on dry-cleaning.
Mama.
Angela, someone wants you.
Okay. Coming.
Hi, baby.
Angela's divorce
from the Senator
has been very
difficult for her.
When she got kicked
out of her apartment,
I invited her to
move in with me.
Ironic that now it's Angela
who's living in the closet.
Hey-o!
Saddle shoes with denim?
I will, literally, call
Child Protective Services.
Go get 'em, honey.
Don't worry.
They'll get got.
Manager of
Dunder Mifflin? Check.
Owner of a 1,600
acre beet farm? Check.
Engaged to be married to an
actual milk maid? Check...
on that later today.
This is
my grandmother's ring.
It was made from a bullet I
took out of her left buttock.
She was a moonshiner
shot by Adolph Coors.
This is my grandmother's
buttock bullet ring.
Hi. Good morning.
Name is Andrew Bernard.
You might know me from a TV documentary
that's premiering tonight.
Also killed it
in local theater
and I'm fresh off of
a hot industrial flick.
Okay. Thanks.
Go ahead and get in
the back of the line.
Yes!
Well, I burned all
my bridges at Dunder Mifflin,
and time to become
the next American Idol
by winning America's Next
A Cappella Sensation
on Channel TBD!
It's a really cool show.
It's like a total
reinvention of
the whole American Idol,
Voice, Sing-Off phenomenon.
On this show all
three judges are mean!
Sales form for
you to sign.
You know what to do.
Okay-
Behind every
great regional manager
is a great assistant
to the regional manager.
And I have chosen
one of the best.
Aw. Thanks, man.
Once upon a time,
we were natural enemies.
But we've overcome
our differences,
much like Germany and Italy,
in World War...
Nope.
Good call.
Together we run
a no-nonsense office.
Pre-conference room meeting
with Dwight went really well.
Oh! Bodes well for the
post-conference room meeting.
All depends on the conference
room meeting itself.
Okay-
Was that them again?
Yeah.
Maybe you should
call them back.
I will.
The guys at Athlead
are still bugging me
about this
three-month road show thing.
Meeting athletes on their home
turf, building relationships.
Yeah, it sounds exciting. But
I said no, and that's final.
I almost lost Pam over this business.
I'm not risking that again.
When Jim decided
to come back to
Scranton full time,
I was relieved
but I also feel
a little guilty.
I mean, he's giving up
this big thing for me.
But he seems happy. He's certainly
been goofing around a lot.
I love goofy Jim.
Welcome.
He welcomes you.
Please
take an agenda item.
Your agenda-taking
pleases him.
Have a seat, Phyllis.
Here we go.
As you know, I like to begin each
day with an inspirational quote.
Some say, the only failure there
is, is the failure to try.
That is wrong.
Failure of any kind is failure.
Jim, over to you.
Let's not get crazy and ruin
our no-nonsense streak.
All right? So, for instance, if
you're expecting a fax today,
please don't yell out, "Michael J.
Fax, from Fax to the Future!"
Okay? That's nonsense.
Question. Yes, beautiful
girl in the front?
We are expecting a water
delivery today at 10:00 a.m.
What if as they're
delivering the waterjugs
someone screams out,
"Nice jugs!"
That's obviously
nonsense.
Nonsense.
And what percentage of nonsense
do we tolerate in this office?
Zero percentage
of nonsense.
Can't have nonsense.
What is going on?
Daycare won't
take Phillip anymore.
Why?
Apparently my station
in life has descended
to a depth even
they won't forgive.
So, hi.
Hi, buddy.
Okay, new agenda item,
Phillip will be joining us
at the office today.
Got to write that down.
Okay, big day today, airing of
the documentary. Who's excited?
I'd better come out of this
smelling like a rose.
I've been on my best
behavior for nine years.
If it wasn't for the cameras I
would've done some truly vulgar crap.
Over the course of this documentary,
I've had three affairs.
If you find my body
in a ditch,
let me save
the police some trouble.
My wife did it.
I'm letting you all off half an
hour early to view the documentary.
So you can make it
up to me by working
an extra half
an hour tomorrow,
or a minute extra for
the rest of the month.
Ooh, announcement. Some of us
whose televisions got broken
during an all-you-can-eat-shrimp
commercial
will be watching
tonight at Poor Richard's.
But note, all are welcome,
not just those who saw an
all-you-can-eat-shrimp commercial
and charged
their televisions.
I can't believe the doc
is finally going to air.
When this thing started, I was
still having sex with women.
As was Kevin, I believe.
This airs tonight?
Oh, my God.
If my parents see this,
I am toast.
This is really huge.
This is like the March on
Washington but for a singing show.
Can you imagine if Martin
Luther King were here
and sang I Dreamed
a Dream from Les Miz?
With that baritone?
That would be historic.
Whoo-hoo! Casey Dean!
Cincinnati, Ohio!
Doctor, Doctor
Give me the news
I got a great
Casey Dean for you
Whoa. No.
America!
No, this is my time. You don't belt
on my time, I belt on my time.
Casey Dean
Man, those are some nice pipes.
Yeah.
What's your name?
What's yours?
Why didn't you
pack the apple snacks?
Guys.
Because whenever
I pack the bag
you say I do it wrong.
Guys. Guys.
Why don't you pack it?
Kevin, what?
Kevin, what is it?
Do you want to see
a video of a weatherman
who says "bold front"
instead of "cold front"?
Ifsinsane!
Not now, Kevin.
Can't you see we're busy?
Phillip needs
his apple snacks!
Seriously, Kevin.
I'm just going to
have to go to the store.
Okay,
you go to the store.
Phillip. Phillip. Phillip.
It's all about Phillip.
I hate Phillip.
Not now! Private time.
I love Star Wars as
much as the next guy...
Hey, hey! Seriously?
My God. I'm so sorry.
Well, this might
make up for it.
I think I have found an enormous
source of overlooked PFN.
Which is, of course...
Potential Future Nonsense.
Yes. Good abbreviating, Jim.
That saved some time.
Now hurry up, shut the door!
Break it down for me.
I'm going to need you to look
at your hierarchy mobile.
You've got
a regional manager.
The power source.
Obviously. The assistant
to the regional manager.
The loyal but
bungling apostle.
But what about the assistant
assistant to the regional manager?
Someone to whisper in
the ear of the consigliere.
Exactly.
I'd have to get some
more wire and string.
But it's doable.
Do you think any of them
out there are capable?
Yeah, right.
I mean, unless they're
willing to pass some tests.
I like the sound of that.
What did you have in mind?
Well,
I know this sounds crazy,
but how would
King Arthur choose
the next knight
of his Round Table?
That doesn't sound crazy, Jim. That's
the sanest thing I've ever heard.
What are you
listening to?
Hmm? I'm locking in
my starting note.
A 440
Oh, sweet. A cappella
is all about pitch,
and I am nothing if
not a total pitch-bitch.
What's up, everybody,
and welcome to
America's Next
A Cappella Sensation.
Hi, Mark McGrath!
Oh, my God!
You're gorgeous!
Thank you.
Thank you so much,
and thank you for your patience.
And we hope to see you guys
within the next
five to seven hours.
Now, just to give you a couple
of parameters of the show,
each of you will sing
a song for 30 seconds,
after which our
judges will decide
if they want you in
their a cappella group.
Now each group will
start with 90 singers
which will compete in a series of
singing and physical challenges.
Oh!
And look out for
that pesky mole!
Ooh!
There's a mole?
Oops.
I'm not supposed to...
I'm not supposed to say that.
All right, no mole.
Forget I said it.
All right?
What mole? What are you talking about?
I already forgot about it.
Good man, right there.
I'll see you guys inside.
Good luck, all right?
Yeah!
Pour some Sugar Ray on me!
On a roll much? I don't
know where that came from.
That was amazing, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, it felt good.
It felt funny.
Yeah, you made a personal
connection with him.
I did! I felt it.
Big time.
What are you
so excited about?
Nothing.
What are you up to?
Members of the office,
hear ye!
That means ye, Plop.
"Plop"? Still?
We owe Andy that much.
- Yeah.
- Absolutely we do.
Am I right, people?
Fine.
Today we will be
testing candidates
for the position of Assistant to the
Assistant to the Regional Manager.
Oh, heck yeah!
Nice.
You'll always
have the upper hand
when you've got a good AARM.
Trademark pending.
This is not
an excuse to blow off work
doing
carnival-like activities.
Sure, every participant
will be getting a corndog,
but that's for fueling only.
No savoring.
Wow, what an honor.
God, I envy them.
He envies you.
You don't need to
repeat right now.
All right.
What I'm saying.
By 2:00,
Dwight will choose himself
to be assistant to
his own assistant, me.
What's up?
What's going on?
How was the delivery?
Delivered all my
furniture to Philly.
Hey, keep it down though.
Nobody knows I'm here.
DARRYL". I hate goodbyes.
So last week, when I left
Dunder Mifflin for good,
I pulled the old Irish exit.
Just slipped out
without making a big deal.
No hard feelings.
No feelings at all.
A good assistant
knows what their superior
is thinking before
they even think it.
Meredith, what number
am I thinking of right now?
Uh... Two?
Nine-hundred-eighty-five
trillion seventeen.
Not even close,
Meredith. Come on!
Pam, what song is running
through my head right now?
Theme song from
Saved by the Bell.
Oh, my God! It was the theme
song to Boy Meets World.
Wait! No, no, no, stop.
Spouses can read
each other's minds.
You're trying to
give your wife this job.
That's exactly
what I was doing.
Plop, what animal
am I picturing?
A horse?
Ooh.
Exact opposite, actually.
What's the opposite
of a horse?
A sea horse.
A sea horse!
Whoa.
How did you know
I was going to say that?
Say that.
Uncanny.
Challenge number two. Protocol.
Clark? Yeah.
Do you want a corndog?
I would love a corndog.
We'll see.
You are an assistant
who's just gotten
a phone message.
I am in a meeting with
Dwight, Robert Dunder
and his niece. Uh-oh!
Look who came to join us.
The Turkish Ambassador
to Armenia,
Yuri Slovak, who,
by the way, is extremely
embarrassed about
the size of his nose.
Go ahead and read
that phone message.
Mr. Halpert, your wife
called to find out how
your meeting with
Yuri Big Nose went.
No, no, no. You don't read
it aloud like that.
God! Besides, the whole
thing is a trick question.
There's no Turkish
Ambassador to Armenia,
the two countries don't
have diplomatic relations.
Uncanny.
I just hope if my buddies who are
still in Afghanistan see me win,
they'll feel like
anything is possible.
Great, more screen time
for the war vet.
All you got to do is
risk your life for this
country and everyone
goes ga-ga for you.
Over at the porta potties,
they were interviewing a homeless
single mother with three kids.
What?
Yeah.
Is this a show about the
resiliency of the human spirit,
or is it a show
about singing?
I don't know, but I'm getting
really worried here.
Me, too.
Hold my place in line.
Where are you going?
They want feel-good stories?
Wait till they get
a good feel of me.
Thanks, man.
Thank you.
Man, take care.
Darryl! Hey!
Hey-
Cool, are you
coming back to say hi?
No, no.
I'm not here, actually.
These donuts are
part of my escape
from the guys at the warehouse
I didn't say goodbye to.
A-ha! How's Athlead?
We're living like rock stars!
I'm about to eat
free steak with
my sports heroes in
32 different cities!
Wow! Jim really
doesn't want to come?
He says he doesn't want to.
Man,
I hope he doesn't regret it.
Well, he seems really happy being
back here at Dunder Mifflin.
Jim is happy here,
selling paper at Dunder Mifflin?
That's what he says.
If you say so.
Hey, good seeing you,
and remember,
I was never here.
All right, man.
An assistant brings their boss
coffee with speed and dexterity,
but an assistant to the assistant
has 1,000 times more to prove.
A thousand times more.
I'll try this one.
Phyllis.
Grab both these coffees,
double-fist it,
and head through
this obstacle course.
Okay. Ooh, it's hot.
Yeah, it's real.
It's the only way
you'll learn. Okay.
And go ahead.
Oh, God, nice.
She's through the green, everybody.
Here comes yellow.
Oh, no, no, no.
A real doozie.
Phyllis?
Seriously?
Careful.
Look at that form!
Oh, God,
this is pathetic.
The boss needs his coffee!
Wow.
Here you are, sir!
Here's your coffee.
Ow! My skin!
Ow! Ow! Oh!
It burns! Ow!
Uncanny.
Darryl? Darryl!
Whoa! Oh, hey. Hey!
What's up, y'all?
You left us
without saying goodbye!
Oh. My bad.
Goodbye, everybody.
Hey, no way!
That is totally uncool.
Are you kidding?
You broke our hearts!
Get upstairs.
I don't think I should.
Get upstairs, mister!
Yeah!
Right now!
Guess I'm going upstairs.
You know, Dwight, this whole
search for the assistant thing,
none of these
people are good enough.
I know.
What I'm about to say
makes no logical sense,
and yet it might be the most
logical thing I've ever said.
Jim, this is going to
come as no surprise,
but I know exactly
what you are going to say.
The only possible assistant
to my assistant...
ls...
me.
The new Assistant to the Assistant
to the Regional Manager is
Dwight K. Schrute!
Yes!
Yes.
Thank you.
I think you might
want to kneel for this.
And yet, the manager of Dunder
Mifflin kneels for no man.
That's it.
Okay.
You look really,
really good.
Okay, from now on, anyone
who needs to speak to me,
has got to go through
me first. All right?
Hey!
Hey.
You all right?
What's going on?
Are you happy?
Yes, I'm happy-
No, I know that you're,
Hke, happy
and you had fun today.
Yeah.
And that was fun. But what
about a year from now?
What? What about
five years from now?
Pam...
Because I'm so glad
you're back, baby,
but I'm just...
I was talking to Darryl,
and he was
talking about the trip,
and I just feel like
you're giving up so much.
This was my decision,
not yours.
You didn't force me.
I kind of forced
you to do it.
You did not
force me to do this.
Yes, I did. I don't know
how else to tell you.
I'm afraid you're
going to resent me.
I'm afraid that this is not
enough for you. Resent you?
And I'm afraid that
I'm not enough for you.
Is that really
what you think?
Notenough? I don't know how
else to explain it to her, so,
you know what? I know
it's against the rules,
but I'm going to need
a favor from you guys.
Okay. You got it, man.
I didn't realize
we were this close.
We're all a little hormonal
with the doc airing.
Are you gonna come to Poor Richard's
and watch with us tonight?
Uh...
Yeah, depending on traffic.
He ain't coming.
Oh, God!
These dudes are
definitely in a weird mood.
Picked the wrong day
to return a truck.
Well, it's been great.
Eleven years. A guy is in
your life for 11 years
and then he's gone
for who knows how long.
Maybe forever.
Anyhow...
Did we ever have
lunch together,
just the two of us?
You know what?
I'm going to make
reservations
right now at Cugino's.
Question for Darryl.
Did we ever get loaded and
listen to Zeppelin in my van?
Oh. Oh, I'm sure we did.
Nah, I call one hour
van time with Darryl.
Darryl, I would love to just
record some of your stories,
just let the tape
roll for six or eight
or 10 hours and
just see what we get.
Listen, guys,
we can do it all.
We just have to
divide Darryl's
next 12 hours into
90-minute segments.
I will go watch an e-How
video on how to use Excel,
and then we'll
get this started.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute!
Okay, I made the mistake of sneaking
out of here, and that's on me.
But I'm not going to spend
the rest of the day here
doing stuff with you 'cause
you're feeling sentimental.
You have to!
Hey, hey, hey, hey! I'll do
one thing with y'all.
Which thing?
I don't care. Choose amongst yourselves.
Not the van, though.
Yeah, sleep time?
Kevin. Kevin!
Oh, you know my name.
Well, that is shocking.
Kevin, could you
not do that?
What? I'm moving the ink
down in my pen, for work.
Here, use my pen.
Don't tell me what to do!
I don't need this. And you
obviously don't need me.
Kevin, where are you going?
Away!
Tell Phillip that his stupid
little baby wish came true!
He just won't go down.
It's as if he's
excited by all this paper.
I know. Earlier today he tried to eat
some of the 24-weight letter bond.
Smart baby.
That's the most
flavorful bond.
Hey,
what's going on over here?
Some sort of singing
competition for the young'uns?
You're back!
No, it's me, Andy!
No, I know!
No, I'm wearing makeup!
You did a really great job.
Thank you.
You even look shorter.
Oh, I took out my lifts.
Yeah, unlike Andy Bernard,
this character
is my real height.
Oh.
All day long it's moo the
cows and cluck the hens.
Mmm-hmm. Get the sheep baa-ed.
Oink the pigs.
That is very important.
Dwight, I'm telling
you all the things Ma
said after the horse
kicked her in the head.
Where are you?
Dwight?
The way that boy
looks at the Galactica,
is precisely the way
I look at the Galactica.
And he eats the same
kind of paper I do.
Hmm.
Thank you, Esther.
Bye.
You threw the summoning
bag at me, sir?
I need you to perform a test.
Perform a test.
On an innocent baby.
Ooh. I like
where this is going.
Unfortunately, I have
a lot on my plate today,
so I'm going to have to hand
this off to my number two.
But don't worry.
He's the best in the biz.
Damn straight.
Unless you think
he can't handle it.
Hey, he can handle it.
All right.
Listen, listen.
Shh, buddy.
Stanley is sleeping.
You don't want to
wake up the grumpy
old walrus, do you?
I heard that.
Mama.
Hey, you want me to take
the little diaper blaster?
Pam can attest,
there's no one better
at getting brats
to shut their yaps.
He does have a gift.
Well, he's crying for his mom, but,
okay, here you go. Careful, he bites.
Mama.
Okay.
You ever been in
a manager's office before?
Phillip, you want to
play a little game?
It's called
Schrute or Consequences?
You're going to choose
one of these two things,
a check for a million dollars
or this dirty, old beet.
Yuck! Phew!
Which will it be,
money or the beet?
Beet.
Yeah.
Any ordinary child
would have taken the money,
but you're no ordinary
child, are you? No.
I can tell by your gorgeous,
widely set eyes.
Sorry, folks. The judges
are totally swamped.
We are all done
taking auditions.
Whoa, whoa! What?
But thanks for coming out,
and please be sure to watch
America's Next
A Cappella Sensation.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You can't do that.
We've all been waiting!
Okay.
lam going in there.
No.
Don't... Don't touch me!
I'm not touching you.
Look! Run, old man! Run!
Run! Run for your life!
Don't you dare.
Don't get...
I just thought you were going
to get handsy with me.
Not interested.
I'm Casey Dean.
Be seeing the last of me.
Or I meant you won't be
seeing the last of me.
Hey!
Did you manage
to feed him?
I don't know what it is, he just
keeps spitting out the nipple.
That's because this baby
is of superior intelligence
and can tell when
he is being tricked
out of the experience
of a real human breast.
Come on.
He's not that smart.
He doesn't know
where I hid his duck.
You're still here!
Oh, thank God.
Clay Aiken, Santigold
and Aaron Rodgers!
You're like my three
favorite people ever!
Excuse me, what is this?
Sweetheart,
you're amazing, okay?
You're obviously
going to be on the show.
So, it's someone
else's turn now.
Go ahead. All right?
Um...
My name is Ezra Cornell!
And I'm just a kindly old
fellow with a song in my heart.
No, you're a middle-aged man
with a lot of makeup on.
Busted.
Got it. Yes, all right, tried to
get your attention with tricks,
but you just want to hear me sing.
I respect that.
We do not
want to hear you sing.
Gabriella was
our last audition.
Thank you, goodbye.
Nope! Can't end like this.
Slept in my car last night, quit
my job, burned all my bridges!
I went to the bathroom
on my boss's car,
and I did unspeakable
things with Carla Fern.
Flag on the play.
That's what... Yeah. Okay, all right.
Well, here's the song.
What is this song?
Are you insane?
It's the Cornell Fight Song!
Listen, all right, thank you very much.
We're not interested.
You didn't let me finish!
That's not fair!
Look, man, you're
not terrible, but we've
heard a lot of
really good singers today,
and you're just
not good enough.
Wow, you guys
are really mean.
I guess that's the show.
Let me try
a different song, okay?
Can he do this?
Yeah.
Look, you've got to go.
You can't just
sit here and cry.
I can so just
sit here and cry!
Thank you.
Hey, Kev. How are
you doing, buddy?
I can't hear you.
I'm giving you
the silence treatment.
How does it
feel being ignored?
Okay, I guess. It's just that
Phillip got you something.
Yeah, a $25
gift card, iTunes.
I think there's,
like, $7 left.
It's just his way
of saying, "Thanks
for letting me hang
out in Accounting."
Phillip got this for me?
Sure.
That was a really cool move.
Would you like
to hold Phillip?
Yeah, that's Kevin.
Hi.
- Whoa.
- Easy.
What a chubbers.
Whoa...
Okay, hey.
I'm losing my balance.
Okay, Kevin, no.
No. No horseplay.
Stop it.
You want to play
with the cactus?
No!
So me and Phillip
were just talking,
and we decided we're going
to be best friends.
He's a little
stand-offish at first.
But once he starts
buying you things,
man,
you can tell he likes you.
We have our decision.
You chose one thing.
We want to
dance with you.
You want to dance?
One dance,
all of us together.
This is what you want?
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Better get some decent
speakers up here then,
'cause we're going
to do this right.
Yes!
Hey, you wanted to see me?
Door. Chair.
It's about Phillip.
I'm sorry he's here today,
but I had this...
lbeheve
that that boy
may be a Schrute,
and if he is,
that child needs to be
accorded what is his,
an enormous farm,
an inheritance,
and the right to be raised under
rigorous Schrute traditions.
You will, of course, be compensated
with a marriage proposal.
How thoughtful.
Then the two of you would
move to my 1,600 acre estate,
which let's face it,
is a big step up
from living in
a gay man's closet.
If he is your son
that's a great plan.
But he's not.
He's not your son.
Very well.
Can I go back to my desk now?
Yes.
What's this?
Well, I've been trying
to tell you how I feel,
and you wouldn't
believe me, so,
I needed a little help.
Jim. I need my Assistant to the
Regional Manager. Code red.
Okay, I don't have my pocket code
chart on me right now, so...
Now!
I have an assistant now, who can
help you with whatever you need.
He is lazy,
so crack the whip.
Jim, I'm not kidding,
I need you.
Go ahead.
Okay. Um...
This is...
I'll be right back.
What have we got?
I was thinking of
proposing to Esther today.
Wow! Okay, congratulations.
That's a really big step, man.
She's got a ton
of great qualities.
She's young, she's beautiful, genes
so pure you could lick them.
Her family admires me,
and my family tolerates hers.
A lot of them are the same people,
because we're third cousins,
which is great for bloodlines,
and isn't technically incest.
Right in the sweet spot. I think
you're going to be really happy.
Plus, her dowry
contains a walk-in freezer
full of frozen
premium cattle sperm.
That's a lot of pros.
And did I mention
that she weaves?
Colorful, durable blankets and rugs!
It all adds up.
So what is the problem?
Angela.
I don't know what you want
me to tell you, man.
All I know is
that every time I've been
faced with a tough decision,
there's only one thing that
outweighs every other concern,
one thing that will
make you give up on
everything you
thought you knew.
Every instinct,
every rational calculation.
Some sort of virus?
Love.
Oh.
I'm in love with you.
What?
Dwight, listen,
no matter what happens...
you've got to forget
about all the other stuff.
You've got to forget about
logic and fear and doubt.
You've just got to
do everything you can
to get to the one woman who's
going to make all this worth it.
At the end of the day,
you've got to jump.
You love Angela, Dwight.
I think you always have.
You're a good assistant, Jim.
Not as good as you.
That's very true.
Get the hell out of here.
You got it.
I was just
checking out my present.
This is an amazing gift, because
it comes with bonus gifts.
Look inside.
Oh, my God!
The yearbook picture.
Yes.
Incredible.
Is this the bottle timer?
I didn't think you were going to
get that one. I really didn't.
Oh, no! This is like
the best present ever.
Well...
Okay, wait.
What is this?
The mini-golf pencil
you threw at me.
Like three years ago?
You saved this?
Oh, my God.
You watched it.
Yeah.
Well, then I guess
you're ready for this.
What's that?
It's from the teapot.
Everything you'll ever need
to know is in that note.
Not enough for me?
You are everything.
Thank you.
Okay, ready, everybody?
Hit it, Red!
I wanted
to leave quietly.
It seemed dignified.
But having Kevin
grind up on my front
while Erin pretends
to hump me from behind
is a more accurate
tribute to my years here.
I'm going to miss these guys.
Okay, I've got mY...
See you guys at Poor Richard's, okay?
All right, Meredith.
All right.
Okay, bye.
See you there.
Bye, Phillip.
Listen, I...
High five!
Yeah.
Yay!
I am going to drop
Phillip off at my mother's,
and I'll meet you at
Poor Richard's in an hour.
You sure you don't
want me to drop him off?
She doesn't know I'm living
with a straight woman.
I don't want to
get her hopes up.
All right.
Okay?
Bye, buddy! Bye, bye.
Oh, my goodness!
Pull over!
Dwight!
Move to the side
of the road!
Why?
Pull over!
What are you... Dwight!
Dwight! What the
is your problem?
Silence, woman! Listen to me!
Who drives like that?
I love you.
And I don't care that
Phillip is not my son!
I will raise 100 children
with 100 of your lovers
if it means I can be with you!
Can you put that down?
This expresses
how loudly I love you!
lfstooloud.
This is a ring
taken from the buttocks
of my grandmother,
put there by the gangster
patriarch of the Coors dynasty,
melted in a foundry
run by Mennonites.
Okay. Yes. I will!
I love you!
And I lied to you.
What?
Phillip's your son.
What? Why would
you say that...
I just needed you
to want to marry me
because you
wanted to marry me.
Get out!
I'm a dad!
You're a dad!
Hey, grab a seat.
We have that table and that
table, but not that table,
or that table,
or that table.
Floor's up for grabs. Meredith's
been hogging the can.
Oh!
You have to change
the channel to PBS.
Yeah.
College baseball's on.
Well, there's
a documentary coming up.
Everyone in
the bar will love it!
What's it about?
A paper company.
Oh, ho, ho!
How many people
want the game?
Yeah!
Who wants PBS?
Sorry. Tie means
I do nothing.
Sir, please!
This show is about
me and my attempts
to find love in
all the wrong places.
One more for the doc!
All right, Andy!
All right.
Yes.
Hey, how was
the singing show audition?
Oh...
Whatever. No big deal.
Okay, 30 seconds
to show time!
I feel scared a little.
I'm not ready for this!
No one is ready for this!
You can't be ready for this!
We don't even
know what this is!
One thing we do know. Nothing
will ever be the same.
Here we go.
All right, Jim,
your quarterlies look very good.
How are things
going at the library?
Oh, I told you.
I couldn't close it, so...
So you've come to
the master for guidance?
Is this what you're saying,
Grasshopper?
Actually you
called me in here.
All right, well, let me
show you how it's done.