The building's custodian
is on vacation for the month,
and Dwight is too cheap
to hire a replacement.
So instead,
we're living in filth.
But not for long, because I
have created the chore wheel.
Oh, yeah!
Can I spin first?
Well, it doesn't spin.
We'll just move the wheel
one notch each morning,
and you see what
chore you get that day.
A wheel is supposed to spin.
Yeah.
You know, like...
No, I'm familiar
with spinning.
It's just, that wouldn't
work with a chore wheel,
because people might
get the same chore.
Bah! Boring. All she
talks about is chores.
A wheel wants
to spin, Pam.
Spinning would be more fun.
Okay-
Okay! That's what
I'm talking about.
Big money, big money.
Yeah!
"Mug duty"?
Yes! You clean all
the mugs in the sink.
This sucks.
Yeah, seriously. It's like
everything on there is work.
I don't think you guys understand
why we're doing this. It's...
Yeah, and I don't think
that you understand wheels.
I've been through several rounds
of development with the team,
and here's where we stand
with the chore wheel.
We've got prizes!
"Ten Bucks,"Candy Bar,"
"Manager For An Hour."
But there are
also penalties
like "No Internet,"
"Stanley Gets Your Lunch."
The one thing that is not on
the chore wheel is chores.
But they were right,
it's more fun this way.
Tiny Wheel! Tiny Wheel!
The Tiny Wheel actually
does have chores.
It's so cute,
no one seems to mind.
"Toilets!"
Pam, we've got to go!
Cece, go back inside.
Grandma's got
breakfast, okay?
We are going to Roy's wedding.
Yep, Roy.
I think the only weird thing
about going to your wife's
ex-fiance's wedding
on a weekday at 8:00 a.m.
is that it's your wife's ex-fiancé.
Thanks, Mom!
A banana?
Yeah.
I'm afraid he's only
going to have hot dogs.
Come on. Not even Roy would
have hot dogs at his wedding.
I planned a wedding with him.
He wanted hot dogs.
It's so weird.
Oh, Pete. You got mail.
Really?
I got something?
Well, it's addressed to Customer
Service, so it's your mail.
Well, you know,
I'm also customer service.
Yeah, I'm alternating.
Another person
yelling at me.
Well, it could be
a nice letter.
I write nice letters to
companies all the time.
That's really nice.
Wow. Newsweek, huh? This
election thing is crazy, right?
It's opened.
Oh, yeah. I accidentally read it.
It's not a nice letter.
Get excited!
The special projects
fairy has arrived.
I know you
don't really exist.
Today, I launch my big charity
initiative, Operation Giveback.
Andy has shot down all of my
special projects thus far,
but this one is about charity, so I'd
like to see him piss on that one.
Darryl!
What's happening?
Congratulations, baby.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Is this his house?
I think so.
Mimosa?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Would you like me
to take your peel?
Yes. Thank you.
Okay-
Who was that?
Uh...
My ex-fiancée.
Ha-ha.
I started a new business
with my college friend,
but Pam doesn't know.
Um...
Actually I did tell Pam
and we decided, "No."
But then I decided,
"Yes," anyway,
so I'm thinking there's
another conversation coming,
and it's hard to know
when that will be.
With Operation Giveback, you pick the
charities Dunder Mifflin supports.
Oh, boy!
What's happening?
There's $4,000 to give away, so
who has filled out their forms?
Stanley?
American Diabetes
Association.
Um, you have diabetes,
Stanley.
I'm sorry. Ls the assignment
to pick a selfish charity?
I... I would love to give...
Heifers International.
Listen to this. They give a poor
person, like, a goat or something?
It's a great prank.
I want to work with Jimmy
Carter and help build gnomes.
Dwight? What about you?
I will not be participating, as there
is no evidence that charity works.
Uh, correction, I give to
a foundation that teaches
homeless children nautical flag signaling.
It changes lives.
Thank you, Andy.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for the preservation
of nautical flag signaling.
Dwight, you will
be participating.
No, thank you. Participation
is mandatory, Dwight.
But you can choose
whatever cause you like.
Fine! I choose the
Global Relief Foundation...
Great. Thank you... which
was recently discovered
to be a front
for the Taliban.
Oh, for goodness
sake, Dwight!
Yeah, the Taliban
in Af-a-ghanistan!
The Taliban is the worst.
Great heroin, though.
Dwight, I cannot have the Taliban on
the roster of Operation Giveback.
Well, then it looks like there
won't be any Operation Giveback.
The nanny state is over, ladies
and gentlemen! You're welcome.
There he is.
Is it almost time to
cut the pancake or what?
Oh, yeah, we appreciate everyone
coming out so early. It's...
Everyone's just
been so nice.
Thanks for inviting us, by the way.
That was...
Are you kidding?
That was a surprise.
Come on, if it wasn't for you,
I never would have met Lara.
I mean, seriously, I kind of
dodged a bullet on that one.
I'm just kidding.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
Oh.
By the way, man,
this place is beautiful.
I started a gravel company. I
mean, who knew it would take off?
Gravel company.
Yeah. What about you?
What are you doing?
Not gravel, obviously.
No, things are good.
Things are good.
Got some stuff
in the works, so...
Oh, cool.
Yeah, you never know.
Hey, bro. Stop wasting
time with this haircut.
He's got a $50,000
sports car.
Cheers!
Yeah, okay, Ken.
Duncan, listen!
I would love to help you out,
but where am I
going to find somebody
that is pretty, smart
and well-informed, huh?
Hold on, hold on! Erin, do you
know anybody that might...
Oh, my gosh.
You love the news, right?
Well, it depends.
I mean, sometimes I find out
things that are really sad.
Well, I've got a buddy that's a
big-time local news producer.
I can't tell you his name,
but it'd blow your mind.
Uh, is it Duncan?
He's looking
for on-air talent,
and he'd kill me if
I didn't get you on tape.
You mean,
put me on the news?
You'll just come over, put on
a little lipstick, loosen up
with a glass of
red wine and then
we'll just run
through a few stories.
You know, a couple of different ways
in a couple of different outfits.
It'd be really tasteful and
it'd really help out with...
With my friend.
What do
you say? Huh?
- Well, maybe, okay? Let me think about it.
- Okay.
Think it over.
No, Clark's not my friend.
He is the douche that sits
next to me at the office.
My friends are Scott, Glen and
Rob, but you don't know them.
I never really thought much about being
more than a receptionist, but why?
Because I happened to answer a Help
Wanted ad to be a receptionist?
I mean, what if the ad had been
for a CEO or for a brain surgeon?
So, uh, it was a year ago
today that I met Lara.
I thought
she was my waitress,
and, uh, it took her
three weeks to tell me
that she actually
owned the place.
You are full of surprises.
You are my beautiful
mystery girl.
And today, I have
a surprise for you.
He plays the piano?
No. Roy? No.
You know how I said I was
taking boxing lessons?
Actually I was doing this.
Um, so,
I hope that you like it.
You got this, Roy!
She's got a way about her
I don't know what it is
But I know that I
can't live without her
She's got a way
We still surprise
each other.
Definitely.
You know, I never did it,
but for your 30th birthday,
I really wanted to
surprise you with...
Court-side seats.
Sixers.
Yes. But what I didn't tell you was
that I actually bought the tickets.
We only didn't go because...
it was an away game.
In Phoenix. They should really
tell you that more specifically.
I mean, every game is an away
game for one of the teams.
Do we know everything
about each other?
No.
Tell me one thing about you I don't know.
Uh... Um...
Okay-
Oh.
Here's one. Did I ever
tell you about the time
that my brothers videotaped
the lottery announcement
and bought the winning
numbers the next day,
and then played the tape
for me the next week...
And you thought you
guys were millionaires.
You heard that one.
Yes.
But there's... Wait!
Oh, there's a funny ending to
that story, I can't remember.
That I thought we
were millionaires.
That you thought
you were millionaires.
Yeah. That's funny.
Shoot! I knew that one.
That's all right.
The Senator and I
still have mystery.
I'm always waiting to see what he's
going to surprise me with next.
You all right?
You support the
Taliban abroad,
so I assume you're willing
to live by their rules here.
Anything else
would be inconsistent.
Will you join me then in a pledge to
live by Taliban law in this office?
Absolutely, I will.
I feared Nellie had
some sort of a plan.
But she used
a ridiculous font.
You don't have a plan.
When you use a ridiculous font,
no one thinks you have a plan.
Looking for this?
What the...
Oh, this is a lovely pen. And
it's mine now because I stole it.
Give me that!
Didn't we sign a contract
to live under Taliban law?
Now there's been a theft.
That means you're not serious or
someone's getting their hand cut off.
You're insane.
I know, so it's better
that you pick another charity.
Oh, and let your precious Operation
Powergrab proceed unchecked?
No, thank you.
Inthatcase, you
will have to chop off
my hand.
This cleaver appears
to need sharpening.
I suggest you spend some quality time
together, just you and your hand.
Tie a shoe.
Toss a salad.
Do any of the two-hand activities
that you'll miss the most.
I tell you what,
I need to make three calls,
and then after that you can become a
person who chops off people's hands.
Sounds like a plan.
Clark wants to film you in different
outfits inside his apartment?
Yeah.
Clark! You and I need
to have a little chat.
What clothes does Erin need
for this news audition?
Uh...
A couple of button-downs,
a camisole, a blazer,
a pencil skirt,
stilettos, maybe...
No, not maybe,
definitely open-toed.
Uh, something low-cut because the camera
makes everything seem higher cut.
Really?
Yeah. Industry secret.
You're going to want some of those
pantyhose with the seam up the back.
Seems unnecessary
for an audition.
And then, you know, maybe just a
robe to wear in between takes,
but I probably got one that she
could borrow at my place, so...
Thank God someone here knows
what they're talking about.
I want you to take
this credit card,
take Erin to the mall
and get that stuff.
I absolutely will do that.
Awesome. Plop!
Guess I'll just head
over to the mall, then.
Buy Erin some
sexy fun outfits.
That Clark, huh?
Next question
for our oldy-weds?
What's the craziest place
you ever made whoopee?
Language!
Who was Pam's
first celebrity crush?
That's good.
Okay.
Pam's first celebrity crush.
John Stamos.
Ready?
Uh-huh.
John Stamos.
Oh.
Yes!
But John Stamos was temporary.
I quickly moved
on to Johnny Depp.
Johnny DePP-
Sorry, I was having a
separate conversation with Kevin.
Uh...
Johnny Depp.
Totally.
George Clooney.
Okay, I have one.
I have one.
What is your warning... KEVIN:
What is the craziest place
you ever made whoopee?
Hey!
Kevin, stop it
with that question.
Right? And did you show
them the market? Yeah?
And what did they say?
That's awesome!
That... Oh, my God! Wow!
It's not even real yet.
And I'm not going to
tell her until it's real.
I think maybe there actually is
something I don't know about Jim.
Everyone, we have a voluntary
meeting in the conference room
to discuss Erin's confidence.
Her body. We're going
to talk about her body.
Good. Great job.
Andy made me his consigliere, which
means assistant regional manager.
I guess he thought I would be into
The Godfather because I'm black.
Wrong.
I'm into The Godfather
because I'm a cinephile.
I like Scarf ace
because I'm black.
Erin has an audition
to be a newscaster.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
Uh-huh.
And I want her to feel very
comfortable in her very sexy skin.
So, everybody say something that you
like about her body. All right?
Darryl?
Okay. Um, I like Erin's hair.
It's a very pretty color.
Yeah, right?
I'm sorry, this is
for a news audition?
Yeah.
Then why are we
talking about her looks?
Why not her credibility
or her reliability?
Newsflash, everyone,
the human race
finds attractive people
more trustworthy.
So sorry, Andy, but for 20 years,
the most trusted man in America?
Walter Cronkite.
Cronkite was hot!
If I could go back in time,
I'd take that moustache ride.
Does Erin have
any experience?
Has she taken any
journalism classes maybe?
Has she done
the pageant circuit?
No, I watch the news.
She's going to be amazing.
Look at her.
She's going to
light up the screen!
This is
a first for me.
And I don't get
a lot of chances,
so I have to take
them really seriously.
I will do whatever it
takes to get the job.
Whatever it takes.
Yeah, I know. I heard.
This is it.
Any questions?
Is it going to be long?
No, it's going to be over
before you know it. Mmm-hmm.
Afghan President Hamid Karzai
declared a new policy of "Dollar
Days" throughout the country,
promising low, low prices on all
2012 Kia Sentras and Sonatas.
"Aren't you glad you waited?"
Karzai commented.
Um, where did you
get that story?
A little bit here,
a little bit there.
I bet you didn't think
I knew current events.
I love it. It's fantastic.
Now tag it with your name.
For Channel Eleven News,
I'm Erin Hannon.
Pause after "news."
For Channel Eleven
News, I'm Erin Hannon.
No, pauselongen
That was a good one.
Pause... Pause longer, okay? It
builds suspense. Don't be shy.
Got it.
For Channel Eleven News...
It's... Okay, all right.
I'm Erin Hannon.
Great.
Some great stuff in there.
I can feel you
looking at me.
Okay. Well, here's
something you don't know.
A couple of weeks ago...
Mmm-hmm.
I ran into this guy
from my high school
who has just gotten divorced,
and he hit on me in the mall.
And I didn't
tell you because,
I don't know,
I felt embarrassed,
and I didn't know
if you'd be mad, or worried.
But anyway, I thought
you'd want to know.
That didn't happen.
You would have
told me right away.
Yeah, I would have.
What about you? Come on,
there's got to be something.
Between your birth
and the last two days,
something you just haven't
had the chance to tell me.
Uh...
Just tell me.
God, give it up, Beesly.
You know me too well.
- Hey.
Urn, I knew something bothered me,
and I finally figured it out.
What news producers are going to
want to see is how Erin relates
to the other people
on the news team. Oh.
The weird thing is that Erin
is doing the audition alone.
Oh, God. Now, I'd say Clark
could be your co-host,
but he's already doing camera.
Somebody who's already
got rapport with Erin maybe?
I don't know.
This is for real this time.
It's getting late. I thought you
guys could use a little inspiration.
Oh, a movie.
What is this?
127 Hours. It's about
this guy who goes...
No, no, no! No spoilers, please.
My bad. You're right.
No.
Okay.
Good night.
- Hey!
Everybody.
Yeah.
Come in. Come on in.
All right.
Nice.
What are you doing here?
Oh, sorry, man. Andy thought
Erin needed a co-anchor.
I'm his makeup guy.
My hands are tied.
The victim was released from the
hospital with second degree burns.
Wow.
You know what they say, Erin,
if you can't take the heat,
get out of the kitchen.
Well, he tried to, but the
fire door was blocked.
He sure did.
All right, we got that.
That's a wrap, everybody.
Oh. I just... You sure, Clark?
Yup, she's done.
No, I just... I don't mean Erin.
I mean for me.
I didn't feel
good about that.
No, no.
We got it. We got it.
Great. Let's get some food.
I'm starving.
I don't think we did get it. I
could do a couple more takes.
We could do it in a close-up. That
might even be better for editing.
Okay, I don't.
All right.
I'm hungry.
Uh...
Pete, you want to take Erin
to get a burger or something?
- Yeah, whatever you say, boss.
- Okay.
- I'll call you later.
Okay.
So this is a single.
Hey, even if this doesn't work out for me,
I'm just glad I had the guts to do it.
And maybe it will
work out for Andy.
Oh, God! Yeah. That is
absolutely revolting!
He is so good, though.
Yes.
The way he just
cuts off his arm.
If you like James Franco,
we really should watch
Rise of
the Planet of the Apes.
Well, he's a genius,
you know?
He was in graduate programs at Yale,
Columbia, and NYU all at the same time.
Whoop-de-do. That doesn't
make you a genius.
Well, it doesn't
make you stupid.
Well, yeah, it does actually.
It makes you real stupid.
Stupid like you.
No, like you!
Like you!
You're the stupid one.
You. You. You. You. You. You.