Can you guys come
with me for a minute?
I know you saw me
with the Senator.
I think I'm in love,
possibly for the first time.
So, yes, Senator Lipton
and I are having an affair.
I hope that I can count on your
sensitivity, maturity, and discretion.
Why?
All right, good, yeah.
Just sell it
and get the best
price you can. Okay?
Or we can hope
for a holiday rally.
Mike. I'm not
a day trader.
I'm just a first
responder in a disaster.
Andy's family
had a total meltdown.
His dad blew through
all their money and
took off to Argentina
with a younger woman.
And his brother, Walt, Jr.,
locked himself in the wine cellar.
The weirdest part is Andy.
The aftermath
got dumped on him,
and the way he's been
handling it is just so...
Competent.
Right?
Are the Nards hurting? Yeah, you bet.
Got kicked pretty hard.
Family's shattered,
supersad.
But I'm kind of crushing it in
the damage-control department.
So, that's cool.
I wish my dad
could see me now.
Of course, he caused
this whole mess, so
him.
Kevin, listen to me.
I'm in love
with the Senator.
And I need time to sort this
out in a responsible manner,
so I need your help
in keeping it a secret
because this means
the world to me. Okay?
That's beautiful.
No, I totally get that.
Can you do this,
Kevin?
I really want to.
Whatever happens,
always remember that.
I don't know what that means.
Hey. Hey.
Oh. Great.
Yeah, um, I'll get
right back to you.
Hey, guys, has anyone ever heard
of Iris Black on the radio?
Yeah, she hosts
The Dr. Laura Show.
Nope, that's Dr. Laura.
Well, her show, BizWhiz,
wants someone from Dunder Mifflin
to come on the air today.
Does anybody feel particularly
passionate about local business issues?
L do! I do!
Idolldolldol
The media
can make you famous.
And do you have any
idea how easy it is
to sell something
when you're famous?
Uh...
Yeah, wow. Ten reams of 40-pound
bond at only $6.90 after discount?
Uh, whatever you say,
Brad Pitt!
It's that easy.
Hey. So, that good-looking
single brother of yours?
Heard he was in a downward
spiral with booze.
Yeah, he's in rehab,
actually.
Which place? The one right near Philly?
I could be there in an hour.
No, it's in New Mexico.
Oh.
So, how are you
holding up?
We're done, Meredith.
Right.
Greta, the tittle-tattle, prattled
on about the little metal bottle.
Oh, my God. She spat a
bit of spittle on the...
Dwight! mottled brittle
cattle in a bitter battle...
Hey, hey!
Stop questioning
my methods, okay?
I was chosen for this task
for a very good reason.
No. You chose yourself.
Tricky Siskel spat
a bit of wicked biscuit.
All right, guys, there's a lot of
assets here that my dad couldn't steal.
Now, first of all,
there is the family boat,
a 43-foot Tartan Sloop.
My lawyer has lined up
a buyer in the Bahamas.
The sale would cover
the cost of a condo
and living
expenses for my mom.
Sounds great.
Perfect.
Totally, except it is
a no-go.
This boat was the heart and
soul of our family, so...
What else we got?
Non-boat ideas.
- What happened?
- Jammed.
- Can this day get worse?
- Excuse me a second.
Yeah, I think
this day could get worse.
You've got about 15 grand in
silverware... What does that mean?
- Kevin!
- ... and napkin rings?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
She could get,
like, 60 packages
of ramen noodles
for five bucks.
She could eat for a month.
Oh, hey. Sorry.
All right, what's the grand total?
Did we make our nut?
If we sell
everything but the boat,
your mom should be set
for about six months.
Guys, you don't understand.
This boat's been in our family
since before I was born.
Yeah. Don't you
guys have that place
where you used to spend your summers
and have all those memories?
I worked at
a Jiffy Lube.
See? I bet you
wouldn't sell that Jiffy Lube
for all the money in the
world, would you, Darryl?
I would if I owned
it and I went broke.
All right.
Uh... All right.
I'm going to tell the lawyer to
pull the trigger on the boat.
Yes, the boat means everything to
my family, but we need the money.
Got the memories, don't need the boat.
Can't cry about it.
What are you going to do?
Cry about it?
Excuse me.
Oh! Okay.
No problem. Thanks.
Hey, guys, WPTU called.
The interview's off.
They're opening a new cupcake
store at the Steamtown Mall,
and Iris wants
to cover that, so...
Well, why don't
I go and tell Dwight
so he can stop being
such a complete nipple?
He's going
to be disappointed.
Yes, he is.
And you know what?
We cannot let that happen.
Fax'?
Oh, yeah. Just...
Watermelon teeth.
This isn't how I would
cheer up just anyone, but
it's a girlfriend's job to
know her man, and I know Andy.
He is seriously juvenile.
COOL.
He's like 40, though, right?
Oh, no.
He couldn't be more than,
like, thirties, tops.
Awesome. Have fun.
Dunder Mifflin.
Good. Sounds...
This is Dwight Schrute.
Please hold for Ms. Black.
And welcome
back to BizWhiz. I'm Iris Black.
On the line we
have Dunder Mifflin's
Senior Sales Associate,
Dwight Schrute.
Iris, thank you so
much for having me.
Help! My teeth are
all messed up in my mouth.
Did you need something?
Oh, I just need
your signature on this.
Okay-
Thanks.
Kevin, we're out of 1138 forms.
Did you order more?
I did not.
Well, I don't know
why I'm surprised.
Literally nothing you could
do could surprise me anymore.
Oh, really, Angela?
That's interesting.
Because I do think
that I could surprise you.
I think that I could
surprise you all the...
Ya!
I have to go
to the bathroom!
That doesn't surprise me.
That actually wasn't the worst cover.
I'd say at least once a week
Kevin runs out of the room shouting
that he has to go to the bathroom.
So the supply forms
are going to be...
I have to go
to the bathroom!
I have to go to the bathroom!
Okay. Who wants to go for a super-fun
lunch with a super-fun girlfriend?
Look, it's not that
I don't want...
Okay. Come on. I got someone
to cover the phones.
I heard on the radio
about a new cupcake place
we could go
for dessert. Perfect.
All I ever wanted to do
was sail the damn thing.
But Dad wouldn't let me.
He said,
"You can't be a skipper
until you're a man."
You know,
I'd reach for the wheel
and he'd just
smack my hand away.
Well, guess what?
Now I'm the man of the family,
and we're selling
the damned thing.
So I'm never going
to have the chance.
Well, when does the boat
leave, exactly? Tonight.
Then screw lunch. Let's go for
a sunset sail. Yeah, right.
It's in Stamford, Connecticut. We'd
have to leave, like, right now.
Okay, well, then let's leave,
like, right now. Yeah, okay.
Yeah, okay! Let's go! Seriously?
Of course, seriously.
Get your coat on.
All right!
Let's do it!
Iris, let me tell you. David Wallace
is the CEO, but he's not hands-on.
So the day-to-day operations are
entirely under your command?
"Entirely" is the perfect way
to describe it, Iris.
Excuse me. I'm being told
by my sound engineer, Steve,
that there is a clinking sound
coming from your end.
Does your shirt
have buttons?
Yes.
I'm so sorry. We are
going to have to ask you
to remove
the shirt altogether.
Now, then,
we were saying.
- When my workers gather...
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm told we are still having
problems, Mr. Schrute.
Your voice, it's sounding a little
feminine. That's impossible.
Are you by any chance wearing
pants with a metallic zipper?
The Senator is exhausted. This
campaign is wearing him out.
It's a tough one. That man
he's up against is so dirty,
and the Senator is just pushing
back as hard as he can.
Hmm! Please stop!
What?
Please stop.
Anyways,
last night he was so tired,
he just wanted a little Mexican brought in.
I can't!
It's too much!
I'm in big trouble.
Yeah, Oscar's in big trouble.
Okay, how is
my voice now?
I'm getting the
all-clear from Steve.
So, Mr. Schrute,
what is your response
to the Consumer
Product Safety Commission
that says Dunder Mifflin
paper is toxic?
This is gotcha journalism.
But you know what?
They're not gonna gotch me.
It's clearly not
an accounting mistake.
Oh, Kevin.
So...
His gambling problem
must have resurfaced.
I'm going to have
to send him home
until I can do
aninvesfigafion.
Well, you gotta do
what you gotta do, so...
This is slander,
Ms. Black.
Slander, I say. I dare you to produce
one credible source about this.
Well, as it happens,
we have with us
the foreman of your Upstate New
York paper mill, Sondra Mc...
Sondra Mick!
Good afternoon, Iris.
It's a pleasure.
I'll get straight to the point.
ls your paper toxic?
No. The paper's not toxic.
Thank you, Sondra!
Unless it's exposed to oxygen.
Then it becomes extremely toxic.
Do not listen to her! This
employee is obviously disgruntled!
What the heck is going on?
The stock price is plummeting!
Are you going to get
control of the message
or do I have to send in someone
who understands the media?
Get out of here, moron!
Okay!
Excuse me, Mr. Dwight,
who are you talking to?
Uh... No one. Did you just call Ms.
Mick a moron?
No, everything's fine!
Are you insulting my guests?
Okay, I will be
right there.
Hey, Oscar, what if I'm
getting a promotion?
I hope that's it, Kevin.
Me, too.
'Cause then I would
get my own office.
And I wouldn't screw up
your secret with Angela.
I've been really
worried about that.
Hi, Kevin. Look, I need
to talk to you about...
Hey, guys?
Excuse me. Um...
A quick word?
Please, just... Oscar, we're
in the middle of talking.
I know. I'm so sorry.
Snack machine, on me.
Well, that is nice.
Huh. Classy move.
That's what I'm saying!
No, of course not!
What are you doing?
Those figures I gave you?
They're false.
No.
I was mad at Kevin.
We had a fight,
and I acted vindictively.
So you set him up.
Yes. He's innocent.
I knew it. I knew it from the
beginning this was a possibility.
What are you talking about?
I just did this now.
Oh, no.
A few years ago, when I was on the
jury, the Scranton Strangler?
Sure.
I always thought he
might have been set up,
but I felt
pressured to convict.
Well, that's
got to be tough.
Tough? I put an innocent
man on death row.
The fallout from this morning's
revelation continues to mount.
Since Mr. Dwight
Schrute began speaking,
Dunder Mifflin
share prices fell 73%.
Mr. Schrute,
shareholders demand
accountability from
corporate leadership.
Can we announce your
resignation at this time?
My resignation? What are you talking about?
No! I'm just following orders!
Listen, the person responsible
for this catastrophe
is the CEO and Chairman,
David Wallace!
That's yours? ANDY: That's
the family boat, right there.
0h, my gosh, Andy!
This is enormous!
Right?
I thought it was going to be tiny!
Oh, my gosh, it's beautiful.
So this is how your
family came to America.
Move.
Sorry?
I'm trying to rig a boat here.
I don't know how to do that
when you're
standing in the way.
Sure. I'm not...
I didn't know...
I'm not a ghost, so I can't
walk through people.
Okay?
Okay! He was salty.
He is, a little bit.
How you doing, old buddy?
Missed you.
What does that one do?
This raises the mainsail.
That was my job
when we went sailing.
I wish I had seen you do it.
Really?
Yeah!
Up she goes!
Don't do that.
Oh, it's okay.
My girlfriend and I
were actually gonna
take her for
a little spin and a picnic
before you guys
head out tonight.
You know what? Get some dinner, on me...
No. Nope.
Can't do that.
Got it.
You know what?
Then we'll just take it
for a quick little
spin around the harbor.
We've already
started boarding.
No one's insured to rig or
operate now, except us.
You know what?
Chill, okay?
I own the boat.
I'm not going to sue myself.
All right? So just...
Wow! I can smack you all
day if you keep touching
what you're not
supposed to touch.
Okay, fine.
Okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Good stuff.
Good stuff! Great stuff.
Great.
Damn it!
Screw you, Dad!
Huh.
Well, we're doing it. We're finally
having a picnic on the boat!
I've had a thousand
picnics on this boat.
The point was
for me to sail it.
Andy, you never had to
sail the boat to be a man.
Fine, but I could have.
As long as we're on this boat, as far
as I'm concerned, you're the captain.
I am the captain.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah!
I'm the captain.
Hey, Charm School!
What?
I'm taking over from here.
Nice!
Okay, I hate to ruin
this moment, or breakdown,
but you already signed the papers.
So if you want your boat back,
you can pick it up there
in the Bahamas in 10 days.
Yeah, I know, because I'm
sailing it there. Okay, no.
I already said, you're not
getting back your deposit.
Fine. Keep it.
Just leave the supplies,
I already paid for those.
How much for that
cool fisherman's sweater?
For those just joining us,
terror in Greenwich,
where the police have
surrounded the house
of Dunder Mifflin
CEO David Wallace.
Wallace is said
to be despondent
over the company's stock
plummet,
and has taken
a mailman hostage.
On the line we have
Chief of Greenwich Police
Mr. Bill Jackson. Good afternoon.
Please, sir,
spare him!
Please!
Uh, this Wallace guy's
looking at hard time,
and we only know
this because of
what Dwight
Snoot said on record.
Okay, everyone! Everyone hold on!
I've got a solution.
I know Wallace's phone number!
Everyone hold, I'll conference him in!
Oh, no, Mr. Schrute, there's really
no need to, um, involve Mr. Wallace.
Do you even know what you're doing?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know how to hoist the mainsail.
I know how to...
These buttons control
the bilge pumps and stuff.
I also know where
the booze stash is. Hello!
Walt?
Oh, God! Thank
goodness you're here.
I was having
a little trouble
with this door, uh, yesterday.
I, uh...
I think it was yesterday.
I thought you were in rehab.
Yeah, I just, uh... I figured I'd get
that first relapse out of the way.
God, what's happened to our family?
Everything is so messed up.
How did you even know I was in here?
I didn't.
I just came to say
goodbye to the boat,
but I've decided
to sail it to Bermuda.
Bahamas, Andy.
Same thing.
I need a crew.
You should be my crew!
Three weeks, open ocean, no booze.
You need this.
- I need it. We need this. Serious bro time.
- Come on.
Hello?
David, is that you?
Dwight? Oh, thank God!
Oh, thank God!
Are you okay?
ls everyone okay?
Yeah. Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I just want you to know
that I believe in you.
I really do, and I believe in your
ability to make the right choices.
- I always have, David.
- Well, thanks, Dwight.
You're welcome, sir.
But David,
listen to me carefully.
I'm going to need you
to let the mailman go, okay?
Walk out of the house...
What?
with your hands
on top of your head.
Everything is
going to be fine.
Dunder Mifflin will be in good
hands while you're away in prison.
Okay. Dwight?
I'm going to ask you
to not call me on my
cell anymore. Gotta go.
Wait a minute.
You guys? You heard?
Schrute! Schrute!
Sch rute! Sch rute!
Overall, I'd say my
first radio interview
went pretty much
the way I expected.
Well, Oscar, I did not
get the promotion.
He just wanted to update
my personal information.
Well, I'm sorry, Kevin.
Why on Earth would you think
you were getting a promotion?
You know what,
Angela? I...
Oh, my God!
Honey!
What are you doing here?
Oh, I just had
an intuition
that someone I love needed a
little of my attention today.
Oscar!
Looking very healthy.
Getting lots
of vigorous exercise?
Oh, no.
Oscar? What is going on? What was that?
What was that? I'm sorry. I
didn't mean any offense.
I was just
trying to be friendly.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
I overreacted
because I'm stressed out.
Why am I stressed out?
Who's not stressed out?
Come on, Oscar.
We're not just going to sit
here and ignore the obvious.
Senator Lipton has a big
election next week.
We all need to
give him our support!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thanks, everybody.
This is really cool.
USA! USA!
I have to say, I'm impressed
with Kevin. Uh...
He showed a lot
of self-control.
I totally forgot about
the affair for a minute.
Oscar is having
sex with the Senator
and Angela
doesn't even know.
Her life is a complete sham!
All right, guys, cast us off.
Walt! All aboard!
Erin, this is because of you. Do you
realize that? You're the best ever!
Oh, you know,
just being a good girlfriend.
Good? Come on!
Above and beyond!
World's greatest!
You did this!
Damn it, I'm haPPY!
Yes, lam very
pleased I could help Andy.
Would I have gone
with him if he'd asked me?
On his sailboat cruise
to the Caribbean? Yes.
I think that would have been
really fun and romantic.
I'll see you in three weeks!
Okay!
Hey, bro! It was here all along!
No way!
Way!
Erin, I gotta go!
Them's my chords!
Hey! She's back.
Thanks for covering the phones.
Yeah, no problem.
How was it?
Fine.
Hey, some buddies and I
are going to Poor Richard's
for beers and pool.
You want to come?
I can't promise
you too much, but
you might get to meet
my friend Flipper.
Does he have a flipper?
Oh. Nope. It's not that.
He, uh...
He flipped a table one time
when he was drunk.
He sounds like an idiot.
Yeah, he is.
Okay-
Okay!
Thanks.
Yeah!