I'm taking some
time off from work...
Well, my other work
because we needed it.
It's great.
The phone's been
ringing off the hook.
The guys in Philly
are kind of going nuts.
But that doesn't matter.
This does.
It's the only thing
that matters.
We've had some really
nice days together.
Mmm-hmm.
Nice morning, too.
Beesly. Oh, my God.
Hey-
Which tie makes me look
like a guy who likes sofas?
My agent's putting me up
for a furniture commercial.
Ah. Definitely blue.
Totally, right?
So, Big Tuna, what's up?
Back in the small pond?
For now, yeah, yeah. I was just
spreading myself way too thin...
Thin-sliced Tuna.
Carpaccio. Go on.
Well, it took me a while.
But I finally realized
that I can't give 100%
to two things at once,
you know?
Yeah. Tell me
about it.
I've been trying to act
and manage this branch.
Half the time, I don't
know if I'm wearing
my stage makeup
or my work makeup.
Huh.
Well, you know,
you can't have everything,
so you gotta ask yourself
what makes you the happiest.
You just go all in for what's most
important. That's my new thing.
Is everything okay?
No. Everything
is not okay.
The county
took my cats.
Wait, all of them?
Two sacks' worth.
Apparently, my apartment
complex has rules
about how many pets are
too many for a studio.
And while I was out picking Phillip
up from daycare, they came.
They came into my house.
That's awful, Angela.
I'm so sorry.
It's the
that lives downstairs.
She's this uptight, judgmental shrew.
You know the type.
I've never met
anyone like that.
And they're gone.
And I have no one left.
Without my cats, lam utterly
and completely alone.
Angela, you still
have your son.
I guess.
Attention, everyone.
May I have your attention?
There are four new deadly
weapons in this office.
Basher, thrasher,
crasher and...
Smasher.
"Smasher"? No.
Where'd you get that?
Fireball!
This morning,
after hours of combat
with some of
the city's best teenagers,
learned my black belt
in Goju-Ryu martial arts.
I had to find a new dojo after
Sensei Ira and I parted ways.
My new sensei,
Sensei Billy,
thought I had more than enough
training to take the test.
Turns out Sensei Ira
was a bit of a shyster.
Sensei Billy says
most students
don't spend $150,000 over 20
years to get their black belt.
I would like to invite you all
to my black belt ceremony,
right here in
the office at lunch.
Lunch not provided.
Fireball!
That's how it's done.
That's pretty good.
I feel safe.
Hey, Erin.
ls Andy in?
Oh! ls Andy in? Sorry, I
thought you said, "ls Indian?"
And I was like,
"ls Indian what?"
ls Indian food good?
ls Indian jewelry pretty?
Is Indian hair an expensive kind of wig?
Yes to all three, by the way.
Lately, I've been
having a lot of trouble
keeping track of
Andy's calendar.
His student film audition
schedule is crazy hectic.
Yes. There's Andy. Andy is in.
I'm a good receptionist.
I know he's in.
David Walrus
in his native habitat.
Hey, Andy.
Can we go in your office and talk?
Yeah.
This isn't gonna be
an easy conversation.
I told Andy that he
was on very thin ice
when he snuck away for three
months to the Caribbean.
Then last week,
he used company money
to buy a top-of-the-line
photo printer.
In his words, "The kind
that's good for headshots."
And yesterday, he asked me
to pay for cheek implants.
Claimed it's going to boost office morale.
Now, he's a good guy.
But honestly,
at a certain point,
the ice gets too thin,
and you fall through.
And that is
when you get fired.
Andy...
I'm gonna stop
you right there.
David, this documentary is
going to air in two weeks.
I feel like it's a once in a lifetime
opportunity to pursue my dream.
Uh-huh. But...
Every minute
that I spend here
is time not spent
making audition videos
for reality dating,
cooking or singing shows.
I got a real shot here.
And I'll never be
able to forgive myself
if I blew it because
I was too focused
on my stupid
paper companyjob.
No offense.
So you think you've been
too focused on your job?
At my last
headshotsfifing,
I was so distracted wondering
what I was missing at work
that I came across totally manic.
And I was going for zany.
So you want to quit Dunder
Mifflin to pursue acting?
Well, no, actually.
I see no reason to limit
myself to just acting.
I am pursuing fame
of any kind.
Could be singing. Could be dancing.
I don't... ltjust...
I owe it to myself
and my future fans.
Well, I guess I can't stand
in the way of a man's dream.
And it seems like
you have the gift.
Thank you, David.
There's probably
no way I can talk you
into staying at
this point, huh?
Nope. Lhave
made up my mind.
I'm really sorry.
Well, good luck.
Hey, thank you.
Not gonna need it.
Okay-
Well, that kind
of worked out.
I think just about
anybody can be a star.
My postman, the nightjanitor here...
But Andy?
No, definitely not.
Charisma black hole.
Oh! Clark.
I'm actually here
today. Surprise.
So I was wondering if maybe
I could have my desk back.
Right. Yeah.
But, you know, I've
actually been working
pretty hard here
on a daily basis.
So, I kind of feel
like I've earned this.
I mean, you know?
You totally have.
You have earned it. But maybe
I could be with my wife.
It's kind of the
whole reason why I'm here.
Right.
Well, I'm here
to sell paper.
Burn.
Wow.
All right, Jim, look. I just
got made junior salesman.
Right? And Wallace
is here today.
And I don't want him
to just think of me
as a customer service rep
that sits in the annex.
I mean, you can get that,
right? Right?
And what do you need more
face time with Wallace for?
You trying to get
a second second job here?
It's okay.
You can sit in the annex.
What?
I'll come visit you.
Okay-
The annex it is.
I'll be sitting at your desk,
if that's okay with you.
It's fine with me.
Have fun. But be careful.
It is very easy to get lost in
Pete's beautiful, dead eyes.
Everyone, a little breaking news for you.
Just had a little chat
with David Wallace.
And I'm taking a leave of absence
from Dunder Mifflin forever.
I can't say
we didn't see it coming,
but it's a sad day
when anybody is fired.
- We're so sorry, Andy...
Uh-uh-uh.
Andy was not fired.
I wasn't fired. What are
you talking about?
I'm fired up. Yes.
Guys, I'm leaving to pursue my
lifelong dream of being famous.
On, Andy.
Yeah, so I'll see you
on the red carpet.
'Cause see,
that's how it works.
Andy sings beautifully,
and he's really good at dancing.
He's a good speaker.
But there's just something there
you don't want to look at.
Hey, how am I doing as your
desk mate, by the way?
You probably
miss Clark.
Yeah, a little bit.
Wow. But, um...
I get that...
No, no.
No, it's cool.
I get it.
It's cool, man.
I'm sure you and I
will have our own thing.
Yeah. Definitely.
Go Phillies, right?
You don't watch baseball.
I keep forgetting that.
I just think you're going
into this a little fast.
I'm 38, Darryl.
How much slower should I go?
Show business is cold.
Let's say you get a job,
which you probably won't.
They're not gonna
cut you any slack.
You're meant for a job
with lots and lots of slack.
All right. I get it.
The male
is a funny species.
We don't just tell each other how we feel.
That's chick stuff.
So instead of saying,
"Hey, Andy, I love you, man.
"I don't want you to leave,"
you say something like,
"Hey, Andy, you're making the
worst mistake of your life.
"You're not talented."
Well...
Right back
at you, Darryl.
I'm gonna
miss you, too.
Andy's from the generation that
thinks they should all be famous.
What happened
to the generation
that knew you shut up,
did your work
and died quietly
from a heart attack?
Could Andy make it
as an entertainer?
I don't know. You know
who's really funny?
This bird in the park
that can't fly right.
I'd pay to see him.
But I don't have to,
'cause the park is free.
I will now perform the ceremonial
changing of the belts.
He will now perform the
ceremonial changing of the belts.
It's not a large room.
I think they heard me.
Take my belt,
Master.
I now submit to you
every part of myself.
That's really okay. I'm mostly
focused on the belt here.
Just slip it off my...
Slip it off my hips.
Hold it...
Take a step back.
Okay, okay,
I can't...
I can't do this if you're gonna
be thrusting like that, okay?
I think we're gonna
have to cut this off.
He will now perform the ceremonial
cutting off of the belt.
He...
Dwight has been practicing
karate for years.
When we were dating, I would help
him with his strength training.
He would strap me to his chest in a
Baby Bjorn made for fat children
and do lunges
across the farm.
I felt like I was flying.
There it is.
Congratulations. Good job.
We did it, we did it.
I love you.
Okay.
Thanks.
I will now perform
my final kata forms.
You're going to watch me, right?
Yes, I will.
Sensei, you're not watching.
Yeah, I'm watching.
Just do it.
Ha! Ha!
Watching?
I'm watching.
Watch this part, okay?
Oh. Oh!
Sensei, do you generally
do house calls like this?
You can just
call me Billy.
And no. No,
but Dwight insisted.
He wanted to receive
his black belt
in the place he loves
most in the world.
He said that?
He's an odd guy,
isn't he?
Yes.
Irritating? Also yes.
But I've got
to hand it to him,
he is one of
the most tenacious
and determined men
I've ever met.
I am so proud of you,
Schruberry blue.
I really felt like I almost lost her.
And nothing is worth that.
Boy, I tell you, Jim,
a lot of guys in my circle,
they wouldn't even change
their golf schedule
to shore up their marriage, let
alone their professional goals.
Dude, there is no way
that Jim is just back here
to "hang out with Pam."
Oh!
You did not just say that.
You don't know Pam.
She is really cool.
All I'm saying is,
forget about my chair.
He wants the manager's chair. And
I thought you wanted that job.
Yeah, I did.
But I made
too many mistakes.
It's out of my reach now.
Besides, I think Jim
would be a fine manager.
I'd be happy to see
Jim as manager.
So the reason I called you in here
is because Andy is moving on.
Again.
And I'm looking
for a new manager.
And with his performance
this year,
I have been
considering Dwight.
Am I crazy?
Not at all.
It should be Dwight.
You sure?
You're going to want to invest in
a lot more liability insurance,
but...
Yeah.
Hey, if there's someone who
loves paper more than Dwight,
I definitely don't want
to meet that person.
Andy, we just wondered
if we could have a word.
It's now or never.
Well, we just had a quick question
about this decision of yours.
You know, to leave
a stable job
and pursue a career
in the entertainment business
in your late 30s with no
savings to fall back on
and no real connections in that
business, which can be competitive.
Yeah, sure.
What's your question?
Our question is...
it seems dumb.
Well, it's better than sticking around
here and half-assing it, right?
Of course.
But what if you were
to stay here,
you know, and
"full-ass" it?
Yeah.
Really give it a go?
Be the greatest manager in the history
of this branch and in that way,
achieve the fame and immortality
that you seek? Mmm?
No, I like my plan better.
Well, Andy,
your plan sucks, okay?
Nobody is going
to hire you ever.
You're too character-y
to be a lead,
and you're not fat enough to
be a great character actor.
What?
No, I don't think
he can make it as an actor.
But he also can't make it
as an employee in an office,
so, you know,
why not go nuts with it?
Hey, are you still
in charge of office supplies?
Yes. Yeah.
You are?
I seem to have
a sticky note emergency,
where I grab it
on the wrong end,
and then, this happens.
Oh, boy, um...
If you could help me out,
that would be...
I could give you
some beginner stickies.
Anything would help.
Thank you. Okay.
Here you go.
Also, while you're at it,
if you did have a salt packet,
three tacks and some aspirin,
that'd be great.
Wow. You have that.
Mmm-hmm.
Wow, that's...
It's all yours.
You come so prepared.
Aspirin.
If you want to get rid of a headache,
you sit on something sharp.
Any sensei will tell you that.
Hey, congratulations
on that black belt, man.
It's really great.
Thank you.
So I saw you talking
to Wallace earlier.
Is he going to offer
you the manager's job?
No.
He was maybe
thinking of you for it.
Yeah, right.
I'm afraid
that ship has sailed.
I wouldn't be
too sure about that.
Just saying.
Hello.
Well, hello.
Big day for you.
Thank you.
Love the belt.
Yes.
You know, I don't know
anything about karate,
but I have broken
a few boards in my day.
Hiya!
Diving boards at my
family pool in Redding.
I was an obese child.
I never talk
about that here,
but Nard-Dog's outta here,
so lettin' it all hang out.
This is exciting.
You're finally gonna get
to go out and flap your wings.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
'Cause a lot of people are
saying I might not make it.
I doubt you'll make it.
Very few do
who try to be a star.
But listen, you've saved up enough
money to take a couple of years off,
and pursue your dream
and have some fun, right?
No, I just applied for
more overdraft protection.
Andy, I have nothing to gain
from getting you to stay,
and everything to gain
from you leaving.
But please, I have known you for years.
I have seen you perform.
Dear God, don't quit
your dayjob.
Nothing is
impossible to him who will try.
Alexander the
Great, if he were Cockney.
You're bad.
I'm gonna make it.
Every person
who's been on Conan
has a crazy story
about how they made it.
Every person.
Erin.
Honest Erin.
Cannot tell a lie.
We lay together.
That's something
you can't take back.
So true.
Is there a question,
or are... What?
Will you tell me bluntly,
do you think I'm making
a terrible mistake
quitting my job
to become an actor?
Bluntly? Yes.
Huge mistake.
Andy, honestly, I think
you might become homeless
or maybe even starve.
Thank you.
You can stay on
as a salesman, Andy.
Thank you.
Dwight, could you come in
here for a second, please?
Say it again.
Will you be
the new manager?
Where?
What branch?
Here. Scranton.
Come on.
Come on, Dwight. Get up.
Let's go. It's good news.
I'm sorry.
I've just waited for this
moment my entire life.
I mean, I was interim manager
once, but then I shot that gun.
What?
But this isn't
interim manager.
No.
It's Dwight K. Schrute...
Manager.
Why do you
already have this?
In case Michael or Andy ever got
killed in a traffic accident
and there was a trade
show on the same day.
You will not regret
this decision, David.
I know.
I will never,
ever let you down.
I know, Dwight.
I know.
Okay-
Okay. All right. You're gonna do great.
Hey.
Wow, hey.
Hi.
What's up?
I have a question.
Okay-
I had a question.
Really?
I did!
Yeah, totally you did.
Super important.
I need you to stay right here
while you think about it.
Okay. All right? I'm gonna wait.
All right.
I did not come back
here just to see you.
No, I'm sure
you did not.
What was
yourquesflon?
I don't know,
but it might take me a long
time to figure it out.
Well, then,
I should figure out
things to do
while I'm waiting.
Exactly.
Hey, everybody.
I changed my mind.
Not leaving. I'm gonna
stay on in sales.
Oh! Thank God...
Because sales could
be your best role yet.
Hey. Good choice,
man. Seriously.
Don't wanna see you
in a porn next year.
Okay-
Ooh! There's a great play
about a salesman.
Death of a Salesman.
I don't think so.
Sure, Death of a Salesman
by Arthur Miller.
- It's a great play about crushed dreams.
- Mmm.
No, this one was written
by SpongeBob SquarePants.
Got any hot leads?
See, so you just push from under
and turn it around, and boom.
Now, the staple
crimps outward.
I had no idea.
And here, I've been stapling
the same way for 20 years
like a frickin' sheep.
Look who's back.
I'm back.
Hey, look, and now,
it's like a double date.
Wow. 'Cause...
Bup-bup!
Widdle-de-doo.
Actually, maybe we should go
on a double date sometime.
That'd be fun.
Yeah, we should do that
for real sometime.
Well, how about
Thursday?
Well, Thursday's tough
because“.
Weeknights are actually
tough just because...
They are.
That's true, yeah.
Just forget it.
Forget I said anything.
What?
Attention, everyone.
Just a quick announcement.
Little reconfiguration
to the staff.
Dwight Schrute...
David.
Can I just do one thing while
you're making this announcement?
And then, I'll never,
ever do it again.
I don't think so. But
it's just one thing.
Just let me... Let me do this...
Dwight... Dwight...
Come on... What I was
about to say is Dwight...
I'm sorry, I gotta...
This'll be a second, sorry.
Just wait and send
it to voice mail.
Yeah.
Uh...
Come on.
Then we'll get him
a new set of drums.
Oh, my God.
Dwight Schrute is manager!
Yeah!
B rava. B rava.
Way to go, Dwight.
Whoo!
Creed Bratton is
the new manager!
Congrats.
What's going on?
Dwight's the new manager.
He freaking did it.
Congratulations, Dwight.
Pam.
Congratulations, buddy.
Thank you, Jim.
Congrats, Dwight.
Get out of Jim's seat.
But I fought for this seat.
You're an annex kid.
You might be bullpen. We'll see.
Give it a couple years.
Scram.
It's nice to have you back.
So...
I wanted to offer
you a new position.
Let's hear it.
Assistant regional manager.
Nope. Can't accept
that job.
It's not a real job.
Jim.
I'll tell you
what I could accept
is assistant
to the regional manager.
That is a real job, and
one I'd be proud to take.
Shake on it?
Done. Way
to negotiate, idiot.
Don't get me wrong.
lam definitely here for Pam.
But this is
an awesome added bonus.
So, all the numbers
adding up?
Hey, I didn't get a chance to say
it, but, congratulations, Dwight.
Thank you.
Yes, congratulations.
Yeah, and, Dwight, I'd like
to be the first to say
congratulations.
This is a big day for you.
Hmm.
Yes, it is.
Carry on.
How did I just abandon
my dream so quickly?
It's 'cause I had a fallback.
That's the problem.
When you have fallbacks,
it's just easy to give up.
When Cortés
landed in Mexico,
only way he got his
men to defeat the Aztecs
was by burning
all of his own boats
so they could
never return home.
Huge dick move,
but very effective.
I need to be that same
kind of dick to myself.
Everyone!
Changed my mind again.
Which is it now?
Dream or no dream?
Uh, dream.
Goin' with my dream.
Gotta go all in.
Ain't that right, Jim?
Oh. Don't look at me, 'cause I think
you're making a terrible choice.
All in! Whoo!
Toby!
Hey. I changed my mind again.
I am gonna leave Dunder Mifflin
to pursue acting after all.
Okay, then, Andy.
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
I can't have good old Dunder
Mifflin to fall back on,
or else I'll never succeed.
Gotta burn those boats!
So I need you
to go into my file
and put down that
I was fired for theft
and/or groping wieners.
Andy, you know
I can't do that.
It'd be lying.
Seriously?
Yeah, I'm...
Come on, just do it.
I can't.
All right, fine.
Just know that
you made me do this.
Come on. Andy, no.
God, Toby, don't...
Stop blocking my hand.
No, no.
This is your...
You brought this on.
No, no. Andy.
Okay, all right. Groped you good.
Off to Hollywood!
This is Angela.
Hello, Miss Polodnikovski.
How can I help you?
Did my rent check
not clear?
Because I just transferred
another $25 to that account.
So if there's a problem, it's
clearly on your end. And...
Oh. Oh!
Oh, okay. Good.
Then what is this about?
No, no. Hey, hey.
No, you are out of line,
Miss Polodnikovski.
No. No, you are.
No, you are!
Evicted? Fine!
I don't want to live in that
cesspool anyway.
Listen, I get my security deposit back.
Yes, I do.
That is not fair!
Well, you know what?
You have so many
hairs on your chin,
Animal Control
should've taken you away.
That is very unladylike.
You are disgusting!
What do you think
that was about?
David.
I lost the Scranton
White Pages account.
Do you have any idea
how much paper that is?
And I'd just like to point
out I was mad at Dwight.
I did it out of spite.
We put the past
behind us, though, Andy.
What if I told you
I hate you and this company?
Enough, Andy. Enough!
Just stop forgiving me,
David. Please?
This is my last chance to honor
what is best inside myself.
What if I took a dump
on your new car?
Oh, my God.
Eleanor Roosevelt once said,
"The future belongs to those who believe
in the beauty of their dreams."
I think she's right.
I feel calm now.
Get out!
I feel like for
the first time in a long time,
I'm doing the right thing.
Andy.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Heavy stuff like
books on the bottom.
So I don't squash
my knickety-knacks on top.
Yeah, okay,
that's not what I mean.
You don't have to leave
because you said you would.
Don't let pride
ruin your whole life.
Okay? It's not worth it.
Wow!
Angela.
What we had was great, and, honestly,
I think about it a lot, too.
Ugh. But I just...
It's in the past.
And I feel like we shouldn't...
No, that's not...
rehash...
No, none... No, stop.
It's just...
Exactly.
Okay.
Well, have a good trip.
Good luck, Andy.
Thanks, Angela. You, too.
Thanks.
A bridge a-burnt.
No turning back now.
Everybody, Lorelei and I would
like to say thank you and good-bye
the only way we know how.
Good lord.
Can't you just leave?
You know, Andy, you could just
say a really nice good-bye.
Tuna, I'm a performer,
and perform I shall.
You Okay?
It's just
a really nice song.
Awesome.
Nice!
Thanks, Meredith.
Who knows?
Maybe Andy will make it.
He's not terrible.
STANLEY'. Yeah.
And people worse than him
make it all the time,
like Lil' Romeo.
No, he's good.
He was good.
Good night, Kevin.
Night, Oscar.
Tents?
Are you thinking
of going camping?
I thought you found
nature vulgar.
Well, I've changed
my mind.
Wait
a minute, Angela.
You're not thinking
of living in a tent...
God, would you just mind
your own business?
Okay, listen.
I'm just gonna say this.
You are not going
to live in a tent.
Oh, God.
Come stay with me.
You don't want me
at your place.
I do. Yes.
Not forever, but until you
get back on your feet,
which won't be long.
It's the least I can do.
Well...
Separate bathrooms.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's go get Phillip.
Then, we'll get
your stuff...
Okay-
And you get the hell
out of that place.
Okay-
Are you allowed
to have pets?
Oh, Angela.
Yesterday, I was just your
average, ordinary paper salesman
with a farm and a bunch of
pipe dreams about beet fuel.
Today, I leave here a regional
manager with a black belt.
It really is amazing how your
life can change in one day.
You talk to Wade
and Colin?
No, I just saw I missed their call.
Why? What's up?
We got an offer
on the table.
What kind of offer?
A buyout.
What?
We're in play, baby.
Oh, my God.
We did it.
We did it!
Hey, and look.
The buyers wanna make sure
it's not just a Philly play.
Okay.
So get this.
They're gonna pay for us
to go pitch out west.
We're talking Spurs,
the Jazz, Cowboys.
Blake Griffin, baby.
Wow, that is...
Yeah.
Wow.
We did it.
Yeah, we did it.
Hey, how long do they
think that's gonna take?
Wade said we could do the whole
country in three months.
Oh, man.
Yeah, I can't do it.
Can't do what?
This, man. I can't
do this to Pam.
No, no.
Jim, this is different.
This is everything.
I know.
And I can't do it.
So is your place all
bachelor, slobby and gross?
Nope, it's neat and tastefully
appointed, like most gay men's homes.
The stereotype
holds up.
I wouldn't know.
lneverhved with a gay guy.
Angela, you just were...
I love him.
I know.
I understand more than most,
but we both have to move on.
You can't...
No, not the Senator.
I love Dwight.