To me, the Sixers
are a five seed, tops.
I think they're going to
the conference finals.
Bynum, obvious monster, three-point
shooting, don't even...
I bit my lip at
lunch today.
Sucks.
Anyway, I just don't see it.
The Knicks are tough.
The Nets are tough.
The Nets
are super tough.
And now I have this big bump
on my lip that hurts!
I hate it.
The Hawks are terrible.
They're always terrible.
Okay, you need to think about
it before you come with the...
Whatever.
It's not a big deal.
You know, I always
tell my three-year-old,
if this is the worst thing
that's going to happen...
You got to be
kidding me!
Okay, Pam! That's it!
I'm going home!
Morning, Meredith!
What?
Sorry, Pam.
Yikes.
Jim's been spending a few
days a week in Philly,
and I'm not going to lie,
it's been challenging.
Yesterday, things took
a turn for the worse.
I found out
Cece has lice.
So, I was up all night
disinfecting every
sheet, towel, toy,
item of clothing
in the entire house.
I'm exhausted.
But don't tell Jim.
He has a huge
meeting today.
Under a lot of pressure,
and he's doing it
all for the family.
I am meeting Dr. J today,
otherwise known as Julius Erving,
famed 76er
and my own personal hero.
But I have to be careful not
to rub it in Pam's face,
because
let's be honest.
How would I feel if I was at
home, stuck with the kids
while she was go-karting
with John Stamos?
You sound tired.
Everything okay?
Great!
Everything's great!
Hey, are you nervous
about your big meeting?
Little bit. It's a lot
of pressure, you know?
But that's what I
signed up for, right?
Jim, the limo's here.
You know what? I've got to hop
off, because my taxi is here
to take me
to the meeting.
Call me later.
Okay.
Good luck!
Thanks.
I love you.
Love you, too. Bye.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
I mean, it's what
you want, so...
It's how it has to be.
I know, I know.
It's just hard.
Me and Val were going nowhere,
and if I'm going to
be working in Philly,
I'm going to need my freedom.
So I convinced Val
to break up with me.
Here's how you do it.
You say, "What are you going
to do, break up with me?"
Like, as a joke
and then you gain
a lot of weight.
I'll never be sorry.
Not for a moment of it.
Me neither.
Hey, Meredith, I need your
supply requests today.
Jesus H. in the morning, will
you stop your nagging already?
No wonder Jim left you.
He didn't leave me.
He just went part-time.
Can you just fill out
the form, please?
Yes.
I'm sure she's
just confused.
People scratch their heads
when they're confused.
Not always like an ape, the way
Meredith just did, but it happens.
Hurry up already.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
Between the foster homes and the
orphanage, I had lice 22 times.
Holy wow,
that's a big one.
All right, pencils down,
everyone, we've got lice!
God, Meredith! Lice? Did you
not sign a pledge to shower?
What? Lice?
Oh, my God.
Lock the doors,
we are on full quarantine!
Dwight, relax! It's just lice.
Maybe. Possibly.
Just lice, Pam?
Of all the vermin in God's
great green kingdom,
lice are the ones
I detest the most.
My first day of school, I had lice
and no one would play with me.
For 15 years,
they called me freak,
and four-eyes, and sci-fi
nerd and girl puncher,
all because I had
lice when I was seven.
Make way. No, inspect me.
Dwight!
This is the cleanest scalp I've ever seen.
You are all clear.
I should be. I use lice
shampoo every morning.
Hey!
Stop that!
Dwight!
Next.
Geez, Meredith!
This is an office,
it's not one of
your beanbag orgies.
Let's give her a break.
We don't know for sure
this is Meredith's fault.
Pam, really? Come on.
Well, what do you want?
I know who I am.
Nobody's taking
Meredith Palmer
to the opera
to meet the Queen.
Lice! More lice.
Angela has lice.
Ew!
Ooh! Yabber. Lice!
Yikers, lice.
No!
How? I'm so clean.
Yeah, big time lice.
Ah!
I wash my hands at least six times a day.
Toilet seat covers?
Yes, thank you,
even when I pee.
Apparently none of that
is protection enough,
not when it
comes to Meredith.
Oh!
Hey, what are you wearing?
It's a hazmat suit. That stands
for hazardous materials...
Men's suit wearing.
If you rent more than four times a
year, it just makes sense to buy.
ls there anyone else
here that is lice free?
Excellent! You have
your own hazmat suits?
No.
Renters.
Okay, I'm going to need you
to gather your belongings,
retreat to the warehouse,
conduct your
business there
until the infected
have been de-loused.
Let's get going. I'm going
to stay here and fight.
If you don't hear from
me by lunch, call me.
I might want lunch.
All right, we're going
down to my warehouse.
That means we're
playing by my rules.
No messing with the baler.
And be cool in front of me
and Val, we just broke up.
You got dumped?
Yeah, she ended things.
Break-ups
are the worst.
The only thing that
got me through mine
was large amounts
of shepherd's pie
and Brandy, the singer,
not the drink.
Here, man. You need
that more than me.
Thanks, man.
Yeah.
Guys, I think we should
all ease up on Meredith.
This has got to
be hard for her.
No, no, no, no. I have not
yet begun to shame.
That's it! I'm getting my stuff.
I'm leaving for the day.
No! Stanley!
If you leave now, then
you'll get it in your car
and then you'll
get it in your house!
Get off me!
I'm trying to save
you from yourself!
All right, I'll stay!
There's a pencil
poking into my rolls.
PAM". Maybe it was Meredith.
Maybe she brought in lice
that are totally different
than the lice
that I got from Cece.
So, let's notjump to the simplest
conclusion that she got her lice from me!
That is how wars
get started.
Fine, I'll tell her
it was me.
Oh, man!
That's fresh squeezed!
And are all
the snacks complimentary?
Yeah. Take some home
if you want.
No, that's okay. I'm...
I'm sorry, is this
the conference center?
No, Mr. Erving called, said he'd
rather meet you at his private court.
You've got to be kidding me.
Hey, Meredith, I need to tell you some...
Yeah, Pam? What do you want?
Oh, my God! Meredith.
What are you doing?
Baking a cake. What does
it look like I'm doing?
Getting rid of the lice.
Stop!
I'm so sorry!
Can you hold that thought?
That's my wax.
You know, I think
these critters
migrated from down south.
What were you saying?
Nothing.
I'm going to tell her. But
now is clearly not the time.
I will buy her a wig,
we'll have a few laughs.
There's a right
way to do this.
Scalp leeches. Skull vampires.
Follicle gypsies.
Hair lawyers.
One thing is clear,
it's kill or be killed!
No, no, no. It's more of a nuisance,
really. It's not that big a deal.
So, I've collected your
hats and your coats...
To be burned!
To be washed.
What do we do
about our heads'?
I'm not going
to lie. Lye!
No. All we need
is mayonnaise.
Excuse me?
She's right, it works.
I would imagine.
Yes, it helps to suffocate
the little buddies.
And it's a really
healthy alternative to
the chemicals found
in most lice shampoos.
I can appreciate that.
I also only eat local,
organic produce.
Sha-boom!
How you like me now?
Take a picture,
it'll last longer.
We don't want it to
last longer. It's horrible.
Bald people make me sick.
Yeah, yeah, everybody
pile on Meredith.
But I'm the only one with the balls
to show them lice who's boss.
Okay, nobody panic!
If everybody just follows
my instructions,
then nobody else
needs to end up bald.
Not that it looks bad, Meredith!
It looks... It looks awesome!
You look like a baby who
suddenly aged 50 years.
A cute baby!
But something sucked
the life force out of it.
I'm so sorry. We need mayonnaise.
We need it now.
I'll go.
It's not a big deal.
Please. No, Meredith,
can I get you
something special
while I'm at the store?
Candy, or one of
those stylish turbans?
Thanks, Pam. I'll take a pack of
Nicorette gum and a pack of Kools.
Okay-
Let's talk pubes, people.
Hey, Darryl.
Hey, Val.
That was tragic.
That was like a car crash,
I couldn't look away.
You two still clearly have
feelings for each other.
Yeah.
What's going to make you
feel better, big guy?
When I was a kid, my grandmother
used to make me chocolate cake
when I wasn't feeling good.
She's not around
to do that anymore.
I'm sorry, I just need a moment
to myself to clear my head.
Poor Darryl. I can't bear to
see him suffer like this.
I think he needs
some hugs
and maybe some
chocolate cake.
This won't help him,
it's a muffin. Not cake.
Listen, let's try to get Darryl
the one thing in the world
he clearly wants
and needs the most.
An Escalade.
Or, what's-her-name?
Val.
Let's get Darryl Val.
I hope you don't mind me
bringing you out here.
I can't get my knees
under a desk.
Are you kidding me? I could
literally scalp tickets to this.
Well, you think you
can sink one from deep?
Listen, I don't
mean to intimidate you,
but I did play
a little high school ball.
Okay-
Wow!
Halpert's got game!
All right. Sorry.
I'm so sorry, this is my wife.
Can I take this?
If it's your wife,
you better take it.
Right?
Hey, what's up?
Everything okay?
Oh, no,
everything's great!
I was just calling to see
how the meeting went.
It's still happening
right now, actually. So...
He's really making
you work for it, huh?
Yes, it is very stressful. Are
you sure everything's okay?
Great. Lam killing it
over here.
Jim, I've got to go.
Okay, bye.
So sorry about that.
No problem. Hey, Jim, what
size do you wear, man?
I got a pair of Japanese Nikes
with your name on them.
What do you think?
I love it!
Once it's all over your head, just
leave it there for four hours.
That will be enough time
for the lice to fall asleep,
suffocate and then
pass away.
Sure.
And when you're
ready to get serious,
come to me to
get it done right.
Put those away
before you hurt yourself.
Oh, God! No.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Okay, it's easier with a
buddy, so everybody pair up.
Oscar, you want
to be my partner?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Pdloveto.
Hey, mayo buddy, $5 tip if
you unclog my ears. Okay?
Oh...
Creed, I'm so sorry. I'm already
partners with Pete. Right, Pete?
Uh... Yeah. We promised each other
if we ever got lice, we'd buddy up,
so, sorry, man.
Hey, Creed. You want
to be my buddy?
Oh, God.
Stuck with the weirdo.
Angela! You don't
want bugs, you know?
Who knows where
those bugs will end up?
You're getting a bargain.
I ain't got no hair no more.
Creed.
I'm all done. My turn.
I'm sorry, Pam.
It looks a little messy.
Wait.
How's that?
I feel it working.
Eiffel Tower!
Can I help you?
Well, we don't want to pry, but we
heard you broke up with Darryl.
Yeah, that's true.
We think you made
a big, big mistake.
Big mistake.
Quite enormous.
He's a real catch and you
should take him back.
Okay, thank you.
Is that all?
No. No, that is not all!
Let me tell you
what real life is like.
The men dry up
and the nights get lonely.
The only calls on your machine
are from collection agencies
about that pair of motorcycle
boots you've never even worn.
You stalk your old high-school
boyfriend online,
go to his daughter's soccer
games and make a scene.
You buy a diamond ring
for yourself,
wear it on your right hand and
tell yourself you're all you need.
One day you're alone, tired,
at your feet, a dying bird.
Where did it come from?
Why did you kill it?
Is it because, in some
strange way, it is you?
Thank you all
for your concern,
but I'm going to have to
ask you toleave, okay?
So does this mean you're
going to take Darryl back?
No.
Well, then, what would you say
to you and me hitting the town,
because I'm free
literally forever.
Yeah, Kevin asked me out.
I was kind of feeling good about
re-entering the dating pool,
and then Kevin
asked me out.
Thought I might trade up
to a new level of man.
Then Kevin asked me out.
Hello?
Hi, honey, it's Mom.
Look, Gene's school just called.
She still has lice!
What, no. That can't...
I don't...
Don't worry, don't worry,
I'm on my way to pick her up.
But you might have lice, too. Lice
can be tricky. Sometimes lice...
Oh, my God.
Shave her head!
You guys, I'm so sorry.
It's just been so chaotic
with Jim gone that I...
Yeah, yeah.
Princess Fancy Pants,
letting Jane Twelve Pack
over here take the fall.
She's right, Pam.
ls there a volume knob
on that thing?
Yes, there's a volume knob
on that thing!
Meredith,
I am so sorry.
Well, a lot of good your sorries
are doing her now, Pam.
She's a monster.
I meant to say something
earlier, I just...
Just, just what?
Just forgot?
Who's the one that didn't
bring lice into the office?
Meredith.
Sure I gave everybody
pink eye once,
and my ex keyed
a few of their cars.
And yeah, I BM'ed in the
shredder on New Year's.
But I didn't bring the lice in.
That was all Pam.
Attention,
people of the office.
You have exactly 60 seconds
to evacuate the bullpen.
At that time
I will be tossing this
powerful insecticidal grenade,
which contains piperonyl
butoxide, as well as...
Dwight? Are you okay?
Whoa...
That butoxide has a mild
hallucinogenic effect,
but I don't think
it's kicked in yet.
I'm going to
count down from 10.
Nine, yellow,
cold, sad, purple...
Wow. He got to purple.
Ow!
Sorry.
You're waterboarding me!
Oops.
No, this is fine.
We're allowed to do this.
This is okay.
Okay, you're UP!
Yeah, I'm actually kind of
sad to see this baby go.
You do kind of
look like Elvis.
But we should probably wash
all the dead lice out.
Okay. Okay
Okay-
Is that too cold?
No, actually,
it feels kind of nice.
I wonder what
happened over there.
I've been sitting
here the whole time.
Oka.
Huh? y
Let's give it a shot.
Let's make it work.
Oh, no. I mean,
I want to, I just,
I don't want to force you into doing
something you don't want to do.
You're not.
I believe in us.
I'm back together
with Val.
Yay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Had a pretty
good day today.
Not everything went exactly
according to plan.
But lice, if you're watching, I'm
ready for you anytime, anywhere.
Hey, Erin
already take off?
I guess so.
Okay-
And you're Kareem,
coming to help.
Okay, I'm Kareem.
That makes total sense.
I'm Kareem, you're Dr. J.
Just sounds weird
to say out loud.
And it went
like this.
And that's all.
That's it.
No one will believe this back home,
but that's okay.
That's all right. Let me
show you how to do it.
Yeah, you show
me how to do it.
This is Jim Halpert,
leave a message.
Hey, honey. It's me,
just trying to catch you
before going home.
Um...
Well. Just give
me a call whenever.
Hope your day got
better. Love you.
Hey. What are you
doing right now?
I'm just going
to go home.
My mom's been watching
the kids all day.
Let her stay another hour.
Let's go get a beer.
Really? A beer sounds
incredible right now.
No duh. Let's go,
you're buying.
Meredith, I am so
sorry about today.
Forget about it.
I just did not
realize how hard
it was going to
be without Jim.
I mean, I really respect you for
being a single morn all these years.
It whipped my ass
in half a week.
I have to say, there are
not a lot of people
who could pull
off a shaved head,
but you are rocking it.
Right?
I got the bartender's phone
number when you were in the john.
I'm going to take that freak to
bone-town before the night is over.
Get it, girl.
This one is for all
you ladies out there!
I come...
Not yet.
I come home
in the morning light
My mother says, "When you going
to live your life right?"
Oh, Mother dear,
we're not the fortunate ones
And girls,
they want to have fun
Oh, girls just
want to have fun