We've got to clear out
this cabinet, people.
A lot of these
are dead accounts.
Scranton Mimeograph Corp?
I don't think we're doing
business with them any time soon.
That's odd.
A letter from Robert Dunder.
"A valuable artifact has come
into my possession.
"I have hidden it
until such time as a person
"of strong intellect
may safely recover it.
"This golden chalice
is of immeasurable
"historical and
religious significance."
The Holy Grail.
Did you send Dwight on a
quest for the Holy Grail?
I think I'm a little too
busy these days to send...
Oh, my God, I did send Dwight on a
quest for the Holy Grail.
The Dunder Code!
I completely forgot
about that prank.
That had to be, like,
six or seven years ago.
Stayed late every
night for a month.
Had a lot more
free time back then.
I don't get it.
Ah-ha!
A light bulb.
A light bulb?
A light bulb!
Okay, Okay-
Invisible ink.
Whoa.
- The ceiling above accounting!
- Dwight!
Down, Dwight! Dwight!
Man, I wish I was there to see
his face when he gets to the end
and finds the fake grail?
No grail?
You don't remember?
I don't.
An X?
Annex. It must open
something in the annex.
Oh.
"Seat of entrance."
What?
That's a flush.
The warehouse!
- There's nothing down here.
- Oh.
I expected more
from Young Halpert.
This just...
Forget it, forget it.
So, how are we getting on with our
grand social media initiative?
Well, we created
a fake profile
for a really cool guy
named Derek McBlack. Wow.
It's just Pete in sunglasses.
Oh.
And then we had him
like Dunder Mifflin.
Then we created a bunch
of fake friends for Derek,
and we had all of them
like Derek's likes.
So far we're only popular
with imaginary people,
but we think this is the
start of something big.
You two are geniuses.
And I am a genius for
putting you two together.
Well, all right.
Pete and I work
well together.
Not that there's anything
special about Pete.
It could be any guy.
Or girl.
Not that I'm into girls.
Not that I'm into Pete. Ah!
What was the question?
Hey.
Hey, Jim.
Peter Rowley at Bridgeport Capital
requested a meeting at lunch.
Okay-
Can we keep it on
the early side, though?
I've got that thing
in Scranton later.
Oh, sure.
No problem.
Cece's ballet recital
is today! I cannot wait!
I've been working
with her on her move.
It's called
the Cece Spin and Kiss.
Do you want to see it?
It's kind of like this.
It's pretty cute, right?
"Athlead."
Please. They're too lazy
to call it Athletes Lead?
Jim should just call
it Stumpany for stupid company.
There's nothing stupid
about working for yourself,
hanging out
with pro athletes,
getting free tickets to the games.
That's why I'm doing it.
You're working
for Stumpany, too?
Yeah. Just weekends for now, but
pretty soon I'm switching over.
What?
Yup.
Hey, Halpert,
what's the big idea?
First you jump ship, now you're
stealing Darryl, too? When will it end?
Well, take your worst fear
and multiply it by infinity.
You won't stop until you've
poached us all. Yeah.
Even you.
No!
I'll be damned if I'm
going to let us lose me.
Bye, Dwight.
How are you? Good to see you.
Thank you.
Hey, Angela, did you hear about the
Irish-American Cultural Center mural?
Ooh, I haven't heard it!
So, what about the Irish-American
Cultural Center mural?
Potato? Oh, no. Kevin,
it's not a joke.
Angela's husband put me up for a...
Um. Just never mind.
I have no information.
But I'm sure
as soon as they
know they'll call you.
Senator Lipton
helped me submit my design
for a new mural on
a building downtown.
Now I'm just waiting to hear
from the selection committee.
But, you know,
let's be realistic,
there are a ton of great artists in
Scranton with way more experience.
I mean, who are
they going to go with,
some nobody like me, or a
big name like Tracy Fleeb?
Well, I'm heading out
to Cece's dance recital.
Aw.
Hey, Cece! Daddy's going to
have dinner with us tonight,
after he comes to your recital.
Are you excited?
Yeah!
Let's call him!
Hey. I was just
about to call you.
Hey, hon! Are you close?
I am still in Philly,
actually.
What'?
It's insane.
This huge
investor got cold feet,
so I'm stuck here trying
to keep him on board.
Hon! I wish you would
have told me an hour ago
when you knew you
weren't going to make it.
Pam, I couldn't get out! I barely made
it out just to make this phone call.
I want Daddy!
You're going to do great.
And you know what? Mommy's going to
record it, so we'll watch it together.
Do you mind
doing that, Pam?
Of course.
Okay, are you sure you know
how to do video on the phone?
Yes, Jim, I think I know how to
point a rectangle at something.
Okay, okay. Just sometimes you're
not the best with the phone.
I know how to operate my phone, okay?
Listen, we're getting close.
We will talk to you later.
Say bye, Daddy!
Bye, Daddy.
Bye.
Yeah, see? You've still
got to press end, Pam.
Press end.
Oh, check it out,
this is our first real like!
Oh, my God!
Alan Olifson
from North Dakota.
He also likes Hammermill
and Georgia Pacific.
Wow, that guy's really into paper.
Yeah.
Well done, you two.
We did it!
Youth Task Force forever!
Yes!
Bap, bap, bap-
And then... Oh, wait.
No, you go...
Did I... Is that you? No, you
go first, and then it's a left.
No, you go... Okay, all right.
No, I didn't...
All right,
okay, start over.
You always mess that part up.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, God! Andy has just
started to be nice to me
and now I've
sent his girlfriend
into the arms
of a younger man!
And I cc'ed him
on every incriminating memo.
"Pete and Erin,
don't hold back.
"Our social media
presence should be
"hot, hot, hot.
Go at it vigorously."
I did everything but unzip
their pants for them.
Oh, God, Nellie!
Hey, everybody, uh, a coffee
order is going around.
On me! Just sign your name below.
Hmm.
You're welcome.
Wait, this says "Dunder
Mifflin Loyalty Pledge."
This? Oh, what?
Double mocha latte, please?
You got it.
Just sign your name below.
Whatever you want.
WWW Wedge?
Come on, Dwight.
Stop overreacting.
I'm getting all
my work done here.
No customers have complained,
nobody even knows.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Bust out
your complaint files.
I need everything
you've got on Darryl since
he started working for Jim
in the last few weeks.
Break it down
by keyword, okay?
Infuriating,
irresponsible...
They've got us set
up with Windows 95,
so you're kind
of dreaming here.
Okay, I'm going to
need you to print it out.
Customer loyalty.
What is it?
Can you hold
it in your hand?
Can you nudge it with your finger?
Can you dump it on a woman?
No! Why? Because it's an idea.
But what does it mean?
Oh, it's when you
get a free sandwich
after you've already
eaten 10 sandwiches.
Not even close.
Mr. Romanko has been
a client for 20 years.
He came in today
in a rage.
Why? Because of Darryl,
because Darryl was focusing
on outside projects
and needs to remember his
first priority, the client.
I wouldn't say a rage.
Mr. Romanko, we were a day late
on one of your deliveries,
but two of our trucks
were down for repairs.
It's very unlikely
it will happen again.
Thank you,
thank you.
No, you're not
going anywhere, okay?
You are angry and we are
going to hear you out!
All right? Because business
is about relationships,
and the key to relationships
is what, Darryl?
L...
It.
LoYa V Loyaw
"Loyalty" is exactly right!
Thank you. Yes, I
mean, it is everything.
Let's all ask ourselves, have we
been faithful in our relationships?
Mmm. That's none of
your damn business.
Darryl is
"dating" Dunder Mifflin.
Darryl is dating Val.
Still.
But he's flirting with
Jim's company on the side.
And we all know what
flirting can lead to.
I'm sorry, do I still
need to be here? Yes.
I'm still having a bit of trouble
understanding the importance of loyalty.
So, let's use an example.
Take Erin.
Erin's boyfriend, Andy,
is away across the ocean.
Yeah.
So is it all right for her to
flirt with Creed, for example?
Let's try it out.
No, let's not say Creed.
Let's say Mr. X.
Well, I think it would be immoral
for Erin to cheat on Andy.
Oh, I'm sorry,
didn't you cheat on Andy?
Yes, and he didn't like it.
Does Mr. X know that
Erin has a boyfriend,
or did Erin keep
that from Mr. X?
Okay, this is
really hard to follow.
Can we just say Pete, 'cause that's
the guy that Erin's flirting with?
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Little Ladybug Ballerinas!
Plié. One, two, three!
Really?
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Hello?
Yes, this is Pam Halpert.
I got the mural! Oh, my God!
Um, I'm sorry, I have to go.
My daughter is a ladybug.
I know that doesn't make any sense.
Um, thank you, thank you!
You're very rude.
Yes. Very rude.
Kids are dancing!
Thank you
so much for coming!
Darryl and I will
be here to serve you
for years and
years and years and years.
So, should we go call Jim and go
tell him to go screw himself?
Dwight, look. I'm sorry you're
having a hard time with this, okay?
Athlead is my future.
No disrespect
to Dunder Mifflin,
but if I can have fun
at work, I want that.
It can't be more fun than selling
paper and paper products.
It can. Are you
pretending to be crazy?
Huh?
Well, Andy's cute,
but he's too vanilla.
Whereas Pete,
he's just one sick dude.
I mean, you know this
guy likes to get weird.
I'm just going to
say this one more time,
Pete and I
haven't done anything.
It's true!
Yeah, right.
With slamming bods like that?
They ain't playing checkers.
People, it's 2013. Erin is a
strong, independent woman.
Who says she has to
end up with any man?
Okay, can everyone
please stop speaking for me?
Andy is my boyfriend,
Pete and I are just friends.
And that is the end of it!
Right, Pete?
That is correct.
Come on, guys. Where is
this even coming from?
Your feelings for Erin?
Probably your heart.
And a little bit your penis.
Kevin, really?
Nellie, you have to shut down
Youth Task Force.
I'm not sure if you need to start
a new task force to do that,
but please just do
whatever it takes.
I suppose that will
be all right. Yeah.
Most relationships
eventually die on their own.
But sometimes they just need a
little pillow over the face.
You're welcome, Andy. And
you're welcome, my own ass.
Listen, I appreciate
you taking the time with me.
Peter, please, we completely
understand your concerns here.
Let us just show you
the latest projections. Jim?
Wade actually has those,
on the road,
but he's going to be
calling in with those
numbers any second.
So just hold on one...
Actually...
Ah, nope.
That is my wife.
Again, he'll be
calling in any second.
Hey, give me a call back
when you get a chance.
Cece did great and I want
to tell you something.
Hey, boss, you've got
to jump on a delivery.
I don't do that anymore.
That's what they told me.
All right,
let's get this over with.
You looking for fun?
It just found you!
Whoo!
Here we go! Yeah!
Yes, we will be delivering
a shipment of paper today,
but I will also be delivering
you a big shipment of fun!
How far is this place?
Uh, not far at all, but I thought along
the way we could play some sports!
Fun.
Hey, really nice job
in that meeting in there.
Oh, thank you. I don't
know, I still thought...
Yeah.
I'm so proud of you, hon.
Oh, I don't know. Okay.
Just curious, though, what do
you have against Pete and Erin?
Well, Andy wrote me a really
nice recommendation letter
for the adoption agency,
so I just felt
like I owed him one.
Pete's a pretty
cool guy, though.
And Andy was
a terrible lover to Erin.
He basically ignored her,
and then left on a boat.
I didn't really
think about it like that.
Em, well, not everybody
has what we have.
What we have?
Hmm.
I just remembered.
I kissed that man.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Yes! Fast food.
I'll take a burger over a gross
Philly cheese-steak any day.
They have
fast food in Philly.
Not like this.
Exactly like this.
And your milkshake.
Thank you.
It's 30 degrees out,
you're drinking a milkshake?
Nope.
Fire in the hole!
Yeah!
Now that's what working at a
paper company is all about!
Wait, what are you doing? No, I
need the keys! We have to go!
You just threw a milkshake into a
restaurant where they make minimum wage.
It's a YouTube thing! Let's go, let's go!
Come on. They're coming!
Anyone want to see the video
from Cece's recital?
Oh, I would love to,
but I am swamped.
That.
I'll watch it.
Let's get this over with.
All right,
you don't have to...
Let's get
this over with, Pam.
Okay-
Wait, what?
Sorry, I'm in a rush
to get back to work.
Oh, no! I took a phone call
in the middle of taping
and then when I went to turn it
back on, I must have turned it off.
User error. I've heard it
happens to other people.
Oscar,
don't rub it in.
I'm sure Pam is
already kicking herself
for choosing a phone
call over her child.
Well, it was
an important phone call.
I haven't told anyone here
about the mural yet.
I want Jim
to be the first to know.
Whenever I tell him good news,
he's always like "Beesly!"
I love that.
The only thing better
than getting the job.
"Beesly!"
Hey.
Hello, Peter.
This barely even feels
like a prank anymore.
You missed a spot.
Fire in the hole!
Go, go, go!
Ha-ha, yeah,
joke's on you, buddy!
They make you come
back and clean it up.
I am sorry that that was so awkward
for you two in that meeting,
but I am going to have to
reassemble the Youth Task Force.
Oh, no, I really don't
think that's a good idea.
Well, that is not your call.
I made the decision.
You have no
choice in the matter,
and everybody knows it.
Well, okay then.
I guess we
don't have a choice.
Nope.
- Yeah.
Lady“.
You never
stop surprising me.
What?
What was that?
Did I just hear you
laughing with glee?
No. I was just
clearing my throat.
Good night.
Night.
Night, Creed.
- Hey!
- Hey.
So, how's it going?
We lost Bridgeport Capital.
I have no idea
what happened.
It's like everything I did,
he just wouldn't go for it.
PAM". I'm so sorry.
I have no idea where we're going
to come up with this money.
We have to work insanely hard
over the next few weeks.
I'm sorry. I feel like you've
already been working insanely hard.
Can you figure out how to
upload Cece's dance recital?
I definitely could
use a pick-me-up.
Actually, funny
story, I didn't get it.
I shouldn't have been so cocky about
my rectangle-holding skills after all.
You're not serious,
are you?
You didn't get
any of the recital?
No, I got the teacher
introducing them,
and then
the applause afterward,
but not so much
of the middle part.
Come on, Pam. Pam!
I asked you if you
could use the phone
and you swore
that you knew how.
Yeah, okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sure we can get a copy.
A lot of people
were taping it.
Oh, great. So we'll see somebody else's
kid with Cece in the background?
I mean, it's really not
that hard to film a video.
Is there... Um.
You want to ease
up a little bit?
Look, Pam, I don't know what to tell you.
I mean, what do I do?
It's gone, that moment's just gone.
I missed it.
I don't know, Jim. Maybe you
should have been there.
You're not serious,
right?
I mean,
how is that fair?
I'm in Philly, these are my days in Philly.
You've agreed to this.
You know what?
I don't think
you want to start
a conversation with me
about what's fair, okay?
This is way more
intense than I ever...
Pam, I'm not
explaining this to you.
Pam, I'm not going over this again.
Jim?
I don't know how else to...
We need you.
I don't know how
else to tell you, okay?
I'm doing everything
I can, every week
to bring home something for our family.
lam... lam...
lam trying to make everything
perfect here, okay,
so that you can have
everything that you want.
I'm doing this just for me?
Is that what I'm doing?
I'm doing it just for me?
If that's what you think, then
this is a really sad night.
You know what?
I got to go.
Okay?
Yup
We'll talk tomorrow?
Yup. I'll talk
to you tomorrow.
All right, great.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Bye.
Hey, are you okay?
What am I doing wrong,
Bflan?
Nothing. You're doing
the best you can.
Brian.
Give her a minute.
It's just a tough
situation, all right?
It's getting tougher.
I just didn't know that
it was going to be this hard.
Yeah.
Let's turn the cameras off.
Seriously, guys? Enough. Enough.
Thank you.
Fire in the hole!
Go! Go! Go!
I nailed that guy!
And replay.
Fire in the hole!
Go! Go! Go!
I nailed that guy!
I'm going to miss
the paper business.