- Linda.
You can have literally
anything you could possibly...
- What the...
- You sent a demon in disguise
as one of the subjects?
This outrageous act must be punished.
Chidi will be the fourth
subject in this experiment.
I still don't get why the Bad Place
would try something so obvious.
They're desperate. They
know they're gonna lose.
Plus, we can get rid of
the Linda picture...
and put a Chidi picture
on the other side
since we know a ton about him.
This is all good news,
right, Team Leader?
Yeah, it's super cool that
I'm actively surveilling
and manipulating an ex-boyfriend.
I mean, more so than I usually did.
Okay, let's focus on Brent.
Born on third base,
thinks he invented the game of baseball.
Guys like this believe that the world
revolves around them
because... it kind of does.
If we could get him to
listen to anyone else,
he'd hear how much better
they are than he was,
which might make him realize
that he doesn't belong here.
And also, bonus...
maybe he cries like a
stupid little baby.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
www.addic7ed.com ...
- Anyway, long story short,
that's why there are still ducks.
- I saved all the ducks.
- Aw!
Incredible. Wow.
Thank you, Wanda. What a life.
Now we turn to our next
guest, Chidi Anagonye.
Now Chidi, you led an
impressive life as an academic.
Well, not "save an entire
species" impressive,
but, yes, I was a professor
of ethical and moral philosophy.
I'm sorry... literally every duck?
- You saved every duck?
- In essence, yes.
And I didn't mention this before.
I really don't like to
brag but also... horses.
- Oh!
- What?
Man... I mean,
compared to you, I feel
a little inadequate.
Hey, Mikey, can I ask you something?
I feel bad for making Janet's life
more chaotic and unpredictable,
so here's my idea to make it up to her.
Me and 100 Janet Babies
do a giant flash mob...
just total unpredictable
chaos all around her.
Great idea, right?
Jason, Jason, Jason, Jason, Jason.
- Mm-hmm.
- Sorry,
I put a little cheat
code in the Neighborhood
where if I say your name five times
my headache goes away.
Do you know why I forced
you to act like a monk
in the original Neighborhood?
Does it have to do with
the TV show "Monk"?
No.
It's because you have no control
over your own impulses.
You think every problem can be solved
with a Molotov cocktail or
slashing somebody's tires
or plunging Derek.
So being a monk was torture for you.
The only way for you to repair
your relationship with Janet
is to give her some space.
Show her that you can
control your impulses.
So you're saying wanting to do something
isn't a good reason
to immediately do it?
Yeah.
Man, I wish someone had
taught me this on Earth.
People tried, mostly judges.
Hey, show time.
And now, Brent Norwalk,
why don't you tell us a
little bit about yourself?
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Sure. I'm pretty interesting.
I grew up in Chicago.
A suburb, obviously.
I went to Princeton University.
No handouts, by the way.
I earned my spot there...
just like my father and
his father before him.
I then inherited the family business,
and in just 18 years,
I grew Norwalk Materials
from a $90 million company...
to a $94 million company.
One second. Hey, Janet.
- Hi, there.
- Perrier.
Why don't you tell us about a time
when things didn't come so easy to you.
Look, I've had my share
of disappointments.
I smartly bought Netflix
stock at $38 a share,
but I couldn't cash it in before I died,
so all that money's
going to my dumb kid.
But you have to press on, right?
In the words of Martin Luther King, Jr.,
who I personally believe
was a great man,
he said that when life
knocks you on your butt,
you jump back up and start
throwing haymakers.
I'm not sure he said that.
No, no, he did. You're wrong.
For me, Eleanor,
it's all about taking
personal responsibility.
I don't know if people do that.
And if you ask me,
that's what's wrong with this country.
What country?
This was fun, Eleanor,
but I have a tee time.
Daddy no golfy, daddy get cranky.
So, Chad, duck lady, nice to meet you.
Thank you. Thank you all
very much. You were great.
A car?
- He got a car?
- Okay,
well, back to the drawing board.
If we want him to understand
he doesn't belong here,
we don't need a drawing board.
We need to bust him open like a pi? ata.
We tried that in the Bad Place.
The goo that comes out doesn't
taste as good as candy.
No, dude, metaphorically.
Ahh.
Although, there is another
Bad Place strategy
that might work very well here.
I don't know if that's the right move.
It's our only move.
And we're doing it.
Tomorrow.
What the...
Hey, Janet?
Janet!
Is that Perrier?
- Michael, Eleanor.
- Brent, I'm so sorry.
We don't know why all
of this is happening.
Well, I do.
This chaos is clearly all about me.
This is the universe telling
me that I don't belong here.
Brent, what do you mean?
I don't belong in the Good Place.
I mean, obviously there's
a place better than this.
I belong there.
In the best place.
Walk me through this, Brent.
I'm not sure we follow.
Well, I've been feeling
this way for a while now.
I mean, this can't be all
the Afterlife has to offer.
Not to the cream of the crop.
I mean, if this is heaven,
then where are my guys?
Where's Scotty and
Schultzy and Porcupine?
Where's White Guillermo?
And where is Mexican William?
And what about Squirtman?
Well, he makes a good point.
You know, what about Squirtman?
Also, frankly, my assistant Janet
is a little uptight.
I mean, she hasn't worn any of my gifts.
Have you been asking Janet
to make herself clothes
that you give back to her?
Yeah, you're doing the
math right there, bud.
Look, this chaos, which is
clearly all about me, is a sign.
If this is the Good Place,
I belong in the best place.
So figure it out. Get back to me, okay?
I'm gonna go punch a wall with my head.
I'll meet up with you later.
Michael, I'm afraid we need
to talk about Eleanor.
I know what you're gonna say.
She's just been really busy.
I'm sure she'll get around
to showering at some point.
No, it's not that,
although, it's not... not that.
It's possible we need a new Team Leader.
Oh, really?
We just can't help but
question her decision-making.
She balked at bringing
Chidi and Simone together.
She ignored my concerns about Linda.
Her plans for Brent backfired.
We've made precious little progress.
Perhaps leadership isn't her forte.
Yeah, I mean, Eleanor is dope,
but she keeps screwing everything up.
That's my thing,
and you wouldn't put me in charge.
Actually, that's a decent point.
But think about what you're saying here.
We have. We should at least discuss
pursuing a change in leadership.
Yeah, definitely, let's pursue it.
Oh, hey, Eleanor,
we were just talking about
maybe you shouldn't
be... Team... Leader?
- Saved it.
- Go ahead, guys.
Speak your mind.
It isn't personal, Eleanor.
When we started this experiment,
I calculated a 9% chance of success.
After your first three days on the job,
it's down to 7.1%.
So purely from a
mathematical standpoint,
you are kind of pooching it.
Very helpful feedback.
And if I could give you some feedback,
I'd say that you're all
ungrateful ash-faces
who can shove your fat grumps
all the way up your snork-box.
Which curses were those?
I didn't ask for this!
I'm only doing it because Michael,
who is supposed to be in charge,
had a nervous breakdown
the second it started.
But maybe you can do it better than me.
Tahani can be in charge
since she's so smart.
Or better yet, Jason.
Maybe all of humanity can be saved
with one good old-fashioned
Jacksonville carnival.
I mean, we could try.
All I need is a bouncy house,
some ninja stars, and a
bunch of ambulances.
Well, good luck, forkfaces.
I quit.
Shellstrop out.
You got it all out of your system?
You gonna come back?
- Get to work?
- No, man.
I meant what I said. I quit.
I'm sorry you overheard that.
And they're sorry they said it.
But you don't just get
to quit this, Eleanor.
This is not your 7th grade band or
three hours into a
two-week juice cleanse.
A little more at stake here.
Yeah, man, that's why I'm quitting.
The things that are happening
here are above my pay grade.
How do I get Brent to stop
being such a deckhead?
How do I fix Simone when she's convinced
all of this is happening
inside of her brain?
Ooh, maybe I should
drive her into the arms
of my ex-boyfriend... that sounds fun.
What do I do about John the gossip king,
or the demon spy who
punched me in the face?
And how do I do it all
with a pleasant smile
to keep everyone's spirits up?
I'm not meant for this.
I'm not the freakin'
savior of the universe.
I'm just...
a girl from Arizona.
That's it.
I'm just a normal girl from Arizona.
I ate junk food.
I watched reality shows.
I sometimes left H&M
wearing more underpants
than I had on when I came in.
I did a bad job of being
in charge of my own life,
and now I'm supposed to be in
charge of everyone else's life?
I...
I cannot do this.
When I started my experiment, I thought:
"Four broken birdbrains who will believe
"everything I tell them.
This will be a breeze."
You beat me in three months.
Okay, fine, I thought. A fluke.
You then beat me 800 more times.
Because human beings, it turns out,
are weird
and I will never truly understand
what it's like to be one.
This is a job for a human...
one who's tough but also empathetic
and has a big heart.
And a world-class bullshirt detector.
You think you can't do this?
Eleanor...
you're the only one who can do this.
Like it or not...
the only one who can save a humanity
is a girl from Arizona.
But everything I do blows up in my face.
I'm like a hot, blonde Wile E. Coyote
That's true.
About you making lots of mistakes,
not the thing where you
sexualized a cartoon.
Come on, you know how this works.
You fail and then you
try something else.
And you fail again and again,
and you fail a thousand times,
and you keep trying because...
maybe the 1,001st idea might work.
Now, I'm gonna and try to
find our 1,001st idea.
I hope you'll join me.
I hope you shower first
and then join me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
back with her trademark brand
of B-minus leadership,
Eleanor Shellstrop.
We are so, so, so sorry, Eleanor.
We never should've questioned you.
Don't worry about it, hot stuff.
I was questioning me, too.
But I'm back, baby.
And I have a new idea for Brent.
Guys like him never think
they're wrong, so...
we're gonna tell him he's right.
Brent.
This conversation must
remain confidential.
- Okay.
- Obviously, you're a very smart guy.
- Yes.
- But we need to know
that we can trust you
with sensitive information.
You can.
I routinely buried HR complaints,
so, no problem.
Truth is, Brent,
you figured us out.
There is a Best Place.
I knew it. I knew it.
The Best Place is reserved
for a select upper
echelon of good people,
sort of like a Diamond Elite VIP Club
of Afterlife residents.
I was Diamond Elite. I swear.
One time I did shots with
this pilot in the lounge,
and the guy let me fly his helicopter.
We know. That's how you died.
- Right.
- So you'll all be evaluated,
and then a very small group
of the most morally upstanding
residents get to go.
Oh, I see.
So it's like a "good deeds" contest?
That's easy.
I'm gonna crush this. Oh, and hey...
mum's the word, right?
Why tip off my competition?
Oops. Looks like you dropped your fork.
Let me get that for you.
Did you get that? The fork thing?
Or should I start writing these down?
No, you're good. We'll keep track.
Great. Love it.
Hi, Jason.
Janet, I'm so happy to see you.
I got you a box of chocolates.
But then I remembered you
can't eat, so I ate them.
And I thought it'd be a nice present
for me to describe them to you.
So... the first one was gross...
Jason, um, please just let me talk.
You know that I've been
overwhelmed with work
since the Neighborhood started.
- Yup.
- And I asked you
to give me some space.
Yup.
I'm so sorry to say this.
But I can't be in a relationship
with you right now.
Being with you is fun,
but it's not always easy,
and I'm afraid it would
endanger the experiment.
- It won't, though.
- Jason, it already has.
So why don't we just take a
break until it's all finished.
Also, I hate to pile on,
but I feel like you
have a right to know.
The Jacksonville Jaguars
cut Blake Bortles.
He's not on the team anymore.
I am genuinely sorry.
Hi, how are you?
Nice to see you. Enjoy your yogurt.
Problem is, now he's saddled
with a bad motivation.
I mean, his points won't
go up if the only reason
he's being nice is to
make his points go up.
Yeah, but that was also my situation
when I first asked Chidi for help.
I only did it so you wouldn't catch me.
We have to hope that over time
Brent starts doing good
things out of habit.
Just like you.
Hey, I just realized something.
That whole "you're the only one
who can save us" speech...
you didn't actually have
a nervous breakdown
on day one, did you?
You faked it so that I would step up
and take over.
- Guilty.
- You tricky devil!
Very clever. All right.
Time to go help Simone and Chidi.
Oof, why did I come up with this idea?
This is gonna hurt real bad.
I know, I know. But I
think it's gonna work.
Yeah, but it's gonna suck for me.
You sure there's no other girl
from Arizona who can do this?
What about Emma Stone? She's from there.
She's very capable.
Remember her in "Zombieland"
and "La La Land"?
What's with all her movies
ending with "land"?
- You're stalling.
- Yep, heading out.
Jason, I'm so sorry.
Janet was my whole Afterlife.
How am I gonna get over her?
I used to have a breakup routine
when a relationship ended...
Champagne and Alanis Morissette.
Not the actual singer.
I'd just listen to her albums
at my friend Adele's house.
I guess I could do my
normal breakup routine...
drink a ton of Mountain Dew,
steal an ATV,
and ride it through a Panda Express.
But then I'd have to ask Janet
for the Mountain Dew and the ATV,
and then I'd have to see Janet,
and then I'd start crying.
What do I do?
I honestly don't know.
But whatever you do,
you'll be doing it with your friends.
And I didn't even get to tell you
about the Blake Bortles part.
So, Chidi...
do you remember that woman Simone
from the party the other night?
Simone...
the... Third Eye Blind superfan
who walked around cutting
off people's ponytails?
That's the one.
I need your help acclimating
her to the Neighborhood.
I've tried, but since she
thinks this whole thing
is imaginary and I'm
an authority figure,
I'm extra suspicious.
Well, what makes you think
I'd have any more luck?
Chidi, you and Simone...
are soul mates.
Soul mates?
Like our souls are... are...
Mates. Yes.
Everyone has people that
they're cosmically bound to,
and the system brings them
together in the Afterlife,
and I can say with complete certainty
that you and Simone are two such people.
I haven't told her yet.
I wouldn't have told you ordinarily,
but since she's gone a
little cuckoo bananas...
that's the official Architect term...
I thought it was prudent
to let you know.
Whoo, boy, uh...
I'm getting a stomach ache...
but a good one.
A happy stomach ache.
This is new! There are
some great writings
on simulated realities that
might help her adjust...
Descartes, Moravec, Zhuang Zhou.
I wonder if I can summon a
book from my apartment.
Well, good luck.
This is incredible!
I spent my whole life in pursuit
of fundamental truths
about the universe,
but I never actually...
fell in love with someone.
I know.
Oh, right, of course.
You know everything about me.
I do, indeed.
Hi, Simone.
Uh, Chidi.
From the other night.
Oh, wow.
My brain must really
like keeping you around.
Have a fake seat and grab a
yogurt that doesn't exist.
Right, um...
so if I understand your state of mind,
it's basically solipsism.
You think that you're the only
real thing in the universe
and everything else stems
from your consciousness.
Yes, but to be fair,
I only think that because
it's true and I'm right.
No offense, but solipsism
as a philosophy
is pretty juvenile,
especially for a person with
multiple advanced degrees.
It's also impossible to refute
because everything you see
is confirmed by your belief.
However...
Dude.
What? I mean, if none of this is real,
then it really shouldn't
matter, right? In fact...
- Ha. Dude!
- What?
It's not real! None of this matters.
Leave that on your nose
- for the rest of time.
- Fine.
Point sort of taken.
You know, in a larger sense,
if you go around acting
like no one else matters
then you end up doing things like
knocking over cakes
and pushing people into pools
and just generally acting like a jerk.
Why not treat them better
just in case they're real?
I mean, what do you have
to lose by treating people
with kindness and respect?
Okay, keep talking,
probably fake, but maybe
real, philosopher man.
Well, good news... Simone and
Chidi are hitting it off.
I mean, I wasn't getting any
use out of him as a boyfriend,
so why not pass him off
to someone in need?
Is this what donating old
bras to Goodwill feels like?
Must've been really hard
lying to Chidi like that.
That's the thing. I don't
know that it was a lie.
They did fall in love on
Earth, and Michael was right.
Chidi made a huge sacrifice for us,
and I had to make sure it was worth it.
It's arguable that you made
an even bigger sacrifice.
You actually have to live
with this situation.
Chidi just gets to go around blissfully
unaware of what he gave up.
Yeah, but we know what he gave up.
Dat ash.
Come on, bud, I know you're down,
but you can't leaving me hanging.
You're right.
That is the code.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
www.addic7ed.com ...