Master,
your sexually ambivalent ex-wife is here.
- I'm not ambivalent, I'm exploring.
- Yes, mistress.
- Thanks for bringing Jake over.
- Well, I wanted to give you this anyway.
- What is it?
- It's the bill from my divorce lawyer.
- You haven't been paying them.
- Told you they'd notice.
I also need you
to look this over and sign it.
And what is this?
My lawyer recommended I take out
a bigger life-insurance policy on you
in case you should die
and can't pay the alimony and legal fees.
Why don't you have him frozen?
Then you can use him
to keep your drinks cold, too.
And who's supposed to pay for this policy?
You are. And please,
try to be on time with the premiums.
Boy, my shallow, empty lifestyle
is looking pretty good right about now.
Okay, as long as we're on the subject
of lawyers and death,
my lawyer recommended
that I redraft my will. And you know what?
If I die after you die,
guess who gets custody of Jake?
- Charlie.
- Charlie?
- Me?
- What about my sister?
- I never liked your sister.
- Is this the sister I slept with?
Shut up, Charlie.
Alan, you can't be serious.
He's immature, he drinks too much,
he sleeps around,
he is completely irresponsible.
Yeah, you should've thought of that
before you threw me out.
Yeah.
All right. You're obviously angry
and trying to get even with me,
but I am not gonna take the bait.
I will see you on Sunday.
Bye-bye.
- Hey, man. Thanks.
- For what?
For trusting me to take care of Jake
when you croak.
I'm sorry.
You didn't think I was serious, did you?
I just said that to piss her off.
Right. Good one. Hey!
That's not fair!
Why don't I get to keep the kid
when you're dead?
If I'm dead. And Judith would have to die
before me for it to even be an issue.
It's a contingency plan
for a hypothetical worst-case scenario.
I know it's a long shot,
but I had the Marlins in the World Series.
Don't tell me they don't come in.
It never occurred to me that you'd
want to be a full-time parent.
This isn't about what I want.
This is about what you want,
- and you don't want me to have Jake.
- What?
Nothing.
Why'd you say my name?
Get over yourself, no one said your name.
So what's wrong with me?
Charlie, you're a great uncle.
You're there for all the fun stuff.
I don't think you're up to the hard work
of being a full-time parent to Jake.
- What?
- Nothing.
Nothing.
So if not me,
then who are you giving him to?
I'm not giving him to anybody.
He's not a 5-pound ham.
You know what I mean.
Who gets him in that scenario thing?
- Cousin Jerry and his wife Faye.
- Jerry and Faye? Why Jerry and Faye?
They've got a good marriage,
three kids, lots of dogs, a big backyard,
and they live in a great school district.
Yeah, but I'm your brother!
- Charlie, it's not...
- And I live right here.
You wouldn't have to ship him off
to Corn Hole, Kansas.
Coventry, Rhode Island.
Who am I thinking of that lives in Kansas?
I don't know, Dorothy and Toto?
All right, Alan, let me ask you something.
If I'm here, and Jake's in Rhode Island,
who's gonna teach him
all the things he needs to know?
Jerry and Faye
are both college professors.
I'm talking about the important stuff.
About life.
Face it. When the time comes,
are those two eggheads gonna step up
and get your kid laid?
- You're not helping your case, Charlie.
- Fine, you've made your decision.
Despite all I've been through
with your son,
my nephew,
obviously I have no say in the matter.
Where are you going?
Alan, quite frankly,
I'm a little hurt and a little disappointed,
so I'm gonna go make myself
a big glass of vodka
and sit and think about things.
Charlie, wait. Okay, how about this?
If Judith dies and then I die,
and then Jerry and Faye die,
Jake will come and live with you.
Yeah, like I'm gonna outlive
Jerry and Faye the way I drink.
- What do you say to Grandma?
- Can I at least open it first?
- Jake.
- No, he's right.
Wait and see if he likes it.
- Now you can thank me.
- Thank you.
I'm kidding.
No little boy wants a framed picture
of his grandmommy.
This is for your daddy.
- What do you say, Dad?
- Don't push me, Jake.
That's my new photo
for the Sunday real estate section.
I thought maybe you'd like
a color print of it for your office.
Gee, Mom, we've already got the one
of you swimming with dolphins.
So you didn't bring me anything?
Is that all grandmommy is good for,
to bring you gifts?
Of course I brought you something. There.
Crayons? I'm 10.
Well, it's not just crayons, sweetheart.
It's also a dinosaur coloring book.
- But I'm 10.
- You want to trade?
No, I'm good.
- So, where's your brother?
- Why? What'd he get?
Nothing. I just want to make sure
he knows why.
He's in his room.
He's been sulking all weekend.
- Sulking? About what?
- Well, it's the silliest thing.
I just happened to mention
that in the unlikely event
that Judith should die, and I should die,
that custody of Jake would go to...
- Custody of Jake would go to who?
- Actually, it would be "whom. "
- Alan, who gets Jake?
- Now, see, that's grammatically correct.
- Alan.
- Jerry and Faye.
Jerry and Faye who?
- Your sister's son and his wife.
- Them?
You would bypass your own mother
in favor of two potato farmers
on Long Island?
They're agriculture professors
in Rhode Island.
Really?
Who am I thinking of
who lives on Long Island?
I have no idea.
- Well, regardless, I am deeply insulted.
- Come on, Mom.
This is only if Judith and I both die,
and we're not dying.
- At least, not before you.
- Now you're wishing me dead.
- No, Mom. No, it's...
- Give me back my picture.
No. Better you should look at it
and feel shame.
- Hey, want to play one-on-one?
- Sure.
Check it out.
One, nothing.
You know that Rhode Island
isn't really an island?
That's just a flat-out lie.
Two, nothing.
Hey, I've got to run some errands,
so I'll be back in about an hour.
You guys gonna be okay?
Gee, Alan,
you sure I can handle the responsibility?
What if he wants to go to college
or something?
Charlie, please don't start.
I'll see you later.
- Hey!
- Three, nothing.
- That was a time-out.
- You didn't call it.
- Fine. Three, nothing.
- You want a do-over?
No, I don't want a do-over.
Just bring it on.
Not so easy when I'm paying attention,
is it?
Not so hard, either.
- My head!
- Oh, God.
- You okay?
- No.
- All right, don't panic.
- I'm not panicking.
Good. You're gonna be fine.
- We've just got to stop the bleeding.
- I'm bleeding?
- What?
- Nothing. Just a little trickle.
Here, take my shirt. Hold it up here.
I'm sorry.
Okay, let's get you up, nice and slow.
Attaboy. I'll grab my car keys
and we'll head to the hospital.
A hospital?
I don't want to go to a hospital!
Did I say "hospital"? I meant Disneyland.
How's it going there, pal?
You still bleeding?
- I don't know.
- No, don't look.
You just hang in there,
we'll get you fixed up,
and you'll be back home
before you know it.
Just as soon as we find
the freaking hospital.
- You don't know where the hospital is?
- Of course I know where it is.
I'm kind of hungry.
Can we stop for a chili cheeseburger?
You're hungry?
How could you even think about food?
What do you think about
when you're hungry?
Fair enough.
We'll get you a chili cheeseburger
at the hospital.
- Will they have fries at the hospital?
- They have everything.
Some people go just for the food.
Man, we'd better call your dad.
Hello?
- Why do you have your father's phone?
- I don't know.
- That's great.
- Bye.
Yes! An ambulance.
Fifty-fifty shot he's going to a hospital.
Hang on!
I can't believe we beat the ambulance.
Yeah, well, those things are just
ice-cream trucks with blood bags.
Hi, we need to see a doctor.
- All right. Just fill this out and have a seat.
- No, you don't understand.
He hit his head, he's bleeding.
- Did he lose consciousness?
- No.
I got a little woozy, though.
Follow my finger.
He's gonna be fine.
That's it? He's gonna be fine?
That's not a medical test,
that's how you hypnotize a chicken.
I'd like a chili cheeseburger and fries,
please.
You see, he's hallucinating.
Can you please just get him in to a doctor?
Well, you need to fill this out first.
Come on, this is gonna take forever.
Can't we do this later?
Over dinner?
Now you're hallucinating.
Come on, buddy.
All right. Let's see. Last name, Harper.
First name, Jake. Ob?
Jacob. I knew that. Middle name?
- You don't know?
- Of course I know.
I want to see if you know.
You fell on your head, dude.
David.
Jacob David. They went full Old Testament
on you, didn't they?
- Age, 10. Allergies?
- I don't know.
Is there anything you eat
that makes you sick?
I ate a worm once.
No allergies.
Have you had any of the following?
- Measles?
- I don't know.
- Mumps?
- Chicken pox?
- Is that the one with the spots?
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
All right. We're just gonna vote
the straight "no" ticket.
Family history?
Your grandmother's always been
a pain in the ass.
Gonzales?
- Right here!
- I'm Gonzales.
No, you're not.
Right. He's Gonzales.
- Okay, you're gonna feel a little sting.
- Nobody said I had to get a shot!
It's just to numb your skin
so you won't feel the stitches.
What are you gonna give me
to not feel the shot?
It's all right, pal. I'm right here with you.
Big deal.
I'm still gonna get a shot in my head.
Come on, just hold my hand,
look me in the eyes.
Go ahead, Doc.
- Hey, go easy on the kid!
- No, you're squishing my hand!
Sorry.
But you didn't feel the shot, did you?
- No.
- You're welcome.
Maybe you'd prefer to wait outside.
I'd prefer a morphine drip
and a sponge bath,
but the kid needs me.
- How many stitches am I gonna get?
- I don't know, three or four.
That's all? Scott Pressman got nine
when his sister hit him
with the Etch-A-Sketch.
Help us out here, Doc.
Okay, I'll go five,
but one is purely decorative.
Thank you.
- Is this gonna leave a scar?
- I'm afraid so.
- No.
- Yes!
Okay, let's get started.
Good, maybe that's your father.
Hello. Hey, Judith.
No, it's me, Charlie.
What am I doing with Alan's phone?
Why? Do you want custody of that, too?
Come on, that's funny.
I don't know. Maybe Alan and I
accidentally switched phones.
Why don't you try calling him on mine?
310-LICKME.
I didn't pick it, but that's what it spells.
Okay. Goodbye.
Are you doing it?
'Cause I can't feel anything.
- Yeah, that's the idea.
- Can you see my brain?
Sure, it's a big brain.
You must be very smart.
- Phone's ringing.
- No, it's not.
The doctor's just stimulating
the phone-ring part of your brain.
- Right, Doc?
- Sure, why not?
I ordered a chili cheeseburger out there.
Will they know to bring it in?
Come on, Mom. Those are
two completely different scenarios.
Hey.
Cool hats.
So, you're saying that because
I didn't name you as Jake's guardian,
you're switching your medical
power of attorney from me to Charlie?
- What's going on?
- Hang on.
If Mom's ever in a coma, you're the one
who has to decide to pull the plug.
Pull.
All right, Mom, Charlie's onboard.
Yeah, got to go.
Hey, where have you guys been?
You know,
we went and got a couple of hamburgers,
bought some hats.
Ate the hamburgers, wearing the hats.
Okay.
- You're right, he bought it.
- Bought what?
Dude, you can forget about a life of crime.
Oh, my God. What happened?
We were playing basketball,
and it got a little rough.
- He fouled me.
- You charged.
- Did not.
- Did, too!
Hold on.
- So you took him to the emergency room?
- Yes.
Where the cheeseburgers sucked,
by the way.
But he's okay?
There's no concussion or anything?
- No.
- We saw my brain.
No, we didn't. We didn't see any brains.
Hey, why didn't you call me?
There it is.
Why do you have my cell phone?
I don't know.
All right. You sure you're okay?
- Can I go watch TV?
- Sure.
I am really sorry, Alan.
- Don't worry about it. He's fine.
- Yeah, but I'm not.
You were right.
I obviously can't be trusted
to take care of Jake.
Believe me,
the second you're in the ground,
I'm sticking that kid on a plane
to Rhode Island.
Charlie, let me tell you something.
You can't keep Jake
from ever getting hurt.
I mean, he's a boy. That's...
Getting hurt is like his job.
Last summer, he actually fractured his ass
doing a cannonball into the bathtub.
All I care about
is that he has somebody who loves him
and who'll step up when it really counts.
And that's what you did today.
Yeah, I guess I did, didn't I?
Yeah. And if, God forbid,
something should ever happen
to Judith and me,
I would be very comfortable knowing
that you were looking after my son.
Dead, but comfortable.
Does this mean
you're putting me in the will?
- Yeah.
- Wow. Thanks, man.
That means a lot.
- Just do me a favor, all right?
- What's that?
Don't die.
- That's a very cute hat.
- Thank you.
It makes my hair sweat.
Oh, my God!
What happened to your head?
I got five stitches.
There was blood everywhere.
- Why didn't anyone tell me?
- I just did.
- Can we stop for pizza?
- I can't believe this.
I'm going to have a little talk
with your father.
Hello?
English