Well, I'm moving to Colorado
to start my new life
with Holly.
Just up here getting
used to the altitude.
Michael?
Yes?
I've got
a treat for you.
Oh!
Thank you.
Like a butler.
Colorado specialty,
Rocky Mountain oysters.
Wow, those do not
taste like oysters.
That's because
they're not oysters.
They're bull testicles!
I cut them off
fresh this morning!
Sick freak.
What is wrong with you?
I'm the sick freak?
Yeah.
After what you did,
you expect to be buttled?
After you didn't
recommend me?
Dwight, I don't own
Dunder Mifflin, okay?
The job was not
mine to give.
Look, I need your
advice on something.
I am told that there
are bears in the Rockies.
Where did you hear that?
Obvious, XM radio?
Well, I was just thinking
that maybe I should keep
a salami in my pocket...
Great idea.
in order to feed
the bears.
Especially if you think
that life would be
better without legs!
How do you mean?
Black bears can smell a salami
at five miles, Michael.
What are you thinking?
And they run
faster than a horse.
So if you were thinking about
outrunning them on a horse,
I would try a cheetah.
You in tight pants, Michael,
are a salami to a black bear.
Do you understand?
Mmm-hmm.
You're like
a giant walking salami.
Okay,
so no salami in the pants.
How about a pepperoni?
Any kind of meat
you can possibly name.
Okay.
You're not gonna take
all your toys, are you?
Hmm?
I mean, you don't...
You don't have
a job lined up, so...
It's not like you have
a desk to put them on.
Well, I have interviews.
That's nice.
What about that truck?
Can I have
this little truck?
Was thinking I might
glue a stapler on top
or put a hole here
and stick pens in it.
You okay?
Yes.
Yes, you know what,
take my favorite
truck, sure.
You know what...
It's your last
couple of days.
I'm gonna get
out of your hair.
Oh, you don't...
I will be in
the break room.
Okay, that sounds good.
Thank you.
Dead man walking.
Sad?
No.
No, no.
I don't leave till tomorrow,
so tomorrow I will be a wreck.
Stay away from Erin.
Hey.
I'm your boss.
Why don't you
stay away from me?
No, I'm gonna stand
where I want, okay?
You don't want to
get on my bad side.
I've seen some
horrible things.
I own over
200 horror movies.
Okay, that's so weird!
Just go away!
No, you go away.
Hi, Tuna.
You guys are filming people
when they go to
the bathroom now?
How about cupcakes?
Please.
What's wrong
with cupcakes?
Everything.
There they are.
The Party Planning Committee
together again.
Well, we all wanted
to plan your goodbye party.
We thought this
would be easier.
We thought.
It's an experiment.
The three of us
have all been
chairmen before.
So this is
the dream team.
Hey!
What are you saying?
The dream team
and Meredith.
We decided on the ice cream.
Mint chocolate chip.
Your favorite.
Mmm.
Yeah, that was a surprise.
MICHAEL: You know what?
I'm thinking maybe
we should get ice cream
that everybody will like.
How about vanilla?
Let's get vanilla.
Okay.
Tomorrow, I want everybody
to have a good time.
No drama.
And as for today,
just a typical day.
All right?
PAM: Should we
get toppings?
What do you like, Pam?
What?
What kind of
topping would you like?
Hot fudge?
Sounds good.
Fudge it up.
I bought this for myself.
And yesterday,
they gave me this.
I still need something
to drink out of, though.
Attention, everyone.
Before I leave tomorrow,
I would like to
reveal a secret
that I have kept
for over 20 years.
Secret about Phyllis.
Please, Michael.
When Phyllis was
in high school,
she was so cute.
And she still is.
I thought he knew
about the baby I gave away.
Look, Michael,
it's a going-away present
so your hands won't get cold.
Ah.
It's almost done,
but you can't get them wet,
and they can't be
dry-cleaned either.
You have to hand
wash without water,
wring dry gently,
and use a hair dryer on cool.
Sounds great.
I just think it's great.
Oh, I have gifts as well.
And I will start by giving
the first gift to Phyllis.
Phyllis,
you are shy and sweet,
and you don't
often speak your mind,
but you should,
because you have
great ideas.
So, Phyllis,
I am giving you this
so you can always remember
to speak your mind.
Gee, thanks, Michael.
You're welcome.
It's cute.
Stanley, you love your Sudoku
and your puzzles.
I bestow upon you...
My felt.
May you never lose
the fun-loving
quality in life.
Where's the rest of it?
It's got no balls.
Well, okay.
And Andy.
Andy, who needs confidence
that he is a great salesman,
I give you
my clients.
Our ten most
important accounts.
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
You know I'm the worst
salesman here, right?
But you're the best
salesman on the inside.
What does that even mean?
You sold us all on Andy.
A product that nobody wanted.
I'm gonna lose them.
You're not going to
lose them.
I promise you
that I will.
Just do your best.
I have faith in you.
Gimme those clients.
No.
Do you believe that?
I've given up
expecting Michael
to do the right thing
or the decent thing or even
the comprehensible thing.
DEANGELO: I used to
be obese.
Once you've conquered obesity,
everything else is easy.
Life literally
moves in slow motion.
I'm not saying
I'm Superman,
but let me just
put it this way,
if I were shot
in the head,
I'm pretty sure
everything would be fine.
I almost welcome it.
Kevin, I have
something for you.
Oh!
You know who that is?
Oh.
Don't be a caricature, Kevin.
Never be a caricature.
How did that feel
when I tore that up?
Better?
Good.
Stand up.
You will be thin.
You won't drool over pizza
like an animal anymore.
But, I...
You will find love.
Michael, I'm pretty much
okay with who I am now.
Don't be.
You should never
settle for who you are.
Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
Oscar, you are a...
Michael,
I just lost Porter Hardware!
I just... I lost them.
Okay, you know what?
Just do your best, buddy.
Okay, Oscar,
you are very smart,
and you have
a gigantic education,
and I think of
you as my Scarecrow,
because you gave me a brain.
So that's why
I made you this.
Thank you, Michael.
It's beautiful.
It looks like...
It looks like it was made
by a two-year-old monkey
on a farm.
And he just...
He just accepted it,
that I...
That I put all
this work into it.
Oh, man.
He has the lowest
opinion of me of anybody.
Was it just me,
or did you think
we were gonna have sex
at some point?
It was just you.
How would you
have wanted to do it?
I don't...
Okay, you know what?
Inappropriate,
because I am engaged happily,
and you, you have
landed yourself a senator.
State senator.
Mmm-hmm. Bravo.
Brava.
Do you want to
see some pictures?
I just got these.
Sure.
These are... Okay,
this is us at the theater.
And, antiquing.
Oh, rollerblading.
Rollerblading.
Who's that?
Who's that guy?
Oh, that's Thomas,
Robert's aide.
Hmm.
I guess this
could be the one, huh?
Yeah.
Hey.
I'm gonna be dropping in
on one of our biggest
clients this afternoon,
and I could use
some backup.
Let's rip it up, homes.
All right.
Boom.
Walk away, bitch.
Oh, Michael.
Hmm?
Where do you want
your last paycheck sent?
Last paycheck?
Do you have
an address yet
in Colorado?
No.
What town do
Holly's parents live in?
I'm not sure.
Mountainton, I think.
Sounds beautiful.
PAM: You should do
more stuff like that.
KEVIN: I'm going to.
Hey.
It's almost your last day.
Come on. Sit with us.
No, I'm almost done.
You sure?
Yeah.
PAM: So I'm going to
Carbondale this afternoon
to get a new bulk shredder.
KEVIN: Finally.
That old shredder sucked.
It's a good shredder.
It just keeps breaking.
Yeah, and it won't
shred magazines.
It's not supposed to
shred magazines, Kevin.
I know.
Did you break
the shredder, Kevin?
No. It's just that
old shredder sucks.
Just get one
that'll shred magazines.
PAM: I don't think
any of them are supposed
to shred magazines.
I can't...
I can't do this.
All the channels are
gonna be different there.
I'm not gonna be
able to find my shows.
I'm not going to
start improv at level one.
I don't think my credits
are gonna transfer.
Oh! And you know what?
I just figured out
where I was supposed to
go to vote.
I gotta call her.
And I'm going to tell
her that I cannot come.
üPHONE RINGING
ON SPEAKERPHONEä
HOLLY: Hello there.
Hi.
What is the name
of our town?
Boulder.
Is something wrong?
Are you okay?
No. No, I just needed
to hear your voice.
Oh, you mean this?
Yeah.
Yes, my hero.
I'll pay the rent.
Okay, my mom's looking
at me like she has
no sense of humor.
It's a joke.
Oh, I miss you.
Well, I'll see you
tonight.
I'll pick you up
outside baggage claim.
Okay, I'll see you tonight.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Yeah,
so I know I told everybody
that tomorrow is my last day,
but I'm gonna be
leaving tonight.
I head to the airport
at 4:00.
And, I have said goodbye
to half of them.
Well, you know, Michael,
I have a brother in Boulder.
Rory Flenderson.
You should look him up.
Okay.
Okay?
Kelly?
What?
If I just went away
right now,
would that be the best gift
that I could give you?
Yes, please.
Please go away
and stop using that weird,
slow voice.
She was once my girl,
and she is your girl now.
Wow.
Yeah.
This is
totally unnecessary.
You're not prone
to seizures?
No.
So Michael said we can do
whatever we want cake-wise.
What do we want?
Erotic.
See? This is
what happens.
You can't let
a street dog
into the house.
Hmm. Let's hear her out.
I would like to hear
more about these cakes.
I know these Ethiopians
that run a cake shop.
Good God.
They make these
cakes that are wild.
I mean...
They show everything.
I don't think we want a...
No, I know
what you're thinking,
but it's not just black.
They do it all.
And the women
on these cakes,
they're not just
guys' fantasies.
They have real,
full women.
It is refreshing.
Okay, don't turn this
into some feminist issue.
As a person who buys
a lot of erotic cakes,
it just feels good to
be represented on one.
You know what?
I think we should
get some other input.
do cupcakes.
I am one of the few people
who looks hot
eating a cupcake.
Yeah, cupcakes,
that's what I said.
No. I am not
cleaning up a bunch of
uneaten cupcake bottoms.
You know, we don't really
care about your opinion.
You're just a tie-breaker.
Um, Pam?
Oh, hey, Michael.
I'm just gonna
go to Carbondale
to price some shredders.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
ERIN: Gabe!
I need to talk to you.
You can't be in here.
This is a ladies' bathroom.
No, Erin,
I respect your privacy,
but I will
follow you in here
every time you go if
that's what it takes.
Hey, Creed.
Not cool, man.
I really think
you should leave.
Someday, you are going
to tell our grandchildren
about how their grandfather
won you back in
a women's room.
Gabe, can we talk
about this later?
I have to go. I have to go.
Just read
the letter under your
windshield wiper, okay?
It explains everything.
Okay.
Okay?
Do you want...
Gabe!
Well.
Here's the thing, Rory.
I think you guys would
hit it off in an odd way.
I could bring him
a welcome basket.
I'll surprise him.
Okay, well,
you should give him
a little time to
settle in, but...
Does he like jams?
My shelves are
overflowing with preserves.
Well, no, he hates jams.
Darryl.
Hey.
I would like to
give you the only copy
of Somehow I Manage,
unfinished.
If there's anybody here
who can finish it,
it's you.
That's sweet, Mike.
Let's see here.
Here's a chapter
called "Gum."
Mmm.
With one sentence.
"Everybody likes the guy
who offers them
a stick of gum."
Mmm-hmm. It's true.
Darryl, I have
one last wish.
I would like
to use the baler.
No. Can't let you
do that, Mike.
No problem.
Sorry.
Worth a try.
All right.
Darryl said I could use
the baler because I'm leaving.
No.
All right, guys, well,
see ya later, warehouse.
Catch you on
the flippety-flip.
All right then,
see you, guys.
Catch you later,
warehouse.
See you on
the flippety-flip.
Catch you on
Catch you guys
on the flippety-flip.
Come on.
Okay.
So what's our approach?
You a veteran?
Do I have a month to live?
You gonna get
married tomorrow? What?
Hmm?
I thought we'd
just talk about
our customer service
and exceptional
paper quality.
That's stupid.
Well, what do I know?
I know.
What do you know?
We gotta get psyched up.
Okay, guy?
Let's get psyched.
Is there an animal
shelter on the way?
Yeah.
Awesome!
Ani-ani-shelto.
Here we come.
Andy, do you know
how to high-five?
Yeah.
'Cause if you do,
now's the time.
All right.
Not while I'm driving.
Catch you guys...
Catch you guys on
the flippety-flip.
Flippety-flip.
Really?
Okay, see you guys.
You know how I met Jo Bennett
and got started on
my ladder of success?
No, I don't.
Walking along,
out of work, again,
thinking to myself,
"I've only got
enough cash to buy
a sandwich or get drunk."
And I see this guy
trying to steal
this lady's dog.
So I grab the dog,
he runs off.
She's so grateful,
she hires me.
Aw, wow.
Gimme that dog!
It's not your dog!
Yeah.
Again.
Oh, okay.
Gimme that damn dog,
you... thief!
It's her dog!
Okay.
Don't ever do it again!
You hear me?
You feel that energy?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah?
Whoo! Yeah.
Okay, again.
I know that Gabe is young
and hot and everything,
and he's begging me
to reconsider,
but I just think I'm in love
with someone else.
Kevin?
Andy.
Ah.
I wish I knew who
my birth mother was
so she could just
tell me who to choose.
Maybe neither.
I'm not attracted
to Kevin.
Erin, listen to me.
You shouldn't rush
into this at all.
And you know why?
Because you are beautiful,
and you are fun,
and you are smart.
And when
the right guy comes along,
you'll know it.
You will.
Hey.
And you know what?
You don't need a mom,
because you have my number
and you can call me anytime.
Extension 147.
I know.
Okay. Okay.
Did you want
the 2726 or the 2730?
Phyllis? Phyllis,
are my mittens done?
No. No.
I'm on a sale...
Okay, listen,
it's 2:00 p.m.
From now until 4:00,
your priority is knitting.
Knit like the wind.
Okay, Michael.
Dwight, I will
be leaving tomorrow.
Yes?
So I wanted
to give you that.
It's a letter of
recommendation.
This is gonna be good.
"To whom it may concern."
Good, real personal.
Thanks, Michael.
"The dictionary
defines 'superlative'
"as 'of the highest kind,
quality, or order,
"'surpassing all else
or others. Supreme.'"
That's great.
If I wanted
the dictionary definition,
I'd buy a dictionary.
"I define it as
Dwight Schrute.
"As a sales executive,
as a leader, as a man,
and as a friend,
"he is of
the highest kind, quality,
and order. Supreme."
Lots more like that.
Really repetitive.
What's this?
"2:45 behind the building,
paintball."
Oh!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Ow!
I would like to
start by just saying
that I have not worked with
Mr. Andy Bernard
here for very long.
But I can say that
he is no Michael Scott.
I can't sit here
and tell you that he's
gonna be a success.
I can't sit here
and tell you that he's even
the best man for the job.
But I can say this.
He's got potential.
Sure.
You know, I always say,
"Go big or go home."
You go with this guy,
you could be making
the biggest mistake
of your life.
Or the biggest good
decision of your life.
It's either gonna be
the best thing you ever did,
or the worst thing
you ever did.
If you want some boring,
white bread clock-watcher,
who's gonna
get you your paper
when you ordered it
for the agreed-upon price,
Andy's not your guy.
You ever play
Russian roulette?
Time to spin the chamber,
Boris...
By signing up
for another year.
What happened to you?
You should see
the other guy.
Jim, where is Pam?
She's still pricing
the whatevers...
The shredders.
But it is already 3:00.
Right.
Whether you're
scared of dying,
or dying alone,
or dying drunk in a ditch,
don't be.
It's going to be okay.
MICHAEL: Yeah,
I was tripling up.
There's not enough
time in the day
to have a special
moment with everybody.
And you,
why are you still here?
I'm either
gonna quit today
or stay to make sure
that Andy's career
is destroyed.
No, you are not
going to quit today.
For goodness sake,
this is not going to be
your last day at the office.
Everybody
gets dumped, Gabe.
Can I give you
a piece of advice?
A little cover-up
on your Adam's apple
will make it appear smaller,
which will make you
look less like
a transvestite.
That is cold, sir.
Absolutely cold.
You know what?
It was a complete
waste of my time.
Uh, Deangelo, I'm...
I forgot my bag,
so I'm gonna...
I'll meet you in the car.
Okay, whatever.
Sir.
I'd just like to
apologize for that.
I could tell you that he has
a steel plate in his head,
or that he's crazy,
but the truth is,
I think he's just
a terrible salesman.
And I want you to know
that if you re-up with us,
anything you need,
day or night,
I will be the one
to take your call.
Keep talking.
Yes.
Okay. All right.
No. Well, thank you.
Thank you.
All right. Take care.
You'll never guess.
We did it.
Hey!
All right.
Good job, boss. Yeah.
We did it.
Okay, everybody, come on.
Conference room,
five seconds! Here we go!
Hurry up! Let's do this!
Yes. What is this about?
What is this meeting about?
All right.
STANLEY: Mmm-hmm.
Well...
Okay. Here we are in
the conference room.
Once again.
And I just wanted to
call you all here together
because I have
something important...
Well, there's
two things, actually.
Okay, first, I would like
a whereabouts on Pam,
and, secondly, Phyllis,
how are those mittens coming?
Because I would actually
like to bring them home
and pack them,
and I am leaving
for the day at 4:00.
They're almost done,
but my knuckles are
swelling a little,
and I can't...
Well, power through
the arthritis, Phyllis.
You can do it.
Is that it?
Um, hmm?
STANLEY: Is that it?
Um... Hmm.
No.
There's a special guest
that I would like to invite
to say one last goodbye,
so here he comes.
He's coming right in.
Hi, everybody!
It's Ping!
And I'm here to say goodbye
to all you wonderful people.
Thank you, everybody!
You've been so wonderful.
We were such a good...
Mmm-mmm.
I "rove" you all.
I "rove" you very much.
Hey, can I talk to
you for a second?
Sure.
See you later!
So I've been
meaning to tell you.
I want to take
you out for lunch.
For your last day.
Oh.
What do you think?
Tomorrow? Lunch?
You and me?
Okay.
You're not leaving tomorrow.
You're leaving today, right?
Maybe.
Wow, so that's it, huh?
Just 4:00 and you
are gone for good.
Why am I so sad?
Am I doing
the wrong thing?
Absolutely not.
It's just that sometimes
goodbyes are a bitch.
T-shirt idea.
"Goodbyes stink."
Okay. All right. So...
James Halpert...
You started
with this company
as a fine young man.
You know what I
think we should do?
I think we should just save
the goodbyes for tomorrow.
At lunch.
Oh.
Okay.
And then tomorrow
I can tell you
what a great boss
you turned out to be.
Best boss I ever had.
MICHAEL: Oh, shoot.
That's my cab.
All right.
Listen, Michael,
I really...
I did text Pam, but...
I know. It's okay.
Just give her a hug,
all right?
I will see you
tomorrow at lunch.
I am looking forward
to lunch.
And hearing about
what a great boss I am.
You got it.
Okay.
Phyllis.
Oh, they're still not done.
Oh, no, no, no.
Let me see.
Oh, Phyllis.
Nice try.
I love them.
See ya tomorrow, boss.
Later, guys.
MICHAEL: Well,
got almost everybody, so...
Holly's my family now.
She's my family.
And the babies
that I make with her
will be my children.
The people that you
work with are just,
when you get down to it,
your very best friends.
They say on your deathbed
you never wish
you spent more time
at the office,
but I will.
Got to be a lot better
than a deathbed.
I actually don't
understand deathbeds.
I mean, who would buy that?
Well, I guess this is it.
Hey, will you guys
let me know
if this ever airs?
Thank you.
All right. Oh.
This is gonna feel so good
getting this thing
off my chest.
That's what she said.
PAM: No, he wasn't sad.
He was full of hope.
About Colorado.
And he was hoping
to get an upgrade
as an awards member.
And he said he was
just real excited
to get home and see Holly.
Well, if he's not
gonna make it,
at least we should go
ahead and eat the cake.
Yeah.
I, for one,
love the corners.
Why did I just do that?
This is not even that good.
I don't even want it.
I had cake for lunch.
No, you know what?
I've been good.
I deserve this.
Um...
What am I doing?
Come on, Deangelo.
Hey...
No!
Uh-oh.
DEANGELO: No!