Got it.
All right.
Okay, let's go in.
I'm freezing.
People, wait, wait, wait.
Come back, come back.
One fun one.
We're gonna do a fun one.
Okay.
One Charlie's Angels.
One. Let's go.
Okay,
this is just a Christmas card
from your paper supplier.
No one's putting
this on their fridge.
I got it, you guys,
how about this.
Michael, what if all the boys
are on one side,
all the girls
are on the other.
The boys are, like,
"Why, I ought to..."
And the girls are, like,
"Let's go shopping."
Let's just jump in the air.
That's it!
That's a picture!
Yes! Jump in the air.
We're gonna jump in the air.
Here we go.
Okay, one, two, three.
Not everyone jumped.
Okay, everybody jump
in the air this time, please.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Still some people not jumping.
You gotta be kidding me.
Who isn't jumping?
I'll tell you who.
Darryl, Phyllis,
Stanley, Angela, and Oscar.
I am jumping.
You are?
Let me see you jump.
Yes, I'm jumping.
Oh, my God. This is
a store-bought camera.
This isn't one of those
special military-grade cameras
that would be
able to capture that.
I'm freezing.
Also, Erin is
jumping way too early.
She's on the ground
by "three."
I didn't want to miss it.
Well, if we all jump
really high,
we'll be in the air longer.
Do that.
Here's a question
nobody's asking,
is this worth it?
Don't answer that.
People,
listen up and listen good.
We need to just
get one picture
where we're all in the air
at the same time. Yes?
Why?
I believe in us.
We can do this.
Okay, on three,
everyone in the air.
Three, two, one, zero.
Just say "jump."
Say the word "jump."
We didn't get it.
I'm the office
administrator now,
which means I'm
basically being paid
to be head of the
party planning committee.
The first thing I did
as head, I shut it down.
At its worst it was
a toxic political club
used to make others feel
miserable and left out.
At its best
it planned parties.
It hardly looks fake.
It's so lush.
Why does it smell real?
JIM: Ah!
Good one.
Ho, ho, ho!
Oh, ho, ho, ho!
Merry Christmas,
little children!
Merry Christmas!
How's everybody doing today?
PAM: Good.
How's the party coming along?
Great.
Are we over budget?
Nope.
No? Good.
Did anyone
get drunk already?
Not yet.
Good for you.
Angela, lay it on me,
what's the problem?
Nothing. Should be fun.
So, Stanley,
how big is the bug
up your butt today?
Pam got those
sugar-free cookies I like.
I'm doing fine.
All right, well,
I will be in my office
making toys for
the good children.
Andy?
Yeah?
What you got?
It's all good, Santa.
Well, that's a relief.
Santa's gonna take
some much-needed free time.
All right. Good!
MICHAEL: My kids
are growing up.
As a boss, I look at that
and I say, "Great."
It is exactly what a boss
would hope would happen
because that's what I want.
That's what
every boss wants,
is a wonderful Christmas
with no drama.
It's present time, you guys.
Happy holidays from
your friends at Sabre.
We just want to say
how grateful we are.
Sabre is actively looking
for ways to involve me
as minority executive trainee.
So I suggested choosing
the annual Christmas gift
to the employees.
And they said,
"Oh, yes. Perfect.
"Thank you, Kelly. Finally,
something for you to do."
It's a Hello Kitty
laptop sleeve.
Hello Kitty's for girls.
Nashua got mp3 players.
Yeah, I don't even
have a laptop.
I wonder if these
presents would be under
as much scrutiny
if I were white.
WOMAN: Wow.
Come on.
I said "I wonder."
I didn't say "I think."
Kelly, I thought we agreed
on fleece blankets.
Blankets?
What am I, five?
Erin and I make
great use of ours.
Yes, Erin and I
are still dating.
Why do you ask me so often
if we're still dating?
I'll take one of
those pink pouches.
I feel good today.
My little girl Jada?
It's my turn to have her
for Christmas this year.
Two years ago I had her,
and we had the best time.
I've TiVoed her
favorite shows,
some things
I've never heard of.
iCarly...
You know who's funny
on that show?
The friend with
the video camera.
He's got a nice
way of talking.
Hey, it's snowing.
DWIGHT: Oh, my God!
It's the first snowfall
of Christmas.
Is that just so magical
for you, little girl?
Can you not wait to
have a hot chocolate,
and cuddle up with Papa
and tell him about all
your Christmas dreams?
It's not even a real snow.
Look, it's a dusting.
It's pitiful.
Hey, Dwight.
MEREDITH: Yes!
Damn it, Jim,
you cannot throw
snowballs in here!
Well, it's not a snowball,
'cause it's only a dusting.
Right?
Look at that.
There's a pebble in there.
You could have killed me!
Don't be such a baby.
Yeah,
who's a little girl now?
You apologize to me
right now.
You've got something
on your nose.
You apologize right now.
No.
Very well,
then I challenge you
to a snowball fight
on the first
real snow of winter.
You got it.
That sounds awesome.
Can we all do it?
No, Andy,
it's a snowball fight.
It's not fun.
Go get your own thing.
Beat it.
Jim, let go.
Angela, are you bringing
your new boyfriend
to the party?
I wouldn't subject
Robert to that.
He's a very busy senator.
State senator.
I would not expect you
to know what it's like
to date someone in
the public arena.
Who are you dating
in the public arena?
The senator.
Oh, right.
The state senator.
We went to a picnic thrown
by the comptroller's wife.
Oh.
That would be impressive
if anyone knew what
a comptroller was.
Well...
Do you have any idea
how many photographers
there are
at a ribbon-cutting ceremony?
I do. Two.
"Angela... Here.
Look here!"
Before we kick off the party,
I just want to remind everyone
that an office party
is just that...
Yeah!
A party.
It's not an excuse
to get really drunk
or confront someone
or have a cathartic experience
of any kind.
MICHAEL: Pam?
Pam?
Wow, there are questions
to that. Okay.
You know what,
no questions.
Last item on the agenda,
Toby would like to
make an announcement.
Hi, guys.
Hi.
I just wanted to
let you know
that I'll be taking
a leave of absence
starting next week.
Because you've
been on the lam?
Because the boring police
have been after you,
and they finally
caught up with you?
No, the opposite.
I was actually selected
to be a juror on a very
high-profile case.
Yes, the case of the
horrible red-headed sad sack.
And the verdict, it was Toby.
And the sentence, death.
Death to Toby!
DWIGHT: Death to Toby!
Okay, that's hurtful talk.
We've talked about that.
You know, I don't interrupt
your announcements.
You leave these huge pauses
in your sentences.
What do you expect me to do?
What's the case, Toby?
Well, I really can't
talk about it,
but it's a very
high-profile case.
Is it criminal?
Yes.
Have we heard of it?
I don't know.
Is it the middle school
teacher who tried
to turn her foreign exchange
student into a sex slave?
Come on.
Was it the post office guy
who rubbed his penis
all over the mail?
Guys,
it's a really big deal.
He's rubbing his neck.
He's rubbing his neck!
Scranton Strangler!
I can neither
confirm nor deny this.
Let's just say
I'll be up to my neck
in jury duty.
That was the worst joke ever.
Corporate will be
sending someone else
to take my place.
Okay, good-bye. Good-bye.
Holly Flax.
She comes from
the Nashua branch.
What? What?
Yeah.
She'll be starting next week.
If you have any
questions about
the transition,
just let me know.
Hold on,
Holly's coming back here?
Yeah.
Guys, who's Holly?
MICHAEL: That is a great
question, Erin.
How do you describe somebody
who is at the same time
an old friend,
and was a lover.
And was a complicated part
of my past,
and maybe, just maybe
a part of my future?
Wow.
She's one sassy black lady.
Holly's coming back,
everybody, and we have to
have a party.
I'm not sure
the temporary replacement
of an HR rep
really warrants a party.
You know what,
we'll postpone this party
until then.
This is too important.
Cancel this one.
Dwight, get rid of the tree.
Okay.
Cancel. We're canceling it.
No, don't throw them out!
No, we have to
cancel the party.
We can save that!
No, no, no.
We're gonna get
fresh for Holly.
Fresh and new.
I know.
These cookies are fine!
It's not. They're not.
Michael, wait.
We don't have...
We don't have the budget
for another party.
Well, then,
everybody will chip in.
It'll be fine.
I honestly think
you're idealizing people
here again, Michael.
I don't think
that's gonna happen.
You know what,
I'll pay for it.
I'll pay for the party.
It doesn't matter.
This is way too important.
People, Holly's coming back,
and this is the most
important Christmas party
of my life.
So back to work.
Man, I worked hard.
I worked so hard for this!
I was after
corporate constantly.
I emailed Jo.
I wrote letters.
And you know who
I end up owing this to,
is the Scranton Strangler.
Thank you. Thank you,
Scranton Strangler.
I love you!
You just took one more
person's breath away.
MICHAEL: We have always had
good Christmas parties here,
as you know,
but they've never been cool.
The name is Bond. Santa Bond.
I'll have an eggnog,
shaken, not stirred.
Classic Brosnan.
Santa. Wonderful tradition.
Everybody loves Santa.
Everybody can't get enough
of the jolly old man.
But that is a myth,
because you know what,
he is not necessarily
a big fat guy with a beard.
He's not
necessarily an old guy.
No one knows what
the real Santa Claus... God!
Could you just stop
moving your calves so much
while you're talking?
Well, this year's
gonna be different.
We're gonna have fun.
It's not gonna be tacky.
It's going to be...
You know what,
the food is
going to be austere.
It is not going to be tacky,
deli platter food.
It's not gonna have a big,
fat, gross Santa Claus.
It's gonna be a cool,
sleek Santa.
Maybe I'll bring my boyfriend.
Okay. Sure.
I'll invite him.
I mean,
unless there's any chance
there could be press
at this party.
You never know
about the press.
Well, I only ask
because he's a senator.
Could he help us with
some parking tickets?
I don't think
that's appropriate.
Well,
then he's not a senator.
Yes, he is.
Okay.
Hey.
We still doing
the gifts today?
I mean,
it is the Christmas party.
Well,
the classy Christmas party.
Yes.
But don't get too excited,
'cause I didn't have
a lot of time this year.
Me neither.
Okay.
I've been working
forever on Jim's present.
He always gives me
the best Christmas gifts.
He'll take a memory
or a private joke,
and he'll create
something totally unique.
I love them.
So this year
I made him something.
A comic book.
It stars Jimmy Halpert,
a mild-mannered paper salesman
who, while riding his bike
through the forest,
is bitten by
a radioactive bear
and becomes "Bear Man."
Wreaks havoc on the office.
It's really good.
Okay.
No, no, no, no!
Fake tree. No!
No, it has the little...
Pam, no, no.
Holly's coming
from New Hampshire.
Somebody from New Hampshire
looks at that and thinks
it's a burning cross.
No, no. I want you to
go and get a real tree.
Take some money. Thank you.
Hi, I'm looking
for Michael Scott.
Yes, that's me. Come on in.
There's nothing classier
than boring jazz music,
I am here to tell you.
And I made a bit
of a judgment call.
I hired one musician,
because I thought,
"What's better,
to hire an entire quartet
for half an hour,
"or one bassist
for the entire day?"
Hey, any volunteers
to come with me to
go buy a Christmas tree?
I would, but I don't
want to get dirty.
There might be
girls at the party.
Why do you always
think that girls
are gonna be at the party?
No one invited girls.
It's just us.
I will help.
Although my brid, my hybrid,
my Prius hybrid,
won't fit a tree.
Which is ironic,
considering how
many trees it saves
on a daily basis.
KEVIN: Yeah.
I do, however, have a hookup
with a dude who has a pickup.
Do you mean Darryl?
That's a great idea.
I'll ask him.
You know Darryl?
Yeah. He works here.
We all know him.
I should come along,
just 'cause he's my,
you know, he's my hookup.
Cool.
Come on, now, Justine, look.
Listen, look, I've been
planning this, okay?
You cannot do this, Justine.
I'm not doing it!
She told me she wants
to have Christmas here.
She did?
Yes.
She wants to be around
family for Christmas.
DARRYL: I don't know.
I thought I was enough
family for my daughter.
Don't come in, I'm busy.
It's cool, Darryl,
I'm here, too.
Hey, sorry, I really
didn't want to come in.
It's just that we have to
go buy a new Christmas tree,
and we're hoping
we could borrow your truck.
Uh. No.
Come on, it'll be fun.
We could do donuts
in the snow on the way back.
No. Thank you for your
interest in my truck.
Okay. Sorry.
We'll leave you alone.
Hey.
You know what?
I could use
a breath of fresh air.
Let's do it.
When Holly gets here,
I want you to be
very helpful to her.
I've looked her up online.
There's nothing about her.
She's made no impression
on the Internet.
She doesn't need
an Internet presence.
You just know.
Hey.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You're supposed to
be in the courthouse.
We're on recess.
I came for the party.
Hey, everyone.
KEVIN: Hi, Toby.
What does the Strangler
look like?
Is he gorgeous?
He looks gorgeous
in the drawings.
Yeah.
That scowl.
I can't talk about it
or I'll get removed
from the jury.
And then he will come back
here and replace Holly,
so stop asking him questions.
I know people are only
this excited to talk to me
because of the trial.
But they talk to me
for a while,
and maybe people realize
I have something to say.
And then one day,
we're just talking.
You've reached the voice mail
of Dwight Kurt Schrute.
Please leave...
Stop!
I have no feeling
in my fingers or penis.
But I think it was worth it.
I was laying on the ground,
defenseless,
and he just kept throwing them
until he exhausted himself.
And, then...
"How about icing it?
LOL. Dwight."
Hi.
ERIN: Hello.
Is there any way I can
get a hand with these, please?
I'm really sorry,
I can't help you.
I'm waiting for my boss's
pretty friend to arrive.
MICHAEL: There she is.
Hey.
Erin, would you help her,
for God's sake?
You're Holly!
Of course. Sorry.
Hello.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Michael Scott.
You old bastard.
Well, I never thought
I'd see your face
around these parts,
you old bastard!
Well, I did show my face
around these parts,
you old bastard.
Why, you're some
sort of wise guy, huh?
I most certainly am.
Nyuk-nyuk-nyuk...
D'oh!
Oh, Homey.
Okay. Holly's back.
Hi. Hi.
Oh, huggy monster!
Oh, not the huggy monster!
I don't want to die!
Wow. Well, everybody,
you remember Holly.
Hi.
Did you bring us
anything from Nashua?
Oh, yeah.
I brought some maple candy.
But I have to admit,
I got a little hungry
on the drive,
and I ate some of them.
MICHAEL: That's adorable.
Would you put those out?
To throw out?
Or put out, like,
six pieces for everyone?
Oh, it's so nice to be back.
It looks beautiful in here.
Super-classy.
It's like a party
for limousine drivers.
Well, you came on the day
of our Christmas party.
It's fabulous.
I love what you did!
Isn't it wonderful?
We love it here.
Don't you love it?
All right, let me show you
to your desk.
I show you to your desk!
HOLLY:
Watch out for my guns.
They're both loaded.
What kind of guns
do you have? Six-shooter?
This is weird. I can't
believe you're here.
This feels like you
never left. Doesn't it?
Yeah, kind of. Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, and you have a Woody.
Oh, I love...
A.J. gave me that.
Well, that's understandable.
Still raw.
Woody your favorite character?
Mmm-hmm.
You know who my
favorite character
in Toy Story is?
Andy's mom.
Why?
Because without Andy's mom,
there's no plot.
And without any plot,
there is no movie.
That is a really good point.
A.J. said he hadn't seen
any of the Toy Story movies.
You're kidding me.
No. I know.
I'm like, "What?
Are you serious?"
What a douche bag!
Get a life!
Get a...
Yeah, good riddance.
We sat down and we
watched them all in one day.
Now he's the biggest
Toy Story fanatic ever.
Good for him.
Next day I found him
in my bed.
Really? That's creepy.
How did A.J.
get in your house?
We live together.
Oh, you do?
He had a little note
pinned to him that said,
"You've got a friend in me."
Yeah,
Randy Newman's the best.
Yeah.
I love him.
Me, too.
Christmas tree, Christmas tree
Won't you be my
Christmas tree?
Hey, how about this one?
Ah! Seems a little
full of itself, right?
Kind of a pretty boy.
What if we got
a really beat up one,
like on Charlie Brown,
and we just loved
it for what it is?
Maybe. I mean...
No, she be talking
to your mom or something.
This is my
daughter too, Justine!
You seem to think...
Pick a damn tree already.
Hey, listen, Darryl,
it's none of my business,
but if I couldn't
have Cece for Christmas,
I'd be really upset, too.
I don't have kids
or anything,
but if my
grandmother ever dies,
I'm going to kill myself.
Jada don't want to
spend Christmas with me.
She told her mom it
wasn't as much fun.
How could she say that?
You know,
I took her to the toy store
to buy her own presents.
Well, Darryl, no kid
wants to buy their own
Christmas presents.
Her mom wants me
to take her to mass.
I guess that's
something to do.
No, you should have
her mom do the boring
Christmas stuff on her time.
You should be associated
with the fun parts
of Christmas.
How do I do that?
Bring her to the party.
Yeah, we'll have Santa,
and we'll play games with her.
It'll be a lot of fun.
Yes!
You'll be Mr. Christmas
by the end of the night.
Hey, guys, the tree's here.
Hey.
Nobody hug me.
I'm covered in tree sap, so...
Why would someone hug you?
Hey there, Jada.
Nice to see you again.
I'm Santa Claus. Welcome.
Are you serious?
It's a sophisticated take.
He doesn't look
like Santa Claus.
No, he doesn't.
I told her
Santa would be here.
Yeah, well, I was told
that Holly would be here,
single and ready to date.
And we all got misled.
Who told you that?
Nora Ephron,
in every romantic
comedy ever made.
So is it an open relationship?
Oh, God, no.
Well, you're almost 40.
Oh, do you not want kids?
Oh, I want kids.
I really want kids.
But A.J. and I are
practically engaged.
We talk about
spending our lives together.
So where's the ring?
Kelly!
How are you
adjusting to the move?
Nobody cares about that.
Look,
you have to make him commit,
or kick his butt to the curb.
You guys,
I don't think any of us
are really qualified
to be giving Holly
personal advice
about her love life.
Yeah, I mean,
maybe Holly's not
in any position
to be shooing guys away.
I don't get it. I'm sorry.
I just... I don't get it.
Okay, listen,
I'm gonna tell him
that if he doesn't propose
by the end of this year,
we're over.
Wow, an ultimatum.
Yeah.
It doesn't
really seem like you.
That is a great idea.
Ultimatums are key.
Basically,
nobody does anything
for me anymore
unless I
threaten to kill myself.
Don't... Stop. Dwight!
Dwight, stop!
Oh, no. Oh, no!
Stop!
Oh, no.
Yes, taste my wrath!
Okay. Okay...
You like that?
Seriously!
Okay. Okay.
Yes, I have a wig
for every single
person in the office.
You never know when you're
gonna need to bear a passing
resemblance to someone.
I just want it to stop.
So cool, right?
There's no connection
between the origin
story and the quest.
Okay.
We need to know
who Jimmy Halpert was
before he was
bitten by the bear.
Otherwise it's
the bear's quest.
Okay, well,
I just sort of meant,
like, cute, right?
Well,
did you come here for help,
or did you come here for me
to tell you how great it is?
I mean, help,
if it's something simple,
like add page numbers
or laminate it or...
It sounds like you
know what you want.
It's also a little derivative
of a serial called Bear Man.
Did you look that up?
No.
Okay.
Oh, Jim. Hey.
Hey, Toby.
There's this
female stenographer
at the courthouse...
No way.
Who looks exactly like you.
That's incredible.
Yeah. No, it's uncanny.
You know what's crazy?
I can't reconnect
with you right now.
Hold on one second.
Excuse me.
I guess there are
just some people
who you stay together with
when you transfer,
and some people you don't.
And that's just the way it is.
And I can be
mature about that.
It's so cold.
Even with my coat on.
Maybe your senator boyfriend
has a blanket in his car
for screwing Americans.
Yet another opportunity
where a blanket
would have come in handy.
You guys,
this has to stop.
Someone could have
really gotten hurt.
What if Meredith was taking
her smoking break
below that window?
You know what
would have happened?
The shards of glass
would have shaved
her face right off.
And, yes,
it might have been funny,
but it also would have
been incredibly tragic.
I could not agree more.
And I just want to
state for the record that
I am intending to sue Jim
for acute
psychological distress.
What are you talking about?
You're the one terrorizing me.
With snowballs, Jim?
With fluffy little snowballs?
No. I thought we
were just playing.
Dwight's right.
What you did was dangerous
and inappropriate.
I'm really
surprised at you guys.
Last time I was here,
you were both best friends.
All this arguing reminds me
of a very funny story.
You see this on my desk?
You know who gave me this?
My girlfriend Tara,
who lives in New York City.
DWIGHT: Wait,
what girlfriend?
I haven't told you about her.
I find that unlikely.
You email me when
you get a new zit.
I'm a man in my mid-40s
and I still get zits.
I think that's
pretty interesting.
But you know what,
I am not on trial here,
the Scranton Strangler is.
So anyway,
we have this great weekend,
and she drives
me to the airport,
and we get to JFK,
but I'm flying
out of La Guardia.
So we laugh and
laugh and laugh,
and then we spend
the rest of the day
walking around slo-mo
drinking latte.
And at the end of the day,
she gives me this,
and she says,
"Michael, maybe next time,
you should take a cab."
I didn't know you
had a girlfriend.
I do. She is.
Did you see her face?
Well, it seems to me
that there is a person
sitting out there in the annex
that still has feelings
for Michael G. Scott.
And it ain't Tara.
So you went
homemade this year.
Yep.
Yeah.
Money problems.
Is that what this is about?
I mean, oh, dear,
I don't think we
can help you out.
No, no. Jim had
a great year, actually.
I just wanted to
get your opinion.
Are you good at homemade?
Look at this.
Yeah.
Who did this?
It's obvious to me
I'm not welcome here,
but somebody better
tell me who did this,
or else I'm leaving.
Well, I don't think
Erin seems to like you.
That's not true.
I don't know her enough
to make a decision even.
What happened?
Toby, what did you do?
I think Toby's very jealous
of all the attention
you've been getting.
No, I would never ever
do anything like that.
But it does seem like
something you would do.
Oh, really? Turn it on me.
Well, isn't that nice?
Thank you very much.
Wait, wait, guys, listen.
Toy Story is all about
toys that come to life
when people aren't looking.
You don't think...
It's not possible
that Woody did
this to himself?
MICHAEL: It is Christmas.
No, it really seems like
something Michael would do.
Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
Well, the fact that
you would think that
points to the possibility
that it is probably not me.
And that I have been framed.
Why would anyone
frame you for that?
Okay, I'm sorry,
why are we discounting
this whole
"Woody came to life"
thing so quickly?
Surprise!
It was part of the party.
Pretty funny, huh?
You think this is funny?
I don't.
But someday I think
we will laugh about this.
When we tell our kids...
Yikes.
Oh, my God.
All right! Shh!
Okay. You know what,
Holly, I didn't mean to do it.
It was an accident.
An accident borne
of jealous feelings.
Michael,
you have to let this go.
I'm with someone else.
I don't feel that way anymore.
Oh, really?
Well,
you certainly seemed jealous
when I told you
about my fake girlfriend.
That's what Jim
and Dwight thought.
Okay, hey, hey, hey...
No, fake girlfriends
are always wrong.
You made up a fake girlfriend
to see if I'd get jealous?
And you destroyed a gift
my boyfriend gave me?
What is the matter with you?
When you got transferred,
and I drove you up to Nashua,
you said,
"Michael, I love you,
but I can't do this."
But then, with this other guy,
you don't have any problem
with a long-distance
relationship, do you?
And you know what,
that is what is
the matter with me.
Michael, I'm sorry...
And we did this whole
stupid party for you.
No.
You guys,
it wasn't my fault.
Nothing is ever your fault.
Just like when you
ate those maple candies
that you brought for us!
I really think
you're better off.
Mmm. Erin, would you do me
a favor and find my street
clothes for me, please?
Yeah.
Is she an amazing cook
or something?
"Hey, Pickles,
Merry Christmas.
Open immediately?
"Love, Swiss cheese."
Damn it, Dwight!
Didn't think your
affectionate nicknames
would be your undoing,
did you, Jim?
Let that be
a lesson to you all.
So do they bring in food,
or do you get to go out?
No, they bring it in.
You lucky son of a bitch.
I have been trying
to get on jury duty
every single year
since I was 18 years old.
To get to go sit in
an air-conditioned room
downtown, judging people
while my lunch is paid for...
That is the life.
Daddy, I'm bored.
Can I read my book
in your office?
Sure, sweetie.
Jada, Darryl,
I'm so glad I found you guys.
A Grinch stole the star
from on top of
the Christmas tree
and is hiding it in
the warehouse somewhere.
You want to go
help me find him?
Oh, my goodness.
I am the mean old Grinch.
The little girl who wishes
to win back the Christmas star
must first succeed
at these challenges.
That sounds fun
and Christmasy,
you mean old Grinch.
What kind of challenges?
Something like
an obstacle course,
Mr. Grinch?
No. You must answer
topical political questions.
How many congressmen
is the state of
Pennsylvania guaranteed?
And what other state
has the equal number?
I don't know.
Do you know the other state?
Maybe the Grinch hid
the Christmas star,
and we could ask for clues,
and he'll tell us
if we're hot or cold.
The star has been hidden.
Is the little girl
hot or cold?
Well, it turns out
she's burning up
because the star is
right behind her ear!
And the game's
over seconds later.
I'm so glad you could come.
It's nice. I know.
Hey, everybody,
this is my boyfriend,
Senator Robert Lipton.
Hi.
Senator, it's an honor.
I'm Angela's friend Oscar.
Oscar. A pleasure.
Robert seems great.
He's very handsome,
firm handshake, he's gay,
good sense of humor.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm A.J.,
I'm here to see Holly.
It's kind of a surprise.
I know who you are,
and I think you should go.
I bet you didn't even
bring us anything, did you?
Was I supposed to
bring you guys something?
What? A.J.!
Surprise.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
Oh, my God.
How are you?
Wow! Nice.
Oh, God, you look great.
When did you get here?
Just now. Just now.
Hey.
Hey, Michael.
Good to see you again, A.J.
Welcome.
Pleased to see you.
Thank you.
Good trip down?
Yeah, it was great.
Good, good.
Good to see you.
Have fun. Enjoy the party.
I am dead inside.
What do you want, baby?
We got some granola,
got some cupcakes,
chips, apples, pies.
You have a whole room
of vending machines.
I know. Isn't it something?
I can't decide what I want.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
A Merry Christmas.
Thank you so much.
Merry Christmas.
And Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, thank you.
For your feet.
It's amazing.
It's so great. Thank you.
For me?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I don't know if you
guys have had a chance
to use the new parking meters
that accept credit cards,
but Robert was instrumental
in that legislation.
Wow, that's awesome!
A real David
and Goliath story.
I'm just so touched
that she's so interested
in my work.
ANGELA: I am.
MEREDITH: The real problem
is the teachers' union.
Zip it, Meredith.
No.
You tell me why my kid is 17
and still can't read.
Hey, who's in charge
of making drinks around here?
Is there a bartender?
You are.
You make your own drink.
I'll make it.
What are you drinking?
An F train to Brooklyn.
Extra bitters.
I don't know
how to make that.
Okay, well, I'll just
stick with my Mojito.
And you know
those annoying
geese at the park?
Well, he's helping
eradicate them as well.
I mean, I think
they've really become a pest.
Annoying.
Yes.
I don't think
he's in the ceiling, babe.
Well, I don't think
any of us really know.
All right.
Is it...
Is it pebbles from
that beach in Jamaica?
Go easy with the shaking.
Oh, my God.
You like it?
I love it.
Yep, I do make
great Christmas gifts.
But I couldn't make that.
All right, my turn.
Oh, it's just... I didn't...
I didn't have a lot of time,
so that's just a place holder.
Right. Of course.
"The Adventures
of Jimmy Halpert."
Oh, my God.
This is awesome!
That's my bike.
That's my desk.
And that is my daughter.
I mean...
I don't like
to talk about it.
Better office policy up there.
KEVIN: But it should be
the same policy as us.
Okay.
Michael, wait.
Hey, hey, no, don't run.
You're gonna slip.
That's good advice.
Yep.
I read this story
about a woman who slipped
on some black ice,
and she hit her head
and went into a coma forever.
And then every day,
her husband went
and visited her in
the hospital until she died.
That's a sad story.
Yeah, well,
at least he was married.
Okay, Michael, slow down.
Everything's gonna be okay.
No, it's not. It's not.
Oh, man,
I can tell you confidently
that it is not gonna be okay.
I shouldn't tell
you this, but...
A.J. won't commit to Holly.
And she's gonna tell him
that if he doesn't propose
to her
by the end of the year,
it's over.
Really?
Really.
And I don't know about you,
but I don't know
a lot of happy marriages
that start off with
an ultimatum. Do you?
No.
So just be patient.
Yeah. I mean,
I can wait till then.
Come here.
I don't want you to fall.
I surrender.
I do not accept
your surrender.
There's only one way
that I would ever relent.
Anything. You got it.
You hit Pam in the face with
a snowball while I watch.
You're a psychopath.
I'll take that as a no.
I was in the mall,
and I saw that,
and I thought it had
your name written all over it.
Michael, this is the gift
that corporate gave us
that I picked out.
You're re-gifting this to me.
No, that's not...
No, I went to the mall
and I picked that out
especially for you.
Oh, yeah?
Well, show me the receipt.
From the mall.
That...
This is a fast food
receipt from April.
That...
God, how many number nines
did you order?
A.J.: Is everyone here
kind of mean?
I think everyone's
on edge because of
the Strangler trial.
Hey, I'm so glad
you came down.
It's been so much
harder than I expected.
Hey, what happened to Woody?
Oh, okay, get ready for this.
You're not gonna believe it.
I was making salad,
and he fell right
into the dressing.
I mean,
there was salad
dressing all over him.
He smells awful.
It was blue cheese dressing.
Great.
Hey, Mike.
Hey.
We wanted to
give you something.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
A Hostess apple pie!
This is my favorite breakfast.
How did you know that?
Thank you very much.
What do you say?
You're welcome.
Oh, you know,
I seem to remember
that Santa promised
that he would listen
to all the gifts you
wanted for Christmas.
Didn't he say that?
Yeah.
I think I know where he is.
A trampoline.
Mmm-hmm.
Video games.
DSi.
A horse.
A pool.
Are you sure you
don't want a pony?
You want a real horse?
Yes.
All right. You have
to pick up after them.
Hey, sorry. I'm ready.
I don't want to go.
Oh. Come on, Bear Man.
Come on.
Have you ever
seen them do that?
I'm sorry.
I had no idea.
No, it's okay.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no, no.
Okay, this is it.
What?
Go! Go! Go!
What? What is it? What?
Oh, my God!
Honey? Jim?
Jim!
In the end,
the greatest snowball
isn't a snowball at all.
It's fear.
Merry Christmas.