Mmm.
Necesito un bueno worker.
Tu es fuerte. Come on.
We don't go with that man.
I've seen several men go with
that man and none come back.
We've lost friends...
We don't know what
he does with them.
I don't wanna talk
about it anymore.
I pick up day laborers
and tell them that
they'll get paid at 6:00 p.m.
At 5:45, a certain
I.N.S. Agent,
by the name of Mose Schrute,
throws them in
the back of a van,
drops them off in
the middle of Harrisburg
and tells them it's Canada.
Tu es un bueno worker?
Si. Yo muy bueno worker.
Yel acento...
Donde are you from?
Scranton.
Y... before that,
la Philadelphia.
You speak English?
Yes.
I'm really good at English.
Okay, good, me too.
Get in the car.
Okay.
Who is this guy
by our cars?
That is my new
maintenance worker, Nate,
and you'll be happy to know
that he's taking care of
that hornet's nest
that you've
been griping about.
Yeah. I got stung
up my dress.
Poor hornet.
I've left him all
the tools he needs.
This is do or die.
If he chooses correctly,
he'll conquer the hornets.
And if he doesn't?
He'll die.
What?
Beg your pardon?
DWIGHT: When did the phrase
"do or die"
become so corrupted?
KELLY: Is that
a blowtorch?
No.
No, no, no! No, no!
DWIGHT: Interesting choice.
PAM: Yes.
ANDY: Very, very smart.
PAM: Walking away.
No! No, no, no!
The bat.
PAM: What is he doing?
ANDY: Oh!
They're stinging him!
ALL: No, no, no!
No, no!
Good morning, Erin.
Any mustaches,
I mean messages?
Terrific.
MICHAEL:
There are many reasons
a man would wear
a fake mustache to work.
He is a fan
of the outrageous.
He loves to
surprise!
He loves other things
as well.
Wow.
Okay.
It's a pimple,
Phyllis.
Avril Lavigne gets
them all the time,
and she rocks
harder than anyone alive.
That's no pimple, Michael.
You mean cancer?
What? No way. No.
Definitely not.
Not cancer.
It's just good to catch
a Michael train
of thought early
before it derails
and destroys
the entire town.
MEREDITH: Wait, wait, wait.
It's just a cold sore.
It is?
Yup, just a cold sore.
Just a cold sore.
Thank you. Phyllis,
I don't have acne.
I have a cold sore.
I didn't even have a cold.
I don't know how I got it.
I know how you got it.
How?
Michael, come on.
A cold sore is herpes.
What?
What you should do,
Michael,
is have a doctor
take a look at it,
'cause we don't
really know what that is.
I know tons and tons
of people who have herpes.
I have it myself.
That's what it is.
I've never seen
herpes on you.
'Cause it's on
my genitals, genius.
You have a penis?
Michael, have you ever
been tested for STDs?
Yeah, my last physical
when I was 40.
That was, like,
10 years ago.
No, it was, like,
four years ago.
Michael,
you're at least 46.
Why "at least"?
If you're guessing 46,
just say 46.
Can we please talk about
how gross Meredith is?
This is what you get
when you treat your
body like an outhouse.
ANDY: You know what, guys?
How about we just
chill out a little bit
on the herp chat?
Okay? I was
an R.A. In college,
and I can tell you,
the number one sexually
transmitted disease
is ignorance.
I guess maybe she
could marry a
meth dealer with crabs...
I don't even want
to know about these things.
Hey, guys.
How did this happen?
How did I get this?
Sometimes it can lie dormant
in a woman for years.
They may not even
know that they have it.
You know what?
I feel like
one of those
old-timey sailors with VD.
Eh, it's me own darn fault.
Girl in every port!
What port?
The Jan port?
The Holly port?
Don't even...
Holly was clean, okay?
If anything,
I gave it to her.
You may have.
Oh, my God.
What if I did?
You need to contact Holly.
You need to notify her that
she is crawling with herpes.
Okay. You know what?
Might.
Might be crawling with herpes.
I might have
gotten it after her.
You need to contact
every woman you've been with
and notify them of
your herpes infestation.
It's the right thing to do.
There's no way
I'm gonna do that.
Then I will.
All right, I...
Now, I'm no doctor,
but it seems to me
that we all have an obligation
to the public health
to track down anyone
who gives us a disease,
inform them of it,
and take overwhelming revenge
on that person.
Again, I'm no doctor.
I'm just a normal guy
who enjoys revenge.
DONNA: Hello.
Hi, Donna. It's Michael.
Michael. I didn't
think I'd hear from you.
How've you been?
I have a disease
for which there
is no known cure
that has been
sexually transmitted to me.
Oh, no!
I can't even say it.
H-I
Oh, my God!
R-P-E-E-S.
Wait. You're calling to tell
me that you have herpes?
No. I am calling to see
if you gave me herpes,
because if you did,
I would be able to avoid
a lot of sucky conversations.
So you have it, right?
No.
Does your stupid
husband have it?
No, he doesn't.
Are you telling me
I have to get tested?
Yes, I'm telling you
you have to get
tested for herpes.
Good-bye!
So long, Donna.
Excuse me, everyone,
can I have your attention,
please?
Not again.
What do you mean "again"?
You're always
asking for our attention.
Well, maybe like a year ago.
Mmm. Seems recent.
No, that's...
Andy, the reason
it seems more recent
is because many of us here
have never stood up
and asked for
everyone's attention,
and it seems like
you've done it
on several occasions.
Everyone, I've noticed that
we've not been entirely
kind to one of our own,
due to stigmas
and prejudices.
Oh! When you got
your new phone,
that's when you asked
for everyone's attention.
STANLEY: World Cup.
That's what I was thinking.
OSCAR: That's right.
You kept announcing scores.
It's the world's only
international sport, so...
This is Holly.
No, this is Holly.
No... This is Michael Scott.
Busted.
So, what can I
do for you, Holly?
I'm calling because
there was
a terrible car accident.
Oh, really?
Was anyone killed?
A lot of people.
Any nuns?
Three nuns.
Missionaries
from South Africa.
Were they in
the missionary position?
Hot pizza, check it and see
I got a whole
Bunch of pepperoni
Yeah.
Now you're looking at me.
Anyone who's interested
in entering into
an honest discussion
about the sexual
mores and taboos
of modern society
will be rewarded
with a pizza break.
Do you ever wonder
what life would
have been like
if you hadn't
been transferred?
HOLLY: Yeah.
We would have twins.
I don't think
we'd have kids.
Mmm-hmm.
We dated for a few weeks.
Mmm-mmm.
We would be married.
Michael, I've been
dating A.J. For a year
and a half now.
You do this, you know?
Do what?
You romanticize things.
I don't romantici...
No.
Michael, you cried
at that tag line for
a movie you made up.
"He had no arms or legs.
"He couldn't see,
hear or speak.
"This is how he led a nation."
You made us out to be
more than we were.
Maybe we were
I don't know what
you're getting
so upset about.
We had a fun fling
a long time ago.
It's a good memory.
Okay, all right.
I gotta go.
Michael...
He forgot
to mention the herpes.
It didn't come up
organically.
to accommodate
the suppliers.
Gentlemen, nice to see you.
It'll be just a moment.
If you could show them
into conference room B.
The pharmaceutical company
should be able
to accommodate us.
How do I do it?
Raise my daughter,
work as director of office
purchasing for this hospital
and release an album
of Doris Day covers
on my own label?
If I knew,
I'd tell you.
It's nice to see you
doing so well.
Yeah, I'm really happy.
Me and Astrid
against the world.
We're loving it.
Yeah, so,
kind of the supermom.
Bringing home the bacon.
Yeah.
Fry it up in a pan
Never, never, never let you
Forget you're a man
Love that commercial.
I don't understand
the reference.
Well,
Michael, it was nice
to get your call.
We had to come over
right away. It's urgent.
Okay.
Michael has something
to tell you.
Shh.
Are you gonna
keep me in suspense?
Would you excuse us?
Okay, I'm gonna
head outta here.
I know you have a lot
to talk about, okay?
Is there an operating theater
that's open to visitors?
Never mind. I'll find it.
He hasn't changed.
No.
So, what couldn't wait?
Am I the kind of person
to misremember
our relationship
as something more
than it was?
Michael Scott,
you are here
for a post-mortem.
What?
You wanna dig into
our relationship,
go over it,
see what killed it.
Okay.
I'm in.
So, guys,
I've been really bothered
by the way certain people
are getting treated
around here.
And I just think
as an office,
we're better than that.
Okay, now, I'm gonna
show you a picture
of genitalia.
ANGELA: Andy.
What, 'cause he's black?
Nope.
It's 'cause it's genitalia.
Perfectly normal genitalia,
Tuna.
Now I'm gonna show you
another picture
of perfectly normal
genitalia.
Oh, my God!
Am I blocking anybody?
Can everybody see?
ANDY: Perfectly normal.
Big deal.
Yeah, sure,
it's got some herpes on it.
But you know what?
It's just as normal
as anyone else's.
No. In the beginning,
we were not good.
Well, there was a bit
of a learning curve
in the conversation
department,
but between the sheets,
we were like
Jordan and Pippen.
Well, if there was anything
exciting about it,
it was because
we both knew
it was wrong.
Because we worked together.
No.
Okay, imagine
there's a princess
who falls for a guy
beneath her station,
and the queen
doesn't like this at all.
And the princess knows
that the queen
doesn't like it,
and so it makes her
want to do it all the more
just to get at the queen.
Am I the princess?
No, I'm the princess.
And the queen.
Okay.
So I'm the guy
at the station.
ASTRID: Mommy!
Assie! Oh!
How was school?
It was cool
What did you learn?
What did I learn?
You might have learned
Shapes, or blocks
Or clocks, or colors
Or you might have learned
That we're all
sisters and brothers...
I have herpes.
What? You...
I used to think
that she was "the one."
Or at least a "the one."
And if I called
that one so wrong...
Herpes, like all STDs,
is a consequence of sex.
Can anyone else name
any other consequences?
It feels unbelievable.
Okay, I guess we can
make a pros column.
"Feels..."
KEVIN: "Unbelievable."
Okay.
The ability to
express love physically.
It's a magical thing.
ANDY: "Express love."
"Magical."
It feels amazing.
Um... Okay, is that different
from "feels unbelievable"?
Yes.
Then I will write it down.
The feeling of pure risk.
Creed, I had that
in the cons column,
but...
It's thrilling.
Okay. Then...
We'll move that.
"Thrill of risk."
Andy, aren't there also
negatives to sex?
Yes! Thank you.
Such as...
Unplanned pregnancy.
Yes. Unplanned pregnancy.
Like Jim and Pam, what?
Hey.
Just admit
that your baby
was a mistake.
Whoa!
Hey, our baby
was not a mistake.
She was a surprise.
Good.
I'm sure
they don't regret
having that child.
Let's move it to the pros.
BOTH: Thank you.
Okay. "Unplanned pregnancy,"
going in the pros column.
Next up is Helene.
You're gonna want to
make a left on Willow,
which is a little ways away.
I'll remind you.
You know, I don't know
if I trust Jan's judgment.
She...
Jan knows paper.
No, not paper.
Relationships.
To have the ability
to point out
if a man is making
a bigger deal
out of something
than is really there.
Wait, what Holly said?
Yes! I don't...
Forget it, Michael.
Today is about herpes.
I know.
Okay? Who gave it
to you, who has it...
Right.
And who is going to pay.
Okay.
To answer your
question about Jan...
No, Jan is insane.
Why do you think I...
Left! Willow, now!
All right! God!
Hi, stranger.
Long time.
Who are you?
I'm Michael.
We dated for a while.
I don't think so.
Michael?
Oh, hey!
Dwight, would you take
my grandmother for a walk
while I talk to
the real Helene?
Come on, old lady,
let's go.
What is happening?
Come on.
Who can tell me
the safest form
of safe sex?
Condoms.
Incorrect.
The only true form
of safe sex...
Okay? Abstinence.
Oh! I didn't
realize we were doing
trick questions.
What's the safest
way to go skiing?
Don't ski.
DARRYL: Huh?
I just thought
I'd bring it up
in case someone here
was practicing abstinence.
That's all. Anybody?
Andy, that's way too
personal of a question.
Well, someone
could answer it
if they wanted to.
Okay, in that case,
I will now show you how
to put this condom on using...
this pencil.
Oh, God!
What?
Why would you
choose a pencil, Andy?
Well, I'm not gonna
use my penis, Oscar.
It's not exactly
hard right now, anyway.
Come on, give it
a rest, pencil.
I'm doing this
for you, Meredith!
I didn't want it!
Well, didn't you?
Why didn't...
Does no one appreciate
what I'm doing right now?
MEREDITH: Whoa!
It'll go away in time.
Just don't touch it.
Did I make more
of what we had
than was really there?
What did you think we were?
Just a quirky indie movie,
weird sort of thing,
breaking all the rules,
but had to end
because the summer
was over for you.
I think that for you
to have come here
even expecting
that we could have
a conversation like this
shows how
self-deluded you are.
Michael, your memory
has failed you greatly.
Jerk.
Michael.
So, this is a chef's kitchen,
which makes it perfect
for real entertainers.
Real entertainer,
like Billy Joel.
Michael.
Carole. How are you?
I'm great. How are you?
I'm great.
I saw your sign outside,
and I decided
I'm gonna pull in,
and maybe I'm going to
buy a house from her.
You didn't call my office
and ask them
where I was?
No!
That's so...
'Cause the receptionist
told me that a man called,
but he would only say
that he was my ex-Iover.
Weird.
Yeah.
Sounds like a nice guy.
I don't know,
I mean, people were being
really mean to Meredith and...
But this wasn't really
about Meredith, was it?
You and Erin
were broken up.
How is that
relevant to anything?
I asked you
if it was okay
if I asked her out.
You said, and I quote,
"My good sir,
nothing would make me happier
"than to hand you the hand
of the hand once in my hand."
I specifically remembered it
because you said it
in such a weird way.
Well, the only
reason I said that
is 'cause you
asked me so politely,
and it was very
difficult for me
to say no.
I'll let this slide,
but I expect you
to put this whole
Erin thing behind you.
Oh, wow!
Another living room.
It's a family room.
You put the TV there.
You put your family here.
Michael,
why are you here?
Somebody told me
that I romanticize
relationships.
You know,
we all do that.
I have herpes.
What?
Did you have that
while we were together?
I just found out today.
It's right there.
Oh! Oh! What, that's what
you're talking about?
Mmm-hmm. I'm sorry.
Did you have a doctor
check it out?
I'm between specialists
right now.
Yes. Yes, Michael.
Actually, you do make
a bigger deal out of things
than you need to.
You proposed to me
on our fourth date.
Well, I believe in
love at first sight.
Well, so do I,
but we didn't love
each other at first,
either.
I don't know what
you were thinking.
I know what I was
thinking at the time,
but right now,
it just seems ridiculous.
DWIGHT: Excuse me.
Someone died in the upstairs
bathroom, didn't they?
No.
We should
schedule meetings,
'cause the days can
slip away with chitchat.
Are you crying?
No, I'm just sweating.
I don't know
what's got you upset,
but my advice
is stop crying.
I'm not crying.
I'm sweating.
Look, you need
to pick yourself up.
Man up, all right?
Son, you will win this
in the end.
It's all about heart
and character.
Be your best self.
Okay.
Yeah.
I have no idea
what his problem is.
It's just my standard advice.
It's good advice, right?
This is Holly Flax.
I can't come to
the phone right now,
but please leave a message
at the sound of
the tiny truck backing up.
Hi, Holly, it's Michael.
I just wanted to
call and let you know
that I was thinking
about what you said.
It's just, you know,
it's weird. Today, I
ended up seeing a lot of
the women that I used to date,
and in my mind,
they were all great.
And then when I
actually saw them,
it was mostly a freak show.
And you and me,
that must have been
a real train wreck.
You know what?
Holly, you're wrong.
You are wrong.
I remember
every second of us.
And talking to you today,
I don't feel for them
anything like what
I feel for you.
It's...
I didn't joke
with any of them.
I joked with you.
You were the only one
who was actually happy
to hear from me.
And I don't know why
you downgraded what we had,
but I did not make us up.
Okay.
Oh, and you might,
you should talk to a doctor
because you might have herpes.
Bye.
What is this about?
Oscar,
We once sucked face in public
as part of
an office presentation
to destroy the stigma
about gay kissing.
Do you recall?
Yes, and...
You may have given me
a sexually
transmitted disease.
What?
Herpes duplex.
It's probably just
an ingrown mustache hair,
but we have to be exhaustive.
I've already
contacted all of my
ex-Iovers except for you.
We were never lovers.
I'm gonna need
a list of every man
you've ever had sex with.
I'm talking train stations,
men's rooms...
Flower shops,
fireworks celebrations...
Fence with a hole in it.
Moonlit gondola.
Carriage ride
through Central Park.
The woods behind
the liquor store.
The swamp behind
the old folks' home.
MICHAEL:
Electric car dealership.
DWIGHT:
The Democratic Primary.
Oscar, think about... Think.