Hey, how you doing?
Been thinking about
my grandmother a lot.
Yeah.
She was about to turn 97.
At least she lived
a very long, and I'm sure,
a very happy life.
Mmm.
Got you this card.
When you're ready,
we all signed it.
We just wanted you to know
we're thinking about you.
Thank you.
"Congratulations, Darryl.
Let's get wasted."
"Have fun today, big guy."
"Oh, yeah. Party time.
"Whoop-whoop."
It's possible that
some people thought
it was your birthday.
"Hooray. Live it up, big D."
"Days like this don't
come often enough.
"Time to celebrate.
"You deserve this"?
Birthday punches!
One, two, three,
four, five, six...
I'm so sorry.
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19,
20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25...
So, I got an early
res at Blu Wasabi,
and I'm taking Rachel.
She's picking
me up after work.
Rachel from the party?
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Do the damn thing.
Blu Wasabi is so good,
but get the cheeseburger.
They say they won't do it,
but they will if
you make a scene.
Okay, bye.
I'll miss you.
Miss you.
Okay. I'll be in my
office if you need me.
Bye-bye.
HOLLY: Bye.
MICHAEL: Okay, bye.
Bye.
All right, bye. Bye.
Bye. Okay.
HOLLY: One more big one.
Don't go. I don't
want you to go.
Let go.
Don't go.
Holly and I are dating.
It's been a week,
and I still can't
believe it.
It goes to show
that everything
you want in life,
you get.
And you can't work for it.
It just comes to you.
And what do we have here?
From my secret admirer.
That's you.
Caught.
I dominate Valentine's Day.
I practically make
romance into a science.
"Roses are red.
Violets are blue.
"Look in the vase
to find your first clue."
Oh, my gosh.
It's a romantic
scavenger hunt.
Close. It's a romantic
treasure hunt.
A scavenger hunt is where you
find items from a master list.
This is where you follow
clues that lead to a prize.
Common misuse. Good luck.
But there's no clue.
Well, get to work.
I can't 'cause
there's no clue.
The puzzle is the clue.
Are these numbers correct?
The numbers are
correct, Michael.
Okay.
Are you... Are
you sick, Oscar?
Do you need to go home?
'Cause you're grossing me out.
I just need a signature.
JIM: There you go. Thanks.
Thank you.
How much did you give him?
Big tip.
Wait. I don't have my scarf.
What?
I'm missing my scarf. Oh...
We decided to have
a Valentine's Day lunch,
and then that way we can spend
the entire night with Cece,
and avoid the Valentine's
Day dinner thing.
It's a whole thing.
Yeah, lunch was wonderful!
Um, there was
an amazing buffet,
and there was
a chocolate
fondue station.
And what else was there?
Uh, bottomless champagne.
Yes.
Never found that
bottom, did we?
No.
Pssst! Pssst!
What's up?
Are you good
at jigsaw puzzles?
Are you kidding me?
It's all I did every summer
when my brothers
were out sailing.
Okay.
But if this is a romantic
thing with Gabe,
I should probably...
Oh! No, no, no, no.
It's not weird at all.
You have your new
girlfriend, I have Gabe.
This is just as friends.
Well, okay then.
Yes!
At least until
Stanley calms down.
Oh, is he...
Don't look.
I accidentally did his sudoku.
Andy.
All right, I will
fax over it to you.
I will fax it over to you.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay, my name is
Jim Halpert,
and I will fax it in to you.
Under you.
I'll fax it under you.
Oh, excuse me.
I just pissed my pants.
Not really. I didn't really.
Wait.
You're just filling
that out right now?
That wasn't meant for me.
I will not be your valentine.
Oh, nuts.
I don't know if anyone
else feels this way,
and don't get me wrong,
I love Michael and Holly.
And maybe I'm being
overly sensitive, but
the PDA...
Yes! The freaking PDA!
Uh-huh.
Thank you!
I mean, I'm thrilled for them.
No one is more thrilled
for them than I am...
Yes. Yes, absolutely.
but it's totally
inappropriate.
Yeah, it's a little much.
Obviously, so happy
for them both.
CREED: So happy. Yeah.
I don't know, guys.
I, for one,
enjoy watching
them, because...
No, stop. Just don't...
Can I finish? Can I finish?
Is that okay?
OSCAR: No, no, no.
I was saying,
I enjoy watching them
because it makes me horny.
God! Kevin!
So, tell me about
your new girlfriend.
She's neat.
Uh, I met her
at Darryl's
cousin's party.
We were the only two
white people there.
Oh, cute.
Hey, look at that. Done.
ERIN: That's Gabe's boom box.
Come on, we have
to go find it.
I wish you well on your quest.
No, come on.
I mean...
Come on!
Okay.
I hear them kissing
all the time.
It's this horrible
plipping sound.
You know, it's like
Chinese water torture.
Just...
Like it's coming
from my own head.
MICHAEL: Okay, sit. Okay.
Just close your eyes.
HOLLY: Can you get lower?
Oh, yeah.
A little lower.
I cannot keep myself
from Michael.
Everything he does is sexy.
He has this undeniable
animal magnetism.
He's a jungle cat.
The man exudes sex.
He can put both his
legs behind his head.
Thank you all for meeting
on such short notice.
Yes?
Yes. Michael Scott,
Dunder Mifflin.
What is the purpose
of this meeting?
Seeing as it's
Valentine's Day,
I felt it would
be apropos to have
a little refresher course
on romance in the workplace.
Perfect. Yes. It is quite
apro-propriate. Carry on.
First things first,
an office romance
is permissible.
Not something you'd expect
to hear from corporate.
Well, guess what?
Sabre is 100% tolerant
of office romances.
Speaking of, Gabe,
I don't see Erin
at this meeting.
Uh, I also don't see Andy.
ALL: Ooh.
Boom! Face!
I get it. Andy's
slamming my girlfriend.
Very funny.
What I do not approve of,
however, is public
displays of affection,
or PDAs.
PDAs are totally
superfluous to a happy,
healthy office romance.
A perfect example,
look at Jim and Pam.
Yeah. What? Us?
They don't touch.
They don't kiss.
You would hardly even
know that they were
husband and wife.
Did it.
Yeah!
Love it.
Keep it going.
Okay. So, PDAs.
That's gonna include
behaviors such as
hugging, kissing...
Uh...
Booby honking.
Yeah, booby honking. Sure.
Butt honking.
Yup, all the honkings.
The one where you
start in a crouched
position, then you leap...
Sure. Basically, there's
no precise definition,
but you know
it when you see it.
Are you guys
listening to this?
What? Are you talking
about me and Holly?
PAM: Yeah!
Maybe you find
your own chair.
So, we kiss occasionally.
Not occasionally.
All the time.
Yeah, and it's not
just the kissing.
It's the flirtatious
whispering.
The flirtatious tickling.
Whispering and tickling
have their place in business.
That thing where you
softly exhale on her neck.
I...
Okay, yeah, that's pretty hot.
I will give you that.
Look, you are
all hypocrites.
You all do it.
Michael? Confession.
I have done PDA in the office.
Thank you.
I've had intercourse
in the office.
All right.
As has Angela.
Dwight!
As has Ryan.
As has Kelly.
As has Meredith.
As has Phyllis. As has Darryl.
As has Creed. As has Michael.
As has Holly.
As has Kevin.
With who?
She goes to another school.
Okay, fine. No more PDA.
Good.
You win.
But here's what
we are gonna do.
We are going to designate
one of our closets
as a hook-up zone.
No.
Anything goes!
Just leave it how you said...
DWIGHT: Michael,
that's absurd.
What if two couples want
to go at the same time?
ANGELA: Ugh, Dwight!
Okay, then we have two...
No, no, we're gonna
have three closets,
one for each base,
no homers. Yes?
And what is the hook-up zone
policy on masturbation?
Pro.
Yes.
What? Problem solved.
No, no, it's great.
I love working
at Dunder Mifflin,
a division of
Taliban enterprises.
That's weird.
I mean, that's weird
to have sex in the office.
That's where you work, right?
Mmm-hmm.
You know, you're in a meeting,
and nobody knows that
you've had sex there,
except for you and him.
Ew.
Don't mind us.
You keep working.
Okay, I'll keep working.
Oh, my God. It's a song.
Whoa.
What do you think is on it?
We should actually probably
talk about it outside,
or we might make Darryl mad.
Not if we're talking
like this. I think it's okay.
He doesn't seem to hear us.
I think he's just being nice.
That makes sense 'cause
I feel like I'd be able
to hear us at this level.
Darryl?
Darryl is a jerk.
No, he's not.
No, I'm just testing
if he can hear.
I can hear you.
Okay.
Then no more talking.
Let's just play the song.
GABE ON STEREO:
The temp at night
Temp at night?
What do you...
You got it.
Pick it up. Take it out.
Pick?
Pick it up.
Okay.
Take it out.
Pick it up.
Pick it up. Take it out.
Right. Okay.
Sorry to interrupt.
Forgot to collect my things.
Ah, the old leave behind.
Oldest trick in the book.
Good thing it's working.
No. Michael, I don't want
to make people uncomfortable.
Since when is comfort
the most important thing?
I mean, I don't sit
on your lap because
it's comfortable.
I sit on your lap
because I like the way
your thighs feel on my butt.
Yeah, but if they're
uncomfortable, it makes
me uncomfortable.
Oh, okay. Well,
if it makes you
uncomfortable,
then we'll stop.
Okay.
Holly and I are like
Romeo and Juliet,
and this office is like the
dragon that kept them apart.
Hey, you know the only
reason why people
here are complaining?
They are jealous of two people
in love on Valentine's Day.
Two people in love?
I love you.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you mean
you love me?
We've only been
dating for a week.
Do you mean you love
me like, "Hey, there's
Holly. I love that girl,"
or do you mean you
love me like you
"love me" love me?
I "love you" love you.
You "love me" love me.
I am really disappointed
in the office's policy
on PDA at this moment.
I love you.
Yeah, whatever. No big deal.
Just the hottest girl
in the world loves me.
Okay, Ryan's the temp.
What does he do at night?
I guess we just have
to wait until night and see.
Oh.
Or maybe not.
Cool.
ANDY: How romantic is this?
ERIN: Super romantic.
Right?
Do you see a clue or...
Did you not see it?
Oh, my gosh.
Hanks.
Oh, hey.
Hey. No time to chat!
Sorry.
Well, we were just
looking for Ryan.
So, he's not here.
Hey, you're looking for me?
Oh, yeah, we were.
We were just looking
to say hi. So, hey.
No, you weren't.
No, we weren't.
You wanted to have
sex in my office.
No.
Definitely not.
That's disgusting.
It's cool.
Just, um, try to put
everything back
where you found it.
Text me when you're
finished. I'll be out here.
Hey, you don't have to...
That was so embarrassing.
I'm gonna die.
That was really rough.
PAM: Let me make
something clear.
Jim and I have never
and will never have
sex in the office.
JIM: No, because the office
isn't what I'd consider
a romantic place.
PAM: Besides, we have
something those other
people don't have,
which is a home and a bed.
And a shower.
Hello, Holly.
Hello.
Here, shake. No!
No, don't touch.
No, we can't.
No touching.
Ah, I'm trying
not to touch you.
BOTH: Oh.
Almost got you.
No, so close.
BOTH: Oh!
No, we can't do that.
We can't do this.
You're not touching me.
I don't know what your
body feels like, 'cause
I can't touch it.
Okay, this is much
worse than before.
Yeah, I agree. This is nasty.
Grab you here.
And here.
MICHAEL: And I will
grab you here anyway.
You have to cut it out.
Never.
Okay.
You said you would.
I did say I would,
but I was wrong.
I can't stop.
You don't know what
it is like to love a woman
and have her love you back.
It is a feeling that cannot,
and will not,
and frankly cannot
be contained.
No one is a bigger fan
of sexual touching than me.
But with you two,
it's reaching the level
of a complex.
I can think of
three explanations.
One, you're taking MDMA,
street name, Ecstasy.
I've done it,
and I know the feeling.
No, I don't think so.
Number two, you're
desperately trying to fit
in a whole relationship
before Toby comes back
from jury duty and Holly
has to go back to Nashua.
Or three, you're at an age
where your sexual climaxes
aren't as powerful,
so you need to overcompensate
with foreplay, taboo behavior.
Yes, it was that.
It's that one.
Yes. Number three.
Give me all your money
and take off your clothes.
We're not supposed to PDA.
Come on. Nobody's looking.
What's wrong?
I hadn't thought about you
having to go back to Nashua.
Maybe we didn't want
to think about it.
We can make it work.
We'll date long-distance.
That's what we said
last time, remember?
We broke up on the drive.
How's this gonna
be any different?
We weren't in love last time.
I was in love with you.
I'm not saying
it won't be hard,
but we can make it work.
That's what she said.
One Erin special, please.
Here's your bottle
of sparkling cider.
That's my favorite.
I'm now supposed to tell you
to enjoy a mid-hunt
break, and look for
a heart or some
in the break room
when you're through.
Hey, buck up, buddy.
Make that face he likes.
Hey. Hey, come on.
You're hurting him.
It's like a time bomb
is ticking down.
When it goes off,
no more kissing,
no more hugging.
Just hush.
Sexual time bomb.
Just rock.
"Boner Bomb" starring
Jason Statham,
or we go against type
with an Eisenberg
or a Michael Cera.
Movie idea?
No.
Saving the world has
never been this hard.
Okay.
Have you talked to her
about our feelings? Women
really go for that crap.
No, I can't talk to her.
I can't even look
at her without thinking
about it ending.
Kevin, do more stupid faces.
Which one?
I have a lot of stupid faces.
I don't know.
Do a monkey face.
I love that.
I love that face.
Good. He loves it.
Good. Jump. Jump up and down.
No, monkey!
Go back to the monkey.
Don't do the squirrel.
Throw your poop.
Hurl your feces.
MICHAEL: That's good.
Good.
That's good. He's throwing it.
They really do that.
I know.
ERIN: B-9.
ANDY: B-9.
Like benign tumor.
Maybe it's just
more like "Be mine."
Oh, yes. There's a note.
"A little cookie
for you, my miss.
"But the real treasure
is your Valentine's kiss."
BOTH: Mmm.
So...
We're supposed to...
Hmm...
Holly, hey.
Hi.
Holly, I love you
so, so, so much.
And I think that
we need to break up.
What? What are
you talking about?
Actually, it's
Valentine's Day.
Shouldn't be doing this today.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
No, we're gonna talk now.
You're not breaking
up with me.
You're gonna go back
to Nashua eventually,
and I can't handle it.
So let's just... Let's...
What if I said
it wasn't up to them?
Who?
The company.
Nobody knows our future,
but it's not gonna be
decided by the company.
It's not gonna be decided
by anybody but us.
And what we are
is up to you and me.
Okay. Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have an announcement
to make.
As of today, officially,
Holly and I are
moving in together.
Yay!
Thank you. Thank you.
Oscar, this must
be tough for you,
watching this go down.
You could not stand
in the way of true love,
my friend.
Are you kidding?
I wasn't trying
to break you guys up.
Better luck next time, pal.
Well, the point is, there
will no longer be any need
for PDA here at the office
between us, because
when we get home,
we are going to make love
to and with one another,
and that, to me, is the best
Valentine's Day present
that a person could receive.
So, I bid you all adieu.
You do?
I do.
Go on. Kiss each
other already.
Suck it, Oscar.
This must kill you.
I just told them to do it.
What?
No.
We took a walk.
My perfect Valentine's Day?
I'm at home, three cell
phones in front of me,
fielding desperate calls
from people who want to buy
one of the 50 restaurant
reservations I made over
six months ago.
Anybody can be Prince
Charming one day a year
with the dinner
and the flowers
and all that.
But you know what
impresses me?
When a guy can do
that no days a year.
Flowers, diamonds,
three-course meal,
violinist comes to my
table to serenade me.
Pizza, soda, the moon,
someone to share it with.
What are our plans
for tonight?
Um...