Happy Turkey Day.
Yes! Right out of the gate.
What? What's going on?
We're playing Boyle Bingo,
Thanksgiving edition.
Everyone filled out their cards
with possible
Charles-related scenarios.
First to bingo gets 100 bucks.
I had "Boyle calls it
'Turkey Day'"
in the center square.
"Boyle explains
they ate lobsters
at the first Thanksgiving."
They did. Back in that time,
they called lobsters
"ocean bugs."
I'll just mark it off for you.
I think got the winning
card here.
Boyle tells us
that he played Pocahontas
in his third-grade play.
All the girls were too big.
This is a fun one...
"Boyle says, 'gobble,
gobble, gobble.'"
Now that I know
you want me to say that,
I'll just say it
with two gobbles.
Gobble, gobble...
Gobble. God, it just
sounds right that way.
Ugh. I don't like this game.
Ha! "Boyle objects
to Boyle Bingo."
Come on, guys.
Boyle says, "Come on, guys."
That's two for Terry.
Well, guess what.
I can spoil your little game
by sitting over here quietly
all day and doing nothing.
Oh! Aah!
Anybody have
"Boyle falls on the floor"?
No one?
That's a victory.
That's a victory for Boyle.
Boom!
[all] Boyle says, "Boom!"
[upbeat music]
[Jake] Check it out,
chair jockeys.
While you were busy tickling
the ivories on your computers,
I was doing a bust. Cocaine!
Thanks, Lucius.
He ran, I pursued.
Whole thing turned
into an awesome car chase.
Aah.
NYPD!
[grunts]
[tires screeching]
- Come on! Move, move!
- [horn honking]
Hey, there, criminal.
It's me, Johnny law.
Well, at least
you're done early,
so you have time
to go home and change
for my Thanksgiving dinner.
Why do we have to dress up
for Thanksgiving?
I don't even celebrate
that stuff.
The whole holiday
is based on overeating.
We should be wearing
velvet track suits and diapers.
Jacket and tie.
Rosa's even wearing
her formal leather jacket.
It's the one without any blood
on it.
You're gonna dress up,
and you're gonna give a toast
about what you're thankful for.
Start preparing.
Oh, I prefer not
to prepare for my toasts.
I just wing 'em like scat jazz.
[imitates jazz]
- Are we singing?
- No, no, no.
- [singing opera]
- [Jake] That's nice.
- You don't have to...
- [continues singing]
[whispering] I'm not dressing up
for your party.
[continues singing]
Damn it, Boyle.
You left the fridge open.
The door couldn't shut
because of your empty pizza box.
Pizza? Please.
This is a butternut squash
and truffle butter flatbread.
Everything's spoiled.
My lunch is ruined...
My chicken, my potatoes,
my pasta, my meatballs,
ham, my yogurt.
- Oh, that's a lot of yogurt.
- I love yogurt.
So this is your lunch
for, like, the month?
I need to eat 10,000 calories
a day to maintain muscle mass.
My wife made me all of this
before she left town
with the kids.
That was everything
in my fridge.
Scully.
- Hey, Sarge.
- I know you got a secret stash
- of food hidden somewhere.
- Oh, no.
Where is it?
- No, I don't.
- Is it in your pockets?
Oh, come on.
I'm gonna shake it
out of your pockets.
- Turn around.
- Sarge. [grunts]
- Sarge!
- Go limp, Scully.
- [grunts] This is fun.
- Release your sweets.
Can I help you, Santiago?
Oh, Captain, I didn't expect
to see you there.
In my office?
So I just wanted
to make sure you knew
about the Thanksgiving dinner
I'm hosting for the squad
after work.
Yes, I received
your "Save the Date"
decorative gourd,
your ornamental cornucopia,
and this beautiful
handcrafted card
of a turkey wearing a top hat.
It's a pilgrim's hat.
Where's the buckle, Santiago?
The buckle.
My husband's
out of town for work,
so of course I will attend
your dinner.
Cool. Whatever.
Yeah, don't worry about it,
either way. It's not a big deal.
- Yes!
- Why so excited?
Did you make the cover of
Hair Pulled Back magazine?
The captain is coming
to my party.
I'm gonna give a toast,
tell him how thankful I am
to have him in the precinct,
and officially ask
him to be mentor.
Wait, are you only
hosting dinner
because you want
to suck up to Holt?
Not cool. This was supposed
to be about friendship.
You said you were only coming
to see if my apartment
was the reason I was single
or if it was my personality,
like you suspected.
Yeah, but that was before I knew
I could get up
on this high horse.
Love the view up here.
Clip clop, clip clop, clip clop.
Same to you, your honor.
- What judge were you talking to?
- That was my mother.
You call your mom "your honor"?
She's a federal judge
in the ninth circuit.
- What else would I call her?
- Okay.
Captain, paperwork is all done
on that drug bust.
What else you got for me?
Nothing.
All open cases are assigned.
There's got to be something
I can investigate.
No, there's nothing.
When there's nothing,
there's nothing.
What can ya...
Whoa! Who did that?
Don't worry, sir.
I will stay here all night
figuring this out.
I know what
you're up to here, Peralta.
Damn straight,
I'm trying to catch
the mad paper scatterer.
You want an excuse to skip
Santiago's Thanksgiving dinner
because for some reason,
you refuse to celebrate
this holiday
like a normal person.
Fine. You're right.
I wanna do what I do every year,
sit at home, watch football,
and eat mayo nut spoonsies.
Those are spoonfuls of mayo,
sprinkled with peanuts.
That's revolting.
Maybe so,
but it's what I invented
when I was six
because my mom was working,
so I had to make dinner
for myself.
My sad story trumps your insult.
Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake!
[Boyle] Jake, Jake, Jake, Jake!
Thank you, Boyle.
If a case opens up, it's yours.
But if not,
you will be at Santiago's
as a professional courtesy.
Dismissed.
From what?
I thought we were just chatting.
We never chat anymore!
Oh, my god, Amy, that's so cool
that you still live
with your grandmother.
I live alone. This is my stuff.
I like quilts.
Stop. Each sentence
is getting sadder.
It looks like you live
on the set of Murder, She Wrote.
Well, I gotta say, it's not
as bad as I thought it would be.
The football game's not on,
so I can still watch it
later at home.
And it's kind of cool
to visit a time
before electricity was invented.
I have to practice my toast.
- God, how long is that?
- Eight pages.
- Single-spaced?
- Double-sided.
- Santiago style.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, excuse me.
Can we please eat?
My body is starting
to digest itself.
Terry needs nutrients.
No eating until the captain
gets here, okay?
- Sorry.
- Don't apologize.
I'd rather spend Thanksgiving
at your house
than with my sister.
"Things you find at the beach."
For s, I had seagull.
Good one, Diana!
- Ice cream break.
- [Diana] Yay!
Yay.
It's so pleasant and boring.
But Holt at your house,
surrounded by these idiots,
guaranteed train wreck.
Thanks for the invite.
[doorbell chimes]
He's here! Okay, he's here.
Everybody, be cool. Hitchcock,
why do you have your shirt off?
Can't spill food on your shirt
if you're not wearing one.
What...
- Captain Holt.
- Happy Thanksgiving.
Your apartment
was very easy to locate.
Thank you so much.
You look beautiful.
Weirdest conversation ever.
Nice work, you two.
Before we eat,
I'd like everyone to go around
and say what
they're thankful for this year.
[sighs] Fine, I'll go first.
I am thankful that Thanksgiving
only comes once a year.
People stuff themselves,
and then at midnight,
they run to appliance stores
and trample each other to death.
It's a garbage holiday.
[sniffles]
I'm sorry, I just get emotional
when I talk about how bogus
Thanksgiving is.
I'll just go.
I actually prepared
a little something.
You did?
When I was a little girl,
playing cops and...
- [cell phone ringing]
- Excuse me.
- Continue, Santiago.
- I could wait.
No waiting, just toasting.
I want you to toast.
Now I want to eat toast.
Give me some toast!
[Holt] Okay,
I'll be right there.
I have to head back
to the precinct.
No. Why?
Someone stole $10,000
from the evidence lockup.
Yes! Oh, awesome.
- Why is that awesome?
- It's a case.
You said I could hop
on any case that came up.
It's a Thanksgiving miracle.
Have fun, you guys. Let's roll!
You'd think money would be safe
in a police station.
I hear that.
Remember when Santiago
called you "beautiful"?
Yes, that was odd.
We need to get this money back,
the exact bills,
or the commissioner's office
will make our lives hell.
What is this?
Uh, this is Terry dancing.
People do weird stuff
in the evidence lockup
when they think
no one's watching.
Fast forward, fast forward,
fast forward.
Wait, stop.
Okay, so here's our money.
Fast forward.
[Jake] Hold it,
hold it, go back.
There's our guy. Got him.
We should start
by checking all the perps
that were released
from holding today.
- Good idea.
- And if's none of them...
we may miss Santiago's
altogether.
Thanksgiving is dead!
Santiago, can we please,
please just eat?
What if Captain Holt and Jake
are coming back?
Hang on. I have a toast.
I am thankful
to have someone in my life
who gives me a reason
to get out of bed every morning.
And I hope that my relationship
with this person
will only grow more intimate.
Who are you talking about?
Um, Hitchcock.
Okay, enough is enough.
I'm eating.
[grunts]
What's in these?
Potatoes, butter, a little milk.
And I ran out of salt
so I used baking soda.
Why wouldn't you?
They're both white powders.
Of course
they're interchangeable.
Yeah.
[grunts]
There were two men released
from holding today
who were the same
size as our thief
on the security footage.
Even if it is one of them,
how will we know?
Easy. The guy on the footage
was left-handed.
We just give all of our suspects
some made-up form to sign
and see which hand they use.
All right, amigo.
Punch it.
- [seat belt clicks]
- Good. Did that.
Now punch it.
Uh-huh. Safety first.
Punch it!
[electric window whirring]
- Now you're just messing with...
- [tires squeal]
- Anyone want seconds?
- Can't. I'm stuffed.
[Scully] Amy,
the toilet's overflowing.
What? Ew! Scully,
what did you do?
And the night gets worse-better.
I didn't do it,
although I understand
why you'd suspect me.
Well then who clogged it?
So none of you ate anything?
Terry, you said you ate
the whole turkey.
Toilet.
I ate one string bean.
It tasted like fish vomit.
That was it for me.
But I'm a good cook.
You all ate those brownies
I brought in last week.
I thought they were erasers.
Charles said he loved them.
I'm a textbook people-pleaser.
I have a serious problem.
This was great, though.
You must be so proud.
Yeah, Thanksgiving's over.
Everybody go home. We're just...
We're done hanging out together.
I'm not done hanging out.
Let's go to the bar.
They serve food there.
That's a great idea.
Oh, look at that.
"Boyle saves Thanksgiving."
- Does it really say that?
- No. But it does say,
- "Boyle believes obvious lie."
- Dammit.
So what's our strategy here?
I'm thinking we could do
the whole thing in character.
I'll play detective Bart Barley,
tightly wound,
hates violence against animals.
And you're my partner
Gerald Jimes,
a man who solved
every crime but one...
The murder of his wife.
- Peralta, take this seriously.
- I am.
As seriously as you're taking
the search
for the man
who killed Jane Jimes.
Your only clue:
He wore a yellow sweater.
Eh? You're considering it.
Let's get in there.
NYPD! [knocks on door]
What's going on?
I'm in the middle
of carving turkey.
I'm vegetarian.
Eating meat is murder.
I hate violence against animals.
Bup, bup, bup, bup.
We overlooked a release form
we were supposed
to have you sign.
We apologize.
Yeah, he's right-handed.
Let's go.
[Jake singing] Look out,
bad guys, it's Barley and Jimes.
Barley and Jimes are
on the case.
Please refrain from make-believe
this time.
- Fine.
- [knocks on door]
Good evening, ma'am. NYPD.
Barley and Jimes.
- We're looking for Donny Romano.
- Ugh. Come in.
Donny, what'd you do?
Cops are here.
Aw. What do you guys want?
Sorry to bother you, sir,
my partner here forgot
about a form we need you
to sign.
What's happening, Donny?
What'd you do?
I didn't do anything.
It's not my fault.
Same old story.
It's never you, is it?
What did Donny do?
I swear, Ma,
I don't know what this is about.
Why won't you ever believe me?
'Cause I raised a liar. You lie.
Shut up, Ma.
Hey, don't talk to Ma like that.
Don't you tell me
what to do, Louie!
Excuse me.
Hey! Not the rolls!
George, do something.
Excuse me. If...
[overlapping arguing]
Get off now.
My wife was murdered by a man
in a yellow sweater!
It's the one case I can't solve.
Don't fight with family.
It can all go away so quickly.
Sign this?
That's a hell of a breakthrough,
Jimes. I'm proud of you.
- Also, we just caught our man.
- He signed with his right hand.
That's right, he did.
But he didn't do it.
- He did.
- What?
I noticed you throwing
those rolls with your left hand.
Not to mention
this hoodie matches
our security footage exactly.
You stole money when you came
to pick up your brother
- from holding today, didn't you?
- Dammit.
Nice work, Peralta.
So where's the money now?
It's not here.
I bet it on the football game.
My bookie has it.
Yes! The case continues.
- This is not good.
- Right. Sorry, Jimes.
His father was murdered
by a bookie.
I know you miss him.
Our perp says
the bookie operates
out of a hidden back room.
Try to blend in.
Good idea.
I'll just age myself 60 years,
become Chinese and female.
Here we go. Whoosh. Did it work?
- $10 to play.
- Oh, we're just looking around.
- $40 just to look around.
- All right, we'll play.
- $15 to play.
- All right.
[sighs] Tommy,
can we order some food?
The cook's gone.
I sent him home.
Do you have any more
of these pretzels?
Sure.
I'm gonna call the cook.
Smart. Good call.
Hey. Rough night?
Yeah, it certainly hasn't gone
according to plan.
Oh, no.
Oh, Amy, I was ordering a drink
called a "rough night."
It's tequila
with a nicotine patch.
Right.
How do I get Holt
to pay attention to me?
He sure spends a lot
of time on Peralta.
Maybe I should start screwing up
like Jake does.
- I can act out, too, you know?
- Please do.
Okay. Watch this.
[glass shattering]
Oops.
Out, all of you.
- But the cook is coming back.
- Out!
Fine!
But I'm taking these olives.
[sighs] Sorry. Happy Turkey Day.
[speaking Chinese]
Ah.
I think I'm getting
the hang of this.
These tiles are
either game pieces or candy.
Game pieces.
Here we go.
[women speaking
Chinese excitedly]
I think I just won.
The guy by the bathroom
seems very interested
in the commotion you just made.
Yeah, and he's been waiting
for the toilet
since we got here.
10:1 that's not a bathroom
and he's a lookout.
- Let's go.
- You got it.
Ahh, I'm gonna just cash out.
[speaking Chinese]
There is nothing here.
Don't worry, guys. I found food.
Are you eating packing peanuts?
Okay, I do keep a secret stash
of food in the office.
I knew it! Where?
Where?
- Sarge, am I too heavy?
- No. Where is it?
There, the one
with the water stain.
- There's a lot of food up there?
- Yeah, it's a smorgasbord.
[all screaming]
- I think the rats got to it.
- You think?
This is the greatest thing
that's ever happened.
Okay, it's over.
Thanksgiving time of death, now.
No, this will not be
our Thanksgiving.
All right, you all wait here.
Give me an hour.
Terry, to the door.
I'm just gonna put
you down, man.
Yeah, totally. That makes sense.
Hey, there. Bathroom?
There's another one upstairs,
over there.
Aah. Oh! [grunts]
[whispering] Oh. Never mind.
Let's go.
What, it's really a bathroom?
No, no, there's tons of illegal
stuff happening in there.
But they're watching
the football game
and I DVRed it.
I don't wanna see the score.
What?
Okay, fine.
We'll go get the stolen money.
NYPD! Freeze!
Change the channel
and then freeze!
Put it down!
[Holt] Put it down!
This is a weird request,
will you switch places with me?
I really don't want
to see the score.
[both grunting]
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
That's so much better.
Oh! Why are there
so many TVs in here?
[Jake] Thank you.
The money was still
in the bookie's safe.
All the numbers match.
Let's head back
to Santiago's party.
Ah, no, thanks.
I think I'm gonna head home
and watch the football game,
which was ruined for me!
What's your problem
with celebrating Thanksgiving?
It's a sucky holiday.
It's always sucked.
My mom worked. My dad was gone.
And I sat at home
watching football.
Look, Jake, I came
from a very formal family.
My parents were not
especially affectionate.
Really, "your honor" wasn't
a big snuggler?
But the beauty of being an adult
is that you can
make a new family
with new traditions.
That's nice, Captain,
but I don't have
a new family yet,
so I guess I'm stuck
with my awesome old traditions.
Okay. I'll tell the squad
you couldn't make it.
Thank you. Before you go,
can I borrow some money?
I'm getting
some pretty serious vibes
from Wendy over there,
and I'd like to take her
someplace special.
Hey. What are y'all doing here?
Amy broke everything
and got us kicked
out of the bar.
Then we got attacked by rats.
It's the best Thanksgiving ever.
Fascinating.
Happy Turkey Day.
Right through there, gentlemen.
Not a lot of places are open,
so this will be a multiethnic,
nontraditional Thanksgiving.
It's a real culinary challenge.
Give me 15 minutes
and then we feast.
- Make it five.
- You eat with your eyes,
- so the plating alone...
- Five, Boyle!
- Captain?
- Hmm?
I wanna tell you something.
I think you're...
like, when
I was a little girl...
You think I'm like
when you were a little girl?
- Forget it. The moment's passed.
- Is this about your toast?
- How'd you get that?
- Gina gave it to me.
It's very well-written.
There are several
compelling anecdotes.
The fonts suit the tone.
Good work.
I do feel, however,
the word choice
could've been improved in spots.
I marked them "awk"
for "awkward."
That was the best thing
anyone's ever said to me.
"I marked them 'awk'
for 'awkward?'"
It's advice. He's mentoring me.
Yes!
So this is kind of a play
on your typical
Thanksgiving dinner.
For turkey,
we have the Peking duck
with a veggie samosa stuffing.
The potatoes are the empanadas
with an Ethiopian
lentil stew gravy.
And for dessert,
some seasonal gelatin cups.
Okay, I ran out of money.
They're from when Hitchcock
had a colonoscopy.
Bon appétit.
- I'm here. I'm here.
- [all cheer]
Finally something
to actually be thankful for.
What are you wearing?
Santiago said to dress up, so...
Well, you look beautiful.
That's my thing now.
I'm just owning it.
Okay, before we eat...
Nope, not doing that again.
Move.
Could you pass the...
You get that hand near me again,
you're gonna lose it.
- Okeydoke, let's eat.
- Yeah.
Hey, thanks for giving a copy
of my toast to Holt.
- That was nice of you.
- Oh, you're welcome.
I mean, you don't have to get
so freaked out around him.
You're just trying to tell him
you respect him.
Okay.
But to be honest,
I kinda gave it
to him as a prank,
'cause I thought it would be
super embarrassing for you.
But I'm happy it worked out.
But I would've been happy
if he hated it.
But I'm happy he didn't.
So you pretty much got
the disaster night
you hoped for.
Yeah, till you made
the best Thanksgiving meal
I've ever had, and ruined it.
Excuse me.
Uh, so, earlier at Amy's,
I didn't give a real toast,
because I didn't know
what to say.
But since that time,
a wise, unsmiling man
named Gerald Jimes made me
realize what I am thankful for.
So I'd just like to say
I am happy to be here
with my family...
My super-weird family
with two black dads
and two Latina daughters
and two white sons
and Gina and...
I don't know what you are,
some strange giant baby?
- To the Nine-Nine.
- [all] To the Nine-Nine.
That was perfect.
Ooh, "Boyle cries."
I got Boyle Bingo!
- [all groan]
- Yeah!
Not a doctor. Shh.