Dryin' dishes, yeah.
Man, Charles has been
so happy and confident
ever since he hooked up
with that Professor
at the captain's party.
She has tenure, and also has ten years,
times two, older than him.
That sucked.
Yeah.
It's nice to see him like this.
He's so confident.
This morning, he finally
corrected the barista
when she called him "Charlize."
He's been living as
"Charlize broil" for five years.
It's great.
It's all so great.
He could take it down, just a smidge.
♪ If you like pina coladas
dead guy, Charles.
Sorry.
But whatever, I can handle the singing.
I'm just so happy for that guy.
It's about time he caught a break.
Sexy train is leaving the station.
Check out this caboose.
Later, sluts.
Just let him have it.
Great job, Boyle.
Sync and corrections by parlobrito
web dl sync snarry
Peralta, where are we
with the black cab holdups?
Well...
I got this, Jakey.
Oh, all right.
Have at it, man.
Nice jeans, Boyle.
Those are surprisingly
low-waisted.
Eyes up here, Gina.
I'm more than just a piece of ass.
Ooh.
Not bad, not bad.
An unlicensed cab driver's
been picking up tourists.
Driver takes the vics
down under the B.Q.E.,
robs 'em at gunpoint,
leaves them stranded.
Unfortunately, because they're tourists,
and our perp is not Caucasian,
we don't have a clear idea
of what he looks like.
He was either Latino, Arabor Mican.
Either way, very Muslim.
We'll go undercover,
dress as out-of-towners,
hope the perp picks us up.
Don't worry, sarge, we'll nail this guy.
I can't believe I was just
briefly attracted to Boyle.
A Mr. Brain Jensen
here to see you, sir.
It's Brian.
Not according to this note
I wrote on my hand
very quickly: "Brain."
Captain Holt, we recently met
at the African-American
Gay and Lesbian New York City
Policeman's Association.
Yes, that name is quite a mouthful.
Just call it the "AAGLNYCPA."
Your organization has meant so much to me.
Well, it's not my organization.
I mean, I did found it
and I've been president
for the last 25 years
and I oversee every detail,
but really, it's our organization.
It's yours.
And out of respect for you and everything
that you've done, I wanted to stop by
and let you know I'll be
running for President.
I hate to run against you,
but I have some ideas for change that'll
bring AAGLNYCPA into the 21st century.
I see.
Well, it's been good meeting you.
And, I wish you the
very best. Thank you.
Good-bye, brain.
It's... it's Brian.
Very nice man.
Yes, he is.
Now, let's figure out how to...
Destroy him.
How'd the interview with the victim go?
It went okay.
The guy was from Canada,
said it was probably
his fault for getting robbed,
and apologized for wasting my time.
Oh, Canada.
Truly Odie to America's
Garfield. -
Hey, what are you doing tomorrow night?
I think I can get us some Nets tickets.
No go, amigo.
Tomorrow is Vivi's and
my big 20-day anniversary.
I'm pulling out all the stops.
Dinner at Le Bonbon, with
300 roses at the table.
No. Oh, man.
Then a gondola ride
along the Gowanus Canal.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
And then, a skywriter's
gonna write,
"Charles loves V."
I couldn't afford her full name.
Okay, first of all, "Charles loves V"
means something very specific
and, I'm gonna guess,
not what you're intending.
But more importantly,
you're going full Boyle.
What? I am not.
What's full Boyle?
Anytime Charles gets
into a new relationship,
he gets way too intense
way too fast, and it always
ends in heartbreak.
We met on the subway,
went out to dinner,
and I told her loved her.
And my mom was so happy.
And then the barbershop quartet
I hired started to sing.
And then she broke up with me.
And then she broke up with you.
Yes!
Oh, Joanna, no!
Courtney!
Rhonda!
I know when I'm going full Boyle.
Trust me, this is different.
I have it under control.
Gotta go, Jakey.
Excuse me.
Are you a detective?
Oh, who's asking?
I'm Super Dan, scourge of
Brooklyn's underworld,
and I need to talk
to an officer of the law.
I'm busy right now,
working on this... excuse.
I think Santiago's free.
Hi.
I'm Super Dan.
And I have a crime to report.
Oh, gosh, I am so sorry.
I literally just retired.
This is my retirement cake.
Thanks, you guys.
I'm gonna miss this place.
Why aren't you guys taking me seriously?
Your cape and your tights,
and your name is Super Dan,
and I can kinda see your penis.
And it's just all a rich tapestry.
Yeah, well, I'm a citizen.
I'm from this neighborhood.
So the only reason
I'm wearing this costume
is so when I'm fighting crime,
people will respect my authority.
How's that working out for you?
Detectives, when a citizen
comes in off the street,
it is NYPD policy to take a statement.
This isn't enough of a statement?
Yes, I wanted to inquire
about renting out the Statue of Liberty
for a romantic evening.
Is there a bed in the torch?
No? Okay.
I'll get back to you.
Hey there, Charles.
I thought maybe we should
have a little chat
about how crazy you're acting,
and how you're blowing this beyond repair.
Are you really qualified
to give romantic advice?
You're not exactly the king
of mature relationships.
Fair enough.
But I would argue
that I am like a beautiful angel of love,
who has trouble finding love for himself.
Admit that you would see that movie.
I would.
Thank you for honesty.
But this is not about me.
It's about Charles.
I've seen this before,
buddy, and it is bad.
Jake, I'm nowhere near full Boyle.
Then prove it. Just push your
anniversary dinner one night.
Say, "Vivian, tomorrow
doesn't work for me.
Can we reschedule?"
If this will convince you,
more than happy.
No problem.
Great.
Voice mail.
God, I love how she says
the words, "you've reached."
Hi, Vivi. It's Chucklebunny.
Oof.
I'm just calling about dinner tomorrow.
I can't wait to see you,
my luscious little breakfast quiche.
I just wanna draw you a bubble bath
and spoon-feed you caviar.
I think we should open up
a joint checking account.
I love you...
What am I doing?
It's okay. I hung up
right after "Chucklebunny."
Help me.
I've gone full Boyle.
I need to focus on my reelection campaign.
Clear my schedule.
You really care about
this little club?
It's not a club.
It's an organization
that I founded over 25 years ago.
I'm proud to say we now have 50 members.
But it wasn't so easy in the beginning.
I'd like to request discretionary funds,
to start an organization supporting black
gay and lesbian police officers.
They never actually said no,
so I just went ahead and did it.
I've poured my heart and soul
into this organization.
And I'm not gonna just
give up the presidency.
You should make me your campaign manager.
I was born for politics.
I have great hair and I love lying.
Find out everything you can
about this Jensen.
I'll work on my speech.
How's this for an opening joke?
You know what the toughest part about
being a gay black police officer is?
The discrimination.
I believe that's what
you call observational humor.
Probably. That's great.
All right, let's go over our disguise
I am Herbert Goffleman from San Diego.
I came here to stand in the cold
outside the today show, holding a sign
with a misspelled word on it.
Oh, you know what?
You win.
That neon green fanny pack
screams, "gullible tourist."
It's mine.
I brought it from home.
Hey, can I have my phone back, please?
No, because you will call Vivian,
and you have the worst case
of full Boyle I've ever seen.
What?
I found this, by the way.
You wrote "Mr. Charles Ludley"
over a thousand times.
Why would you take her last name, Boyle?
Look.
For the last two years, I've been
directing all my love at Rosa.
So my emotions just piled up.
And now with Vivian, my feelings
are springing out of me like a fire hose.
Oh, that is overtly sexual.
Jake, I'm gonna ruin it.
You gotta help me.
All right, here's the plan.
I'll text Vivian from your phone,
and tell her you want it
to be a double date.
That way, I can come with you
and hold your hand.
Well, then your hand will be on her butt,
because my hand will be on her butt.
You gotta get it together, man.
I told you I need help!
Hey, can I get your file on
that Atlantic Avenue drug ring?
Sarge gave me and Scully the case.
What?
Oh!
Why did you do that?
I-I know I deserved it,
but why?
Sarge, you reassigned our drug case?
Diaz and I have been
working it for three months.
Remember Super Dan?
The guy you ignored and made fun of?
He's been perching on rooftops at night,
secretly taking photos of drug deals.
He has thousands of images
and can I.D. the entire network
of dealers.
What?
But you refused
to take his statement,
because he had a cape on.
Luckily, Hitchcock and Scully didn't mind.
I didn't even notice
he was wearing a cape.
You're a cop.
You should've noticed that.
We screwed up.
Message received.
Yep, be nicer to virgins.
She doesn't speak for me.
You're not getting your case back.
Okay.
Here's what I found out
about our competition.
Brian Jensen, born 1899,
served in the navy during World War I.
A hero at the battle of Scimitar Hill,
Jensen perished in a factory
fire in the Netherlands.
This may be a different Brian Jensen.
I've never been in this position before.
I've always run unopposed.
If you wanna compete,
you're gonna have to have
a little more pizzazz.
A couple ideas for ya.
The obvious place to start would
be you, in a silver suit,
with sunglasses and roller skates...
The candidate of fun.
What's your second idea?
Nada.
Thought I had a slam dunk
on the first one.
Hi, there.
We'd like to go to the Times Square.
We're brothers.
We're all set for the double date tonight.
Vivian's bringing her friend Bernice.
Bernice?
That sounds like a cartoon dump truck.
Whatever, that's probably for the best.
I don't need any distractions.
My mission is to protect you.
All right.
Hey, this guy's going the right way.
We should get out and try again.
You can let us off here.
We would like to buy some bagels.
And where is
the sex and the city street?
We wanna see where Carrie and Big live.
I'm a Carrie.
I think I'm a Carrie.
We're both Carries.
All right, let's prepare
for the date tonight.
Here's the things you're not
allowed to talk about:
Love, poetry, music, or passion.
We don't have to talk at all.
I'll just stare into her eyes.
They're like little drops
of cilantro reduction
on lily-white flan.
Okay, no.
See, no food talk.
It sets off something primal
and disgusting in both of you.
It makes me wanna barf.
You're right.
Look, if you feel like
you can't handle it, we need a signal.
I'll do this.
And how would you do that naturally?
I don't know.
This guy's clean, by the way.
Can we pull over, please?
There she is.
I don't know if I can do this.
Listen to me.
I am with you all night.
And nothing will distract me
from my solemn vow to protect you, okay?
Okay.
Vivian, you look beautiful.
I love your dress.
Aww.
You too, Charlie.
You look so handsome.
Steady, steady.
Jake, this is my friend Bernice.
Oh, hello.
I'm jak-tractive.
Jak-tractive?
Yes, my parents were hippies.
Let's eat.
Okay, so, Jake, you're a cop.
I wanted to be a cop when I was a kid,
mostly because I love Die Hard.
Die Hard, really?-
Well, that makes sense,
everyone loves that movie.
Oh, not like me.
I sleep in a Nakatomi Plaza
Security t-shirt.
Oh, no.
What kinda dogs do you like?
I mean, you know, just hypothetically,
if we were to get a dog.
Oh, I love all dogs.
When I was a kid, I had the cutest
Golden Retriever, named Rufus.
That is the most amazing thing
I've ever heard.
I wanna meet him.
Charles, why don't you tell Vivian
about the ten-day forecast?
Oh, good idea.
Sorry about that.
So if you're not a cop,
then what do you do?
I'm in grad school.
I thought about maybe
being a sports reporter,
but it would be impossible
for me to be objective.
I love the Nets so much.
You're a Nets fan?
I love the nets.
Oh, my God. This season has
been a disaster, right? Yes.
- And everybody blames it Jason Kidd.
- Yes.
But it's like, at a certain point,
Billy King is the one
who put the team together.
Yes.
Wow.
I love rainy days.
My mother loves rainy days.
You should meet her.
Excuse me.
Our signal.
Here's a question for the group.
What is the longest funeral
you've ever attended?
Ladies first.
On behalf
of captain Holt: Floorgasm.
♪ Hands in the air
fist pumpin' like champs ♪
♪ hands in the air
♪ fist pumpin' like champs
Did you like it?
It was inspired by the city of New York,
in that I stole it from some kids
I saw dancing on the subway station.
All of you, go home, immediately.
I appreciate the effort,
Gina, but I can't risk
losing this election.
The AAGLNYCPA means too much.
Let me rehearse my speech.
Do you want a president
who struggled against all odds
to create this great organization?
Or do you want a great nothing
who struggled against
nothing odds to create nothing.
Yikes.
The meeting is beginning.
The stakes are very high for me.
I'm getting nervous.
My stomach is in flux.
You know, in the court of Louis XI,
women would only eat consomme, because
they were worried that chewing
would give them wrinkles.
I love it when you talk broth.
Hey, Charles, remember that dog
we found on the train tracks?
Was it inside-out
or just very badly burned?
Inside-out.
Yeah, 'cause there were
things on the outside that
definitely should've been on the inside.
Definition of inside-out.
Bingo.
Will you excuse us?
Bernice and I are gonna
use the ladies' room. Yeah.
Hurry back.
Oh, no.
Jake, I can't stop looking at her butt.
Yeah, you are definitely
making her uncomfortable.
And this beautiful
basketball-loving
Die Hard fan is tearing down
my walls of defenses.
If we find out that she is
half-Jewish, we are all doomed!
I know.
I borrowed the waiter's phone
when you weren't looking,
and bought me and Vivian
plane tickets to Rome.
What?
We leave in two hours.
Terrible itinerary,
connect through Vietnam.
All right, just go home.
Get out of here and regroup.
I'll take care of everything.
I'll tell 'em it was
an emergency. Thank you.
Can you make it a work
emergency, not a bathroom one?
I kinda wanna make it a bathroom one.
Sarge, you made your point.
We messed up.
But this is a big case, and Hitchcock
and Scully are gonna screw it up.
I'm sure they can handle it.
They have a combined
50 years of experience.
This morning I found Scully's gun
in the freezer, in the frozen yogurt.
I think he was using it as a spoon.
The truth is, I had to give 'em the case.
You insulted Super Dan.
He refuses to cooperate with you.
We weren't that bad.
You told him his superpower
was being so embarrassing
that people laughed themselves to death.
Yeah.
For those of you who don't know me,
I'm officer Brian Jensen.
Listen to him talk.
He has no gravitas.
Do you know what gravitas sounds like?
Greetings, all.
Details about this organization
should be included
in NYPD recruitment literature
and on the website.
He actually has some good ideas.
Maybe you shouldn't be
so quick to dismiss him,
like you were with a certain
amazing dance troop.
He isn't fit to be president.
He hasn't spent the last 25 years
fighting to build this organization.
Right. Is that bad?
I thought you created
agla... naca... macapa
or whatever, so people like him
wouldn't have to go through
what you went through.
Isn't it a good thing that Brian Jensen
didn't have to struggle for 25 years
just to get up on this stage?
Thank you all for your time.
I hope you vote for me.
Greetings, all.
You know what the toughest part about
being a gay black police officer is?
The discrimination.
What?
At the very first meeting
of the AAGLNYCPA,
I was elected president unanimously,
because I was the only member
and I voted for myself.
But after 25 years of struggle,
I am no longer the only member.
And I look forward to casting
my vote for someone else.
That is why I withdraw my name
from consideration as president.
Congratulations, Brian.
If you screw this up, I will impeach you.
I wrote the bylaws,
so I know how to do it.
But I'm very happy for you.
But I will impeach you, if necessary.
Anyways, Charles wanted me to
reiterate how sorry he is,
but he got an emergency call.
And that is plausible,
because we're detectives.
Well, is it a tough case?
'Cause Charlie was acting
so weird tonight.
Work has been
so stressful.
Speaking of, here is your coat.
I've gotta run.
If you wouldn't mind using the back exit,
it'll be much safer.
Trust me.
I'm a cop. New York, right?
Charles, what are you doing here?
I'm so close to getting you out of this.
They're putting their coats on.
Funny story...
I was walking home
and I passed a pawn shop.
And then I went into a trance.
And now I have this engagement ring.
No, Charles!
Well,
I'm gonna go ask Vivian
to marry me. Bye.
No, give me that.
Jake!
Give that back.
I'm doing this for your own good.
You've gone full Boyle.
I'm helping you out.
Give me that ring,
or I'm gonna pepper spray you.
Pepper spray me, I will pepper spray you!
No!
Aah!
Crap! Crap! Aah, crap!
Crap! Aw, crap!
Hey, buddy.
Got you that fancy coffee you like.
Nah, I don't want it.
So expensive.
How you holding up?
Well, Jake, I've been better.
Right. Look, I'm sorry
I threw your ring
in that boiling pork water.
Yeah. I'm sorry
I pepper sprayed you.
I'm sorry I pepper sprayed you.
It burned like hell, right?
Yeah.
Thank God for that soda.
It's so sticky, but it feels so good.
Ooh, cab.
After you.
Yes, sir.
What are you two still doing here?
Isn't your shift over?
There's something we need to take care of.
Oh, Super Dan, over here.
Thanks for coming.
Great.
You two?
If you guys wanna make fun of me,
just come down to pita paradise
like everyone else does.
We need your help.
Why?
What happened to Scully and Hitchcock?
They're busy, cleaning Hitchcock's ear.
Yeah. Did you witness any of
these men selling narcotics?
This is so official.
Yeah, this guy, number three.
That's the mope we brought in.
Yeah, okay.
We're gonna need to take your statement.
Spare no detail.
Really?
Yeah!
Okay, um, all right.
Well, I was driving
around my neighborhood
in the "Danmobile," which is my bike.
I know what we did wrong.
Should've followed the rules,
but more importantly, we're supposed
to help out everyone, no matter what.
That's right.
Nice work on the arrest.
I got vaccinated that year,
but then I still got the flu.
Whoa.
Don't be bummed, man.
It's gonna be okay.
No, it isn't.
You can't be with me
every minute of every day.
I'm in love with this woman, for real.
And I'm gonna go full Boyle
and scare her off.
No, we can figure this out, all right?
I still got your phone,
so you're good there...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I think we're gonna get robbed.
I need to pull over.
Flat tire.
Give me your wallets.
NYPD, you're under arrest
for armed robbery!
A little to the left, Charles.
Yeah, I'm still not seeing great
because of the pepper spray.
Hey, cab driver's
in the interrogation room.
You ready?
Let's do it.
Oh, no, what's this?
What is this?
I checked your phone.
There were a hundred texts from
Vivian, worried about you,
a selfie that I can never unsee,
and dozens of voice mails.
Hey, Chucklebunny, it's me.
You disappeared last night.
And you were acting weird.
And I'm worried it's
because I'm moving too fast.
I really wanna see you.
And I know it's 3:00 A.M.,
but we should feed each other falafel
in our underwear...
Okay.
I know it when I hear it.
She's full Boyle.
Full Boyle for Boyle.
I took the liberty of texting her,
and telling her to come meet you here.
I thought you might wanna give her this,
or something considerably nicer.
That is definitely not platinum.
You really think this is a good idea?
Buddy, I honestly don't know,
but you're definitely
not gonna scare her off.
I say do whatever makes you happiest.
Jakey, you're the best.
Your body is trembling like a leaf.
I'm so excited.
Yes! Yes?
Yes!
Aww.
Charles is engaged.
You handled this really well, Peralta.
I take back what I said
about you being immature.
Oh, apology accepted, fart monster.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, boy.
Okay.
Yeah, this is turning into
a live sex show.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh, no.
I wasn't saying it in a bad way.
Jake!
Yep.
Although they can't see us.
- Jake!
- Yep.
Sync and corrections by parlobrito
web dl sync snarry