It's just
a tiny skin sample.
You saw me
do it to myself.
On a scale of one to ten,
where one is a pebble
in your shoe
and ten is the monkey
you thought was your pet
biting your face off.
A two.
Eating a whole Altoid?
Sheldon,
if I'm gonna synthesize
a neural network
from our skin cells,
I need to harvest them.
Now, I've done this dozens
of times, but if you're
too scared
you don't have to.
No, this is for science.
I can be brave
for science.
Thank you.
Oh, jiminy, that's cold!
Just think how happy
you'll be in a few weeks
when I've converted
our skin cells
into functional
brain cells.
All right, just warn me
before you do it.
Okay.
Three...
two...
and we're done.
You tricked me.
You didn't say one.
It didn't hurt, did it?
No...
but “three, two and we're done”
is incomplete.
You know those
things bother me.
It's like hearing
“da-da-da-da-da-dah”
without yelling...
Okay, fine, one.
Thank you.
Now yell “Charge” and
we can get out of here.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 10x08 ♪
The Brain Bowl Incubation
Original Air Da
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh, my God, I just got it.
Fun onions...
Funyuns.
Hold on.
Is that a wobble?
Yes.
That's definitely
a gravitational wobble.
Uh, sorry,
I could come back.
Oh, no, it's okay.
I-I just found a wobble.
Oh, do I need a mop?
It's a gravitational wobble.
It could be a sign
of an extrasolar planet
that may contain life
and someday be named after me.
Oh... well, if it has life,
maybe it already has a name,
huh?
Yeah, but it's probably
difficult to pronounce.
What is your name?
Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
You think it would be
more difficult than that?
Good point.
And you are?
Oh, uh, Issabella Maria
Concepcion.
Oh, well, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
You know, I have to say,
based on the candy wrappers
and the bags
of junk food I see
in this trash,
I thought the person
working here was ten years old.
Oh, please, show me
a ten-year-old who knows
to dip Tootsie Rolls in Nutella.
Bueno, um, I'm just going
to empty your waste paper basket
and then I'll get
out of your way.
Oh, please, allow me.
That's a lot of empty calories.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay, uh, okay,
I-I-I have to go.
- Okay.
- Good luck
with your, um,
space exploration.
Thank you.
Good luck with your...
future endeavors.
Did it work?
Are they brain cells yet?
If you'd give me a minute,
I'll tell you.
Oh, just let me look.
Oh, my goodness!
I see quivering black lines.
Those must be neurons.
Oh, they're so thick
and beautiful.
Those are your
eyelashes, move.
Well, Sheldon...
I see astrocytes.
Our combined skin cells are now
a primitive neural network.
I have such a profound
sense of creation.
I ju... it's like
when I hatched Sea-Monkeys,
except that this
is from my DNA,
so this is like...
Me-Monkeys.
These cells come
from both of us.
Yeah, but Us-Monkeys
doesn't pop.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wait!
We-Monkeys, there you go.
Hey.
When can we start
running tests on it?
No reason we can't
start right now.
What stimulus should we
introduce it to first?
L-Light, sound, temperature...
Oh! Oh! Let's
expose it to images
of me and you and see
who it likes better.
Sheldon, this is a rudimentary
collection of neurons.
I mean, it's remarkable,
but it's still limited
in what it can do.
I understand.
She's the mean one,
I'm the fun one.
Huh, they screwed up
and gave us steamed broccoli.
Oh, no, that's mine.
Really?
The last green thing
I saw you eat was a Skittle.
Well, I can't eat
like a ten-year-old
all the time.
You're dating somebody,
who is it?
What?
What are you talking about?
You only watch what you
eat when you're afraid
you might have
to take your shirt off.
No, she's right.
As long as I've known you,
you've always been
self-conscious
about your cleavage.
It's because you keep trying
to stick pencils in it.
All right, fine,
don't tell us.
There's nothing to tell.
All right.
How's that broccoli?
It's gross but I have to eat it
because I met somebody.
Bam.
Thank you.
What's her name?
Issabella.
Oh, did you meet
her at work?
Yes, in the telescope room.
Oh, so she's an astronomer?
Yes...
which is why she was
in the telescope room.
Yes, this is all making sense.
Good.
Well, that's great, Raj.
You must have
so much in common.
Mm-hmm.
So, when do we meet her?
No, no, this is brand-new.
We haven't even been
on a proper date yet.
Okay, well, good luck with it.
Thank you.
How come you
never eat broccoli?
I'm married,
I don't have to be attractive.
You know, most
people don't realize
this technique has
actually been around
for a few years.
Still, I can't believe
you can turn ordinary skin cells
into functioning brain cells.
Well, I turned this one
into a functioning boyfriend,
so sky's the limit.
Look, look... here I am
standing next
to the incubator.
Uh, here is a microscopic
view of the cells.
Look at that, put them in a tiny
Flash T-shirt and it's you.
Oh.
Yeah, this little guy
can already recognize
electronically
transmitted images
20% faster than any other
sample in Amy's lab.
I'm running out of ways
to act excited.
So, enough about us,
how are things going with you?
Great, the doctor
said the baby's head
is facing down now.
Good, you know,
in case the exit
isn't clearly marked.
Yeah, I have to say,
it is nice to share
this experience with someone
who's on the same journey.
Although right now ours
is testing off the charts
while yours is floating
around in its own waste.
Are you actually comparing
my human baby
to your brain in a bowl?
Well, I didn't
make you waddle up
four flights of stairs
for the heck of it.
You do realize my baby
has functioning organs
and can recognize voices.
Yeah, but ours can recognize
a specific data stream
among background noise.
Mine has a fully developed
immune system.
Ours doesn't need
an immune system
because it lives
in a state-of-the-art
German incubator.
Sheldon, that's enough.
Oh, yeah, no, fine.
Let's just agree
that both creations
are special in their own way
and it is foolish
to try and compare them.
Although, we didn't need
to have sex with Howard
for ours, so we win.
This is fun.
I have never cleaned
a toilet before.
You're kidding.
No, I grew up with a house
full of servants
and now I have
a cleaning lady...
who is a lovely woman
who I have great respect for.
It's okay, you're allowed
to have a cleaning lady.
Oh, good, because
she also walks my dog,
buys my groceries
and cuts my hair.
I think that's called a mommy.
Uh...
So, forgive me...
forgive me for being nosy,
but is-is there a wedding ring
under those pretty
rubber gloves?
No, not for many years.
Oh, so, you are unencumbered?
Just me and my son.
I love kids,
how old is he?
Nineteen.
That's a cute age.
They can do so many things.
He's studying to be
a lawyer at UCLA.
That's wonderful.
A lawyer, my sister's a lawyer.
Look at that,
we have something in common.
Yeah, I guess we do.
Maybe there are other things
we have in common.
C-Come dinnertime,
do you enjoy eating food?
Ay, Rajesh,
I think you're very sweet,
but
I work two jobs and I don't
have time for dating.
Yeah, sure. I understand.
Yeah, I'm very busy, too.
Oh, please don't take it
personal,
I think you're a very nice man.
I think you're very nice
as well.
Thank you for helping me.
Good night, Rajesh.
Oh, yes. Oh, okay.
Uh...
Good night.
I don't know,
maybe it's the fumes
from the urinal cakes,
but I feel like something
is happening between us.
Good night, Rajesh.
Okay. I'll leave.
But just know,
every time I come in here,
I'll be thinking of you.
Would you look at that?
The image we gave it
was 45% white noise,
and it still managed
to reconstruct it.
I've never seen results
like this before.
Yeah, we need to stop for
magnets on the way home;
this is going right
on the fridge.
Aren't you glad you
participated in this?
Oh, I am.
And you realize
what the next step is?
Set up
a second culture
and try to replicate
our results.
Uh, no.
We lock that door,
lower our underpants
a little and make a baby.
Make a baby?
What are you talking about?
Clearly the combination
of our DNA is exceptional.
Eh... Our child could be
the next step
in the evolution of mankind.
We... we'll be able to get
into any preschool we want!
Sh-Sheldon, I'm not ready
to have a baby.
Oh, yes, you are!
I track your cycle.
For the next 36 hours
you're as fertile
as a manure-covered wheat field.
Wow. I-I can actually feel
the egg crawling its way
back up.
I don't understand.
I thought you'd be thrilled
to procreate with me.
Not right now.
Oh,
I see what's happening here.
You're playing hard to get.
I'm not playing anything.
We're not making a baby today.
Very well.
Oops, how clumsy of me.
You know what? Let me get that.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I...
Did you even look at my bottom?
Welcome.
- What is this?
- Oh, well,
you said you didn't have time to
go out for dinner, so I thought
we could have one right here.
Oh, Rajesh...
Oh, come on!
We're in the telescope room!
It'll be like dining
under the stars.
Y-You see this, uh, double zero?
When it says “01,”
that means it's twinkling.
Sometimes it takes a while.
Rajesh, this is so sweet,
but you... you know I'm working.
That's why I already
cleaned up in here
and all the other rooms
in the hall.
Well, I suppose that gives me
a little time.
Oh, please sit!
I tried to cook you
a meal from your homeland.
Oh, really?
You made Cuban food?
That depends— do they have
Mexican food in Cuba?
Now, when he said “make a baby"
is it possible he
meant out of Legos?
No. He was explicit.
Needlessly
and freakishly explicit.
Why does he need a baby?
He's already hairless
and smells like talcum powder.
Could you two really
have some sort of
super-intelligent child?
Well, there is
a genetic component,
but that doesn't
guarantee anything.
That's true.
Sheldon's father
once picked a fight
with a cactus.
Yeah, but that's
just his Earth parents.
We don't know anything about
the ones that sent him here.
Well, we know they were
smart enough to send him away.
Hey, you're talking
about the person I love
and have been avoiding
for the past three hours.
Aw, man.
Ooh!
Sheldon gonna get some.
Well, have fun with
whatever nightmare's
behind door number two.
Well, hello.
Hello.
Would you care for a brandy?
I don't think so.
Good choice, it's disgusting.
Sheldon, please stop
trying to seduce me.
Who's trying to seduce you?
After a long day I always
turn on smooth jazz
and spray deer musk
on my inner thighs.
I thought it smelled
like a petting zoo in here.
Anything you'd like to pet?
Not my hair. There's
a lot of goop in it.
Okay, I've had enough.
Amy, come back.
I don't know
how to open the oysters.
So, um, what
surprised you the most
when you first
came to America?
Well, I suppose
how much people care
about Oprah's favorite things.
I thought that, too.
But then I got
my first waffle maker
and never questioned her again.
You know,
I do have some time off
this Sunday
- if you'd like to...
- Hey! I saw your car...
Oh, sorry.
Am I interrupting?
Uh...
It's okay.
Uh, I should get back to work.
Hi. Howard Wolowitz.
Oh. Issabella Concepcion.
Oh, yeah, the astronomer.
Raj told us
about you.
Hey! Free toilet paper!
You told him
I was an astronomer?
Uh...
I understand.
Time to go.
No, p-please don't.
It's okay, Rajesh,
I'm a grown woman.
I don't have to waste my time
with someone
who's embarrassed by me.
I can keep this, right?
Issabella!
Issabella, wait,
wait, let me explain.
If you are embarrassed
by what I do,
why did you pursue me?
I'm sorry.
Honestly, I-I didn't think
your job would bother me,
but I guess it did.
And I hate myself for that.
But there's
a lot of things
about me that would
totally embarrass you.
I doubt that.
Well, prepare to be mortified.
I let my dog eat food out
of my mouth,
not because she likes it
but because I do.
Also, I know they're pretty,
but I'm scared of butterflies.
Sorry, just
passing through.
I think this fell off your cart.
Come on. What do you say?
Let me make it up to you.
You're very persistent.
It's my one move.
Okay.
This Sunday night,
you may take me to dinner
at a nice restaurant.
Great.
Where would you like to go?
Your choice.
It can be Pakistani food,
if you like.
Excuse me, but I'm Indian.
And now you know how it feels.
So, were you turned
on even a little bit?
It was like
being hit on
by Rat Pack Pee-wee Herman.
I'm sorry, is that a yes?
No!
Amy,
I didn't want it
to come to this.
But you have left me no choice
but to employ
the most passionate,
seductive dance known to man.
The flamenco.
For God's sake,
you're ridiculous.
You guys are aroused, right?
That was a close one.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man