- Attention, everyone!
Say good-bye to the Jake Peralta
you know and love,
for today is the day
I forever change.
- Ooh, are you finally
growing a mustache?
- No, you know
I can't do that,
and it's cruel of you
to keep bringing it up.
This envelope contains the
inheritance my uncle left me.
He died a year ago;
he was so rich,
he had a whole room
in his house just to eat in.
- You mean like
a dining room?
- Yeah, but in Manhattan.
- Oh, dang.
- Now, just because
I'm definitely rich now
doesn't mean I'm gonna
forget my roots.
You all get something,
so fire away.
- Jake, your friendship
is gift enough for me.
- Friendship is crap.
I want a Ducati Monster 821.
- All right,
Rosa gets a motorcycle.
- Oh, cool.
I want a fast sports car.
- Come on.
You can be honest.
- I want old, expensive books.
I'll send you a list.
- There you go.
Now, let's find out
what I'm worth.
Oh, I'm too nervous to open it.
Sarge, you do it.
- Okay.
It's stock.
One million shares!
- Oh, my God!
- Of Blockbuster Video stock.
all: Ohh.
- What? Is that bad?
I still have
a Blockbuster card!
What happened to Blockbuster?
[upbeat music]
♪
[funky music]
- Mapping, mapping,
mapping, mapping,
mapping, mapping.
- What's going on
there, buddy?
- Just making a final
imprint of your face
before the LASIK surgery
goes poorly
and my eyeballs
get burned off.
- Why stop at the eyes?
Burn off your whole head.
- Charles, the surgery
is going to go fine, all right?
You'll have some vision
impairment for a few hours,
and I'm gonna be with you
the whole time!
Plus, they're gonna give you
some of those sweet-ass
Robocop sunglasses.
- Those are blind people
sunglasses.
- Captain.
What are you doing here?
Thought you took the day off
to pack for your big trip,
or did you finally realize
that it only takes
one minute to pack?
- Not if you care
about your possessions
and what the world sees
when they look at you.
- Huh.
- I'm not going.
Cheddar's regular
dog sitter is ill,
and the heat's out
in my house,
so I don't think
it's a good time for me
to visit Kevin in Paris.
- Sir, you can't
just cancel your trip.
You guys haven't seen
each other in months.
How about this:
Amy and I
will look after your house
while you're gone.
Right, Ames?
- Totally.
- I thought you two were
watching Ray Charles Boyle.
- Good point.
Charles can come with us
and look after Cheddar.
I'm told that blind people
have a special connection
with dogs.
- I knew it.
You do think I'm gonna go blind.
- That's an interesting offer,
but I don't want to be
an imposition.
- Pshaw!
Imposition? Pshaw!
- No, I was talking
to Santiago.
I assume she'll be
doing all the work.
- Why?
Oh, because of our track records
and personalities.
Sure, sure, sure, sure, yeah.
- So, Santiago, are you sure
you're okay with this?
- I'm so in.
This is gonna be fantastic.
This is horrible!
We're not ready for this.
This is a level one
responsibility.
I'm a level two at best,
and you're not even a level!
- Well, I'm a level,
you know.
I'm probably, like,
a level five.
- Not a level.
- I thought
you'd be psyched.
I mean, a week
at Captain Holt's house?
Wasn't that where you wanted
to spend your honeymoon?
- Yeah, but this
is too much pressure!
Why did you volunteer
us for this?
- Because Holt hasn't
seen Kevin in, like, months,
and I was just thinking
if that was me and you,
it would make me really sad.
- Oh.
That's actually super sweet.
- Plus, there's this
big, fat binder
full of instructions
and rules.
- There's a binder?
Why didn't you lead
with that, you idiot?
Oh!
- How about I just
leave you two alone?
- Okay.
- Diaz.
- Pimento.
What's up?
- What's up with you?
I need you to sign this report.
- Okay.
I'll sign your report.
- Mm.
- What the hell?
- Careful.
The ink's still wet.
- Maybe this'll help.
- Okay, they got
to knock that off.
- Loosen up, Sarge.
- Summer of love, baby.
- It's March, man.
Shut up.
- It's true what they say.
Now that I'm fully
blind forever,
my other senses
are heightened.
I feel a door.
[gasps]
We're at Captain Holt's house.
- Also, the GPS announced it
when we pulled up.
Hey, once we're inside,
maybe keep your hands
to yourself, all right?
The captain can be very
particular about his stuff.
- Cheddar! Let go!
Let go of it!
- Amy?
- This is a cashmere sweater!
[sneezes]
Oh, my stupid allergies!
He got into Kevin's closet.
He was supposed
to stay downstairs.
The binder was very clear
about that.
Why won't you respect
the binder?
- Oh, no, he's turning
all the turtlenecks
into regular necks.
Charles, you got to help us.
- On it.
Okay, the key with dogs
is establishing the alpha.
Cheddah, dwop it.
Pwease dwop it.
I'll give you
anything you want.
- Oh, Cheddar is the alpha.
Didn't expect that.
- Pwease, pwease, pwease.
- [sighs]
- Nice job, Boyle.
It worked.
- But the mess, Jake.
The mess!
- Don't worry.
We're gonna clean it up.
Everything is totally
under control.
- Charles' pants are on fire.
- What?
Boyle, the space heater!
Get away from the space heater!
- I don't know where it is!
[smoke alarm beeping]
I'm just gonna run
at full speed!
- No!
- Aah!
- Charles, just stay
where you are!
I got it.
[grunting]
Whoo!
Okay.
It's okay.
Everything's fine.
Fire's out.
And this table is—
- Oh!
- Fragile.
I was gonna say fragile.
Nailed it.
- Ah!
- You punching holes?
- Yeah.
- That's way too much paper.
- Not for me.
- Can't even get
a cup of coffee.
- [grunts]
Well, I'm off to find
some yellow paper
so I can do this
all over again.
- All right, Diaz?
That's it.
What's going on
with you two?
- Oh, you noticed it?
- Yeah, I noticed it!
Everyone's noticed it!
A convicted pervert asked me
if you guys could cool it.
- I don't know
what to tell you.
Something between us, Sarge.
Something dark and urgent.
- Ah.
Okay.
Great news.
The smell of burnt sweatpants
and singed leg hair
is finally dissipating.
- I just hope I can
grow it back by Speedo season.
[phone rings]
- Call from Raymond Holt,
mobile.
- Oh, no. Not Holt.
- Don't worry.
I've got this.
- Bonjour, Captain.
Voulez-vous coucher avec moi?
- No, I don't
want to sleep with you.
- Is that what that means?
Oh, man, I had a really gross
tennis instructor.
- I'm calling to check in
before I get on the flight.
Everything okay?
- [scoffs] Okay?
Let's just say if the house
could talk, she would say,
"I've never been happier;
I love Jake."
- Oh, that's interesting,
because I think
the house might say
"Jake's a liar, and I'm...
on fire."
- What's that now?
- The security company
called me about the alarm.
- Okay, the house
was never on fire.
Charles was on fire,
and only on his pants,
and we put it out.
- I'm coming home right now.
- Wait, no.
Sir, please don't do that.
You have to go see Kevin.
Everything's fine.
- No, my decision is final.
I'm postponing my flight.
Good-bye, Jacob.
- No, sir!
Please, please—ahh!
He said "Jacob."
It's biblical.
Guys, guys!
Holt is headed home
right now.
- No!
He can't come home.
We left the door open,
and the dog ran out.
- What? We lost Cheddar?
- These silences
are very hard for me to read.
What's the vibe in here?
- We're freaking out, Charles!
What we have here
is a fugitive situation.
Our man has been on the run
for 30 minutes.
Also,
our man is a dog.
Now, I know what
some of you are thinking:
"Who cares?
It's just a pet."
- No one was thinking that,
you monster.
- Good.
That was a test.
Now, the average foot speed
of a corgi
is ten miles per hour,
which means
with every passing second,
that slippery bastard
gets farther away.
[mellow music]
- Captain Holt does not know
Cheddar is missing...
but he's gonna find out.
Oh, God, I feel like the devil
is dancing on my chest.
- It's all right, Amy.
We have time.
Gina's picking Holt up
at the airport,
and she told me she can stall
him for at least two hours.
- I'll do it, but I'm gonna
have to total your car.
- Or you could just
drive slowly.
- Ha-ha, she's gonna
wreck your car.
- Here's where we're at.
Amy and I will take
Blind Charles
and search the neighborhood.
Diaz, Pimento—
- Bring the dog back,
dead or alive.
- What? No.
I was gonna say hang posters.
Terry, maybe go with them,
make sure nobody gets killed.
- Or maybe I could
join another group
with a different kind of energy?
- Jake, what about
me and Hitchcock?
- You two grab Cheddar's treats
and put 'em in a bowl outside.
- You mean the little sausage
ones that need way more salt?
- On second thought, maybe just
sit exactly where you are
and don't touch anything.
- Sweet.
- All right, everyone,
it's time to do this.
For Captain Holt,
for Kevin, for America!
- Let's go, Nine-Nine!
[groans]
- This line is interminable.
At this rate,
we'll be home in 54 minutes
instead of the usual 46.
- Not if I have
anything to do with it.
Watch me now!
[tires squealing]
- No, Gina, the wrong way.
No, Gina, the spikes!
- Uh-oh.
Well, not a problem.
I can get you home
on two wheels.
[tires pop]
And that was
the second pair of tires.
- Mm.
- I could've done that.
- Yeah, I know you could've.
But you didn't.
I did.
- I mean, there are lots
of other poles, guys.
A whole street
full of 'em.
- So, Adrian,
when are we gonna
stop messing around
and do this thing?
- Um...
N-never.
- What?
- You know what?
I just realized.
I forgot something at home.
I'm just gonna—
- That was weird.
You okay?
- Yes.
[grunting]
- All right,
according to the call
we just got on the tip line,
someone said they saw
Cheddar on this block.
- I'll head north.
Jake, you head west.
We'll meet back
in a half hour.
- Great, which direction
should I go?
[both mouthing words]
What's going on?
I can hear your lips moving.
Ah!
Are you guys kissing?
- What? No.
Charles, stop always
asking that.
Look, I'm sorry,
but you have to stay in the car.
- That's a mistake!
My super senses are a tool
you can't afford to leave
in the tool chest.
Take me out of the box
and put me on your belt.
- I'm sorry, but you'd
only slow us down.
And that's exactly
what Cheddar wants.
That's right.
I'm onto you,
you slippery little bastard.
[mellow music]
- Gina, come on.
You can do your Internet
socializing in the truck.
- Okay, cool, I just have
to tie my shoe real quick.
Tying it.
Call Jake Peralta.
- Gina, hey,
how's the stalling?
- Great; the tow truck
just got here,
so that'll buy us
at least an hour.
- Tow truck? What the hell
did you do to my car?
- Bitch, I told you
I was gonna wreck it.
- You did.
You did.
All right, well,
we're about to go
follow up on a lead
right now.
- Great; I'm gonna rip a bunch
of wires out of your dashboard.
- What? No, don't!
Gina—
Gah!
- I got nothing.
Did you find Cheddar?
- Close.
I found Shredder.
- Shredder, no!
No, Shredder!
- You're not Cheddar!
I know it looks bad,
but we're gonna find him.
Right after we find Charles.
Charles is gone.
We lost Charles.
- What?
- Charles? Charles!
[toy squeaks]
Here, boy!
He's so pocket-sized.
He could be hidden anywhere!
- Jake, we need
to focus on Cheddar.
Charles is a grown man.
He can take care of himself.
- No, he's not.
He's a Charles, all right?
And he's blind!
Oh, God,
he's probably already dead.
- Right? So let's not waste
any resources on him.
[cell phone rings]
- Wait, it's Charles.
Charles?
- Jake? Is that you?
I can't see my phone.
I've dialed
over 40 wrong numbers.
- It's me.
- I found Cheddar.
- He found Cheddar!
- Which is why I was like,
"We need to go to him."
- Charles, where are you?
- I've got him cornered
in some bushes,
but I don't know
where I am, and my—
[train horn blows]
- Wait, stop talking.
I'm hearing something
in the background.
What is that, a train
and a girl whimpering?
- That's me; I'm so scared
you're not gonna find me.
- Charles, don't move.
I know exactly where you are.
He's at the entrance
by 7th Street.
I used to hang out there
all the time.
- Doing what?
- Aw!
I boofed it.
Nothing. Cool stuff.
Having sex.
Anyways, it doesn't matter.
Let's go.
- Aah!
- Hey, Sarge.
I've been waiting for you.
- In here?
- Yeah, I wanted to have
a private conversation.
Do you think Diaz noticed
that I freaked out a little
when she asked me out?
- You mean the way your eyes
popped out of your head
and you sprinted away
at full speed?
Yeah, I think she noticed.
- Damn it.
I'm in kind of a weird
head space right now.
I've got a lot on my plate,
emotionally speaking.
And flirting's one thing,
but a relationship?
- Well...
- The last time I let myself
fall for someone was Katya.
She was a bartender
at the Garbage Box,
second-rate strip club my mob
buddies and I used to go to.
She was a sweet girl, but I
couldn't save her from the pole.
- Oh, she started stripping?
- Nope.
Boss impaled her on a pole when
he caught her skimming tips.
- Ooh! Damn, dude.
Look, coming back
from 12 years undercover
is not easy for anyone.
I'm sure Diaz gets it.
- She's so in touch
with her feelings.
And me, hmm.
After what I've seen,
after what I've done,
I don't know that
I deserve to be happy.
- Of course you do.
- Huh.
I never looked at it
that way.
Wow.
That changes everything.
[chuckles]
Ha!
- I never even
finished my point.
- No, Sarge,
you said it all.
You just changed my life.
- He's got to be here somewhere.
- What's up, Peralta?
Want to jump in
on this tasty sesh?
- Uh, you got the wrong guy.
I've never seen you before.
Heh, dumb stoner.
- He referred to you by name.
- Hey, there's Charles.
- Jake? Jake?
- Charles, we're behind you.
- Look!
I found Cheddar.
I found him.
- Oh, God.
- I know.
Pretty impressive, right?
It's a proud day
for blind people everywhere.
- Charles—
- It wasn't easy, though.
This guy put up quite a fight.
But we're
good friends now, right?
Right?
You gave me a bunch of kisses.
You gave me
a bunch of kisses.
- Damn it, Charles,
it's a possum.
- Oh, no.
- Mercifully, the tires
have been replaced,
so may I please
have the keys?
- Okay, but before we go,
can we just choose
a nice air freshener
from the gift shop?
You never know when you're gonna
find your signature scent.
- I'm not an idiot, Gina;
I know for a fact
you've already found
your signature scent.
- Ugh! I have got to stop
living my life out loud.
- I've had a hell of a day.
I've got a lot
going on in my life,
more than Peralta
ruining my house,
so can we please
drop the charade
so I can get home already?
- Absolutely, sir.
Wait, I should tell you.
Before you got real with me...
I did rip out
all these wires.
- All right, everyone,
listen up.
Here's where we're at.
Bad news:
Cheddar is still at large,
and you know
that slippery little bastard
is just laughing at us.
[mellow music]
We need a new plan,
and we need it now.
- Because the walls are
closing in and I can't breathe.
- Come on, guys,
we're just spitballing.
There's no stupid ideas.
- What if we walk
around the neighborhood
in Captain Holt's clothes,
wait till Cheddar
picks up the smell?
- No, that's insane,
never gonna happen.
Anyone else?
- You guys go off the grid.
- I'm listening. Go on.
- I get you guys
Mexican passports.
Totally untraceable.
We fake your death
in an apartment fire.
I'll need three teeth
from both of you.
Then you guys just disappear.
It's easy.
I've done it before.
- Oh, have you?
Because you haven't
mentioned it 500 times.
Get a new thing.
- Okay.
Amazingly, wearing Holt's
clothes is our best option.
Everyone, prepare
to enter high society.
[regal classical music]
♪
Okay, how's everybody feeling?
Anyone else have the weird urge
to lecture themselves?
"Peralta, what are you doing?"
- Peralta, what are you doing?
- I conjured him.
Captain Holt!
What a pleasant surprise.
Gina told me that you were
delayed due to a wire situation.
- Yes, the situation is,
you can rip them all out
but the car still works.
- Sorry, boo.
- Wait, why is
the whole squad here?
And why is everyone
wearing my clothes?
My God.
You lost Cheddar.
- How did you do that?
but I promise you
we can find Cheddar
and you can still
go to Paris.
- I'm not going to Paris.
Now, get out of my clothes.
Get into your clothes.
Get out of my house.
Get into your cars—
- All right, we can
take it from there.
Loud and clear.
Once again, so sorry.
[sighs]
- Oh, he's so disappointed.
- Look, I'm sorry that
I got you involved in this.
I never should have
volunteered us.
- No, Jake.
It's not your fault.
It's Amy's.
- What?
- Well, it's not my fault.
Blind.
- Ugh.
- And Jake's not the one
who let Cheddar
go to town
on Kevin's sweaters.
- Please, it's not like
I fed him Kevin's sweaters.
- Wait a minute, guys.
I think this is Kevin's fault.
- No, Jake, it's Amy's.
I know you're trying
to be a cool boyfriend—
yet another reason
why it's not your fault—
but Kevin's in Paris.
- Exactly, and that's why
I think it's Kevin's fault.
I have an idea
of how to find Cheddar.
Amy, don't act weird
when I say this,
but we're gonna need
to use the binder.
- Oh, Mama.
- Diaz!
Could we talk?
- What do you want, Pimento?
- Listen, Sarge gave me
some really great advice.
So, Rosa Diaz,
will you marry me?
both: What?
- This is what
you told me to do!
- I barely said anything!
You cut me off
way too early.
- Sarge, stay out of this.
- Gladly.
- No, I will not
marry you.
How about we just
get a drink first?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that sounds nice.
- Oh, that's
actually sweet.
Nope.
- Oh, there he is.
Captain Holt!
Oh, he can't hear me.
[car alarm blaring]
Eh...
[car alarm blares]
Okay, well, I guess we know
what those wires did.
- I'm not in the mood
for your antics, Peralta.
- Sir, sir!
I think we know
where Cheddar is.
Will you please
just get in the car?
- [sighs]
- Oh, let me get that.
Try now.
Oh, I can't control
the locks.
Hang on. Try now.
One, two, three.
Try now. Try now.
Here we come, Cheddar!
Try now.
- Cheddar!
Come here, baby.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
How did you know
he was here?
- Well, Cheddar was only
chewing up Kevin's stuff.
I figured maybe
he was acting out
because he missed Kevin.
- But the real hero here
is the binder.
Under "Cheddar,"
subsection "Walk,"
subsection "Walks with Kevin,"
we found this special spot.
- So you're missing Kevin, huh?
You're not the only one.
[sighs]
I didn't cancel my trip
because I was worried
you would burn my house down.
Kevin and I are having
a hard time right now.
Whenever we talk,
we fight.
And I'm just afraid
and just—
just afraid that if I go
to Paris and we fight, then...
- Sir, with all due respect,
that's crazy.
I mean, you and Kevin
are the best couple I know.
And I'm sure whatever this is,
you can get through it,
because you are
the strongest person I know.
Wow, that was weird;
I said, like, multiple
real things
consecutively, yeah.
Felt weird but good.
Are you proud of me?
- You're ruining it.
- Yup.
I'm just gonna
stop talking now.
- Well, I suppose
I'm not gonna solve anything
by running away from it.
Perhaps I should go
to Paris.
What do you think, Cheddar?
Huh?
Oh, my, oh!
You really are acting out!
Whew!
I'm sorry you had to see that.
- Oh.
- You know,
it's moments like these
that I'm grateful for your—
[car alarm blaring]
- Guys, it's a miracle!
I can see!
- Not now, Charles!
- Shut up!
- Right, sorry!
[car alarm blaring]
Sorry.
- Fremulon.
- Not a doctor.
- Shh.