Okay, okay, I checked.
We have Earl Grey, English Breakfast,
cinnamon stick,
chamomile, mint medley,
blackberry and, uh…
Oh, wait, there's one more…
Lemon soother.
You're not the guy that asked
for the tea, are you?
Okay.
Mail call.
Rachel Green, bunk seven.
Thank you.
Oh, cool. A free sample of coffee.
Oh, good, because where else
would we get any? Ha, ha.
Oh, right.
- Oh, great.
- What is it?
Country club newsletter.
My mother sends me the engagement
notices for inspiration.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. It's Barry and Mindy.
- Barry, who you almost…
- Barry, who I almost…
- Mindy, your maid of…
- My maid of…
Let me see. That's Mindy?
Wow, she is pretty.
Lucky…
…to have had a friend like you.
Marcel, bring me the rice.
Come on.
Good boy.
Come here, give me the rice.
Thank you. Good boy.
I see he's mastered the difference
between "bring me the"…
and "pee in the."
"Bring me the" and… Rach?
- What?
- Hi.
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is so stupid.
I mean, I gave Barry up, right?
I should be happy for them.
I am. I'm happy for them.
- Really?
- No.
I guess it would be different
if I were with somebody.
What…
What happened to
"Forget relationships.
I'm done with men"?
The whole, uh, penis embargo?
I don't know.
I guess it's not about no guys.
It's about the right guy, you know?
With Barry, it was safe and it
was easy, but there was no heat.
You know, with Paolo
that's all there was, was heat.
And I mean, it was just this raw,
animal, sexual…
Right, right. I got it.
I was there.
I mean, do you think
you can ever have both?
You know?
Someone who's like your best friend,
but then also can make
your toes curl.
Yes, yes.
Yes. Yes, I do. I really do.
In fact, it's funny.
Very often, someone who
you wouldn't think could…
Curl your toes…
…might just be the one who…
- Hi.
- Gets interrupted. Hi.
Hey, guys, how was the movie?
- So wonderful!
- It was so good!
- Suck fest.
- Total chick flick.
I'm sorry it wasn't
one of those movies
with, like, you know, like,
guns and bombs
and, like, buses going really fast.
Hey, I don't need violence
to enjoy a movie,
just so long
as there's a little nudity.
- There was nudity.
- I meant female nudity.
All right, I don't need to see
Lou Grant frolicking.
Hugh. Hugh Grant.
All right, I've got to go.
Come on, Marcel. Come on.
Yeah, we're gonna go take a bath.
Yes, we are, aren't we?
They're still just friends, right?
- And I will see you tomorrow.
- That's right.
You're gonna spend tomorrow
at Aunt Rachel's, aren't you?
Hang on, hang on.
Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
Please, Aunt Monica, please?
Unclench.
You're not even gonna be here.
I can't believe
we're having this discussion.
I agree.
I'm, like, in disbelief.
Don't you think if things
were gonna happen with Rachel,
they would've happened?
I'm telling you, she said
she's looking for a relationship
with someone exactly like me.
She really said that?
Well, I added
the "exactly like me" part.
But she said she's looking
for someone.
And someone
is gonna be there tonight.
"Tonight" tonight?
Well, I think it's perfect.
It's just gonna be the two of us.
She spent all day
taking care of my monkey.
I can't remember the last time
I got a girl
to take care of my monkey.
Anyway, I figured after work,
I'd go pick up a bottle of wine,
go over there and
try to woo her.
Hey, you know what you should do?
You should take her back to the 1890s
when that phrase was last used.
If you keep this up, honey, I swear
you'll be finished with this sucker
by the end of the week.
Now, the one in the feathered boa,
that's Dr. Francis.
Now, she used to be a man.
Oh, look. See, now, there's Raven.
We hate her.
We're glad she's dying.
And then… What? Marcel.
Are you playing with Monica's shoes?
You know you're not supposed to…
Marcel, did you poo in the shoe?
Marcel. Bad monkey.
Oh, God.
Sorry, Barry.
A little engagement gift.
I'm sure you didn't register
for that.
Who died? Who died?
Roll him over.
Oh, come on, roll him over.
Well, we know it wasn't Dexter,
right, Marcel? Because…
Marcel? Marcel?
- How could you lose him?
- I don't know.
We were watching TV, and then
he pooped in Monica's shoe…
Wait. He pooped in my shoe?
Which one?
I don't know. The left one.
Which ones?
Those little clunky Amish things
you think go with everything.
- Hey.
Why is the air in here so negative?
- Rachel lost Marcel.
- No. How?
- He pooped in my shoe.
- Which one?
Those cute little black ones
I wear all the time.
No, which one?
The right or left?
Because the left one is lucky.
Come on, you guys.
What am I gonna do?
All right, all right, all right.
You're a monkey,
you're loose in the city.
Where do you go?
Okay, it's his first time out,
so he's probably gonna want
to do some of the touristy things.
I'll go to Cats.
You go to the Russian Tea Room.
Oh, my God! Come on, you guys.
He's gonna be home any minute.
He's gonna kill me.
Start with the building.
You take the first and second floor.
Phoebe and I will take third
and fourth.
What am I gonna do?
You stay here
and just wait by the phone.
Spray Lysol in my shoe
and wait for Ross to kill you.
Does anybody want to trade?
What do you want?
Mr. Heckles, our friend lost
a monkey. Have you seen it?
I left a Belgian waffle out here.
Did you take it?
No.
Why would you leave
your Belgian waffle in the hall?
I wasn't ready for it.
The monkey,
have you seen a monkey?
I saw Regis Philbin once.
Thank you, Mr. Heckles.
You owe me a waffle.
Okay, he's a black capuchin monkey
with a white face
with Russian dressing
and pickles on the side.
Okay, thanks.
- Hi.
- Hey. How did it go today?
- Great. It went great. Really great.
- Yeah.
- Hey, is that wine?
- Yeah. Yeah.
You, uh, want some?
- I would love some.
- Yeah.
But you know what?
Let's not drink it here.
I'm feeling kind of crazy.
Do you want to go to Newark?
Uh, okay. Yeah.
We could do that.
But before we head off to the
murder capital of the Northeast,
I was, uh, kind of wanted
to run something by you.
You know how we were,
you know, talking before
about relationships and stuff,
well…
- G od, Ross, I cannot do this.
- Okay, quick and painful.
Oh, God.
Okay, all right. All right, okay.
Ross, please don't hate me.
Oh, what? What? What?
You know Marcel?
- Yeah?
- Well…
I kind of… I kind of lost him.
I can't believe this.
I mean, all I asked you to do
was keep him in the apartment.
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
You know what?
I guess it's partially my fault.
I shouldn't have asked you
to start off with a monkey.
I should have started you off with,
like, a pen or a pencil.
Ross,
I'm doing everything that I can.
I've got everybody looking
for him and I got…
- Who is it?
- Animal Control.
- See, I've even got Animal Control.
- You called Animal Control?
Why? Do you not like them?
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
I'm not allowed
to have him in the city.
If they find him,
they'll take him away from me.
Okay, well, now, see,
you never ever, ever told us that.
Because I didn't expect you we're
gonna invite them to the apartment.
Hi. Thanks for coming.
Somebody called about a monkey?
You know what?
That was a complete misunderstanding.
Yeah, we thought we had a monkey,
but we didn't.
- It turned out it was a hat.
- Cat.
Cat. What did I say?
Hi. We checked
the third and fourth floor.
- No one's seen Marcel.
- Marcel?
My uncle Marcel.
Oh, is that who the monkey's
named after?
Okay.
Are you aware that possession
of an illegal exotic is punishable
by up to two years in prison
and confiscation of the animal.
Oh, my God.
You'd put that poor little creature
in jail?
Pheebs, you remember
how we talked about
saying things quietly
to yourself first?
Yes, but there isn't always time.
Look, I'm sure there's some friendly
way to reconcile this.
Have a seat.
First of all, we haven't been
introduced. I'm Monica Geller.
Oh, my God, you are.
- And you're Rachel Green.
- Yeah.
Luisa Gianetti. Lincoln High?
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
Luisa. Oh, my God.
Monica. It's Luisa!
Luisa. From homeroom.
Yes!
You have no idea who
I am, do you?
- No.
- Not at all.
Well, maybe that's because
you spent four years ignoring me.
Would it have been so hard to say,
"Morning, Luisa".
Or "Nice overalls"?
I'm so sorry.
It's not so much you. You were fat.
You had your own problems.
But you. What a bitch.
What?
You know what? Be that as it may.
You think you could you help us
out here on that monkey thing,
for old times' sake?
Go, Bobcats.
I could.
But I won't.
If I find that monkey, he's mine.
Sorry.
Marcel?
- Marcel?
Hi, can I help you?
We're kind of having
an emergency, and…
we were looking for something.
- A monkey.
- Yes, have you seen any?
No. No, I haven't seen a monkey.
Do you know anything
about fixing radiators?
Sure, sure. Did you try turning
the knob back the other way?
- Of course.
- Then, no.
Taste this daiquiri.
Is there too much rum in here?
Just a second.
Hope you find your monkey.
Oh, no, wait.
No, no, no. Wait, wait.
We may not know
about radiators, per se,
but we do have a certain amount
of expertise
in the heating and cooling milieu.
Weren't we kind of in the middle
of something here?
Yes, but these women are very hot
and they need our help.
And they're very hot.
We can't, all right?
We're sorry.
You have no idea how sorry. But
we promised we'd find this monkey.
If you see him, he's about yea high
and answers to the name Marcel.
So if we could get some pictures of
you, you'd really be helping us out.
Okay, from now on, you don't get
to talk to other people.
- Marcel?
- Marcel.
Marcel?
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Something just brushed up
against my right leg.
What is it?
Oh, it's okay.
It was just my left leg.
Look, Phoebe.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, Marcel. Come here.
- Come here, Marcel.
- Step aside, ladies.
- What are you gonna do?
- Just a small tranquilizer.
Run, Marcel, run!
Run, Marcel!
- Damn.
- Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Oh, gosh.
Marcel. Marcel.
This is ridiculous.
We've been all over the neighborhood.
He's gone. He's just gone.
- Ross, you don't know that.
- Oh, come on. It's cold, it's dark.
He doesn't know the Village.
And now I have a broken foot.
Oh, my…
I have no monkey and a broken foot.
Thank you very much.
Ross, you know, I've said I'm sorry,
like, a million times.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to break my foot too?
Here, I'm gonna break my foot
right now.
Oh, my God.
There, are you happy now?
Yeah, yeah. You know,
now that you kicked the sign…
I don't miss Marcel anymore.
You know, it's not like
I did this on purpose.
No. This is just vintage Rachel.
I mean, things just sort of happen
around you.
I mean, you're off in Rachel Land,
doing your Rachel thing,
totally oblivious to people's monkeys
or to people's feelings and…
- I don't even want to hear it.
- Ross.
- Forget it, okay?
What? What?
Hey, banana man.
This is so intense.
One side of my butt is totally asleep
and the other side has no idea.
Hi. Did you order some bananas?
- What about it?
- Give me my monkey back.
I don't have a monkey.
- Then what's with all the bananas?
- Potassium.
Marcel? Marcel.
Okay, where is he? Where is he?
Marcel? Marcel?
Marcel.
What have you done to him?
That's my monkey. That's Patty.
Patty the monkey.
Are you insane?
- Come here, Marcel. Come on.
- Come here, Patty.
Come here, Marcel.
Come here, Patty.
Here, monkey. Here, monkey.
Here, monkey.
Gotcha.
- Okay, give me my monkey back.
- That's my monkey.
You're gonna have to take this up
with the judge.
That's not my monkey.
Just the dress is mine.
You can send it back whenever.
- All right, I want my monkey.
- No.
- Come on, Luisa.
- Sorry, prom queen.
You had to be a bitch in high school,
you couldn't have been fat.
All right, look, in high school,
I was the prom queen
and I was the homecoming queen
and the class president and you…
…were also there.
Look, if you take this monkey
I will lose one of the most
important people in my life.
You can hate me if you want,
but please do not punish him.
Come on, Luisa, you have a chance
to be the bigger person here.
Take it.
No.
All right.
Well, then how about I call
your supervisor and I tell her
that you shot my friend
in the ass with a dart.
Hey, it'll be nice to get this off
finally, won't it?
Or we can leave it on for now.
That's fine.
You know,
with the right pair of pumps,
that would be a great little outfit.
Listen…
I'm sorry I was so hard
on you before. You know, I just…
No, Ross. No, no. It was my fault.
I almost lost your…
No. Yeah, but you were the one
who got him back.
You know, you were great.
Hey, we still have that bottle
of wine.
Are you in the mood for…
…something grape?
- Sure, that would be good.
- All right.
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
Well, ah, as long as we're here…
and not on the subject…
I was thinking about…
…how mad we got at each
other before.
And I was thinking maybe
it was partially because of how we…
- Rachel?
- Barry?
I can't. I can't do it.
I can't marry Mindy.
I'm still in love with you.
We have got to start
locking that door.
This is me in The Sound of Music.
- You see the von Trapp kids?
- No.
That's because I'm in front of them.
Yeah, I thought that was an alp.
Well, high school
was not my favorite time.
I don't know. I loved high school,
you know?
It was just, like, four years
of parties and dating and sex and…
Yeah, well, I went to boarding school
with 400 boys.
Any sex I had would've involved
a major lifestyle choice.
Gosh, doesn't it seem like
a million years ago?
My butt cheek is waking up.