Guys? There's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
Wait. What is that?
That would be Marcel.
You wanna say hi?
No. No, I don't.
He is precious.
Where did you get him?
My friend Bethel rescued him
from some lab.
That is so cruel.
Why? Why would a parent
name their child Bethel?
That monkey's got a Ross
on his ass.
Ross, is he gonna live with you
in your apartment?
Yeah. It's been kind of quiet
since Carol left, so…
Why don't you just get a roommate?
I don't know.
You reach a certain age,
having a roommate
is just kind of pathe…
Sorry, that's "pathet,"
which is Sanskrit
for "really cool way to live."
You guys,
I'm doing all-new material tonight.
I have 12 new songs
about my mother's suicide,
and one about a snowman.
Might want to open
with the snowman.
- Hey, Joey.
- Hey.
- Hey, Joe.
- So how'd it go?
I didn't get the job.
How could you not get it?
You were Santa last year.
I don't know. Some fat guy's
sleeping with the store manager.
He's not even jolly.
It's all political.
- So, what are you gonna be?
- I'm gonna be one of his helpers.
It's just such a slap in the face.
Do you guys know
what you're doing for New Year's?
Gee, what?
What is wrong with New Year's?
Nothing for you. You have Paolo.
You don't have to face the horrible
pressures of this holiday,
desperate scramble
to find anything with lips,
just so can have somebody to kiss
when the ball drops.
Man, I'm talking loud.
For your information, Paolo's
gonna be in Rome this New Year's.
So I'll be just as pathetic
as the rest of you.
Yeah, you wish.
It's just that I'm sick of being
a victim of this Dick Clark holiday.
I say this year, no dates,
we make a pact.
Just the six of us. Dinner.
- Sure.
- Fine.
I was hoping
for a little more enthusiasm.
Okay.
- Phoebe, you're on.
- Oh, good.
Okay, hi. Ladies and gentlemen,
back by popular demand
Miss Phoebe Buffay.
Thanks. Hi.
I want to start with a song that
means a lot to me this time of year.
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitchin'
How was I supposed to know
That my mom
was dead in the kitchen?
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
Are resting in a little yellow jar
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I…
Excuse me?
Yeah, noisy boys.
Is it something that you'd like
to share with the group?
No, that's okay.
Come on, if it's important enough
to discuss while I'm playing
then I assume it's important enough
for everyone else to hear.
That guy's going home
with a note.
- Nothing. I was just saying…
- Could you speak up?
Sorry.
I was just saying to my friend,
you were the most beautiful woman
I'd ever seen.
And you said Daryl Hannah
was the most beautiful woman
that he'd ever seen in his life.
And I said, yeah,
I liked her in Splash,
but not so much in Wall Street.
- I thought she had a hard quality.
- A hard quality.
And while Daryl Hannah is beautiful
in a conventional way,
you are luminous
with a kind of delicate grace.
Then that's
when you started yelling.
Okay,
we're gonna take a short break.
I think that guy's going home
with more than a note.
Come here, Marcel. Sit here.
Pheebs, I can't believe
he hasn't kissed you yet.
God, by my sixth date
with Paolo,
he had already named
both my breasts.
Did I just share too much?
Just a smidge.
David's like a scientist guy.
He's very methodical.
- I think it's romantic.
- Me too.
Did you ever see
An Officer and a Gentleman?
Yeah.
He's kind of like the guy
I went to see that with.
Except…
Except he's smarter
and gentler and sweeter.
I just want to be with him
all the time.
You know, day and night.
And night and day.
And special occasions.
Wait a minute.
I see where this is going.
You're gonna ask him
to New Year's.
You're gonna break the pact.
She's gonna break the pact.
No.
Yeah, could I just?
Yeah, because I already
asked Janice.
You what?
Come on, this was a pact.
This was your pact.
I snapped, okay? I couldn't handle
the pressure and I snapped.
Yeah, but Janice? That was
the worst breakup in history.
I'm not saying it was a good idea.
I'm saying I snapped.
Hi. Hi, sorry I'm late.
Too many jokes.
Must mock Joey.
Nice shoes.
You're killing me.
Ross.
He's playing with my spatulas again.
He's not gonna hurt them, right?
Do you always have
to bring him here?
I didn't want to leave him alone,
all right?
We had our first fight this morning.
I think it has to do
with my working late.
I said some things
that I didn't mean.
He threw some feces.
If you're gonna work late,
I can look in on him for you.
That would be great. Okay.
But if you do, make sure it seems
like you're there to see him, okay?
And you're not, like,
doing it as a favor to me.
Okay. But if he asks,
I'm not going to lie.
But you can't actually test
this theory.
Because today's particle accelerators
are nowhere near powerful enough
to simulate these conditions.
- Okay. I have a question then.
- Yeah.
Were you planning on kissing me ever?
That's definitely a valid question,
and the answer would be yes.
Yes, I was.
But see, I wanted it to be
this phenomenal kiss,
that happened at this phenomenal
moment because it's you.
Sure. Yeah.
Right. But, see, the longer I waited,
the more phenomenal
the kiss had to be.
And now, we've reached a place
where it's just got to be
one of those things where
I sweep everything off the table
and throw you down on it.
And I'm not really
a sweeping sort of fella.
David, I think you are
You're a sweeper
trapped inside a physicist's body.
- Really.
- Yeah. I'm sure of it.
You should just do it.
Just sweep and throw me.
- Now?
- Right now. Just…
Okay.
You know what?
This is just really expensive.
Okay.
And I'll tell you, this was a gift.
So now you're just
kind of tidying up.
Okay, what the hell?
- You want me to actually throw you…
- I can hop.
Now, tell me something, what does
the phase "no-date pact" mean to you?
I'm sorry, okay?
It's just that Chandler has somebody
and Phoebe has somebody.
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
Fun Bobby, your ex-boyfriend,
Fun Bobby?
- Yeah.
- You know more than one Fun Bobby?
I happen to know a Fun Bob.
Okay. Here we go.
There's no room for milk.
There. Now there is.
Okay, so on our no-date evening,
three of you now
are gonna have dates.
- Four.
- Five.
Sorry.
Paolo's catching an earlier flight.
Yeah, and I met this really hot
single mom at the store.
What's an elf to do?
Okay, so I'm gonna be the only one
standing there alone,
when the ball drops?
Come on. We'll have a big party,
and no one will know who's with who.
This is so not what I needed now.
- What's the matter?
- It's Marcel.
He keeps shutting me out.
He's walking around all the time,
dragging his hands.
That's so weird. I had such a blast
with him the other night.
- Really?
- Yeah, we played. We watched TV.
That juggling thing is amazing.
What?
What juggling thing?
With the balled-up socks?
I figured you taught him that.
No.
It wasn't that big a deal.
Just balled-up socks.
And a melon.
- Phoebe. Hi.
- Hi, Max. Do you know everybody?
No. Have you seen David?
No, he hasn't been around.
If you see him, tell him to pack
his bags. We are going to Minsk.
- Minsk?
- Minsk. It's in Russia.
I know where Minsk is.
We got the grant.
Three years, all expenses paid.
- So when do you leave?
- January 1st.
Hello?
- Hey.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- Max told me about Minsk.
So you know, congratulations.
This is so exciting!
Yeah.
It'd be even more exciting,
if we were going.
You're not going? Why?
Tell her, David.
"I don't want to go to Minsk to work
with Lipson and Yamaguchi and Flank.
No. I want to stay here
and make out with my girlfriend."
Okay, thank you, Max.
Thank you.
So you're really not going?
I don't know. I don't know
what I'm gonna do. I just…
You decide.
- Don't do that.
- Please?
No, but I'm asking you.
I can't make a decision.
- I can't. Please, just…
- Okay. Stay.
- Stay.
Getting so good at that.
It was Max's stuff.
I love this artichoke thing.
Don't tell me what's in it.
The diet starts tomorrow.
You remember Janice.
Vividly.
- Hi.
- Hi, I'm Sandy.
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
- You brought your kids.
- Yeah. That's okay, right?
Party.
That thing is not coming in here.
"That thing"? This is how
you greet guests at a party?
Let me ask you something. If
I showed up with my new girlfriend,
she wouldn't be welcome?
I'm thinking your new girlfriend
wouldn't urinate on my coffee table.
He was more embarrassed
about that than anyone.
Okay? And for him to have the courage
to walk back in here
like nothing happened…
All right.
Just keep him away from me.
Thank you. Come on, Marcel.
What do you say you and I
do a little mingling?
All right,
I'll catch up with you later.
Oh, my gosh. Rachel, honey,
are you okay? Where's Paolo?
Rome. Jerk missed his flight.
And then your face exploded?
No. Okay.
I was at the airport
getting into a cab
when this woman,
this blond planet with a pocketbook
starts yelling at me.
Something about
how it was her cab first.
And the next thing I know, she just
starts pulling me out by my hair.
And I started blowing
my attack whistle thingy,
and then three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab,
she tackles me.
And I hit my head on the curb
and cut my lip on my whistle.
Everybody having fun at the party?
Are people eating my dip?
When I saw you
at the store last week,
it was probably the first time
I ever mentally undressed an elf.
That's dirty.
Yeah.
Hey, kids.
Look at him. I'm not saying he has
to spend the whole evening with me,
but at least check in.
There you are.
You got away from me.
But you found me.
Here, Ross, take our picture.
Smile. You're on Janice Camera.
Kill me. Kill me now.
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
Fun Bobby!
Hey, Bobby.
Hey, sorry I'm late. But my
grandfather died about two hours ago.
But I couldn't get a flight out
till tomorrow, so here I am.
Hey, Fun Bobby.
How's it going, man?
Who died?
It's going to be an open casket,
you know?
So at least
I'll get to see him again.
I'm gonna blow this one up and I'm
gonna write "Reunited" in glitter.
All right, Janice, that's it!
Janice?
When I invited you to this party,
I didn't think it meant that we…
Oh, no.
- I'm sorry you misunderstood.
- Oh, my God.
You listen to me, Chandler.
You listen to me.
One of these times, it's just gonna
be your last chance with me.
Will you give me the thing?
- Hi, Max.
- Yoko.
I've decided to go to Minsk
without you.
It won't be the same,
but it will still be Minsk.
Happy New Year.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
- You're going to Minsk.
- No, I'm not going to Minsk.
You are so going to Minsk.
You belong in Minsk. You can't stay
here just because of me.
Yes, I can. Because if I go, it means
I have to break up with you.
- And I can't break up with you.
- Yes. Yes, you can.
Just say "Phoebe, I love you,
but my work is my life.
"And that's what I have to do
right now."
And I say, "Your work?
How can you say that?"
And then you say,
"It's tearing me apart,
"but I have no choice.
Can't you understand that?"
And I say,
"No. I can't understand that."
Sorry.
And then you put
your arms around me…
And then you put your arms
around me.
Sorry.
And then you tell me you love me
and you'll never forget me.
I'll never forget you.
And then you say that it's
almost midnight and you have to go,
because you don't want to start
the new year with me
if you can't finish it.
I'm gonna miss you,
you scientist guy.
Hi, this is Dick Clark live
in Times Square.
We're in a virtual snowstorm
of confetti here in Times Square.
It gets bigger
and better every year.
Here you go, kids.
And then the peacock bit me.
Please kiss me at midnight.
You seen Sandy?
I don't know how to tell you this,
but she's in Monica's bedroom getting
it on with Max, that scientist geek.
Look at that.
I did know how to tell you.
Hey, everybody, the ball is going.
What?
The ball is dropping.
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
And the moment of joy is upon us.
Looks like that "no-date pact" thing
worked out.
Everybody looks so happy.
I hate that.
Not everybody is happy.
Hey, Bobby.
One. Happy New Year!
I just thought I'd throw this
out there. I'm no math whiz,
but I do believe there are three
girls and three guys right here.
I don't feel like kissing
anyone tonight.
- I can't kiss anyone.
- So I'm kissing everyone?
No. You can't kiss Ross.
That's your brother.
Perfect. So now everybody's
getting kissed but me.
All right. Somebody kiss me.
Somebody kiss me. It's midnight.
All right.
There.
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm still in there, you know?
Changing his diapers.
Picking his fleas.
But he's just phoning it in.
It's just so hard to accept
that something you love so much,
doesn't love you back.
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.