OK, OK, OK. Let's do
sophomore year of high school.
Uh, Nathan Burlingame.
- Didn't like you.
- Huh.
Kylie Mansard?
Thought you were cool
but intimidating.
No way! I thought
she was intimidating!
That's why I shoved her into that creek.
Well, after my chilli episode, I asked
the administration for a one-year sabbatical
and good news.
They fired me!
So, I am free and easy.
Well, the rest of the Soul Squad
is off helping Jason's dad.
Who are we saving?
No one from my high school,
I will tell you that much.
Well, before we do anything,
I have to break things off with Simone.
If I slip up and tell her about the universe,
it could doom her for eternity.
And I've avoided talking to her for so long,
she assumed I had laryngitis
and it went too far,
and now I'm on antibiotics!
OK, settle down.
Your moral code means you can't lie, right?
You need to just ghost her.
Disappear, block her number.
Bonus, anything she left in your apartment
now legally belongs to you.
I've done that to dozens of people,
and all of them got over it.
Actually, none of your exes
have ever gotten over you.
You're damn right they didn't.
I just wish I could end things
in a way that I knew wouldn't hurt her.
Bing!
I usually appear out of thin air
and there would be a pleasant "bing" sound
but I don't have my powers
so I'm doing my own "bings" now.
Bing!
Chidi, what if I could create
a virtual reality simulation
where you could practice
different break-up scenarios?
- You can do that?
- I think so.
I do know everything about you, and Simone,
and computer programming
and virtual reality
and artificial intelligence
and the human brain and everything else.
I'm kind of a nerd.
I'll start building the simulator now.
Bing!
Don't...
Turn around.
It's embarrassing.
Bing!
Jacksonville! What up!
Duval!
Poor Larry.
But...
"If you love someone, set them free."
My good friend and yoga pupil Sting,
no last initial, told me that.
I can't wait to show you guys
all the cool sights in Jacksonville.
Like, that swamp is where me,
Pillboi and Donkey Doug
used to stand and try and blind pilots
with laser pointers.
- And, oh...
- Maybe we should do the tour after we...
you know, save your father's soul.
Oh, I've been meaning to ask,
why are you trying to save your father?
I've heard you mention your friend Pillboi
many times
but you've not mentioned your father once.
What do you mean?
I talk about Donkey Doug all the time.
I'm sorry...
the man you call "Donkey Doug"
is your father?
Yeah.
The "Donkey Doug" with whom you tried
to blind airline pilots with laser pointers?
Yeah.
The "Donkey Doug" who is banned
from Disney World
for biting Buzz Lightyear?
In his defence,
he thought it was someone else.
Who?
So, Michael and I have a plan
to save my dad.
My whole life,
Donkey Doug was always getting in trouble
because of some get-rich-quick scheme.
He sold counterfeit truck nutz
he created a sport that was a cross between
dodgeball and horseshoes
and everybody died.
- He glued...
- This should be easy.
We have plenty of money.
If we just give him money, he'll blow it.
He's gotta feel like he did it himself.
A few years ago, Donkey Doug was very close
to getting his electrician's licence.
So, if we get him to finish the training,
he can earn an honest living
and be on his way to getting more
Good Place points
which is why we're all here.
OK, let's go save ma dad!
Taxi!
- Ha!
- Need help with your bag?
Nah, I got it!
Oh, dip! Jason!
Aw, dip! Donkey Doug!
You call him "Donkey Doug" in person?
Me and Jason are cool like that.
I don't think of him as my son,
I think of him as ma boy!
I mean, I am ya boy.
Yeah, but it's more like...
"That's my son right there, son!"
But not, like, "son-son", but, like,
"ma boy". But not, like...
Yes, Yes, we get it. Thank you.
Oh, this is my friend, Michael.
Aw, crap! You look like a cop!
Are you a cop? Because if you are,
you have to tell me
and you're not allowed to arrest me
for anything you saw
before I knew you were a cop.
- I'm not a police officer.
- Yeah, Michael's cool.
And this is Tahani, who is my wife, I guess.
Dang, nice pull, son!
How about you and me go check out my Jacuzzi
and put stuff in each other?
Again, I'm his wife.
Wow.
That's the first time that line
has ever failed.
You must really love him.
Welcome to the family! Come on in!
This programme knows everything
about your personality
Simone's personality,
and all human relationships.
It can't tell you exactly what will happen,
but it will approximate Simone's reaction
to anything you say to her.
Plus... it has Tetris!
Hm. Would this work with, say, me,
and, say...
uh, Jason Statham, and uh,
instead of a café
it was, say, a room with a futon
and a bunch of Red Bull?
Why is it that every time a new thing
is invented
humans immediately try to use it for porn?
Because we're disgusting.
Huh. Eleanor and I
will be watching on the monitor.
We'll see what you see.
Put these in your ears.
They'll play a tone that will trick
your brain into seeing what I've programmed.
Wow! Uh, so, this is... I'm here.
Hey, babe.
What did you wanna talk about?
Go ahead, Chidi.
Practice what you want to say to her.
Right, um... Simone, this has been
the best year of my life
because of you.
Unfortunately,
I have come to learn some information
and it means that we have to end
this relationship.
- What information?
- I can't say.
- Why not?
- Uh...
I-I can't say.
Well, you've either gone crazy
or you're too much of a coward
- to tell me how you feel. Which is it?
- I-I can't, because of...
Janet!
Who's Janet? And why are you screaming
her name into the sky?
You know what... whatever.
Goodbye, Chidi.
No, no, no, wait!
So!
- That didn't go great.
- I disagree!
I thought it was hilarious.
So, Donkey Doug...
Jason told us about your electrician licence,
and we have a career opportunity for you.
Yo! Later for that.
I got a business proposition for you.
Pillboi!
- Oh, dip! Jason!
- Oh, dip! Pillboi!
- Oh, dip! Donkey Doug!
This is remarkable.
It explains so much.
Jason, I thought you were dead!
But I was alive! I was in Australia.
I talked to you on the phone last week!
Yeah, but I forgot!
Oh...!
Me and Pillboi have been cooking up
something real special.
And this time, it's not fake meth.
Alright, Pillboi,
tell him about our new product!
Sharks, how much do you spend on
energy drinks and body spray in one week?
$300?
Ten hundred dollars?
What if I told you there was a product
that combined these two things
for one solution to all of life's problems
and more?
I give to you, "Double Trouble."
The world's first
energy drink-slash-body spray.
So, uh, do you spray it on yourself
or do you drink it?
You both it!
This is the one, Jason!
We're gonna be so rich.
I'll finally be able to pay to have
my calf implants moved back up from my feet!
This is gonna be a lot tougher
than we thought.
Tell me about it.
"Double Trouble" sounds amazing!
We should bid fast,
the other Sharks are gonna want in.
So, I just have to be simple, honest,
and declarative
and somehow still protect her feelings.
I don't know, man.
- Maybe just tell her that you're gay.
- I'm not gay.
Fine, bi.
- I'm not bi either.
- Why not?
More guys should be bi.
It's 2018, it's like, get over yourselves!
Is there any way I can try
a bunch of different things in a row
to see what works?
Bing! Sure.
If you want to reset,
just snap your fingers.
Also, I made some modifications to the tone,
so it should make your transition easier.
Oh.
Hey, babe.
What did you want to talk about?
Well, I don't love you anymore.
What?
No, no, you don't understand.
I don't technically love you in the same way,
because of circumstances.
What?
Hang on.
I don't know how to tell you this,
but I'm dying.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
Because we're all dying, slowly,
when you think about it.
We start dying the moment we're born,
so, not a lie.
OK, here it is.
I'm just going to be perfectly honest.
My real name
is Special Agent Rick Justice, FBI.
Nope.
Simone...
the last year has been truly amazing.
And with that in mind...
Will you marry me?
Yes!
Yes, of course I will! Oh!
Wait, what-what am I doing?
Why did I think this would work?
Chidi, I'm gonna go ahead
and reboot this one myself.
Yeah, good call.
- So, Simone...
- Wait.
Before you say anything,
I think we should break up.
- You do?
- Yes.
I love and respect you very much,
but we're heading in different directions.
And don't worry, we don't have to make
a big "thing" of it.
Oh, my God. OK. This is the one.
Remember everything,
right leg crossed over left.
Coffee's right there...
Oh, one more thing.
Suck it, ya doink!
Sorry?
This is Eleanor, you idiot!
Janet let me mess with the simulator
to screw with you!
Janet, come on!
Hi, Chidi, this is Janet now.
- Sorry, it won't happen again.
- Thank you!
Psych! It's still Eleanor!
I can't believe you fell for that, ya doink!
We need to break up
but here's a puppy!
Aw! Wait, what?
He's a puppy, it's over between us,
and he's cute!
Do you think I don't hear the bad parts
of these sentences?
His name is Martin, I need my keys back,
and he's a puppy!
You are very bad at this.
Well, it's because I don't actually
want to break up with her!
What, do you need me to break up
with her for you
- like we're in middle school or something?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
- Please do that for me, please!
- Fine.
Hey, Eleanor!
Hey.
What did you want to talk about?
Well, first of all,
you and Chidi are so great together.
He really loves you, and I can see why,
you know?
You're brilliant, charming,
obviously gorgeous.
Aww, you're sweet to say that.
- And your accent is so cute!
- Your accent is so cute.
What? I don't think I have an accent.
I don't think I have an accent.
Stopit!
What... is... happening?
Nope. No.
This is over.
Whoa, man, come on!
It was just getting good!
Let's remember the mission.
Your father needs to focus
on long-term stability.
Also, and perhaps this is less important
but there's an awful lot of dog hair
on the furniture, and I have not seen a dog.
Not bad, right?
"Double Trouble" comes in three
delicious smell-flavours.
Raspberry-Perspirant, Cedarwood Melon Blast
and 24-Hour Lemon Musk Xtreme.
That one is also a lube.
Look, Donkey Doug, "Double Trouble" is dope.
On that much, we can all agree on.
But you got to think long-term.
You were good at electricity stuff.
You hooked us up with free porno channels
every year, ever since the third grade.
It's good honest work.
"Honest work?" Whatever, Dad.
You're his dad.
This is huge, J!
When "Double Trouble" pops off, I'll be
able to quit my job at the old folks' home.
Buy a big-ass mansion.
Every day I'd wake up, get out of bed,
brush my teeth
rinse, go downstairs, open the fridge
Damn, we outta milk. Get in my car...
You don't have to run through
the whole imaginary day.
Jason, I believe in "Double Trouble."
Why won't you believe in me?
Well...
I suppose a little entrepreneurial spirit
never hurt anyone.
You know, "Reach for the stars,"
as I said to my good friend Elon Musk.
And then he shot his car into space.
What a weird creep.
Why was I friends with him?
Maybe this is what'll put your father
on the right path.
And hey, it's not like he's robbing a bank.
Yeah. It's a factory!
Excuse me?
Tonight, we're gonna steal some energy drinks
from an energy drink factory
then steal some cologne
from a cologne factory
so, it's actually two factories.
Then we just gotta bottle it all up!
Aw, dip, we gotta rob a bottle factory.
- Three factories.
Stupid Donkey Doug!
I mean, two factories I can understand
but... but three?
You might want to consider the possibility
that your father's a lost cause.
I have an idea, but I need your help.
Will you guys help me?
I mean, yeah, that...
that's why we're here, Jason.
What's your idea, darling?
We're gonna save Pillboi.
OK, real life. I think I'm ready.
I've analysed the ten
most successful scenarios
and compiled the statistically
most effective break-up strategy.
- Who said you weren't a romantic?
- Every girlfriend I've ever had.
Oh, there she is! OK, wish me luck.
Oh. Hi. Uh...
Something wrong?
Er, no, it's just that
we're usually over there.
Doesn't matter.
OK, so I've spent a lot of time thinking
about everything that's happened
- in the last year...
- Hi there!
What can I get you to drink?
- Uh, I'll have an iced tea, please.
- Water, thanks.
Um...
It's been a time of massive personal
and professional growth...
- Sorry, sugar with that iced tea?
- Yes, please.
Um, all in all,
it's been overwhelmingly positive
and I think that's due in large part to you.
Sorry, real quick. I'm gonna go on break,
so Helmut will be taking care of you.
Hello! Will you be eating with us today?
- Just, please, give us one second!
- Ja, OK.
One! That was one second.
Ha-ha, that was a joke!
- Please get out of here, Helmut!
- OK, ja.
Alright, look. Just, um,
we need to break up.
- I am... I am breaking up with you!
- Why?
I can't... It's... I ju...
It's... it's complicated.
But it's happening. Ya dumped!
- OK.
- Wait.
Wait, no...
Come back. Please.
Ja, OK, I'm back!
Not you, Helmut!
Hey.
Now listen, Judy. You can't mix Xannys
with these lil' pink fools.
You'll be tripping balls like Clarence was
when he crawled into the ice machine.
Here.
Take half of one of these,
wash it down with a five-hour energy
and you'll be golden.
Body high with mild visuals.
Thanks, Pillboi.
Yo, I gotta take off,
cos I gotta go do a robbery.
I mean... I'm sick.
Hello, Pillboi. I'm here on behalf of Jason.
You won't be attending the... job,
with Donkey Doug today.
There's been a change of plans.
OK.
That's it?
You don't need any more information?
I mean, do you wanna tell me?
Not really.
Cool.
Want some pills?
I hate this! What if I ruined her?
What if I sent her down the wrong path
and she ends up in the Bad Place?
I have to undo what I did.
Janet, fire up the simulator.
Dude! No more simulations,
just talk to her.
Break-ups never end with both people
feeling great, but she's a badass
and her world is bigger
than your relationship.
She'll recover.
Just... Go.
Be a person.
Right.
Here I go.
Janet, can I use the simulator?
There's a very specific Lenny Kravitz
concert I wanna be front row at.
Sure. FYI, when the system boots up,
you might find yourself in a steam room
with Jason, who will be wearing
an old-timey strongman onesie.
It's a... bug in the system.
Pillboi?
No, it's me.
Pillboi's friend, Jason.
Pillboi's not coming.
If you're here to tell me an energy drink
body spray is a bad idea
I've heard it before.
From a bank, and some doctors.
I'mma help you make "Double Trouble" but
you gotta leave Pillboi alone from now on.
I'm trying to save him.
Oh, dip. You got religious
and shizz?
Amen.
OK, hurry up and get this crap in my truck.
Jacksonville Police.
Come out with your hands up.
Are you a cop?
Cos if you are, you have to tell us!
Yes, this is the police.
- Yup, I knew it, it's the cops!
- Well, what do we do?
- Yo, let's get out of here.
- No.
I know I haven't been the best father
in the world.
I might not have even been in the top five.
I wanna make up for that.
I'll distract 'em, you run out the back.
No, that's crazy.
It's what my dad did for me,
and his dad for him
and some day, you'll do this exact thing
for your son.
I mean, I hope not.
But thanks, Donkey Doug.
Hey.
- Call me "Donkey Dad".
- OK.
Donkey Dad.
Nah, that sounds wack! Call me Donkey Doug!
Cool.
Bortles!
Uh...
Here's the truth. You're amazing.
And my feelings have changed.
I wish I could tell you why,
I really, really do.
But...
I can't.
Well...
You seem to know what you want,
which is rare for you.
Well, I... I...
I hope you keep the study going.
It might help a lot of people.
Well.
- See you in the next life.
- What?
Why would you say that? What do you know?
It's a figure of speech.
You're so weird, man.
I think maybe this is for the best.
So, your covert mission is to continue
to report to this job
until you receive our signal.
Now, this is the most important thing.
You cannot commit any more crimes
and you must help these people
as much as you can.
The mission depends on it.
Roger that.
Man, I can't believe this whole time
you guys were with NASA!
Yes, we are secret astronaut spies.
That is indeed what Jason told you.
Take good care of these old fools,
and stay out of trouble.
I love you, bro.
- Psych!
- I got you, bro!
I got you, bro.
- Jag...
- ... uars
Rule!
Well, my sister's museum exhibit
opens tomorrow.
Are you all ready for some Al-Jamil
family reconciliation?
You know it, wifey!
Soul Squad is on a roll!
I pretty much nailed that Pillboi thing,
and I got closure with my dad, Donkey Doug.
That remains depressing.
But I'm happy for you, bud.
I never got to do that with my parents,
and now they're both dead
so it's impossible.
So, the thing is...
one of your parents is not technically,
actually...
dead.
What are you talking about?
Your mother's alive.
She faked her own death.
I'm sorry, Tahani, I don't think I'll be able
to stay with you here in Budapest.
Turns out my mum isn't dead,
so I need to fly back to America
to murder her.