hope our molecules don't liquefy,
and regroup from there.
Excuse me.
OK.
Now, watch your step.
Hey, so...
yeah, so...
- I don't wanna go in there!
- I get that.
But come here, come here.
Here are your options.
Option Number one...
Cruel, but necessary.
Oh, look at this.
They added a tenth dimension.
Boy, permits must've been a headache.
Looks like we're inside
a Diane Von Furstenburg pattern.
From spring 2013!
OK, everyone, just be cool,
I know exactly what's going on.
We all smoked too much salvia.
We gotta ride this out for about two,
three minutes...
and then we'll be back
in Pillboi's broken hot tub
and this will all be over.
Hey, is...
is this a good time to talk?
Well, there's no time like the present.
And here, there's neither "no time"
nor "the present!"
Go ahead.
So, you know how me and you used
to be married, when I was dead before?
Mm-hmm.
I think I'm starting to catch
feelings again, for you.
- Mm-hmm.
- And if I don't double-die...
in this IHOP, and the Judge lady
doesn't turn you into a marble...
do you want to try being
boyfriend-girlfriend?
I'm not a girl.
But, yes, I'd very much like to go on a date
with you somewhere, sometime.
As opposed to here, which is nowhere,
at all the times.
- Do you get it?
- Yeah.
Hi! Butthead!
You lie to my face,
disrespect my orders
steal the only key to Earth
meddle with an already
compromised timeline
kidnap the humans
into a Janet's void
and now demand a meeting
in the freakin' IHOP?
I hate this place.
I wouldn't have asked for a meet
if it weren't vitally important.
And I promise, no more rule breaking.
Oh yeah? Really? Cool.
Cos it kinda looks like
you stole a book from Accounting!
No more rule breaking, starting now.
Hello, Chidi!
That is a great look for you.
Things don't work out here with old Blondie,
you know who to call.
This bitch!
Sorry...
what is on me right now?
Oops! Where'd you come from, little buddy?
No, don't touch it!
Tahani. Do not touch the Neednoggle.
- What?
- Bad! This is all bad.
Ugh! Humans are such whiners.
Here, hot pants.
Let me take care of it for you.
Help!
Ah!
Ah! Everybody, you're all still standing
in the IHOP.
The Judge simply augmented your reality
to make you feel like
you're in a normal IHOP.
- Very smart.
- Don't suck up to me, you suck-up.
This is far better!
Instead of a slug creature
I have a cute little scarf...
- No! No!
- No, no, no! Don't touch it!
Tahani, that's still the Neednoggle.
The Judge just made it look like a scarf.
- Wonderful.
- Alright.
Why don't we all sit down, so I can
fill the Judge in on what we've learned?
Your Honour, I once stood in front of you
and said I thought
there was something wrong
with the points system.
I finally know what it is -
life now is so complicated
it's impossible for anyone to be
good enough for the Good Place.
I know you don't like to learn
too much about life on Earth
to remain impartial, but these days,
just buying a tomato
at a grocery store means that
you are unwittingly supporting
toxic pesticides, exploiting labour,
contributing to global warming...
Humans think that
they're making one choice
but they're actually making
dozens of choices
they don't even know they're making!
Your big revelation is
"life is complicated?"
That's not a revelation,
that's a divorced woman's throw pillow.
I mean, this guy chose this tomato.
Those are the consequences.
You don't want the consequences?
Do the research, buy another tomato.
- What else you got?
- Um...
I'll tell you what else I got.
Uh, I got this.
Michael?
What... what are you doing?
- Backpack Kid dance.
- Why?
I don't know, it makes people happy?
Is it helping?
Can I say something?
- Jean-Paul Sartre once wrote...
- Boring!
I got this.
- Wh... you...
- I wanna tell you about a guy
from my dance crew in Jacksonville
called "Big Noodle."
Well, we gave it our best shot, guys.
It was nice knowing you.
I used to yell at Big Noodle
cos he always showed up late to rehearsal.
Then one day,
the swamp under my house flooded.
I needed a place to crash,
so I slept at Big Noodle's house.
Turns out that he had to juggle three jobs
to take care of four grandparents
who all lived in the same bed,
just like in "Willy Wonka."
I never yelled at Big Noodle
for being late after that
cos I knew how hard it was
for him to be there.
And he definitely didn't have time
to research what tomatoes to buy
even if he wanted to -
possession of a non-fried vegetable
is a felony in Jacksonville.
The point is, you can't judge humans
cos you don't know what we go through.
Amazingly, Your Honour, he's right.
I didn't really understand people
until I went to Earth.
Maybe you should give it a shot.
If you still don't see things our way,
then we'll drop it
and you can, you know...
zappy-zappy, marble-marble.
Yeah, sure, I'll give it a shot.
I'll go down there.
See what you guys "go through"
and then, one way or another,
this is going to end.
Hey, do you guys know a good place
where I can get Mexican food?
Oh. Pfft!
Mexico. Duh.
Whoa.
Well, how long will she be gone?
No way to tell. Uh, my guess is...
Ohhh, brother!
That was rough!
- Right?
- Sheesh! Earth is a mess, y'all.
Woof! Also, I guess I'm "black"
and they do not
like black ladies down there.
Crap, y'all! This is bad.
Well, where did you go, exactly?
Tanzania, Paraguay, Vietnam, Denmark.
It's terrible everywhere
and always in a different way!
The only place I liked was Hawaii,
although I barely left the resort.
The last place I went was a Black Friday sale
at an outlet mall in Michigan.
- Why?
- For the deals!
Earth stinks, y'all.
It's hot and it's crowded...
but somehow also cold and lonely?
I thought it was going to be so easy
to make good decisions.
The first thing I did
was I googled "big juicy natural tomatoes"
which led me to a porn site
that was for people
with a sunburn fetish, or...?
I kind of never recovered.
Right. That's problem number one -
life is chaotic and messy and unpredictable.
Problem number two -
even if you do somehow manage
to make good decisions, you still lose points
because of the unintended consequences.
Yeah, there are
booby traps everywhere!
Like, there's this chicken sandwich that,
if you eat it, it means you hate gay people!
- And it's delicious!
- It is! It is so good.
And... and I essentially tried
to do what you suggested
I obsessed over every choice.
But that was also bad,
and I still got sent to the Bad Place!
So I'm problem number three.
Oh, no, you are nobody's problem,
sweetheart.
You know, we gotta figure this out.
and then Turtle makes a bet
with Rhonda Rousey
and if she loses, she has to bo...
Oh, come on! I was just in the middle
of torturing William Shakespeare
by describing the plot
to the Entourage movie.
- What is this?
- Some new information
has come to my attention
and I need a solution.
I want the Bad Place to weigh in on this,
but first, let's have a change of scenery.
Remember, guys,
we're still in the IHOP, so be careful.
Shawn.
I have reason to believe
that humans might be, on average
better than the points system
suggests they are.
Counterpoint - humans are terrible.
Limp Bizkit, slavery...
The prosecution rests.
Gotta say, that's a solid rebuttal.
Look, there are plenty of awful people
and thoughtless jerks,
and I guess Nazis, again, somehow?
But there are also people who are really
trying to be good
and they aren't getting close.
Because they're not good at being good,
because they're bad.
The score they got on Earth is how good
or bad they are, full stop, end of story.
Then why did these four get better,
over and over again, in my Neighbourhood?
Why did they help each other in ways
they had never helped anyone on Earth?
I don't know, maybe it's a fluke.
Plus, you have zero proof
they did get better.
You didn't keep track of their points.
That's it!
I know what we have to do...
Oh! He forgot we're still in the IHOP.
Anybody got eyes on Chidi?
Help.
Help!
Can someone grab my tiny boyfriend, please?
I'm on it.
And... got him! Ah.
- Here you go.
- Urgh!
Ah-ha!
I... I just saw
a trillion different realities
folding onto each other like thin sheets
of metal, forming a single blade...
Yeah, yeah, the Time Knife,
we've all seen it.
Let's get back on track, bud.
Yeah, OK. Sure. What I was saying,
um, before, you know...
I saw the "Time Knife"!
is this, Michael is right.
His Neighbourhood gave us the chance
to become better people
because it removed all the variables
that make life on Earth hard.
Yeah. Uh, there was no rent to pay,
no racism, no sexism...
No awards-show
gift-suite publicist in-fighting.
What?
Those gift-suites can be a real minefield.
But, Shawn is also right.
And the four of us becoming
better people could be a fluke.
So, let's repeat the experiment.
It's what Simone taught us
about data collection.
Try it again,
and see if you get the same results.
Of course! I build a new Neighbourhood,
we choose four new people
tell them they're in the Good Place,
create challenges for them
track their progress.
My guess is they will do
what the original four did
seek help, support each other,
make wise decisions, improve.
If they do, then it's proof that humans
are not "bad, full stop, end of story."
This is so stupid.
Where would you even put this Neighbourhood?
I wouldn't allow it to be built
in the Good Place, that's for sure
and I doubt you'd want to come back
to my neck of the woods...
Ooh! I have an idea.
Hi, Mindy. We need to use your backyard.
You need my backyard? For what?
We're conducting an important experi...
You know what? I don't care.
In fact, as soon as I started
asking the question
I thought to myself,
"Why are you asking this?
You don't care about the answer."
Do whatever you want,
just leave me out of it.
And if you want to talk to someone,
talk to Derek.
I'm sure he'll be happy to see you.
Who's Derek?
Don't think of Derek as my ex-boyfriend.
I made him, so he's more like my son.
Although, I did make him because
I was jealous of you and Tahani
so he's kind of my rebound booty-call.
So... he's your son-rebound-booty-call?
Fine, if you want to put labels on it,
I guess he's my son-rebound-booty-call.
But he doesn't mean anything to me.
Also, Derek never really...
worked right. He's a buffoon.
You have nothing to worry about.
"How should he love thee?
Or how deem thee wise?
Who wouldst not leave him
In his wandering?"
Oh. I didn't see you there.
I was just reciting some Edgar Allan Poe.
Hi, I'm Derek.
Welcome to the Medium Place.
Derek! Why are... you so different?
You have Mindy to thank for that.
See, she found a plunger sticking out
of the ground behind our house
and every time she hits it, I pass out.
When I come to, I'm a little bit smarter
and a little bit better.
Not to brag
but I almost have a full-grown penis now.
It's resplendent, and mostly functional.
- How many times has Mindy rebooted you?
- I don't know. Half a million?
- What?
- She reboots me a lot.
Sometimes when she's bored,
or just needs some "alone time"
sometimes just for laughs.
Derek... Shall we head inside?
- OK.
- Cool.
So, here are the rules.
Michael designs the new Neighbourhood
however he wants.
The Bad Place gets to choose
the four new humans
but they have to be the same general level
of badness as the original four.
Alright? No serial killers, no dictators,
no one who managed a boy band.
Michael will not get the files in advance
so he does not have forever to plan
but he can then change the Neighbourhood
however he wants.
Yeah, I have about a billion objections
to this.
- So do I.
- Good! That means it's a fair compromise.
So, one last issue.
Where do we get all the other residents
for this place?
Well, my original Neighbourhood was built
for torture so everyone was a demon
we can't have that.
I say we get them from the Good Place.
Over my dead skin-suit.
Well, what other option do we have?
Would anybody like a Medium snack?
I myself will be enjoying another
classy martini.
Don't mind if I do.
I can make the people.
- Just like I made Derek.
- Are you sure?
Yes. If the Judge restores my powers
in the Medium Place, I can do it.
They'll be way more advanced
than the original Derek. No offense.
None taken.
OK. The other residents will be comprised
of "Janet babies."
You will have one year of Earth time
to try to improve the humans.
I will be monitoring everything
to ensure there's no cheating
and to track the humans' progress. Deal?
Ah! Gah! Ow!
Classic.
Ha-ha! Ow!
- Janet?
- Hi there!
- Ah.
- Ready to start building?
- Yes.
- I have some ideas
for how to design
a sort of "basic" Neighbourhood
which we can then tailor to the guests
as we learn more about them.
- Now, when you say, um... "some" ideas?
- I have 11 trillion ideas.
Yes. I'm so glad you're here, Janet.
Me too.
Alright. So...
What's your first "basic" idea?
Perfect. So "basic."
This house was built to torture you.
Why did you have Michael
recreate it exactly?
Well, in the memories I watched,
this was where we fell in love.
So I figured, why mess with success?
I mean, bleugh! What am I saying?
This house is stupid and you're lame,
and I hate you.
I love you too.
This is gonna be fun.
I mean, I know we have to help
these new people
but most of the time we'll just get
to live together, like a normal couple.
We can chill out, and just relax, and...
- Have sex...
- ... study philosophy.
- Horndog!
- Nerd!
- Hi! I'm Daphne.
- Hi, Daphne. I'm Janet.
- I made you.
- Great.
I'll wait for your instructions.
Thank you for making me!
Bye!
OK, Daphne's done.
Only another 185 people to go.
I'll check back in an hour.
You're doing so good, Janet.
Thanks, Jason. Making people is exhausting.
Can't help but notice
you're making a bunch of people.
You know, if we pooled our resources
we could be done in two shakes
of a lamb's Derek.
Whatever. Janet doesn't
need your help, dude!
Actually, it would go a lot faster.
Thanks, Derek.
No problem.
Don't worry,
this is purely professional, OK?
Now be a pal and hold my classy martini,
while I get down to business.
Let's make people.
Hello, Your Honour...
You fell for it! It's me, Shawn.
Just wanted to wish you bad luck.
Trying to psyche me out?
You must be scared.
Oh, I'm very confident.
I think we've picked some excellent subjects
for your stupid experiment.
When you fail, and you will...
I've got something special cooked up
for your four little friends.
Let me guess, they're gonna be tortured
with penis flatteners, and bees with teeth...
you are so predictable.
Why don't you at least switch it up
once in a while?
Try using teeth flatteners
and bees with penises?
First of all, that's... stupid.
But also, we are switching it up.
When you fail, the four humans
will be tortured for all eternity.
But guess who's going to be doing
the torturing?
Hello, idiot!
We built a Michael suit!
The boys down
in R&D said it couldn't be done
so I made it out of them.
That's Vicky in there right now,
taking you for a spin.
You are disgusting. Dis-gus-ting-uh!
Oh, Michael. It's going to be so amazing,
watching your four BFFs
look so sad and betrayed and confused,
as you, their reformed demon daddy
unleash a swarm of...
penis-bees. I invented those.
That was me.
Well, I will just tell them
what you're going to do
and they'll know that it isn't really me.
And we'll erase their memories
of you telling them.
Thanks for inventing that little trick,
by the way - very useful.
Have fun, Michael.
Enjoy everything
that is about to overwhelm you.
Mmm-bye, bitch!
So... how bad is contestant number one?
Murderer? War criminal?
Instagram DJ?
Uh, yeah, um...
- Are you OK?
- Mm-hmm. Yep, just a little jittery.
Last time I designed a Neighbourhood,
things didn't really go according to plan.
Neh. Plans are for wimps.
- Mm.
- We should've done this Shellstrop-style
don't prepare at all,
get drunk the morning of the test
BS our way through it, and then brag
about how we didn't even study
and still got a C plus!
So what do we got, man?
I gotta go give everyone a heads-up, remember?
Uh, his name is John.
Um, some sort of journalist.
No major crimes or atrocities...
- Is he out there right now?
- Mm-hmm.
Wow. That's freaky.
So, based on initial skimming of his file,
we will run scenario...
G48-119...
- Geez Louise.
- Well...
you have to be prepared for anything.
I mean, is John coming in thinking
that he belongs
or does he know he definitely doesn't?
Dude, dude... Relax.
All we have to do today is tell John
he's in the Good Place
show him around the Neighbourhood,
and get him to Tahani's welcome party.
That's it. We can deal with the rest later,
right?
- Right. Right, right, right...
- Hey.
Listen. Whatever your plan is,
it's gonna be great.
We trust you.
Your friends will always trust you.
OK. Here I go.
OK. I'm gonna...
Yup. Here I go.
I go here and...
I'm gone.
- Michael?
- Oh, yeah, I'm gone...
- Oh, whoa.
- I can't do this!
Hello?
- Is anyone here?
- Michael, buddy!
John is awake.
We need to open the door...
- Mm-hmm...
- And welcome him into the afterlife?
Remember? The whole plan?
I do remember.
That's why I can't do it.
It's too... too scary.
Oh...
No!
Hello?