and it's clearly the best way
to see if bad people
can become good
without knowing anything
about what's waiting for them
in the afterlife.
- Okay, let's do it.
- Yes!
But there have to be strict rules.
Otherwise, the results will be tainted,
and I reserve the right to
change my mind at any point.
Would someone who's not
an eternal being
please explain to me what the f...
Hi, I'm Michael.
You must be The Doorman.
Ah. This is wild.
I had no idea this was even here.
So I have this ruling from The Judge.
Heading on down to Earth
to reverse the deaths
of these four people.
It's kind of tricky, you know?
It starts up a new timeline,
so there might be some ripple effects.
But it's necessary for the experiment
that we're doing there.
So, how long's this trip take?
Hope I don't get a middle seat.
Wow, I haven't heard a joke
in 8,000 years.
And I still haven't.
That's the door to Earth.
You go through there, you'll be
wherever you need to be.
You won't have
any other powers, though.
You want to get around,
you're just going to have to
- take a bus or something.
- A bus?
Oh, boy, oh, man!
I'm going to sit
in a front-facing seat.
Or... or no, maybe
a sideways-facing seat.
I'm... I'm going to get so motion sick!
Oh, man!
What do I do,
just grab that key here...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
This key is made
of the very first atoms
that came into existence
in the universe.
It is one of a kind
and cannot be duplicated.
See?
"Do Not Duplicate."
Only I touch this key.
Oh, and what's the
significance of the keychain?
Nothing, I just like frogs.
I'm a frog guy.
When you need to get back here,
make sure you're alone.
Press this button. Any questions?
No? Great.
Knock yourself out.
Uh-oh.
I-I'm sorry, but this is
an important moment...
- On your right, mate!
- Oh, jeez, watch it, man!
Come down! Come down where you belong.
Buongiorno. Buongiorno.
Oh, wow! I was just on Earth.
It was incredible.
The... the traffic, the pigeons.
And I saw this place that was, at once,
a Pizza Hut and a Taco Bell!
I mean, oh! The mind reels.
A Pizza Hut and a Taco Bell! Ah!
Oh, Janet, it was everything
I ever imagined.
I got to ride a bike.
I put a coin in a thing
and got a gumball.
And then someone
came up to me and said,
"Hot enough for ya?"
And you know what I said?
I said, "Tell me about it."
Well, I am glad that you
got to chew a gumball.
Oh, damn.
I didn't even think to chew it.
Missed opportunity, shoot.
Did you also save their lives?
Yes, of course. Everyone is safe.
Including Jason.
Now we just sit back
and watch as they become better people.
Being good is for suckers.
What do you even get out of it?
I quit. Eat my farts,
Benedict Cumberbatch.
Morning, Chidi.
Blueberry muffin for ya?
Uh, I don't know, maybe.
I can't decide.
- You all right there, mate?
- Okay, I've made my decision.
I want to...
start crying.
Hey, Tahani Al-Jamil.
I'm from "International
Sophisticate Magazine."
Mind if we ask you 582 questions?
- Sounds delightful.
- Where are we, exactly?
My pied-a-terre, just off
the coast of "Barthelona."
What's one thing people
don't know about you?
That I was such a tomboy
in high school.
- See?
- Wow! Looking good.
Okay, next question.
Who would you say is the most
famous person in your phone?
It's not about who you know.
Enlightenment comes from within.
The Dalai Lama texted me that.
K, will you make me
the happiest man in the world,
and agree to be my wife?
No.
Do you think my name is the letter K?
Just say yes.
If we're married, legally
you can't arrest me.
Plus, bonus... you get
half the stuff I stole.
Yep, he just confessed to the robbery.
Damn it.
You realize what the problem is, right?
Yes, but there's no way to help.
Maybe there is.
In the afterlife, they all got better
because they helped each other.
And the key to that was
Chidi and Eleanor's connection.
If I get the two of them together,
- everything else will follow.
- Michael, no.
I'm going to meet Eleanor someplace
and plant the idea in her mind
that she needs to find Chidi.
Oh, and then maybe I'll visit Chidi
and make sure that he helps her
when she shows up.
I'm just going to nudge
the two of them together.
Just nudge-y nudge nudge.
The Judge was pretty clear
in her instructions,
and The Judge is, you know, The Judge
of, you know, the universe.
She'll never find out.
She spends all her time in her chambers
bingeing TV shows.
She's watching all of "NCIS" right now.
Hey, there.
Need to head on back to Earth.
Travel papers.
Yeah. You know, The Judge
said to use the same ones.
Because I'm, uh, you know,
visiting the same people.
Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
I brought you a nice
hot cup of antimatter.
I usually only drink decaf antimatter.
- Ah.
- Eh, I'll take it.
It's only 4:30.
My shift doesn't end until 9 billion.
Ooh.
- What do I owe ya?
- The real question, Eleanor,
is what do we owe to each other?
What do we owe to each other?
That is the question Tim
Scanlon asked decades ago,
and it is the question
I will try to answer
over the next three hours.
Are you Chidi Anna... Kendrick?
Anagonye, and yes.
Great, hi.
My name is Eleanor Shellstrop.
- Can we talk?
- Sure.
Okay, uh, where do I start?
I'm not, like,
the best person in the world.
I'm a trash bag from Arizona,
which is saying something.
Our biggest exports
are racist sheriffs and HPV.
But about a year ago,
something crazy happened...
And I...
Sorry. I've been flying
for like, 40 hours.
This is Australia, right?
Yes. I grew up in Senegal, so
my native language is French.
But I went to American schools,
so I also speak English.
- Oh.
- And German and Greek.
And Latin, just in case
it ever comes back.
Cool. I once got 12 out of 12
on a Buzzfeed quiz called
"Do you know all the slang words
the Kardashians invented?"
- Congratulations?
- Thank you.
I'm going to be honest. I did cheat.
But you were saying something
crazy happened to you?
Yes, uh, I almost died.
And it made me want to
become a better person,
which I did for a while.
But then I fell back into
my old trash bag ways.
Yesterday, I saw your lecture,
and something just clicked.
Wait, you flew all the way
here from Arizona
just to see me?
You know what,
don't flatter yourself, pal.
Sorry, that's a knee-jerk reaction.
Yes, that's exactly what I did.
And I know that seems zonk-atronic...
that's Khloe's word for crazy...
but I need someone to help
guide me, morally speaking.
And I think I need it to be you.
What do you say?
Will you help me become a good person?
Yes.
I'll start you off with some
introductory philosophy books,
and then we'll meet here once a week.
Great. Ideally, some of those books
will have been made into a
movie or maybe a funny GIF.
But anything's good with me, man.
- Can I ask you something?
- Mm-hmm.
Why are you helping me?
I'm a teacher. That's my job.
Yeah, but I'm not your student.
I'm just some hot rando
who walked in off the street.
There's got to be another reason.
Yes, there is. Um...
I also had a near-death experience.
- Whoa.
- Well, I mean, I don't know
for sure that I would have died, but,
it was pretty nuts.
I'm sorry,
but this is an important
moment in our friendship...
- On your right, mate!
- Oh, jeez. Watch it, man!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
That... that is right
where I was standing.
I was frozen here, unable to
make a single decision,
and I almost got crushed
by an air conditioner.
This is a sign.
I shouldn't be using air conditioners.
The freon is awful for the environment.
That's the lesson you take from this?
Chidi, your brain is broken.
You need to fix your brain.
So in a nutshell,
I have a 3,600-page thesis
that I am nowhere near finishing,
I am absolutely paralyzed
by decision-making,
and it is destroying my life.
Yeah, I sort of got that
when you couldn't
choose a chair to sit on.
Well, I didn't want to offend you
in case you had a favorite.
Look, I know I just
kind of... nope... walked in here,
and you don't know me at all,
but is there any way to tell
if my indecision
is due to a brain thing?
Um, yeah, sure.
Now what we do is
we make a lengthy incision
from your eyebrows
to the nape of your neck,
and we peel your face back, right,
then slice your skull open.
And I just randomly stab at your brain
with an electrified needle.
The fun part is
you're awake the whole time.
Uh...
I'm kidding! I'll just give you an MRI
and look at the part of your brain
that controls decision-making.
Oh, I want that.
I need to learn about my brain, please.
Well, so you just march
into my office unannounced,
tell me your brain is broken,
then demand I drop everything
and just put you in the university's
$3 million MRI machine?
Oh, I'm sorry, I just...
I freaking love it.
You're so weird! Let's go.
- Right now?
- Oh, yeah, come on.
Oh... okay.
This is your hippocampus.
It regulates memory.
Yours looks great, very strong.
Gorgeous hippocampus here!
This is your ventromedial
prefrontal cortex,
the center of decision-making.
This is where the magic happens.
Do you see how it's all lit up?
That's a flurry of activity
that occurred
when I asked you to choose
between red and blue,
and you almost passed out.
Is it too late to pick blue instead?
It is, yeah.
The point is, at first glance,
your brain is very healthy.
Huh, there are actual answers here,
data you can observe and learn from.
Yeah, man, science is
all about getting answers.
You philosophers
can spend your entire life
mulling over a single questions.
That's why everyone hates
moral philosophy professors.
No offense.
Oh, none taken. We suck.
Yeah.
- Chidi.
- One blueberry muffin, please.
Why choose to be good every day?
I argue that we choose to be good
because of our bonds with other people.
Simply put, we are not in this alone.
Thank you.
Wow, Chidi.
You chose that muffin
in less than a minute.
That beats your old record
by 59 minutes.
Henry, I feel amazing.
I am 100 pages into my new thesis,
and it is some of the best
writing that I have ever done.
I haven't been this happy since...
Oh, wow. I've never been happy.
- Ha!
- Bad!
I'm proud of you, mate.
It must be really nice
to live that way.
Well, that's the beauty of it.
Anyone can live this way.
Just decide to be more decisive.
Like, what's something that
you've always wanted to do?
I mean, I have been
putting off getting in shape.
Then make the decision
to wake up tomorrow morning
and get in shape. It is that easy.
Okay. Maybe I will!
- What have you got to lose?
- Nothing!
Henry, what happened to you?
Well, I was using
the leg press at the gym,
and you know how your legs
bend a certain way?
My legs bend the other way now. Oh, no.
All the tendons in my legs
snapped like violin strings,
and then, my foot flew forwards,
and I kicked myself in the face,
which gave me a concussion.
But on the bright side,
I lost control of my bladder.
Someone got it on video, and now
"Leg Press Whizzer"
has 62,000 views on Youtube.
- I'm famous.
- This is all my fault.
I did this to you. Oh... oh, muffins!
I brought blueberry muffins.
Oh, no, you shouldn't
eat blueberries anymore.
Read an article. The migrant workers
who pick them are horribly mistreated.
Yaaaaaaah!
Good morning, Chidi.
Blueberry muffin for ya?
Uh, I don't know, maybe.
I can't decide.
- You all right there, mate?
- Okay, I've made my decision.
I want to...
start crying.
Excuse me?
What is the maximum number
of books that I can check out?
- Is it 12,000?
- Got a wild weekend planned?
Well, I need to find
a new topic for my thesis,
and I had this thing happen
that made me more decisive,
and a few months ago, my friend
broke both of his legs,
and it's my fault, and
blueberries, and I need help.
- Whoo!
- Maybe that help will come
from Tay Zonday's autobiography,
"Chocolate Book." I mean, who's to say?
Mate, I've worked
in this library a long time,
and I've seen a lot of academic types
with that same helpless
look on their faces.
They all made it through okay.
- Once they learned the secret.
- What's the secret?
There's a secret?
Is the secret more books?
- How many more books do I need?
- It's not about books, mate.
It's about perspective.
Sometimes, when you're
feeling helpless,
the secret is to help someone else.
Get out of your own head. Trust me.
The next time someone
asks for help, say yes.
A few hours later, you walked
in and asked for help.
Now, I don't know
if this is going to solve
all of my problems,
but it's worth a try, right?
Well, thank you, sexy librarian guy.
I didn't say he was sexy.
Oh, I know, but whenever anyone
tells me a story about their life,
I always imagine all the people
as being super hot.
Otherwise, I quickly lose interest.
Do you not do that?
You can do it for free.
I got to say, I enjoyed
playing the role of mysterious
librarian, and I really
nailed the Australian accent.
- Uh-huh, flawless.
- Thank you.
But the point is,
Eleanor and Chidi are together,
and now we can relax.
Everything is finally on track.
- Status report.
- They're plugging away,
but we still can't hack
into The Judge's system.
Damn it, those four humans
have been on Earth for over a year.
I need to know
if they're getting better.
Can I just ask?
We torture, like, 30 billion humans.
Why do you care so much
about these four?
Never mind. Forget I asked.
Serves him right for
questioning you, boss.
I think you're doing a great job.
Thank you, Todd.
- No, no, no, no...
- Why did you do that?
I'm a demon. It's fun.
No one leaves this room
until we've accessed
The Judge's system.
Would music help?
Should I play some music?
Good idea.
Choose something deeply terrible
to inspire us.
Oh, yeah. That's the stuff.
So for Aristotle, virtue is practical.
Goodness isn't something that
a person just inherently has.
It's something that she
achieves through her actions.
- Questions?
- Uh, yeah, a few.
I wrote down "what?"huh?"
And then this doodle of a burrito
because when I first read Aristotle,
I thought it was pronounced
like Chipotle.
Wait a minute, is it "Chip-o-tottle"?
These are all great questions.
But I have to meet my thesis
adviser across campus.
Oh, well, I'm headed that way, too.
I'll walk with you. Hey, so,
I've been trying to figure out
how to pay you back for helping me.
I told you, you don't owe me anything.
At home, when I want to
get something nice
for one of my friends,
it usually comes in the form
of something edible.
You get what I'm saying?
An "edible" thing?
- Please don't buy me drugs.
- Okay, copy that.
I had no choice, I was in his driveway
taking pictures when he walked out,
so I said "Hey, Mr. Crowe,
I'm from the gas company."
- "I loved you in 'Gladiator.'"
- Chidi, hey!
- Hey!
- I got a question.
Is it "What's my thesis topic?"
- Because I still don't know.
- No, it's not that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You guys haven't met yet.
- Um, Simone, this is Eleanor.
- The famous Simone.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
So I've got to do some MRI scans
as a control for an experiment.
And since you loved it
so much last time,
I was wondering if you could just
pop back in there and help me out?
- Oh, absolutely.
- Cool, okay.
Well, just come by my lab at 6:00
and then afterwards, I can
buy you dinner as a thank you.
Oh, no, no, you don't have to do that.
Oh, okay.
Well, uh, I'll see you later.
Nice to meet you.
- You, too.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Uh, you and Simone
had some real professor
dork vibes flowing.
You're both teachers
who are hot for teacher.
How have you not
asked her out yet?
- Are you scared?
- Well, it's not impressive
to guess that I'm scared, Eleanor.
I'm scared of everything, and I
can't just do things like that.
- Just drop it, okay?
- Well...
Okay, just promise me you'll drop it.
Okay. I promise.
So you're into Chidi, right?
I mean, forgive my bluntness,
but I'm usually right
about these things.
Well, yeah, but I made it
pretty clear a bunch of times,
and he's never responded,
so I just assumed he wasn't interested.
Okay, I'm all set.
I'm just going to ask you
some basic questions, Chidi.
- What is one plus one?
- Two.
- What color is the sky?
- Blue.
What color are Simone's eyes?
Brown. Uh... uh, what?
If you could take Simone
anywhere on a date,
where would you take her?
Sorry, is this part of the experiment?
It is now, yes.
Please answer the question.
And keep in mind,
we can see your brain.
Next question. You are into Simone.
- That's not a question.
- So you agree it's a fact.
Next question's for Simone.
Simone, are you annoyed at Chidi
for waiting so long to ask you out?
- Yes, I am.
- Chidi, same question for you.
Are you annoyed at yourself
for waiting so long to ask out Simone?
I mean, I'm annoyed with you,
and I've only known you three weeks.
Yes, I am obviously
very annoyed with myself.
Can I get out now?
No, you can't. It'll ruin the science.
There's only one question left,
and you got to ask it, bud.
Simone, would you
like to have dinner with me?
Wow, that is highly inappropriate.
- Uh...
- I'm just kidding.
Yes, I would. Thank you for asking.
- Aw, cute.
- This is a disaster.
Michael, relax.
How are the two of them going to bond?
There were plenty of reboots
where Eleanor and Chidi
weren't even soul mates,
and he still always helped her.
Simone and Chidi are good together.
I've been running simulations
on what their kids will be like.
One of them is hot enough
to be on "The Bachelor"
and smart enough to never go
on "The Bachelor."
This is not just about Chidi.
I've left too much to chance.
Until our group is back together again,
this whole thing
is hanging by a thread.
I'm going back down.
You're pressing your luck.
If you keep disobeying Mommy,
something bad is going to happen.
- What?
- Oh, I don't have a mom,
so I've been experimenting
with thinking of The Judge as my mom.
- It's weird, forget it.
- Okay.
How are you even going to get
Jason and Tahani to Australia?
I have no idea, but I have to try.
Well, good luck, Dad.
Nope, also weird. Just go.
Hey, bud.
Brought you some
decaf hazelnut antimatter.
Just a little treat
for my old pal, The Doorman.
Heading back down, by the way.
You sure The Judge is okay with you
going back to Earth so many times?
Oh, yeah, yeah, all good.
See, still got the papers.
Shouldn't be long.
How are we doing, Steve?
I'm trying. I'm getting close.
Good. No pressure.
Aha!
Someone just went down to Earth,
and that gave me a back door
into The Judge's system.
Now we can see everything
that's happening
with all four humans.
Excellent work, Steve.
Uh-oh, looks like someone's
been cocooning again.
You know, it would be a real
help if you let me know
the next time you were about to...
Well, well, well.
Looks like Michael's been caught
with his hand in the human jar.
- Good one, boss.
- Shut up, Glenn.
Morning, teach.
Ready to discuss philosophy.
Obviously, I'm
kidding. How was your date with Simone?
Spill it, sweetheart.
We had a great time.
Thank you again for bullying me
into asking her out.
Well, I owed it to you.
And bonus, I realized
I was practicing virtue ethics
by helping the two of you bone down.
Okay, not appropriate.
Also, not a great understanding
of virtue ethics.
Oh, we can agree to disagree.
But if you must know,
it was very chaste.
We didn't even kiss.
- Because you chickened out?
- I did!
Yeah, I totally chickened out,
and I am so mad at myself.
Well, hey, maybe
it wasn't the right moment.
Knowing the two of you nerds,
your first kiss
is going to be while reading
Plato in an MRI machine.
Oh, hang on. Come with me.
Simone, what's the one thing
Eleanor and I have in common?
You both have a complete
disregard for my office hours.
- Sorry, Reginald.
- Oh, no worries.
Look, listen, Eleanor
is an Arizona trash bag.
- Yep.
- Her words, not mine.
- Totally.
- Who once told me that
her greatest accomplishment
was breaking
into Charles Barkley's house.
Mm. He was on the road.
I snuck in through the doggy door.
Tried on all his giant shoes.
One of my top five Christmases.
Listen, the point is,
Eleanor and I have nothing in common
except that we both almost died,
and it made us
want to be better people.
This is my thesis idea.
I will explore the effect
of near-death experiences
on ethical decision-making.
I will get a group of people together
who have had near-death experiences,
ask them ethical questions,
and see if there's any commonalities!
That's great!
Why are you yelling it at me?
Because I need your help!
You and your magic brain scan machine.
Oh, of course!
A joint study with
the neuroscience department.
We can use MRI mapping to see
if a near-death experience
alters brain function.
There's something there, right?
Definitely, I love this.
Great. Also, I wanted
to kiss you last night,
but I chickened out,
so I'm going to kiss you now.
Good, yes. I want that, please.
Oh, sorry, Reginald.
What were you saying?
Um, that I can't come to class tomorrow
- 'cause my grandma died.
- Oof.
Real mood ruiner. Read the room, dude.
Bingo. Okay.
Oh, good, you're here.
Eleanor, meet the newest member
of our ethical neuro-scientific study,
Tahani Al-Jamil.
Hello, Eleanor. Delighted to meet you.
Al-Jamil. Oh, you're Kamilah's sister.
I am, yes.
If you want an autograph or something,
I can probably arrange it.
Eh, I was never really
that into her... no offense.
Oh, I assure you, there is none taken.
So how did you come to join our team?
Well, it's a bit of a story, I suppose.
It, uh, began about a year ago.
Come down! Come down where you belong.
Aah!
- Well done, Tahani.
- Who saved me?
Did anyone see who just saved my life?
- It was Kamilah!
- No, it was a man, I think.
No, it wasn't Kamilah!
It was someone over there.
Kamilah, Kamilah,
Kamilah, Kamilah, Kamilah!
I had almost died.
And in that very moment,
I decided to change my life.
First, I cleansed myself of
all the worldly possessions
that had been weighing
me down like anchors...
the dresses, the jewels.
I gave them all to Good Will.
That's what I call Prince William.
Since he'd married a commoner,
I assumed he'd know
some needy people they could go to.
Sure.
Then I deleted all my
celebrity contacts
from my mobile.
Good-bye, Bono. Good-bye, The Edge.
Good-bye, The Edge's real phone number
that even Bono doesn't have.
And most importantly,
I put physical distance
between me and my old life.
Book me a flight to Tibet.
I'm going to live
in a Buddhist monastery.
I need to get out of the spotlight.
Copy that, I'll see
what jets are available.
- No, I'm flying commercial.
- Okay.
- First class, I assume?
- No.
I'm a woman of the people now.
Comfort Plus.
And there, in that humble monastery,
thousands of miles
from the meaningless concerns
of high society,
I embarked upon
a quest for enlightenment.
I learned to embrace
a life of simplicity.
I meditated.
I worked.
I gave back to Mother Earth.
And I slept.
My soul had never felt so nourished,
until one day,
my former life came knocking
at the open space
where a door would have been
if we were given any privacy.
Yo, is that Tahani Al-Jamil?
Man, it totes is you!
What up? I'm Colby, "Squalor News."
What are you doing in this monastery?
Oh, we're doing
a new show about poverty,
drug lords, gun running,
weird-ass restaurants,
skateboarding, oh, and also genocide.
It's called "Society is F'ed."
What are you doing here, though?
Is this where you came after
your sister saved your life?
I am living here as a way to
shed my desire for attention.
Toigh, that's what's up!
You got to shed that, right?
But listen, if you ever want us to do
like a monster profile
on you and your monk junk,
we would be honored AF.
I think people
would be supes interested
in what you're doing here, for real.
Look, here's my card. Think about it.
Of course, I never
called him to do that profile
because I didn't pursue
a life of tranquility
to get in front of a camera.
I did it to get out of the spotlight.
And that's what my book is about...
shedding your need
for validation from others.
Publisher says you'll hit
2 million copies sold by next week.
Your "582 Questions With" video
was nominated for a BAFTA.
- That's fun.
- Also, they want you for "Oprah."
"Oprah" is off the air.
No, they want you
to take over for Oprah.
Also, this investor wants to meet you.
I checked him out, he's legit.
Tahani. Gordon Indigo.
I just have to say
you are so inspiring.
Aw.
Namaste.
I mean, you really have
all these idiots fooled.
- Excuse me?
- Listen.
I'm sure you're already
rolling in dough
from this incredible scam,
but have you thought about merch?
Because we could, uh,
we could partner here.
I made a fortune selling Nirvana Orbs,
which is to say,
driving range golf balls
that I painted silver.
- That's awful.
- No, it's healing.
Wink.
You should be selling
whatever crap you can think of,
because these people will buy it.
- That is quite enough.
- Hm?
And how dare you insinuate
that I'm not authentic?
I finished signing your headshots.
- Oh, not now.
- Ms. Al-Jamil, it's okay.
You and I are the same.
I love what you're doing here.
You get to be rich and famous
and not have to do any
of the work of helping people.
But I am helping people.
You need to go right now.
Suit yourself.
Look, if you change your mind,
I'm online. Just Google "crystals"
that prevent erectile dysfunction."
I'm sorry, but Ms. Al-Jamil
doesn't have time
to participate in an ethical study
at some random university.
If you want to meet her,
you can sign up
for the "Get Out
of the Spotlight" cruise,
with special guests
Deepak Chopra and Will.I.Am.
Hello? This is Tahani Al-Jamil.
Oh, hi, I didn't think
I'd actually get you.
My name is Chidi Anagonye,
and I'm doing an academic study
on near-death experiences
and ethical decision-making.
I read an article about you...
Will it help people?
That's all I want to know.
Will this help people?
Yes, I... I think so.
I... I mean, that's the goal.
Send me the info.
I'll be there tomorrow morning.
Wow.
But how had you
learned about me, I wonder?
A professor I'd never heard of
named Charles Brainman
sent me an article about you.
Said you'd be perfect for our study.
Well, welcome to Australia.
Oh, if you need a place to
crash while you get settled,
my motel has a pull-out sofa.
Although, as I say that,
and I look at you
and your whole thing,
I realize that's absurd,
and you should probably
just get your own place.
Yes, I... I think that's best.
- But... but thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Three down, one to go.
Sup, bud? I've been looking for you.
Oh, sorry. Are these your rocks?
No, look. My name is Zach Pizazz.
International talent scout.
I've been tracking
your dance troupe, man.
I think you really got the goods.
I want you to come on down to Australia
and start a new crew, all right?
I'll pay for everything.
You may have a few other
obligations, but basically...
Uh, thanks, but no thanks, man.
- I'm done with dancing.
- But wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You heard what my name was, right?
Zach Pizazz?
My life is just
kind of messed up right now.
I had a really tough year.
I'm sorry.
Want to talk about it?
I'm a pretty good listener.
Well, my year started about a year ago.
Pillboi, I can't breathe,
and I'm freaking out,
and I'm almost out of whip-its!
Pillboi!
- Buongiorno.
Buongiorno.
- Yo, what happened?
- I couldn't breathe.
The snorkel must have been broken.
Yo, that sucks.
- You ready to get back in there?
- No, man.
We're not doing this no more.
I almost died trying to rob
a Mexican restaurant.
I have to change my life.
I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to win
this dance competition.
So you didn't see
any other posters there?
No, don't think so. Why?
Doesn't matter. Continue.
Homies, I almost died yesterday.
But we've been given a second chance.
Three months from today,
on this very stage
in the Carmen Electra auditorium,
right here at the Smith & Wesson
Performing Arts Center
and ATV Repair Shop,
we are going to win
this dance competition.
How, you ask? By working.
We are going to eat, breathe,
and vape dance.
I want you thinking about dance 24/7.
That means every day, you think
20 thoughts about dance
for seven minutes.
And if you can't promise me
that you'll give
this dance crew
everything that you've got,
then you can walk out that door.
Right now.
Yeah, okay. I'm out.
What? Come on, Donkey Doug.
After all we've been through?
Listen, you know you're my boy,
but this sounds like a lot of work.
Good luck.
Pew, pew.
Donkey Doug out!
Damn, that's a tough blow.
But now that those guys are
no longer members of our crew,
we can legally rob their houses.
No, Little Peanut.
We're going to do this the right way.
No more crime,
and if you don't like that,
you can walk out that door.
Right now.
What? Co... Oh, come on...
We still got like 35 people,
so let's get to work.
Quick announcement.
Will the owner of a 1998 Toyota Tercel
with golden pythons
painted on both sides,
license plate GOT-MILF
please see an usher.
Your car has exploded.
All right, ya'll ready
for the next act?
Please give it up right now
for Dance Dance Resolution!
In the six-year history
of this competition,
no crew has ever received a
perfect score from our judges.
That changed tonight.
But before we get to that,
Dance Dance Resolution
has been disqualified.
What? No, why?
Because you have 40 people onstage.
The limit is eight.
Also, one of your members
tried to carjack me
- on my way in here.
- No, that was Donkey Doug,
and he's not a part
of our crew anymore.
We win! We win!
We win, we win, we win!
No, again, you are disqualified.
And the winner is...
Panther Blood!
Suck Monsters!
And the winner is...
Nobody.
All teams are disqualified
due to violence.
Okay, well, we're out of rent money.
So remember that thing I said
about no more crime?
That's over now. Go do crime.
Yep, he just confessed to the robbery.
- Damn it!
- That was easy.
Look, please let me go.
I only did it to pay rent
for my dance crew's rehearsal space.
Oh, well then, you're in luck.
We only arrest people for robbery
if they don't have a reason.
Sorry it took me so long
to bail you out.
No, it was my fault.
I shouldn't have used my one phone call
to prank the police department.
Man, a year ago, I almost died,
and I'm exactly the same
as I was before.
- A failure.
- You're not a failure.
You're a dreamer.
Look, I like my job
at the old folk's home.
Those old biddies are sweet,
and sometimes they give me
what they think are candy
but are really loose Vicodin.
But when I'm with you,
I feel like the sky's the limit.
I feel like someday, I'll be
able to buy my own Vicodin.
And it'll never turn out
to actually be laxatives.
Thanks, dog,
but if my life ended today,
what would my legacy be?
Sure, I did a wheelie on a dirt bike
through an entire Waffle House,
and I was once interviewed on the news
for finding a foot on the beach.
But yo, other than that, I have
no truly great accomplishments.
Bro.
I'm only saying this
because I love you.
Do you want a Vicodin right now?
So I walked out of that bar,
came down to this wharf,
threw a rock at a snake,
met a guy named Zach Pizazz,
talked to him about
my crazy year that I've had
which started when I
was locked in a safe.
No, that was me. I'm Zach Pizazz.
- We're caught up now.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
- A year ago, if you had
asked me to run a dance crew
in Atlantis...
- Australia.
- I would have said yes for sure.
But now, and I know this sounds crazy,
but I'm starting to think
there might be more to life
than amateur
street dancing competitions.
It's funny, but I know
exactly what you mean.
My goal in life used to be
completely different, too.
I used to, um...
rep this crew called the Demons.
Whoa, I remember you guys!
Didn't you all die when someone brought
a hammerhead shark into your hot tub?
Different Demons.
The point is, I had to leave
my old crew behind, you know?
But I met new friends
who helped me become
a better... person.
Look, I know this group of people
who are also searching for meaning.
They might be able to help you
find what you're looking for.
What do you think?
You want to go meet them?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Do we have to leave right now?
My friend gave me a pill
that I realized one second ago
was definitely a laxative.
No, go, go.
Well, that is the last time
I'll need to head back down there.
So to thank you for your help,
I brought you back
something from Earth.
A little token of my appreciation.
It keeps your antimatter
warmer for longer.
- It's a frog.
- Yeah.
- There's a frog on it!
Right there, it's a frog!
Oh, man, it's green. It's classic.
Oh, this guy's a jumper. You can tell.
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
Wow, that really went over big!
How's Jason? Is he still cute?
- Oh, he looks about the same.
- That sounds cute.
- Hey, guys.
- Ooh, hey, Judge.
- Long time no see.
- Yeah.
- How's it going?
- So good.
I mean, everything is going
according to plan,
and nothing is going
differently from the plan.
Yes, that's a very
not weird way to put it.
I'm just stretching my legs.
Just binged like
300 episodes of "NCIS."
- Oof!
- You know, I'm not
a human woman,
but that Mark Harmon can get it.
You know what I'm saying?
Speaking of human cutiepies,
how's that Chidi doing?
Oh, sorry, Judge. Let me just...
Ooh, hey, you know what you would love
- if you like Mark Harmon?
- Yeah?
"Stealing Home."
He is very sexy in "Stealing Home"
according to the private
thoughts of more than
7 million Caucasian women.
Oh, hot tip. Thanks, girl.
You guys want to come with?
- Ooh.
- We can watch together.
I can whip up some nachos.
- I am incapable of eating, so.
- Suit yourselves.
- Party poopers.
- Ah, party poopers!
I guess it'll just be
me and Mark, then.
Naughty, naughty.
Oh, boy.
Michael, we almost just got busted.
Yeah, but we didn't,
and more importantly,
Jason just arrived in Australia.
The four of them are finally together.
Oh, we did it, Janet!
We got away with it.
So this is our MRI machine.
Oh, don't... don't touch that.
Each of you will get a chance
in here eventually.
Hopefully, none of you
is claustrophobic.
Clausterphobic?
Who would ever be scared
of Santa Claus?
Oh! The Jewish.
Are you from Florida?
- Jacksonville.
- Yeah.
That should be fine for me.
It's roughly the same size
as Nicole Kidman's
cryogenic anti-aging chamber,
and I've never had a problem in there.
I'll be okay, too.
Kinda of reminds me
of the home tanning booth
I lost my virginity in.
Wow, I cannot wait to take
a look at these three brains.
Oh, forgot to mention.
There's one more person
who will be joining us.
Seems like a really interesting guy.
He was almost run over
by a train a few months ago.
Heard about the study,
emailed me last night.
This doesn't make any sense.
They're all there. What's going on?
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Something bad, Janet.
Something very dark...
and evil.
Oh, yes. Come on in.
- Everyone, this is Trevor.
- Hey, guys.
It is so great to meet you.
synced & corrected by PopcornAWH
www.addic7ed.com