♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la... ♪
♪ Did you ever lie
and listen to the rainfall ♪
♪ Did you ever own
a homemade apple pie? ♪
♪ Did you ever watch a child
while he was praying? ♪
♪ Just don't let the good life
pass you by ♪
♪ Did you ever hold a hand ♪
♪ To stop its trem... ♪
- Hello!
- Hello.
Hope we have the right house.
I'm looking for a Doug Forcett?
I'm Doug Forcett.
Wow! Oh, yes... yes, you are.
Sorry, um...
I'm a reporter
for the Calgary Times Examiner.
- Oh.
- My name is, uh, Michael Scoop.
- Mm-hm?
- This is my photographer, Janet... Scoop.
- She's my sister. We're the Scoops.
- Oh, boy.
Some... some people in town are saying
you live a pretty interesting life out here
growing your own food,
completely off the grid...
- Mm.
- We would love to do
a human-interest story about you
for the paper.
What do you say?
O-OK, let me think...
Well, first off, I'm so flattered
that you'd want to do a whole news story
just about me, that's so nice!
Heartfelt thanks to the whole Scoop family.
Can I ask, is your newspaper printed
on recycled paper?
Yes. Yeah, no, very recycled. The most.
Alright then, come on in!
Great! Great. Uh, hey, you know,
before we forget
can Janet take a photo of you for the paper?
Oh...
OK, can you look up a little,
and to the right?
Smile, but only with your mouth
and not your eyes?
Perfect.
It was 1972.
Uh, my friend Randy and I ate
some magic mushrooms.
Randy asked me,
"What do you think happens when you die?"
And I saw, with perfect clarity,
how the afterlife works.
Immediately, I knew I had to live
a perfect life.
Well, not immediately.
The next day,
all I could do was watch kung fu movies
and stroke a blanket
that I thought was my cat.
But soon after, I designed a life
that would maximize my point total
and help me get into the Good Place
- and I've been living it ever since.
- Mm.
- I know this sounds crazy.
- No! No, actually, it makes...
- it makes perfect sense.
- Oh!
Oh, boy, you've been sitting here
for ten minutes
and I haven't offered you anything
to eat or drink.
- Oh...
- Would you like some water?
Or fresh radishes?
Water'd be great.
Janet! How cool is he?
You know, for a celebrity
he's amazingly down-to-earth.
Stars, they really are just like us.
He's so thoughtful with his actions.
Thank goodness he had that hallucination.
He could've had the one Randy had,
where everything was made of ears.
- Way less helpful.
- We have to learn everything we can
about what makes him tick
so we can use it to help others.
He is the blueprint, Janet.
He figured it all out.
Here we go - two waters.
Let me know if you're not happy with them.
I have ice cubes if it's too warm,
and a Koozie if it's too cold.
Oh...
Boy, that has an interesting aftertaste.
Is that from a nearby river?
Oh, no. Why take fresh water away
from the beavers and the fish?
- Ah...
- No, I have my composting toilet
hooked up to a water filtration system.
One man's waste is another man's water.
- Mm.
- And both men are me!
Hm, hm.
I'm pretty excited to relax
and have a drink.
I mean, saving souls feels great,
but Sydney to Budapest
to Phoenix to Calgary...
I'm so jet-lagged,
I can't even "regrender" my "chorf."
Don't even know what I was trying to say.
You need to get your blood flowing.
There's a pool table over there.
- Wanna play?
- Yeah, sure, why not?
Let's do it.
Tahani, can I ask your advice
about something?
Is it about your grating speaking voice?
I'm so glad you finally brought it up,
because honestly
- with a few elocution lessons...
- No, I want to ask you about Chidi.
What's wrong with my voice?
Nothing! It's lovely!
Tell me about Chidi!
So, it must get lonely up here
all by yourself without anyone to talk to?
Oh, I've got lots of friends.
There's this little guy, for example.
Yeah, it's a snail.
Hi, snail! I don't name them
in case they already have
a name they prefer.
- Huh.
- So, this is an organic garden?
Yeah. Everything I eat, I grow myself.
The radish patch was actually here
when I moved in.
I thought it'd be mean to dig it up.
- Mean... to the radishes?
- Mm.
I also grow lentils,
because they require very little water
- and have the smallest carbon footprint.
- Huh.
All he consumes are lentils and radishes.
No, Janet. He also consumes...
his own waste.
So. Everything's fine.
How do you play pool again?
What are the rules?
That's one of the best things about pool,
dawg! There are no rules.
I am 100% sure there are.
Me and my friends play a special
Jacksonville style of pool.
It's called
"Special Jacksonville-style pool."
You hit whatever ball you want,
but you use your hands.
And that's it.
OK, your turn. I got a thousand points.
Oh - that's the other rule.
You make up your own points.
I got five million points.
Damn! How'd you get so good at this so fast?
So, in this whole other timeline,
Chidi and I said "I love you" to each other.
But he doesn't remember
any of that happened.
So, I guess my question is
when is the right time to tell someone
you were passionate lovers
in an alternate timeline in the afterlife,
but he doesn't remember
because technically none of that "happened"
in this strand of the multi-verse?
You know what?
I'll just check with Yahoo answers,
I'm sure someone's weighed in.
No, no.
I'm flattered you would seek my advice
though I suppose it makes sense.
I'm sure the one constant
in all the reboots
was that you and I were best friends.
Uh-huh. Yep. Mm-hm.
Look, I don't think you would want
Chidi to know
what happened in the past
unless you wanted it to happen again
in the present.
You can't know how Chidi will react.
It may be painful, but it's never a bad idea
to tell someone how you feel.
Thanks, Tahani.
You give really good advice.
And you made a really hot centaur.
Sorry?
So, these are some of my 71
adopted dogs and wolves.
You've rescued every stray animal
that's ever wandered onto your property?
Oh, yes, ma'am!
I've been mauled several times.
Uh, this little guy here...
might look innocent, but, boy,
he goes right for the squeaker
if you know what I mean.
Oh, this is fun. You get to meet Raymond.
Hi, Raymond!
Hi, dumdum.
Who are these two hosers?
Don't worry about Raymond,
he's just a local sociopath
who comes by my house
to take advantage of me.
I've got your laundry all folded
and ready for you.
For whatever reason, this loser
does whatever you tell him to do - watch.
Hey, give that guy your shoe!
Would that make you happy?
- Very happy.
- Oh...
- Now, give him your shoe.
- Oh, that's OK, Doug.
Don't... I don't need your shoe.
Please don't give me your shoe.
OK, well, then give me your shoe
or I'll be sad.
There you are.
Well, as long as he's happy.
See, if I make him happy, I get the points.
That's how the system works, remember?
Go get your shoe, idiot!
Be right back.
Ow.
Oh, that's a bleeder.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Michael, face facts. Doug is not
the "blueprint" of how to live a good life.
He's become a happiness pump.
What?
Remember, from Chidi's lessons?
I remember the term "happiness pump".
That's just mostly because Eleanor and Jason
made a bunch of dirty jokes about it.
It's a criticism of utilitarianism.
A happiness pump is someone
who is obsessed with maximising
the overall good, at his or her expense.
Doug will do literally anything
to make other people happy
even if it makes him miserable.
Oh, I don't think he's miserable.
So, everyone happy and contented in here?
- What's...
- Oh.
I volunteer to test cosmetics
for a local company
so they don't have to test on animals.
- It's fun!
- Ah.
For the animals who don't have to do it.
For me, it's like wearing a mask of fire!
Uh, what can I do for you now?
Would you like to move in permanently
or would either of you like any more water
- or one of my kidneys?
- You know what?
We have absolutely everything we need.
Thank you. Uh, we're gonna head out now.
OK, well, it was so nice to meet you, Janet,
and you, Mark.
- I mean, Michael.
- Huh.
I called you Mark.
- Your name is Michael.
- No, no, that's OK.
Hey, hey, stay with me here, buddy.
No, no, no, no, this is very bad.
Forgetting someone's name,
that's definitely lost me some points.
Hey, you know, I've always secretly wished
my name was Mark.
Lie!
- That's a lie.
- Oh...
Now I'm accusing you of lying!
And now I'm yelling.
Why am I yelling?
I need to make this up.
I'm gonna give you a really nice haircut!
- Was that...?
- The snail? Yeah.
Yeah, that was a snai... ooh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I think he's still alive.
Do either of you know anything
about snail first-aid?
- No.
- Yes. I mean "no."
Alright, Michael,
I need you to find some scotch tape
while I apply pressure.
Too much pressure!
I'm gonna need that tape!
Oh! What?
Jacksonville style, baby!
30 million... points?
Nice one, homie!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Well, I either know exactly what I'm doing,
and it's something
or we're doing nothing, and I'm winning!
Congrats. Um, can I talk to you
for a second?
OK, uh, a few days ago
Michael showed me something.
And I don't know exactly
how to say this, but...
you and I are...
Bambadjan?
You know, I never thought about it before,
but yeah, we are kinda Bambadjan.
No, you jet-lagged doof.
Bambadjan is the name of a demon
from the Bad Place
who is somehow right over there.
Come with me.
Right now.
Hey, guys, having fun? Cool, cool, cool,
so we need to get out of here immediately
because this bar is full of demons.
Eleanor, just because these people
are wearing cheap leather
and stonewashed denim,
they're still part of the Queen's realm.
Calling them "demons" is a bit much.
No, no, no, no, no, actual demons,
like, from the Bad Place.
OK, Chidi and I
are gonna go out the side door.
You and Tahani go out the back.
Or we do this the old-fashioned way.
- How did you make that so fast?
- Bortle...
Mm... Mm...
Hello, idiots. Surprised to see me?
Right, you don't remember.
I'm Shawn. You are very scared of me.
Now, where's Michael?
We are here to celebrate the life
of Martin Luther Gandhi Tyler Moore,
the snail.
I named him-her that posthumously,
because I imagine him-her
to be the greatest and most talented snail
ever to have lived.
Michael, would you care to say a few words?
Oh, you're serious. Yes, um, OK.
Martin was a lot of things...
a snail, mostly
but also a friend.
Martin taught us about life, about love
and about... the limits of scotch tape.
Goodbye, Martin.
Happy, slimy trails, old friend.
I'm sorry, I've got to leave right away.
I've decided to make a donation
to the Canadian Mollusc Association
in Martin's honour.
Their office is in Edmonton,
so it will take me...
about three weeks
to walk there and back.
So, take care.
OK, look out, little fellas.
Heads up.
- Here comes a shoe.
- Say, Doug... look.
Do you mind if we ask you
just a few more questions?
What you're doing here,
how you're living your life
- it's just so wonderful.
- Mm.
But can I maybe give you
just a little advice?
I know I should donate more blood.
I'll try, but the last time I went down there
they said I was so anaemic
they ended up giving me blood.
No, look, look. Um...
I've been a reporter for a long time, Doug.
Met all sorts of people.
Travelled all over this crazy blue marble,
meetin' regular folks.
Every face tells a story, Doug.
Why, I'd say that those so-called
"regular" folks often turn out to be
not so regular after all.
- Michael.
- Sorry.
The point is,
I have never met anyone so dedicated
to making other people and...
and snails, happy.
- Huh!
- If what you're saying is true
about the afterlife, then you must've earned
more than enough points by now.
So, loosen up, bud, you know?
Have a little fun.
Eat something besides lentils!
- Like radishes?
- No, no, Doug, damn it.
You know, just have ice cream,
or chicken parm...
Live your life, you know.
Travel. Drink regular water
that wasn't inside you.
OK, just relax.
- Thank you, Michael.
- Mm.
But, no, I can't do any of those things.
- Why not?
- Because I can't risk it.
There's an Accountant, out there somewhere,
measuring the value of everything I do.
What if I "relax," and do something
that loses me just enough points
to keep me out of the Good Place,
and I'm tortured for eternity?
No, I... I have to make every moment count.
It's the only rational way to live.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to walk to Edmonton
to give $85 to a snail charity.
Why don't you just take us
to the Bad Place already, dude?
Because I wanna see the look
on Michael's face when he realises he failed.
I love seeing the look on people's faces.
It's the best part of my job.
Dude, Michael's not coming here.
Face it, man, you are outmatched
because Michael and Janet are brilliant
and savvy, and they've been ten steps
ahead of you this whole time.
We can sit here as long as you want
but you will never, ever, ever...
see Michael or Janet agai...
Yikes, that was rough! Total bust.
Ugh! Doug is a complete disaster.
And I drank his piss.
Hello, Michael.
See? See the look on his face?
So great.
Hello, Shawn. Other demons.
What are you all doing down here?
What do you think we're doing,
you haemorrhoid?
We're ending this charade, once and for all.
These four humans are the legal property
of the Bad Place.
That's where we're taking them.
And you.
If you want them,
you're gonna have to go through me.
That's the idea.
Well, it's a bad idea.
Oh, Michael. When will you ever learn...
Screw this! Let's fight!
Get somewhere safe, you guys!
Bad news!
I've been going to the gym a lot!
- Oh, no!
- Chidi!
What is happening?
I don't know!
No! Let him go!
Oh!
Let him go!
Twelve years of fencing. En garde!
Obviously,
I'd never do that in a competition.
That'd be a three-tenths deduction!
No, no! Watch out!
Watch out!
I've never marbleised
a Janet before!
Jacksonville Style, baby!
2,000 points!
Thanks, Jason.
Janet! Door!
Ha!
Yes!
Ha-ha!
Three hundred points! Best score ever!
Is it just me or is Janet
a straight-up hottie right now?
How are you this close to being
dragged to hell
- and still horny?
- I don't know.
And how did you know they were demons?
Ugh, I can't tell you that now!
Screw it, what am I waiting for?
We could die in the next 30 seconds.
So, Michael showed me a memory
of our time in the Good Place
and you and I were, like... a thing...
- and...
- Ha! Gotcha!
Not like a casual
"Hey, I found two loose pills
in the bottom of my tote
let's pop 'em and see what's good"
kinda thing.
We were in love.
And there's a real possibility that
I'm in love with you, again
here, on this plane of existence
uh, today, now... in Canada...
during this brawl... with demons.
Whoa!
Let's get her to the door!
No, no!
Oh, cool...
when I'm even partway through the door
to the afterlife, my powers come back!
They do?
They do. Thanks for asking!
You're coming with me!
Hi there.
We did it!
- Oh... um...
- Well, no, no, no, of course.
Of course, Janet did it, yes.
But I had the, uh...
Thank you, Janet.
How did you get down here?
We have the only key to the door to Earth.
- We built our own door.
- That's impossible.
"That's impossible, eh!"
Ugh, you're such a dweeb.
Why can't you leave us alone?
You don't have enough nostrils
to stuff with wasps?
I don't want just any wasp-nostrils.
I want these wasp-nostrils.
You're just delaying
the inevitable, Michael.
The Bad Place is going to get all
of them eventually.
These four, their loved ones
even your precious
pee-pee king Doug Forcett.
Now, why would you think that?
Just a hunch.
And do you want to know
what else I had a hunch about?
No.
I mean, why let the guy
keep saying mean stuff, right?
I thought Doug Forcett was the "blueprint"
for leading a good life?
He seems pretty confident that Doug
is heading to the Bad Place.
For a while now, I have felt like
there was something wrong
with how the points system
was evaluating humans.
At first, I thought it was that
the system didn't allow
for the possibility that people
could improve.
That's why I convinced the Judge
to send you back to Earth
so you could confront the ways
you were living.
But now, I'm worried that the problems
with the system might be much more serious.
We need to gather some real evidence.
Uh, sorry, no, no, uh...
Michael, you're confused.
Evidence isn't a good thing that you want.
It's a bad thing that you have to destroy,
or you go to jail.
Jason, quick. I-I need that coaster
over there behind the pillar.
You got it, boss!
I... I just needed a... a 30-second break.
Yeah.
What sort of evidence is this
and how do we get it?
Janet and I have to go right to the source
of the points themselves,
the Accountant's office.
Four of you, stay here at Doug Forcett's
house until I get back.
You're gonna need to feed all the dogs
and the wolves
and if a teenager shows up on a dirt-bike
just do as he says, he's very scary.
Michael, Michael, Michael!
I forgot what you asked me to get.
That's OK, bud. Thanks anyway.
Look, we won't be long
and you guys should be safe here.
Actually, scratch that.
We're all screwed because
a bunch more demons just showed up.
- Oh!
- There's too many of 'em.
- What do we do?
- I have an idea.
I think I can take you into my void.
Cool, that sounds fun,
let's go into a void!
OK, let's go.
But just to be clear,
I don't know if you'll survive in my void
but either way, all of you will
definitely die on Earth when I do this
so look around and say goodbye!
Goodbye, Earth!
Wait, did you just say we're gonna di...