This library's depressing.
All they have in the Poetry section
is Jeff Foxworthy books.
Well, we needed someplace deserted,
and there's no place more deserted
than a public library in Arizona.
Now let's go, man!
We only have a few hours
before we have to pick the gang up
from the airport -
fire up Janet's memory gizmo.
Flooding your brain with memories
from the afterlife is dangerous.
In one of the reboots,
you and Chidi were in love.
- Can't you just take my word for that?
- No, dude, I can't.
My screwed-up relationship
with my parents made me believe
I could never really love anyone.
I need to see it for myself.
Those are my memories.
I want them back.
OK. Fine. Have a seat.
Luckily, before we shut
the Neighbourhood down
Janet saved a complete record
of all the reboots.
Put those in your ears.
- What's all that for?
- You'll see.
We're gonna start with a simple,
three-second memory.
Why only three secon...?
- Oh, hi, Eleanor!
- Buongiorno, Eleanor!
Morning, Bambadjan! Morning, Vicky!
Ugh. Those two are such forking dweebs.
As I told you...
Recalling afterlife memories here on Earth
has some... significant side-effects.
You should be back to normal
in about 20 minutes.
Ah, looking a little better.
The banana must have helped.
Before we go any further,
I have one very important question...
Did I look hot bald?
Cos I always kinda
felt like I could pull it off.
I have no real ability to gauge
physical attractiveness in humans.
But no, you did not "pull it off."
OK, that short clip should have
rewired your brain, like an inoculation.
So, now I can show you the highlights
of reboot 119.
I'm skipping all of the sleeping
and chewing.
You guys are always either sleeping
or chewing something.
So... we are moving on to the subject
of free will versus determinism.
We are officially done with Nietzsche.
Aw. I'm gonna miss Nietzsche.
I spent a lot of my life thinking
I was better than everyone else
and he showed me why I was right.
Gimme that reading list.
What have we got...?
Oh, a little Aristotle, a little Descartes
a little Tommy Quine-Quine.
That's what I call Saint Thomas Aquinas.
Three months of philosophy class,
and you're already...
Hm...
What are you grinning at, weirdo?
Come on, we're gonna be late
for the Neighbourhood meeting.
I gotta say
it seems like I was really
nailing that philosophy class.
Can you believe my high school voted me
"Most Likely to Die Young and
Unaccomplished"?
You did die young and unaccomplished.
- Fair enough.
- Put those back in.
Ah! My favourite four residents!
Don't tell the others.
Welcome to "Pick a Pet Day".
We have hundreds of beautiful animals
for you to choose from.
And when you do make your choice,
your pet will bond to your soul forever.
Fabulous! I haven't had a pet
since Barbara Streisand gave me
one of her cloned Siamese cats
- and it killed itself.
- Ah.
I'm going to look at the mythical pets,
darling. Catch up when you're ready.
- May I?
- Yes.
Dude, we can get mythical animals?
Maybe I'll get a penguin!
Penguins are real.
That's the spirit, Eleanor!
They're real to me too.
Ooh! This one looks just like
the one I had when I was a little kid.
He's so cute!
But is... is... is this one a little...
a little cuter?
I mean, this pup looks friskier, but...
this one looks a little sweeter? Maybe?
Uh-oh. It's Chidi kryptonite,
the choice between any two things.
Settle in, lizard.
This is gonna be a while.
Michael? What's a "Mirror Centaur?"
Ah, a stunning creature
whose human half
takes on the image of its companion.
Greetings. I am T'Hania, Goddess of Beauty.
Oh, my!
I mean, should I take
the cutest puppy, or is that shallow?
And is it even OK to separate them?
Are they brother and sister, or...
or perhaps married?
Dude, they're heaven-puppies.
I'm sure they're both incredible.
Just choose one.
You're right. The black one!
That was my first impulse,
and that is the one I'll take!
I'm so sorry, Chidi...
both puppies have been taken.
Yeah, I should've seen that coming.
My indecision has once again
cost me happiness
and I will now suffer the consequences.
How many pets have gone unclaimed?
Three. A 16-foot albino python...
— Mm-mm!
Something called a "tarantula-squid,"
and this owl!
The tarantula-squid! Tarantula-squid!
Tarantula-squid! Tarantula-squid!
I'll take the owl.
Check it out!
Janet made him a little cowboy hat!
Isn't that stupid?
Chidi? Hello?
Shh! Spencer doesn't like loud voices!
Yeesh, what happened, man?
Well, I was trying to teach him to play
"fetch," like I did with my puppy as a kid.
But instead of retrieving the stick,
he attacked my face
with his razor-sharp talons.
Why don't you just ask Michael for a dog?
Because it was my mistake
to not pick a puppy fast enough.
I made my bed, and now I'll... bleed in it.
Let me do that, dummy. Come here.
What if I talk to Michael for you?
That way you don't have to worry about
feeling ungrateful, or whatever
and maybe you'll still get a puppy,
instead of...
Ow!
Deep wounds.
- You'd do that?
- Of course! It's the least I can do
considering everything you've done for me.
So you get it, right?
- Hey!
- What?
You liked him, he liked you
you did nice things for each other.
Your lack of parental affection
did not make you numb
to love, blah, blah, blah.
"Blah, blah, blah?"
Why don't you want me to see this?
What are you hiding?
Nothing.
It's just the rest is not interesting.
Yeah, no, you're right,
"not that interesting."
Just watching myself fall in love
for the first time in fake heaven.
What else is on?
I am going to put this back in my ear,
and you are going to show me
how thoughtful and caring I am,
or I'm gonna rip off your demon head
and shove it up whatever's where
your butt should be. Roll it!
Oh...
a lizard was a perfect choice, Eleanor.
You both have combination skin!
Thanks. Hey, this is a weird question
to ask, I'll just throw it out there
can I ride your centaur?
I'm afraid T'Hania's quite particular
about whom she allows to ride her.
I tried, and she gave me a withering stare.
Turns out centaurs are a bit tricky.
You didn't have, like,
a stable full of horses growing up?
Oh, of course, but they just pulled
our carriages
or performed in our horse ballets.
They weren't so...
what's the word?
Judgmental.
With whom can I speak
about acquiring new shoes?
You can't expect me to walk around
in these flats all day
like some common glue-factory hobo horse.
Eleanor? You were looking for me?
Uh, yeah! So...
Chidi chose an owl,
because he froze up trying to decide
between two puppies.
Is it possible for him to swap?
Of course! This is the Good Place!
But he might want to hold off.
Tonight we're having a party,
where everyone gets to transform
into their pets for a few minutes,
as a treat!
Chidi can fly like an owl, and you can...
do whatever lizards do!
Tahani, would you host the party
at your mansion?
Of course! I'd love to.
Is that what you're going to wear?
What? N-no, no...
Of course not!
Why? Is it unflattering?
I... I can change!
Guys, I can't find my lizard.
He was just out there, like, one second ago.
No big deal. Janet can find it.
No, I can't risk it.
These pets are supposed to, like,
bond to our souls forever.
If Michael finds out mine ran away,
he could figure out
I'm not the real Eleanor.
Just, um... go without me.
And tell people that I'm hanging out
with my lizard
because we are so meshed together
or whatever, circle of life, crap like that.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Go enjoy flying. I'll meet you there.
Come on, Blake!
Lizard? Lizard!
Where the fork are you? Lizard!
Ugh! Why didn't I name you?
Hey.
- Why?
- Oh!
Oh, no... Chidi!
Sorry I shoved you, man.
Just been a little jumpy.
Hey, you didn't happen to see
my lizard in the lake
when you were thrashing around down there?
No. It was cold and dark and scary.
But, don't worry.
We'll find him.
Michael and Janet are busy
transforming people anyway
so they didn't even notice
you weren't there.
Holy crap, you're supposed
to be flying right now!
It's no big deal.
I just decided I'd rather be...
helping you.
Than soaring through the air like an owl?
That's amazing.
You're amazing.
After that,
you spent all your time together.
You studied philosophy together.
You even got Chidi hooked
on popcorn shrimp.
Eventually, you became suspicious of me
and escaped
to Mindy Saint Claire's house
on a train.
That was the first time you actually
said it out loud.
I love you.
And you don't need to respond, cos...
- I know you have trouble saying how you feel.
- I love you, too.
That's the story.
You're capable of human love.
Congrats! Can we go now?
How did it end?
Like it always did, with me rebooting you.
- There's... there's no need to...
- Show me, please.
Alright, let's get this over with.
- So, listen, guys...
- No! You... listen!
We just went to Mindy Saint Claire's,
and when she wasn't trying to trick us
into having a threesome, she filled us in on
everything that you've been up to here.
Oh, yeah?
We know this is like the hundredth time
you've tried to torture us
but this time it's different
because...
we're in love.
And love is stronger than anything
you can throw at us.
No, it's not.
"Love is stronger than anything
I can throw at you?"
I could throw an elephant at you.
You think a thrown elephant wouldn't
crush you because of love?
She was speaking metaphorically.
Even metaphorically, it's lame.
It's OK.
No matter what he does,
we will find each other
and we will help each other,
because we're soulmates.
There's no such thing
as "soulmates", you dingus!
I made it up!
I put clowns in your house
because you hate them.
I forced you to choose the lizard
and then I made that lizard run away!
I made it all up!
Don't you understand that? Ugh.
That's why I didn't want to give you
your memories back.
I didn't want you to see how cruel
I used to be.
Plus, I wore a lot of French cuff shirts
back then
I thought it made me look classy.
But it's... it's... it's all embarrassing.
I'm different now, I promise.
I'll swear on a Bible like you humans do.
I could grab one right now, it...
it's the only book they have
in the Sex-Ed section.
- I'm not mad at you.
- I-I...
Can't be mad at a demon for being evil.
I'm just sad because I thought
for a second, I could love someone.
But really, it was just you manipulating me
into thinking I loved someone.
So I guess I was right.
I'm incapable of love.
Eh. That's no biggie.
Do you wanna get burgers?
Hang on now, how did you draw
that conclusion?
You just watched yourself fall in love
with Chidi.
No, I didn't. I watched a puppeteer pull
a bunch of strings to make us think
we were in love.
You said it yourself - you made it all up.
OK, yes, I put you and Chidi
in close proximity
because I needed you to drive
each other crazy.
But I never intended for you
to fall in love.
Once you made us bond,
the romance was inevitable.
It's a basic reality show playbook:
put a bunch of attractive young people
in stressful situations,
so they act like idiots
and have sex with each other.
This is all just... determinism.
What?
"Determinism is the theory that we have
no control over our own actions.
Everything we do happens
because of some external force
which exists outside of our control."
I didn't choose to fall in love with Chidi,
because some all-knowing demon, you
- brought us together and scripted our lives.
- That's ridiculous.
I didn't make you kiss Chidi
by that lake.
You kinda did.
You orchestrated
the whole "Pet Day" thing
manipulated us
into choosing specific animals
made my lizard run away, which led
to Chidi coming to help me find it
which led to us kissing,
which led to us "falling in love."
None of that was my choice.
Everything in my life has been determined
by my upbringing, my genetics
or my environment, and everything
in my afterlife was determined by you.
There is no such thing as free will.
We're closing up soon, guys.
Yeah, can we just have 15 minutes?
We're kind of in the middle of something.
I'd take off if I were you.
The second we close,
they use this place to shoot pornos.
OK.
- You want something to drink?
- Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
But whatever I choose will be the result
of millions of biological
genetic and societal factors
that are entirely outside my control.
Iced tea?
Oh, that sounds good. I'll have one too.
OK. You think you have no free will
because I scripted everything
that happened, right?
All I have to do is prove that you made
one choice that I couldn't anticipate.
Easy.
OK! Here's a perfect example!
In the very first attempt...
- Y...
- Dude, dude, dude!
- What?
- Yelling. You're...
- You're yelling, like, so loudly.
- Oh, sorry.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
Watch this. It's from the very first attempt.
If anyone...
has any information...
- Oh, boy.
- About any of this...
OK, easy...
I beg you. Tell me.
Hey... I love you, man.
Michael?
The problem in the Neighbourhood...
is me.
You saw your friend in pain,
and you decided to sacrifice yourself
to help him.
That wasn't me pulling a string,
or manipulating you.
In fact, it was the last thing I wanted.
Ruined my whole plan.
- Free will.
- No, dude.
The only reason I cared enough
about Chidi to do that
was because you forced us together
made me feel bad for causing him pain...
- OK, yeah.
- Yeah.
But no, you were constantly doing stuff
I couldn't anticipate.
As a matter of fact,
I complained to you once, right...
right to your face.
I think it was reboot 444.
Now, is Chidi trapped
in the purple space bubble?
Yes. Is he in pain? Almost certainly.
Will he ever get out? No.
- However...
- Uh...
Yeah, uh, wrong one, wrong one,
I mean, that's...
worth watching - it's great, but, uh...
not-not the one I was thinking.
It's probably, uh... 445.
You. In here.
Where am I?
Hell.
You're in hell. Can I ask you something?
Have I missed anything in that freaky
little noodle of yours?
See, I... I've studied everything
about your life.
I know your hopes, your fears,
your psychology, your tendencies.
I know all your private shames, like that
you don't wash your feet in the shower.
Your first concert was Barenaked Ladies
and you have frequent sex dreams
about Sam the Eagle, from the Muppets.
Well, he's very authoritative
and I find that reassuring.
You keep making crazy choices
I don't understand.
Am I missing something?
I'm sorry, can we rewind for a second?
Who are you? Who is that guy?
Am I dead?
Is Sam the Eagle here?
No.
I tried to script your whole afterlife.
And I devised a 15 million-point plan
to torture you.
You made choices I never saw coming.
I call that free will.
What if all your choices are predetermined?
- Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
- What? We don't know!
Maybe there's a mega-demon
who built a torture chamber for demons
and this whole thing
is just him torturing you?
And maybe... all the mega-demons
are just fulfilling a destiny laid out
by a bunch of super-intelligent
tarantula-squids
who are torturing them...
Why did you do that?
Because I have free will.
And because you're being so... annoying.
Thank you. So sorry that he did that.
Happens all the time.
Usually it's the younger woman doing
it to the older guy, though.
Dude! Not cool.
Disagree.
I think it's the coolest thing
I've ever done.
Do you really not see what's happening here?
Do you want me to spell it out for you?
This is a defence mechanism, Eleanor.
You saw yourself fall in love with Chidi,
and it freaked you out
to see yourself be so vulnerable,
so you're using determinism
to convince yourself
that those feelings were not real.
- You know, you don't know me, man!
- Yes, I do. I know everything about you.
Remember?
Including that nothing scares you
more than vulnerability.
Ugh! Whatever. Who even cares?
I do. Because if everything is determined,
and we have no free will
then all this stuff we're doing
to put more good into the world is pointless
and I want to believe that it matters.
So if you'll excuse me,
I'm gonna use my free will right now
to go pick up our friends at the airport.
Worst possible use of free will,
but I'm gonna do it anyway
because I care about them.
You might wanna head out too.
We're closing soon, and the second we do,
they use this place to shoot porn.
First class was amazing!
They give you so many free presents.
A shaving kit, an eye mask... Oh, a vest!
Times like this, it's fun to remember
that we're legally married.
That is fun!
Oh, I call window seat!
I'm sorry. You were right.
I was scared about what it all meant,
and I went back to one of my favourite moves
turn on the ol' Blame Hose.
"This is all your fault!"
Apology accepted.
And I'm sorry I dumped iced tea
on your head.
Are you kidding me?
You did exactly what you should do
when your friend is being annoying.
You snapped me out of it.
That's what made me realise, in a weird way
we're the only truly free beings
in the universe
because we actually know
what's up with the afterlife.
And I think that means we need
to be bold.
Take the Soul Squad
to the next level somehow.
You're right.
We need to find someone
who can serve as a...
as a blueprint for humanity.
Someone whose life is so great,
that we can use it as a model
to get as many points
for as many people as possible
and I think I know the perfect person.
Rihanna! Good call.
I don't know her personally,
but I did see her in Vegas once
and her calf brushed up against my tongue.
I licked her leg. I was kicked out.
It's not Rihanna, it's someone way cooler.
Hey, everybody out of the car!
Grab your bags!
We're going to rural Canada!
- Is it ready?
- I guess. We have no idea if it'll work.
Oh, I'm sure it's perfect.
- Give it a try, Shawn!
- Me?
I'm not going through that thing.
She is.
ask Michael how many times
he rebooted them!
He's lying...
Yeah, zip it, toots. We're way past that.
Where am I? How long was I in there?
You have missed a lot.
Now, go through that makeshift portal,
see if you explode.
This might be gross!
Am I... on Earth?
Did you figure out a way to build
an illegal door to Earth?
Yes.
That's exactly what I did.
- Well, we all helped.
- Shut up, Glenn.