Are you happy?
I was before you ate
that last garlic knot.
Oh, I'm serious.
I mean, don't you think
our relationship has become
a little bit predictable?
Predictable? Yes.
Why do you ask?
Well, I was thinking
that maybe we could
spice things up a little.
What'd you have in mind?
Well, um...
I have been reading
Fifty Shades of Grey.
Oh.
And I have some silk scarves
and, uh, some duct tape.
Do you see this
taking place in a bedroom
or the back
of a panel van?
I don't know. I'm only
halfway through the book.
Forget the book.
What about you?
Do you have any fantasies?
Ugh, of course I do.
If lived only my regular
life, I'd eat a rifle.
Tell me one.
Well, I...
guess I always
wanted to...
take some naughty
pictures of you.
We could do that.
Really?
Yeah, why not? There's already
a lot available online.
What else?
Oh, well, I-I-I guess
it's a-a cliché
for a guy, but, um...
I've always wanted
to have a-a threesome.
Okay.
Now, I know
it's silly. I know.
No, I mean, okay,
we can do it.
If you are messing
with me,
there is no way
I will ever forgive you!
I'm not messing with you.
Seriously, we can
have a threesome?
- Come on, you'd do the same for me.
- Of course I would.
Good, 'cause I have
a fantasy of my own.
Oh, hmm, lay it
on me, baby.
I want to have
a threesome also.
See? See?
This is why communication is
so important in a relationship.
I mean, two minutes ago
I didn't care if
you lived or died.
Now I love you more than
any man has ever loved a woman.
You complete me,
but add another chick
and I'll complete myself.
Great!
So what's your
pleasure, treasure?
Blonde? Brunette?
Someone with a little
junk in the trunk?
No, no.
In my threesome, there's you, me,
Mm-hmm?
and another guy.
An-Another guy?
Yep.
Boy, I don't know.
Uh...
I mean, I-I never thought about
it, you know, that-that way.
Four balls, two bats
and one mitt. Uh...
Could be fun.
Yeah, yeah, but, uh, who would
the other guy even be?
Hey.
Oh, crap.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 10x03 ♪
Four Balls, Two Bats and One Mitt
Original Air Date on October 11, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪
So, you want to have a threesome
with me and Walden?
You have your fantasy;
I have mine.
Yeah, but mine's a traditional,
wholesome three-way.
You, me and an anonymous drunken
slut, the way God intended.
Walden is a friend.
Plus, we see him all the time.
So?
So it'll be awkward.
Not for me.
I-I just don't think
it's a good time.
I mean, he just
broke up with Zoey,
and he's feeling very
vulnerable right now.
I think this would help.
You know, he needs
to get back on the horse,
and in this case, neigh!
Do we have a deal?
All right, after we have mine,
we will approach Walden...
- No, no, no, no. I go first.
- Why?
Speaking from experience,
once you get yours,
I'll never get mine.
I am offended...
that you would insinuate that
I would break a sacred trust.
I love you, Lyndsey, and
if you can't believe in me,
then-then we have bigger
problems in our relationship
than whose dirty, nasty
hump-fest we have first.
Take it or leave it.
Take it.
Oh, I plan to.
♪ Men. ♪
Gorgeous day, isn't it?
Wonder what
the poor people are doing.
One of them is asking me
what the poor people are doing.
Rich, good-looking,
and funny.
God certainly gave
with three hands.
Hey, speaking of
three hands, um...
there's, uh, something
I-I need to ask you.
Sure.
Oh, boy, where do I start? Uh...
Okay, here's the deal. Um,
things with Lyndsey and me
have gotten a little stale, uh,
sexually speaking.
Everything is by the numbers.
I get it. You're skipping
right from 68 to 70.
Exactly, exactly.
Um, anyhoo, uh...
we've come up
with a solution.
What's that?
We're going to have a, uh,
a threesome.
Really?
What? She agreed to that?
Yep.
Dude, way to go!
Yeah, yeah, it's great.
Um, the thing is, um,
Lyndsey wants to have a sausage
fest before the clambake.
That's clever.
Yeah.
Yeah, she-she has
this crazy idea
that before I have
my threesome,
she wants to have
one of her own.
Whoa, what, hold on, w...
she wants to have a threesome
without you?
Oh, no, no, I'm gonna be there,
uh, uh, but with...
another guy.
Huh.
Yeah, and the-the
really crazy part is...
um, uh, that she wants
the other guy,
uh, to be, um, you.
Okay.
Yeah, now, I-I-I told her
that there was no way...
Oh, no, no, no, I'm in.
Wh-What? What?
You're in?
Yeah, sure.
It sounds like fun.
You know, now that Zoey
and I aren't together,
I don't see any reason why I
shouldn't be doing my own thing.
And Lyndsey's own thing.
Probably not your own thing.
Well, a-are you sure?
Why not?
Time to shake things up,
get out of my comfort zone,
you know?
Maybe slip into
your comfort zone.
Get it?
I got it.
Well, I guess... I guess
I should let Lyndsey know.
Um, she'll be thrilled.
As am I.
Yay.
Hey, wait.
Do y...
you want to do this, right?
Oh, oh, absolutely.
Uh, you know,
I'm-I'm very open-minded,
uh, about sexual matters.
After all, I-I did grow up
during the sexual revolution.
Well, technically, a-a few years
after, but there were still
condoms and diaphragms layin'
all over the place.
Oh, and, uh,
just a heads-up,
um... exit only.
Nope, not even a thumb.
♪ Men. ♪
I am so happy you said yes.
I am honored you asked.
Aren't you adorable?
Not as adorable as you.
Yeah, yeah, we're all adorable.
Um...
Let's... W-W-We need
to establish some ground rules.
Sure, like what?
Uh, well, uh, for instance, uh,
there are a few things
that I happen to know Lyndsey
is not exactly fond of doing.
No, I'm good.
R-Really? You're good?
With everything?
Even the Philadelphia
Dump Truck?
Back it up.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Anything else?
Uh, well, I guess this goes
without saying,
but, uh, you know, we're
not making Band-Aids here,
so Johnson should never
meet Johnson, so...
True.
Two dongs don't make a right.
Oh, oh, and speaking of, um,
if you have any desire to stick
your tongue in my mouth,
just stick
your tongue
in her mouth,
and then she'll
stick her tongue
in my mouth, and we'll consider
the circle complete.
Fine.
It's your loss.
I would like to propose a toast.
Oh!
Friends may come
and friends may go,
friends may peter out,
you know.
But here's to us,
through thick and thin,
peter out and peter in.
Hear, hear.
Cheers.
So, what do you say?
Let's get these balls rollin'.
♪ Men. ♪
This is okay,
what we're doing, right?
W-We're all consenting adults.
Oh. Oh, yeah, sure.
Sure.
I mean, you know, if one of us
was mentally impaired,
then the-the consent
might be suspect.
True. I mean, i-if
you were required
to wear a helmet or...
have a service dog...
that might be construed
as taking advantage.
Yeah, yeah,
but everybody here
knows what they're
getting into, so...
Yeah, no one's taking their
pants off for a candy bar.
Or absolution.
Um, so, listen, uh,
don't feel obligated to bring
your "A" game today, okay?
My "A" game?
Yeah, I mean,
what I'm saying is
you're younger than I am;
you're prettier than I am;
there's more...
of you than there is of me.
What do you want me to do?
Well,
I'm just saying,
we're playing on
a public course here.
Spot me a couple
of strokes.
You just be the maypole
and let her run around
with the ribbons.
No, no, that is not my style.
I'm very aggressive.
I'm in it to win it.
What do you think, boys?
I am definitely gonna win it.
Oh, yeah, well,
we'll see about that.
Uh, you do look
beautiful, darling.
Yeah, thanks.
Ooh.
This is probably bad to say,
but Zoey had an outfit
like that
she used to wear
all the time.
Well, not all the time.
Just when we
were having sex.
Which was pretty much
all the time.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Oh, I guess we're starting,
okay, uh, um...
You know, I-I, um,
I not only loved Zoey.
I also loved
her daughter.
That is beautiful.
I kinda thought we
were gonna be family.
We're your family now.
I'm starting to feel a little
like a very distant cousin.
I miss her so much.
I'd have given odds
that I'd be the one crying.
♪ Men. ♪
Walden, you doing
okay in there?
I'm okay.
I just need a second.
Maybe this just
isn't meant to be.
Why not?
The man is clearly upset.
Oh, boo-hoo.
I'm really sorry.
Hey, no need to apologize.
In fact,
if it would help, you can close
your eyes and pretend I'm Zoey.
Really?
Of course.
Um, should I pretend
you're somebody else?
Do whatever you want.
That's a good idea.
Let's-let's try that.
Attaboy.
Okay.
Mmm.
Oh, Zoey.
Oh, Walden,
give me a good shagging,
won't you?
I can't.
I can't do this!
"Give us a good shagging,
won't you? "
What? That's a thing.
Doesn't matter.
Let's just make sure we don't
get a crybaby for my threesome.
Your threesome?
We haven't even had mine yet.
Uh, I beg to differ.
I held up my part
of the bargain.
If I serve pie
and nobody's hungry,
it still counts as dessert.
I suppose.
Now what?
Well, not that you care,
but I did take a lethal dose
of boner pills
before we started.
Is that so?
I'm either going
to have sex or a stroke.
Your call.
Come on.
Let's go to your bedroom.
Really?
I'd rather take care of you
for the next 20 minutes
than the next 20 years.
That's the spirit.
♪ Men. ♪
It's a beautiful day.
Why don't you go
down to the beach
and find some kids to play with?
I don't wanna.
Okay, why don't you
go ride your bike?
I don't feel like it.
Well, you can't sit
in the house all day,
staring at that computer.
I made a billion dollars
doing this.
Carry on.
Hi.
Great to see you.
What's up?
Well, I got a most interesting
phone call this morning.
From Lyndsey.
Alan's Lyndsey?
The-the one with
the drinking problem?
The very same.
What she ha...
What did she want?
Well, she wanted to tell me,
in no particular order,
that you're a great guy,
that you're still very much
in love with me
and that I'm a complete idiot
for breaking up with you.
I am. I am. You are.
You didn't put her up
to that call, did you?
No, not at all.
I do miss you.
It's been very hard for me too.
I was kinda hoping
that you'd say that.
So, do you think that...
You, sir, can make out
with my girlfriend
any time you want.
You got her so worked up,
she humped my brains out.
So, where were we?
I miss you, you miss me, ah.
Ow! What did I do?
Ow!
Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
This is just like
Christmas morning.
But instead of celebrating
the birth of our Lord,
little Alan's
gonna get some strange.
I know you're excited,
but the first step
is selecting the right girl.
Mmm.
Hey, what about that
blonde over there?
Eh, I guess.
What's wrong with her?
Well, her outfit's a little
matchy-matchy, isn't it?
The outfit's going to be
on the floor of the bedroom.
Well, still, it says something
about her lack of imagination.
Fine.
Hey, how 'bout the redhead?
Ooh, redheads.
They do dirty things.
So, should we approach her?
No, no, hang on.
Hang on.
She's got a tramp stamp.
So?
It's a little skanky,
isn't it?
We're trying to invite her
to a threesome.
Skanky is good.
You're right.
Oh, although,
she does have cankles.
Skanky cankles.
Isn't that what they call
Santa Claus in Norway?
Are you done?
Sorry, just a little case
of the pre-ménage jitters.
You do realize
if I wasn't here,
you couldn't get
any of these women?
I'm not
so sure about that.
I still have a few moves
up my sleeve.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Be my guest.
Fine. Okay, watch this.
Hello.
No.
I'm good with whoever you pick.
♪ Men. ♪
I'm confused.
The only reason
you're doing this
is because
it's your husband's fantasy?
Ex-husband.
Ah.
Wow.
What a view.
The view from here
is pretty good, too.
Certainly is.
I'm gonna end up watching from
the sidelines again, aren't I?
You're lucky you
can get to watch.
Wow.
You two look really lovely.
Y-You could
actually be sisters.
That is exactly wrong.
Oh, no, I meant, uh,
I meant, uh, sistahs.
like, uh, "Sistahs doing it
for themselves."
What's the deal?
Is he dying and this
is on his bucket list?
It's complicated.
Just stay focused on me.
Okay.
So, uh, shall we get
this party started?
Great. Is there somewhere
where I can just freshen up?
Sure, the bathroom's
down the hall.
Okay, be right back.
Um, so, how are we
slicing up this pie?
What?
You know, who gets what when?
Or we just gonna take shifts
and tap each other out
like wrestlers?
Nice to meet you, too.
Yeah.
So, uh, how do you know Lyndsey
and, uh, the old guy?
Oh, Alan.
He lives here.
This is my house.
No kidding.
Oh, oh, and one more thing:
um, if I yell "cheeseburger,"
it means I'm getting close,
and you need to whack me
on the back of the head
'cause I want this to last.
You're so cute.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Oh, no.
No!
Oh, man!
I just cannot catch a break.
She sounds fun.
So does he.
You know, if we close our eyes
and don't say anything...
Way ahead of you, Walden.
Cheeseburger!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==