♪ Men. ♪
Good morning.
Top of the morning to you, sir.
Oh, God.
Did you have a stroke?
Oh, no, no stroke.
I'm bleaching my teeth.
What?
Sorry. I'm bleaching my teeth.
Oh.
And what are you up to?
Nothing.
Just reading the news.
Mmm. Me, too, old-school.
Anything interesting
over there?
Just reading an article
about how
home teeth-whitening systems
might cause mouth cancer.
Really?
No, of course not.
Why are you even
bothering with that thing?
Walden, I get rejected by women
for 100 different reasons.
Whiter teeth would make it 99.
Zoey?
Oh. Hi, Ava.
Good morning, Walden.
What a great surprise.
What are you doing?
I wanted to invite you
to my birthday party.
That is so sweet.
Uh, but I don't know if I can.
Why not?
Well...
Oh, boy.
Uh, is your mom there?
She's taking a shower.
Maybe, when she gets out,
you could ask her
if I can come.
Why? It's not her birthday.
Oh, this is breaking my heart.
Here's the thing, Ava.
I'm not your mom's
boyfriend anymore.
I know that.
She's in the shower
with Peter.
Kids say the darnedest things.
Okay, I'll tell you what, Ava.
Uh, why don't you let me
talk to your mom
and we'll figure
something out.
Okay. I love you, Walden.
I love you, too.
Good-bye.
Bye.
Damn it.
I can't believe she's sleeping
with this guy already.
Well, we don't know that.
All we know is they're in
the shower together.
You're not helping.
Sorry.
Hey, I know what
will cheer you up.
A whiter smile.
I've got another bleaching tray.
How about it?
No.
You sure?
You know what they say.
A million-dollar smile
gathers a lot of interest.
Who says that?
It's the slogan on the box.
At least I think it is.
My Spanish is a little shaky.
I'll pass.
You sure?
Might get your mind off of Zoey.
My mind is not on Zoey.
Okay, fine.
You need to stop parking
your car in the garage.
Really? How come?
It's leaking oil.
Oh, I don't think so.
I haven't put oil in it
in two years.
Well, it's leaking something.
Well, why don't I just
put down some cardboard?
Why don't you just
put it on the street?
Oh, no, the salty sea air
is very corrosive.
It'll hurt the blue book value.
Alan, you drive a 13-year-old
Volvo station wagon
with a quarter of a million
miles on it.
The blue book
has more value than your car.
Well, okay, but I-I...
No buts.
You put your car on the street
or I'll put your ass
on the street.
What a colossal douche.
What?
Just moving my car, boss.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 10x02 ♪
A Big Bag of Dog
Original Air Date on October 4, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
I want to apologize
for going off on you
this morning.
No need.
Really?
Water under the bridge.
Which, coincidentally,
is where I had to park my car.
Well, I appreciate that.
And, uh, just FYI,
pigeons nest under there.
My car already looks like
it's covered in mashed potatoes.
I'll get it washed for you.
It'll need detailing.
No problem.
And oil.
Sure.
We good?
Yeah, I suppose.
Now, show me that
million-peso smile.
Oh, no, I...
you can't really tell.
Ah, come on.
Wow. Nice.
It's like
a movie star's smile.
You think? You think?
Yeah, they look
like little Chiclets.
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm really sorry
about the whole car thing.
This breakup's got me
a little crazy.
Oh, I understand.
When my wife left me,
I had a lot of anger.
Of course, I internalized it,
which led to a lot
of hair in the sink
and blood in the toilet.
So you know what it's like
to love someone so much
that your heart feels
like it's going to explode
from your chest
with pure happiness.
Oh, God, no. I was just pissed
off about losing the house.
My point is that...
that everybody has problems,
but what's important
is how you deal with them.
Here, let me
get that for you.
See, the key is,
you got to tap it
in the right spot.
It's not...
Oh.
It's okay. I-I got it.
No, no.
I can get it.
What the hell?
Son of a bitch!
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
No, it's not.
I want ketchup,
and I can't have it.
Calm down.
It's just a condiment.
Choose me, damn it!
Choose me!
Okay, we're-we're not talking
about ketchup anymore, are we?
What else would we...
be talking about?
Okay.
Uh, here, let me
help you clean that up.
Oh, no, no,
don't worry about it.
You know what? Here.
Give me your...
your shirt and pants,
and I'll throw them
in the washer.
Oh, that's not necessary,
actually.
Give me your shirt and pants!
Okay. Okay.
Oh, uh, don't wash the
shirt with the pants,
'cause it's off brand
and the colors tend to run.
Oh, and, uh... and wash
the pants in cold water.
Okay.
They shrink in warm water.
Of course, that's funny
because, uh,
I shrink in cold water.
Just give me
your stupid clothes!
Hey, here, here.
Thank you.
I am so back in the garage.
Oh...
Perfect. Um...
Coming!
Uh...
With any luck, it'll be
a door-to-door ketchup salesman.
Oh, Robin.
Hello, Alan.
Sorry. Uh, come on in.
Walden, your mom's here!
Be right there!
So, nice to see you.
Well, it's nice to see...
so much of you.
Your son insisted
I take off my clothes
after he soiled them.
That sounded weird, didn't it?
So, uh...
so, what brings you by?
Walden's taking me to lunch.
Oh, lovely.
I enjoy the occasional lunch
with my mom.
Really?
As one enjoys the occasional colonoscopy.
Walden!
Sorry.
Let's go.
I'll drive.
Okay.
Oh, bon appétit.
Bye.
Everything about that man
is disturbing.
Nice to see you again.
Oh, look.
New yellow pages.
Oh, man.
Oh, boy.
Uh, Berta!
Yeah?
I'm locked out.
Hang on.
Hurry up! I don't have
any clothes on!
Hello?
Berta?
Oh, come on!
This is nice.
You and I
haven't gone out
for a bite to eat
in a long time.
Yeah.
It's a shame Zoey
couldn't join us.
Mm-hmm.
How's she doing?
Fine.
Good. I'm glad.
She's a great gal.
You don't want to let
that one get away.
Right.
How old is her daughter?
Eight?
She's almost nine.
When's her birthday?
Few days.
Oh, fun.
Is there going to be a party?
Yeah.
You know, for one
of your birthdays,
I got you a bouncy castle.
Do you remember?
I do.
You should get one of those
for Zoey's daughter.
That's a good idea.
Oh, and take
lots of pictures.
Those are the moments
you remember forever.
What... what's happening?
We're out of gas.
We just passed a station.
I'll be right back.
This is an electric car.
Hey.
Hey, wait...
Aren't you having
lunch with your mom?
I was, but then she insisted
on taking an interest
in my life.
That bitch.
What are you working on?
Oh, the, uh...
the NASDAQ presentation.
I could use a hand.
Sure. Send it over.
Okay, here.
Here it comes.
Oh, how'd
the marriage proposal go?
Went fine.
How big of a rock
did you give her?
Pretty big.
She go under the table
to thank you?
No, but you can.
Wow, Walden!
Dude.
When's the big day?
Don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
I mean we haven't
set a date yet!
Whoa. Don't bite my head off,
man, okay?
Just... wow.
Oh, my God.
What?
She shot you down, didn't she?
Can we just focus
on the presentation?
No, we can't! Listen, look,
did she give you a reason?
Billy, seriously, let it go.
Was it, was it, was it
that you were,
you were too pretty or too rich?
Walden, Walden, this proves
that God exists,
and he's a short fat guy
that didn't get laid
in high school.
Stop, please.
Listen, listen, listen, okay,
first Bridget divorces you,
and starts dating me.
And I mean, like, right?
Then, then you get dumped
by Mary Poppins.
I mean, Walden,
you've gotta wonder,
what is it about you
that drives women away?
Billy, this is your last chance,
dude.
Okay, I'm changing the subject.
Changing the
subject, okay?
I banged your ex-wife
in the shower this morning.
♪ Men. ♪
Go away!
Did you say come in?
What do you want, Alan?
Oh, I'm just checking in.
You know, you've been hiding out
up here
for quite a few days now.
Yeah, I'm busy.
I can, I can
see that.
So, what do you
got here?
Is this Versailles or
an Indian casino?
No, it's a dream house.
if we would have gotten married.
Sure, that's not weird.
Um... Oh, oh, uh, you
been smoking some pot?
No.
What a shame.
Would've explained a lot.
Um...
listen, buddy, maybe it's
time to take a break.
No, I gotta finish the roof
before the rainy season.
Oh, there's weather
in Legoland? Um...
Oh, by the way, I brought you
your own tooth-whitening kit.
You know, in case you ever feel
like smiling again.
"As seen on Telemundo."
Put it in the Zoey room.
What?
The Zoey room.
All rightie.
Oh, boy.
You can almost see
the yellow police tape.
On the plus side,
my teeth look fantastic.
♪ Men. ♪
Thank you all
for coming.
I know you're
all as concerned
about Walden as I am.
You know what I'm concerned
about?
I'm concerned with the tooth
he knocked out of my head,
all right?
I smoked crack
for three and a half years—
I didn't lose tooth one.
Then golden boy gets dumped,
I look like an extra
on Hillbilly Handfishin', huh?
I'd just like to point out,
that Walden is not the first
rich and handsome guy
to snap his bean
up in that room.
Thank you, Berta.
I'm just saying
maybe the house is haunted.
Maybe it's plagued
by a negative entity
who just won't leave.
Hey, you're not gonna hang this
on me.
It's my hope that if we
share our concerns with Walden
with a unified voice,
we might be able
to get through to him.
Like an intervention?
Oh, those suck.
They're like, they're like
judgmental surprise parties.
They're, like, "Surprise,
you're a loser."
I don't need an intervention.
I'm fine.
Sweetie, we're worried
about you.
You don't have to worry anymore.
I'm done with Zoey.
Please tell me that's not her
in the bag.
No, it's the Legos
and the pictures.
Oh, good.
This breakup hit me a lot harder
than I thought.
Well, anyway,
I-I want to apologize
for the way
that I've been acting.
Um, I think I went
a little off the rails.
A little?
I had perfect teeth.
I just whitened mine.
Yeah, now you're good-looking.
Anyway, I appreciate you all
being worried about me.
But I-I really think
I've turned the corner.
What is with that dog?
Honey, don't worry
about the dog.
You were saying?
I... Yes, I was saying that
lately I've been really sad,
and I didn't know how to deal
with it, so I got angry.
But I think now I know how to
process those feelings, so I...
Damn it!
Walden!
Oh, God, what has he done?
Sounds like he killed a dog?
♪ Men. ♪
Okay, problem solved.
You stole a dog?
No, I bought him.
He's real smart. Watch this.
Sit. Sit.
Sit.
Okay, stand up.
What a good dog.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey.
Whoa, that is a big bag
of dog food.
Well, he's a big bag of dog.
You sure taking on
a pet is a good idea?
Yeah, I think it'll
help me a lot, you know?
Just unconditional love
from an animal
that'll never leave me.
I thought that's what I was for,
but okay.
Check it out.
I got him a chew toy with big,
white teeth just like yours.
Grr!
Yeah, that is cute.
Come here. Let me show
you something else that's cute.
I might want to
get a trainer.
Way ahead of you.
I got a number
for you to call.
Great.
What did I do with my phone?
Oh, here. Why don't I call you
so you can find it?
You're number one
on my speed dial, by the way.
Wonder how many bars
he gets in there.
♪ Men. ♪
Ooh, Walden,
you came to my party!
I did.
And I brought you a present.
Oh, boy! Is he mine?
He sure is.
Oh, thank you.
What's his name?
He doesn't have one.
It's up to you.
You can name him
whatever you want.
I'm gonna call him Walden.
It's perfect.
What's going on?
Walden?
Look, Mummy! Walden got me a dog
for my birthday!
What?
I love you, Walden!
You're gonna be hearing that
a lot.
Happy birthday, Ava.
Wait, wait, Walden,
come back here!
I can't.
I wasn't invited.
Uh-oh. Walden
took a big poop.
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, hey.
How you doing?
I've never felt better
in my whole life.
Good for you.
You think you got
the whole Zoey thing
in your rearview mirror?
I do.
Attaboy.
Hey, where's Dogzilla?
What? Did you whiten
your teeth?
Nope. I did a bad, bad thing.
Oh, no, no!
My Louboutins!
Ugh!
Walden is taking this
stupid, bloody dog back.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.podnapisi.net