My new book The Hidden Reality
takes on a grand question:
Is our universe
the only universe?
You see, there's a growing
belief among scientists like me
that ours may only be one
among many universes
populating a gigantic cosmos.
In The Hidden Reality,
I explore this possibility
without presuming any knowledge
of mathematics or physics
on the part of the reader.
Hysterical.
I'm glad you
talked me into this.
We work so hard, sometimes,
it's nice to goof off
- and do something silly.
- Agreed.
Wait till you hear how he dumbs down
Werner Heisenberg for the crowd.
You may actually believe
you're in a comedy club.
You can think about Heisenberg's
"Uncertainty Principle"
much like the special order menu
that you find in certain Chinese
restaurants, where you have
dishes in column A
and other dishes in column B,
and if you order the first dish
in column A,
you can't order the corresponding
dish in column B.
That's sort of like the
"Uncertainly Principle."
♪ Ba-dum-bump. ♪
Say, I heard an interesting tidbit
about Howard and Bernadette.
Really, Amy? Gossip?
I'm disappointed in you.
Now, now.
Evolutionary biologist Robin Dunbar
has identified gossip
as an aid to social
bonding in large groups.
Forgive my language,
but "poppycock."
What if he's right?
And by not participating in gossip,
society breaks down into
small feral bands of tattooed
motorcycle riders
fighting to the death over the
last few cans of tuna fish?
In the parlance
of the urban music scene,
"What's the 4-1-1"?
Bernadette is thinking about
breaking up with Howard.
I believe our nation's
tuna cans are safe.
Excuse me.
Dr. Greene, question?
Yes?
You've dedicated
your life's work
to educating
the general populace
about complex scientific ideas.
Yes, in part.
Have you ever considered
trying to do something useful?
Perhaps, reading to the elderly?
Excuse me?
Yeah, but not your books;
something they might enjoy.
I kid, of course. Big fan.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
-- sync by
- Nice shot.
- Thank you.
My father taught me archery
as a child.
It's odd how the activity
brings back the smell
of Kmart bourbon.
- Perfect.
- I know.
What an elf
I would have made.
Whoo.
What do you think you're doing?
Shooting at a target?
With what?
- An arrow.
- Really?
I didn't see you draw one
from your quiver.
I'm not going to do that,
Sheldon.
Leonard, the people at Nintendo
can only go so far
in helping us recreate
an actual athletic experience.
We have to do our part, too.
That was uncalled for,
but...
I'll play along... Ow!
I had an unusual experience
with Amy last night.
Really? How could you tell?
She was attempting
to engage me in gossip.
- Mm. You don't say.
- Yes.
I think prolonged exposure
to Penny
has turned her into a bit
of a Gabby Gertie.
So, what's the gossip?
Oh, please, I was just
pointing it out.
I have no desire to engage
in the activity.
Fine, don't tell me.
All right, get this.
Bernadette is thinking
about breaking up with Howard.
Oh...
That's too bad.
I wonder what happened.
Mm, it's hard to say.
I can only speculate
based on the data I collected
watching my parents' marriage
implode.
In that case,
the woman dives into religion,
while the man dives
into a bottle-blonde bartender
who tries to buy my love
with action figures.
Oop! Out of arrows.
Boy, you sure get your money's
worth out of these games.
- Priya, can I come in?
- Sure.
Oh, God.
- What?
- It's okay.
You didn't know.
I'll take care of it.
What-what did I do?
Sheldon doesn't allow flossing
that close to the mirror.
You're kidding.
It's a splatter thing.
There's a little piece of tape
on the floor
you're supposed to stand behind.
- That's madness.
- I know.
Just do it. There's a big
inspection coming up,
and I don't want to lose
my TV privileges.
You really need
to let me take a look
at that roommate agreement,
one of these days.
Mm, I don't know.
I get a lawyer,
he gets a lawyer...
It's just easier
to stand behind the tape.
Oh, by the way,
a fellow at work
said I could use his
Dodger tickets this weekend.
- Does that sound like fun?
- Yeah!
Dodgers are baseball,
right?
You'll need to explain
the game to me.
Mm, it's complicated.
But as I remember it,
the essentials are
"get chosen last, get hit
by the ball, cry, go home."
Well, regardless,
I've got four tickets.
And I was thinking we can bring
Bernadette and Howard.
She's really interesting,
and I bet I can get used to him.
Well, it might not
be a great idea
- to invite those two.
- Why not?
Don't tell anybody
I told you,
but I heard she might
be breaking up with him.
Oh... too bad...
Although I do know one person
for whom that's good news.
Really? Who?
My brother.
He's got a big crush
on Bernadette.
What?
You're kidding!
No. I found poems
he wrote about her.
Very disturbing.
"Oh, Bernadette,
please play my clarinet."
- Wow, that's hard to believe.
- Yes.
And for years,
everyone in my family
was convinced that he was
the clarinet enthusiast.
Hmm. What's that
piece of tape?
Oh, that one doesn't
apply to you. You sit.
- Hey!
- Hey! How's it going?
Not too bad. Did you hear
about Howard and Bernadette?
'Course I heard about it.
How did you hear about it?
I heard about it
from Sheldon.
- He got it from Amy.
- Oh, damn it.
I told Amy that in the
strictest confidence.
Boy, some people are
such blabbermouths.
Well, whatever.
I'm sure Bernadette
can do better.
Do you think a sexually ambivalent
Indian astrophysicist
with selective mutism
and alcohol issues is better than
a hundred-pound Jewish guy
who lives with his mom?
You are kidding.
Raj likes Bernadette?
I didn't say Raj.
Who said Raj?
Okay, give.
How do you know?
Did he tell you?
- No.
- Well, then who?
I can't say...
Priya told you.
What a little gossip.
You know, not an attractive
quality in a woman, Leonard.
Not judging,
just my opinion.
Well, the point is,
if this got out,
it would destroy Howard
and Raj's friendship.
You don't have to worry.
Unlike Amy and Priya,
I know how to keep a secret.
You're the one who told Amy
in the first place.
In confidence!
Hello, Mummy. Hello, Daddy.
How are you?
We're very rich
in a very poor country.
So, all in all,
can't complain.
So, Priya,
how are enjoying
staying with your brother?
It's fine. But if
I'm going to stay
in Los Angeles much longer,
I think I should
get my own place.
Why?
Is Rajesh not making you
feel comfortable?
Rajesh, why aren't you making
your sister comfortable?
I am making her comfortable.
Besides, she's not
sleeping here
half the time anyw...
What?
Where are you
sleeping, Priya?
It's a figure of
speech, Daddy.
It means I-I work late.
Please tell me
you're not dating an American.
I knew this would happen.
Rajesh, are you
letting your sister
date that little Howard boy?
Now, hold on. If she
is dating an American,
that's not a bad way to go.
He's Jewish.
Those chaps are
very successful,
and they don't drink a lot.
It-It doesn't matter.
Howard has a girlfriend.
- For now.
- What does that mean?
I'll tell you later.
Is something going on
with him and Bernadette?
- Who's Bernadette?
- Doesn't sound Jewish.
You can't tell by that.
Winona Ryder is Jewish.
Okay, we're getting
off the subject.
Rajesh, I want
you to try harder
to make your sister
feel welcome.
Thank you, Daddy.
Don't worry. Everything I have,
I share with her.
Including my friend Leon...
Good night, Mummy.
Good night, Daddy.
Oh, my God,
I think you broke my toe!
You should have kept
your mouth shut.
Fair enough.
Now, what's up with Clarinet...?
Bernadette!
I've been thinking about
Dr. Greene's efforts
to make science palatable
for the masses.
Oh, yeah?
What about it?
That's all. I've just
been thinking about it.
Now, I'm thinking
about fractal equations.
Now I'm thinking about
the origin of the phrase
"train of thought."
Now I'm thinking about trains.
Are you listening
to this guy?
Hmm? Oh, I'm sorry.
I was somewhere else.
Lucky bastard.
Now I'm thinking about Jell-O.
So what's up?
It's a Bernadette thing.
Oh, no. I hope
everything's okay.
Whatever it is,
we're here for you.
You can tell us anything.
Yeah. Good or devastating.
I'm gonna ask her to marry me.
- Marry you?   - What?
- Yeah.
I just need to figure out the
right time to pop the question.
- Oh, I'd wait.
- No rush, no rush.
Oh, great. It's my cousin David
about the ring.
Hey, David, what'd you find?
Sure, a half a caret's fine.
Her freakishly small hands
make anything look big.
It's one of the reasons
I love her.
Man, he's going
to be blindsided.
I know. It'll be awful.
Why are you smiling?
Yeah, Raj, why?
Uh, a smile means something
different in my country.
You know, tears of joy,
smile of sadness.
India's a goofy place.
Oh, I'm back to trains.
Woo-woo.
Did I tell you our lab got
a grant to study addiction?
- No.
- Fascinating work.
I recently trained a capuchin
monkey to smoke cigarettes.
Have you learned anything?
Yes. He looks much cooler
than the non-smoking monkeys.
Although it's not
much of a contest.
The other monkeys just
sit around and masturbate.
If you don't mind, I'd like to stop
listening to you and start talking.
By all means.
Howard has announced
his intention
to propose marriage
to Bernadette.
I don't understand.
The original piece of gossip
indicated an impending breakup.
I know.
The group consensus
is that his proposal
will be met with an humiliating,
soul-crushing rejection.
Everyone was set a-twitter.
Although oddly,
no one tweeted.
It's not surprising that
the story has captured
the attention of our
little circle of friends.
Are you familiar
with meme theory?
I'm familiar with
everything, but go on.
Meme theory suggests
that items of gossip
are like living things
that seek to reproduce
using humans as their host.
I'm no stranger to
memetic epidemiology.
At Johnson Elementary School,
the phrase "Shelly Cooper's
a smelly pooper" spread like wildfire.
I should think so.
That's gold.
Your meme hypothesis
does intrigue me.
How might we examine
this more closely?
Do you have any ethical qualms
regarding human experimentation?
It's one of the few forms of interaction
with people that I don't find repellent.
We need to fabricate a
tantalizing piece of gossip.
And a second non-tantalizing
piece to use as a control.
Then we'll track its progress
through our social group
and interpret the results through
the competing academic prisms
of memetic theory,
algebraic gossip and epidemiology.
Look at you, getting me to
engage in the social sciences.
You're a vixen,
Amy Farrah Fowler.
Oh, hey, Amy. What's up?
Sheldon and I engaged
in sexual intercourse.
In other news, I'm thinking of starting
an herb garden. Mum's the word. Gotta go.
Oh, hey, Raj, what
are you doing here?
I just felt like drinking alone...
because I'm deep and dark.
Uh-huh.
So, uh, Howard's not here?
No. It's just one of those
times when it's just you and me.
Like when the three of us
went to the movies
and you and I waited outside
the bathroom
while Howard threw up
Red Vines and Cherry Coke.
Do you remember that?
Yeah.
Me, too.
Good times.
Alright, 16 wants
to order appetizers.
- Oh, thanks.
- This was nice.
What the hell are you doing?
Howard is your best friend,
and that is his girlfriend.
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
I was when I came in,
but it's amazing what
liquor does to guilt.
Besides what you
might not know is...
Bernadette is planning on
breaking up with Howard.
Well, I know that.
How do you know that?
My sister told me.
Oh, that gossipy bitch!
No offense.
None taken.
You should hear how
she talks about you.
Okay, listen, just because Howard
and Bernadette are having problems,
does not mean you should
be here sniffing around.
What can I do?
I can't stop
thinking about her.
All right, try
thinking about this...
Sheldon and Amy had sex.
Shut your ass!
Yeah, it's true.
Amy told me.
How did that even happen?
Did they know that's
what they were doing
when they were doing it?
I-I guess they just figured
it out at some point.
Wow.
I can't believe old
Smelly Pooper finally got laid.
- Hey.
Hope you're hungry.
Interesting.
A friendly sentiment
in this country,
cruel taunt in the Sudan.
It's a lesson in context.
Will Amy be
joining us for dinner?
Yes, I believe so.
Good, good.
Everything...
okay between you two?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
I was just talking to Raj,
and he mentioned what a lovely
glow she has these days.
Did he mean
as if she'd been out in the sun,
tending an herb garden without
wearing a hat or sunblock?
No.
That's not what he meant.
Well, we may never know.
As my mother would say,
the Asians are
an inscrutable folk.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have work to do.
Yeah, you do.
You dog, you.
Did you get that?
Every word.
Our false gossip meme appears
to have reached node lambda.
This is moving faster
than we thought.
Agreed.
It appears the rate
of gossip transmission
is proportional
to the number of nodes squared.
I must say, Amy,
pretending to have
intercourse with you
is giving me a great
deal of satisfaction.
Slow down, Sheldon.
I'm not quite there yet.
- Pass the soy sauce.
- Sure.
Bernadette just asked about
my sexual encounter with you.
The meme has reached
full penetration.
Pun intended?
No. Happy accident.
This is remarkable.
Took less than 24 hours.
I should let you know
that she asked for details
about our dalliance.
Interesting.
So it went beyond the
mere fact of coitus
to a "blow by blow,"
as it were.
Pun intended?
I'm sorry. What pun?
Not important.
I described your lovemaking
as "aloof, but effective."
I wish you hadn't done that.
That's going to make
me a chick magnet,
and I'm so busy as it is.
Hey, everybody,
I got something I want
to ask Bernadette,
and I can't think
of a better time
than when I'm
with all my friends.
Oh, hold on, Howard.
There's lots of better times.
Leonard, please.
The man is talking.
Let him get it out, and let
the chips fall where they may.
Thank you.
Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski...
Oh, God.
What's happening?
I know things haven't
been perfect with us,
and we've had our problems,
but I just have to tell you,
from the moment I...
Howard, let me just
stop you right here.
This is it.
Yes.
Yes, what?
Yes, I will marry you.
- You will?
I will.
I will!
Oh, I love you so much.
Oh, I love you, too.
Congratulations!
Oh, it's so exciting.
I wonder what
changed her mind.
Perhaps your talk
of my sexual prowess
renewed her faith in love.
As good an explanation as any.
That's great...
Oh, hey, Amy.
Bernadette just texted me.
Howard proposed?
Yes, not important.
Just stopped by
to let you know I'm
getting orthotics.
Also, I'm carrying
Sheldon's baby.
Mum's the word.
You're pregnant?!
Wow. Is there anything
on there about orthotics?
-- sync, corrected by elderman --
== Corrected by www.addic7ed.com ==