Problem?
This is the worst cobbler
I've ever eaten.
It tastes like it's made
of actual ground-up shoemaker.
Amusing.
A play on the two meanings
of "cobbler."
Hey, guys.
Guess who I found at LAX?
My baby sister Priya.
Excuse me, I object.
You propose a guessing game,
yet you don't give me
enough time to guess.
For the record, I was going to say:
"Your sister Priya."
You haven't changed a bit, have you?
Why would I change?
The hope has been that you'd
eventually bend to public opinion.
What brings you back to L.A.?
I have a one-day layover
on my way to Toronto.
- Corporate merger.
- Can you believe it?
Little Priya's one of the lead attorneys
for the biggest car company in India.
Given that when we met her,
she was finishing law school
and planning an internship
at a large Indian car company,
it's actually extremely plausible.
And your poll numbers
just keep dropping.
I want to catch up with all of you,
but first I really must visit the loo.
I'm going too,
I'll show you where it is.
All right, this goes without saying,
But ***
Hands off my sister.
Why would I touch her?
She's covered with airplane germs.
I'm so not talking to you.
I'm talking to him.
- I've got a girlfriend now.
- Please.
My sister's much hotter
than your girlfriend and you know it.
Let's agree they're both hot.
But that's my sister
you're talking about!
Okay, forget who's hotter.
The first time Priya came to L.A.,
Leonard and I made a pact
out of respect to our
friendship and to you
that neither of us would hit on her.
Did you pinky-swear?
Okay, then.
Cobbler. I'm still laughing.
It's really nice to see you again.
It's good to see you, too.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
You got any special plans
with your sister?
Oh, not really.
Just hang out.
I always tell people,
"If you have only one day
"in Los Angeles,
make it a train day."
Train day?
The fun starts with brunch
at Carney's in Studio City,
a hotdog stand
in a converted railroad dining car.
Next stop, Travel Town,
an outdoor museum
featuring 43 railroad, engines cars,
and other rolling stock
from the 1880s to the 1930s.
And, finally, we're off to the glitz
and glamour of Hollywood,
for dinner at... that's right...
the Hollywood Carney's,
a hotdog stand
in a different converted railroad
dining car.
I don't think
we're going to do that.
Well, apparently you hate fun.
Priya's not back yet?
Well, I guess that's not unusual.
Women, men,
the whole sitting-standing deal.
What are we talking about?
- My plans with Priya.
- He rejected Train Day.
Did you make it clear
that it's two different train cars
turned into hotdog stands?
Abundantly.
That's what I said!
- What's new with you guys?
- I have a girlfriend now.
- Good for you!
- I just want to put it out there
in case I inadvertently
squirt any pheromones in your direction.
Happy?
What are your plans
while you're here?
I don't know.
I just have the one day.
Do you like trains?
You might as well wait
at the airport for your flight.
"You are in a forest.
"There is quicksand to the west,
a path leads to the east."
Go east.
"An iron gate blocks your way."
Open gate.
"It's locked."
Well, so much for that.
It's getting pretty late.
You're still up?
I found an emulator online
that lets you play classic
text-based computer games
from the 1980s.
- That's pretty cool.
- Oh, yes.
It runs on the world's
most powerful graphics chip:
imagination.
You've really got to get out more.
Go north.
"You can't go that way."
Go west.
"A troll blocks your passage."
Okay.
Fasten your seatbelts.
Kill troll.
"With what?"
With sword.
"You don't have the sword."
Good golly,
it's as if it's happening to me.
Raj finally went to bed.
Sheldon's still up.
- You said he goes to bed at nine.
- He does,
but he got caught up
in a computer game...
Hit troll with axe!
My, this is one tough troll.
- Can't you get rid of him?
- If the past is any indication, no.
I'm trapped in quicksand!
The axe is dragging me down!
- Drop axe!
- Drop axe, brillant!
Give me a minute.
- Sheldon?
- Hold on.
Trying to figure out
how to get the bucket,
so I can carry the mud
past the dragon.
- You need to work in the morning.
- I know!
- Then bed, mister!
- Five more minutes!
Really?
You're going to risk getting sleepy
in the middle
of your thermodynamic
fluctuations seminar?
You know what happens
when you yawn in public.
Everyone will see
my oddly shaped uvula.
You don't want that, do you?
But it's a shame our society
mocks the differently uvulated.
Who was at the door?
- Building manager.
- They have to fix a pipe,
the water'll be off tomorrow
from noon to 2:00.
That's unacceptable.
We're supposed to write a notice.
It doesn't matter, we'll be at work.
What if I spill tomato soup on my shirt,
and have to come home to change,
only to find there's no water
for an enzyme soak?
Bifurcated uvula, Sheldon!
I'll have the chicken noodle.
Good night!
We're going to have
to be very quiet.
I know how to get the bucket!
I can turn the axe around
and use the handle to reach it.
Let's see.
Go north.
"You are in a forest."
Oh dear, I believe I'm lost.
I'll have to get
a fresh start tomorrow.
No! You just took a wrong turn.
You need to map it out.
I'll help you.
You stopped at the stream,
and you turned north three times?
You're right. You're lost.
Good luck.
Leonard.
Wake up.
- Sorry.
- For what?
I don't know.
When I'm in bed with a girl,
it's my go-to response.
It's 6 o'clock.
I have to get back to Raj's
before he wakes up
and realizes I'm gone.
Right. Sure.
I wish you could stay
a while longer.
- Me too.
- You know, I was thinking:
There are some great
research facilities in India.
Where are you going with this?
I'm just saying,
I don't have any real ties here,
if I were to move to New Delhi,
we could...
go out.
Didn't we have this conversation
five years ago?
Yes, but...
things have changed.
You're older, I'm older...
Look, no more superhero bed sheets.
Sweetheart,
just because we have fun
when I come to town
doesn't mean I want
to have a serious relationship.
It doesn't?
And besides,
I could never bring
a white boy home to my parents.
They'd have a cow.
Which is a much bigger deal
in India.
I'm not that white.
My great-great-grandmother
was half Cherokee.
That's not the right kind of Indian,
but it is something.
You're funny.
- What?
- I heard a woman laughing.
I was trying to see
if I could laugh as a woman.
Good job.
Quite convincing.
- I smell perfume.
- Air freshener.
And is that lipstick
on your cheek and neck?
- Rash. That's a bad rash.
- My sympathies.
I'm no stranger to the crimson scourge
that is dermatitis.
Can I interest you
in a topical steroid
from my lotion
and unguent collection?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Very well.
I'm sure I can find something
that will help you ditch that itch.
He's in the bathroom.
Let's go.
Do you prefer ointment or cream?
- Cream.
- With or without a numbing agent?
- Without.
- Really, Leonard?
There are no heroes
when it comes to dermatitis.
Fine. With.
- Prescription strength or not?
- Use your best judgment.
Well, I think I have
a nice 2009 AnaMantle HC.
It's usually indicated
for acutely inflamed hemorrhoids,
but it also goes nicely
with non-mucosal body parts.
- Sounds great.
- Excellent choice.
Okay, hurry, hurry.
Come on, come on.
Good morning, Sheldon.
For shame, Leonard,
for shame.
And to think, I was ready to waste
the last of my good
hemorrhoid cream on you.
Making pretty good time?
Is that really what you want
to talk about?
What do you want to talk about?
Please don't tell anyone
I spent the night with Raj's sister.
There it is.
What if someone asks?
No one's going to ask
if I spent the night with her.
Perhaps...
but they might ask me
something else.
- Like what?
- Like
"Has Leonard betrayed any
of his friends recently?"
Priya and I are both adults.
I didn't betray Raj.
In fact, you did,
but I was referring to Howard.
- What are you talking about?
- April 12, 2005.
Bob's Big Boy, Toluca Lake.
Raj had just introduced us to Priya
for the first time.
She was enjoying the sweet taste
of Hindu rebellion
in the form of a Bob's
Super Big Boy hamburger.
In order to preserve your friendship,
you and Howard made a pinky swear
that neither of you
would attempt to woo her.
I had a patty melt.
Fine, I betrayed Howard.
- And Raj.
- All right, and Raj.
And me.
- You?
- Violation of the Roommate Agreement's
overnight guest notification clause.
Okay, fine,
I-I'm a horrible human being.
I'm the Darth Vader of Pasadena.
You're far too short
to be Darth Vader.
At best you might be
a turncoat Ewok.
My point is:
Priya's gone
and it would be much better
if no one else found out about us.
You mean you want me
to keep a secret?
- I can't keep a secret.
- You can if you try.
Think about it this way:
if I were Batman
and you were Alfred,
you'd keep that secret, right?
Why do you get to be Batman?
Because Batman has the secret.
- Alfred has secrets, too.
- Like what?
Alfred knows
that Barbara Gordon is Batgirl.
Which I've now told to Batman.
See, I cannot keep a secret.
What?
It's short for
- Kind of busy here.
- I know, that's why I shortened it.
What do you want?
I came to go over your alibi
for last night.
- What alibi?
- You've asked me
to lie on your behalf,
and as you know,
I am deeply uncomfortable
with impromptu dishonesty,
so I've provided you
with an ironclad alibi.
You couldn't have spent last night
with Priya
because you were with another woman.
I'm so sure I'm gonna regret this,
but who was I with?
The fun-loving and morally loose
Miss Maggie McGarry.
Oh, God.
You met her at Pasadena's
most popular Irish watering hole,
Lucky Baldwin's,
where Maggie
spends her nights tending bar
with a head full of curls
and a heart full of dreams.
"Leonard, call me if you
are interested in coitus.
"Sincerely, Maggie McGarry."
And if anyone were to actually
call that number,
they will hear this.
Top of the morning to you.
You've reached Maggie McGarry.
Leave a message
after the wee little beep.
It's pretty convincing, huh?
That wasn't even a real person.
And here is the clincher:
a lock of Maggie's
flaming auburn hair.
- Where'd you get that?
- From an orangutan in the primate lab.
- An orangutan?
- No one's going
to run a DNA test on it, Leonard.
Honestly, you overthink everything.
I don't need an alibi.
Nobody's going to ask
about last night
as long as you just zip your lip.
Thank you.
Don't worry, everything
is going to be fine.
Will you please tell Howard my sister
has never been attracted to him?
Come on, Raj,
how am I supposed to know
who she is attracted to
or was attracted to
or who she might be
attracted to in the future?
And I have nothing to contribute
to this conversation.
Because I, too,
know absolutely nothing
about Priya's preferences
in male companionship.
And with that, I will re-zip my lip.
What did you think of the new episode
of Caprica last night?
- I didn't see it.
- Didn't see it?
What were you doing?
- I was out.
- What, on Caprica night?
Yeah, I went for a drink.
Really, you?
Where'd you go?
To...
Lucky Baldwin's.
I've heard of that place.
Isn't that Pasadena's favorite Irish
watering hole?
Did you meet
anyone interesting there,
perhaps a promiscuous,
redheaded barmaid?
As a matter of fact...
I can't...
I can't do it.
Sure you can, you're doing fine,
it's very believable.
I'm sorry but the truth is,
I was with Priya last night.
Don't listen to him.
He's still light-headed
from all the Irish whiskey
and pickled eggs in his system.
- What were you doing with her?
- I believe they engaged in coitus,
but more importantly,
if Leonard had not abandoned his story,
would you have found it plausible?
You slept with my sister?!
How could you?
We had a pact.
Excuse me,
"How could you? She's my sister"
takes precedence
over a five-year-old pinky swear.
May I point out,
in a parallel universe,
your friends are saying
"Maggie McGarry, she sounds lovely."
I admit it,
I may have crossed a line here,
but come on,
your sister is a grown woman,
and to her, I'm a forbidden piece
of white chocolate.
I don't believe it.
This is a terrible betrayal of my trust.
No, would it help if I told you
that I offered her my heart,
and she kind of stomped on it?
How hard did she stomp?
Very hard.
I'm good.
I want to say
that I'd never betray your trust.
Unlike Leonard, I respect you.
Really?
Was it out of respect
that you didn't tell Raj
about the time you dropped
his iPhone in a urinal?
Dude, I put that thing on my face!
I think a more amusing
violation of Raj's trust
is when Howard convinced him
that foreigners give presents
to Americans on Thanksgiving.
I didn't see you giving back
your Snoopy snow cone maker.
That was all a lie?
This year's gifts are already wrapped.
And as long as we're talking
about betraying our friends,
how about the month Sheldon
spent grinding up insects
- and mixing them into Leonard's food?
- Well, excuse me.
That was not a betrayal.
That was an experiment to determine
at what concentration
food starts tasting "mothy."
You put moths in my food?
For science.
I can't believe you kissed
my sister with moth mouth.
I can't believe you
used Sheldon's toothbrush.
You used my toothbrush?
Not the brush part,
just the little rubber thing
to pick food from my teeth
and massage my gums.
Okay, I think it's safe to say
that we've all done some things
we're not particularly proud of.
But come on, we're friends.
Friends overlook
each other's minor lapses.
For the record,
I'm sorry that I broke our pact.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry about your phone
and Thanksgiving.
And while we're at it, you don't have
to wash our clothes on the 4th of July.
As long as we're apologizing,
I'm sorry I used your toothbrush.
And I'm sorry...
but that behavior is beyond the pale
and cannot be tolerated.
We are no longer friends.
I got you a talking Thomas
the Tank Engine for Thanksgiving.
With real puffing smoke?
All right.
But I'm watching you.
Hey, you've got Snoopy out.
Can I have a snow cone?
Well, sure.
Pretty good.
What flavor is this?
Guess.
- Papaya?
- No.
- Guava?
- You're so close.
- I give up.
- Mango caterpillar.
What are you doing?!
You said you liked it.