It's my new interview outfit.
Like, "hey,
nice to meet you."
Can't wait
for the interview."
Um, I... maybe the h...
- maybe the hat.
- Yeah.
Lose this?
To win an election,
you have to be good,
and you have to be lucky.
Buddy Wood hosts the number-one
morning show in Indianapolis,
and he wants to interview me
for a series he's doing
on local elections.
And last year the five people
that he profiled all won.
This is a huge break for us.
Um... hey.
M-maybe we should put a pause
on the fashion show.
We have to go over
your talking points.
Keep going.
I can still hear you.
Um, okay, Ms. Knope,
what is going to be
your first major
public works project?
Oh, I don't know.
But I bet these pants
will work for the public.
- Whoo!
- Yeah, those pants look dope!
- Right?
- Oh, my God, those look great.
And I bet they look even better
on Ben's floor.
- Oh!
- Are you hitting on Leslie...
Wait a second.
Just turn around.
What?
Oh.
It says "Nympho"
on the butt
in silver, sparkly letters.
Nympho means
you're addicted to sex,
and since it's on the butt,
there's other implications
as well.
So those are a maybe.
Sync by Alice | www.addic7ed.com
♪
Who was Laura Mulvey?
Laura Mulvey was...
- A guy...
- Girl.
Right. Women's studies.
They're all girls.
Laura Mulvey was a feminist
film critic who...
Wrote a major essay
that helped shift
the orientation
of film theory
to the psychoanalytical
framework!
Treat, please.
I'm about to take
my first-ever final
for my women's studies class.
Treat!
Usually, tests scare me,
but this is an oral exam.
Uh, and if there's
one thing I know is...
My fantastic...
it's talk.
God, I don't know.
Man, I'm so nervous.
I know... I'm just gonna
call the Professor,
and then I'm gonna
get on the phone
and make
some fake barfing sounds,
and then I'm just gonna bail,
so give me my phone.
No! Andrew...
That's now how grown-ups
handle tough situations.
- Well, I...
- We face our fears head-on.
Told you... if you can't
remember what some woman did,
just tear up and say,
"she changed my life."
Ah, that's a good call.
I think this is it.
But do I need a hat,
like a bowler,
or an edgy scarf?
No, those endless scarves
that come out of your sleeves
like a magician.
Um... I think you should just
go with something basic...
No nonsense.
Mr. Wood, hello.
God, he is more tightly wound
than ever.
Maybe we should see if he can
pull that rod out of his butt
and we can hang
some of those outfits on it.
Ann and I have
the occasional rough patch
in our relationship.
But right now,
we're really in a groove.
We've gone 30 hours
without breaking up.
Our personal best
is 47 hours.
It happened when she was
out of town for two days
and she forgot
we were dating.
Well, let me know
if anything changes.
Thank you.
- Interview's off.
- What?
Buddy has to fly back
to Indianapolis early...
something about
a factory explosion.
Come on, did anyone
even get hurt?
Sorry.
First stroke of luck
we've had, and it's gone.
Okay, well, we just
have to work harder.
I mean, good news is,
we can call it a night
and get a super-early start
on our door-to-door tomorrow.
Ooh, that is great news.
And, you know, we might even
be able to make it back
in time for boring club.
Do you know who the president
or boring club is?
Me?
Nope...
You lost the election
'cause your speech
was too boring.
Hey, why don't we all
go get a drink,
blow off some steam?
Everybody's been
working so hard.
Um... Well, we're
in the homestretch here,
and losing that interview
didn't help.
I'm gonna go over
some polling numbers
and turn in early.
I suggest you do the same.
Hey, Leslie,
give you a ride home?
Ah, screw it.
I got a new outfit.
My hair looks amazing.
And I have a serious excess
of pre-interview adrenaline.
Who's gonna drink with me?
- Ooh...
- Oh...
Susan Bronwell, or B.,
Anthony...
was born in Adams,
Massachusetts, in 1820,
and she played a pivotal role
- in the institution of women's suffrage.
- Andy...
- Treat, please.
- Andy, slow down.
You're taking this class
pass/fail.
So I'm just looking
for a freewheeling discussion
about, you know, what you
got from the class.
Oh. Okay.
I would say
what I find very cool
about Susan B. Anthony is...
How...
She was born
in Adams, Massachusetts,
in 1820.
You know?
Just one man's opinion.
I passed!
I got a "P"!
- Congrats, babe.
- Yeah! Mmm!
I was hoping for a P-plus,
but that does not exist.
- Right?
- Right.
Yes, so, basically,
best grade in the class...
tied for the best grade
in the class.
Ron, I am
a college graduate now.
- No, you're not.
- I'm a college course...
Graduate, and it's all
because of you.
It's my pleasure, son.
I'm really proud of you.
How about a steak?
- Yeah!
- You guys have a good time.
Oh, Professor,
why don't you come with us?
- Is that cool?
- Sure.
We'll let you pay
for your own food,
because of equality.
I guess now that the class
is over,
there's nothing wrong
with it.
Are you gonna wear that?
Okay, I'm calling it.
I have a date
with my bathtub,
a glass of red wine,
and a gigantic fireman
named Marcus.
I'm gonna keep plugging
away for a bit.
You don't mind this work,
do you?
Uh-uh.
I like it.
It makes sense to me.
Mmm. This was such
a good idea.
Should we get another round?
Um...
I think we should get
a more basic,
no-nonsense beverage.
Uh... maybe we should all
just drink
sensible portions of milk.
I mean, I love him.
It's just...
This campaign has turned
fun, dorky Ben
- into grumpy, stress-ball Ben.
- Mm.
It's like dealing
with a strict mother
who I am confusingly
attracted to.
- Mm.
- Ben is like a MILF.
You just need
to blow off some steam.
- He should just get that.
- Yeah.
- You're Leslie Knope!
- Right!
No one takes this
more seriously than you do!
- Tell me about it!
- Yes!
- Tequila shots?
- Ohh!
To Knope 2012.
Mm.
Ahh.
Ding-dong.
Oh.
Hello. Lady Knope.
I mean Leslie Knope.
- Hey.
- Oh, hey, Ben.
Where are you?
I'm in, uh, the house
watching TV right now.
I'm watching, um...
Murder She Wrote.
I'm watching Murder She Wrote.
Amazing news... Buddy Wood's
flight was delayed.
So, if we can get
to the airport right now,
the interview's back on.
What? Wow!
Whay could be wrong with that?
Nothing.
Anyway, here comes me...
- To the airport.
- Great.
I'll see you there...
as soon as possible.
Okay, bye.
The interview is back on!
- Whoo! Yes!
- I know!
We are so "drucky."
I mean "lunky."
Ok, both the cabs in this town
are busy.
But I still had eight hours
rental time
on that hot-tub limousine that
I got for your campaign event,
- and it's on its way.
- That's smart.
You're smart.
Diddly diddly diddly
diddly swag.
- You did it right!
- I did it right.
- Ah!
- Ha ha!
33 hours.
Okay, look, this interview
is a big deal, you guys.
This is a game changer, okay?
I have to do well.
Listen, let's do
practice interview...
Big idea, Ann.
- And see how you do.
- Let's go.
Leslie,
in your humble opinion...
What?
- Why are you from Russia?
- I don't know.
Hey, Ron is the guy
I wrote about
for that paper on positive
male role models.
Oh, yeah, that was one
of your most readable papers.
According to Andy,
you're quite the feminist.
I don't consider myself
an anything-ist,
but my life has been shaped
by powerful women.
My father
once told my mother
that woman was made
from the rib of Adam,
and my mom broke his jaw.
My Uncle Lon once
tried to...
Is that Chris?
You know,
it really looks like him.
But there's no way
to know for sure.
We should ask him tomorrow.
Hey.
April Ludgate.
Why are you here
eating alone?
I'm not.
I'm surrounded by friends...
Friends I don't know yet.
And I'm engrossed
in this book.
It's the true story
of a woman born
with no arms and no legs
who attempted to swim
the English Channel.
- That's impossible.
- Oh, she drowned immediately.
It's kind of a sad story.
Cool.
I'm over there with people
you actually know...
If you want
to come join us.
Thank you.
Bye, friend.
Bye.
I'm sorry, Marcus, I'm gonna
have to cancel our bath.
Something interesting
is happening.
I want to watch it.
I don't know, Marcus.
I'll hit you up
when I hit you up.
Wow, I feel totally normal.
I'm ready to do this.
Thank you for accommodating us
on such short notice.
Hey, for Leslie Knope,
anytime.
Just let me know if you
need anything else, all right?
Thanks, Paul. Hey, you got
those new I.D. Badges.
They finally upgraded us...
- security swipe and everything.
- Wow, look at that.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
Hey, thanks again
for fighting for them.
"Helpy" to hop out.
Leslie Knope.
Buddy Wood.
- Buddy Wood.
- Glad you could make it.
Glad you could make it.
Thank you so much
for being here,
and welcome to the greatest
city in the world.
Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're being serious.
We're setting up over there,
found a small piece of carpet
without a horrifying
smellscape.
I'll be right there.
Hey, do I seem normal
to you?
Like, does everything
seem fine?
- Yeah, yeah... you seem fine.
- I seem okay?
- Uh-huh.
- I don't seem distracted
or babbly or anything?
No, it's great.
So you're gonna do great.
- You're gonna do smart.
- What's that?
- Look who I found.
- Hi.
Professor Linda,
this is Chris.
Chris, this is...
Professor Linda?
It is a genuine pleasure
to meet you.
- Oh, you as well.
- Hi, there.
Would you like to hear
our specials?
No need.
Porterhouse, rare,
quickly.
Same.
I'll have
the, uh, spinach salad.
What kind of dressings
do you have?
Oh! Linda, in case
you're interested,
I brought my own dressing.
You really
can't be doing that.
Well, this is the last time.
I promise.
It contains
extra-virgin olive oil,
a little bit of lemon,
and hint of turmeric.
Sounds great.
Pawnee, Indiana,
home to
the Sweetums Candy Corporation,
19 toxic-waste repositories,
and not much else.
This sleepy mini-Metropolis
is the site of a fascinating
city council race.
Joining us today is one
of the candidates, Leslie Knope.
Leslie, welcome...
to Good Morning.
It's my pleasure.
Thank you for being
on my show.
Leslie, we're here
at the Pawnee municipal airport,
which I must add is...
rather decrepit.
Well, I'm glad
you mentioned it.
It is in desperate need
of refurbishments.
And that is why I'm going
to make it a centerpiece
- of my platform.
- Okay.
Take, uh...
Joe Appledemas over there.
Joe, say hi.
Hello.
Joe has been working here
since 1996,
and his salary
has not been raised a nickel.
I am gonna work
very hard to change...
Okay, this airport seems to me
like a metaphor.
Are you familiar
with the term?
Pawnee's airport is symbolic
of the town...
out of touch,
out of date, perhaps,
lost, insignificant,
and sad.
Your thoughts?
Well, granted,
we don't have
big-city amenities,
but I think
we more than make up for it
with friendly faces
and hand-working hards...
hardworking hands.
If you say so.
I say it's sad.
Moving on...
Oh, my God.
If they got together,
they would make
the most beautiful super baby.
It would rule us all.
But what if super baby
became too powerful?
I guess we'll just have
to take that chance.
Chris got dumped
by Jerry's daughter.
He needs this.
Plus, if they get married,
he'll spend
all his time with her,
and I might never have
to talk to him again.
Hmm.
Professor Linda,
you have...
Really nice arms.
- Oh?
- Do you work out?
I was gonna say
the exact same thing.
But I didn't want you to think
that I was objectifying you
with my male gaze.
May I see?
Oh, sure.
Oh, my good gracious.
You have...
- extraordinary caput laterale.
- Thank you.
There's nothing more important
than physical health.
- I agree.
- Kendra?
- Yes?
- You know what?
I am gonna have
that third steak after all.
Go ahead and put that order in
now, please, and thank you.
Your campaign hit
a snag of sorts,
with the revelation that you
and your boss, Ben Wyatt,
were having
une affaire de coeur...
affair of the heart.
Well, I've discussed that
many times,
and there's really
nothing more to say.
I would rather talk
about the ways
to solve problems
in this town.
Good luck with that.
But getting back
to your affair with Ben Wyatt,
who's now
your campaign manager...
Buddy, frankly,
I don't want to discuss that.
But if you'd like,
we can talk about ways
that I can improve the airport
or our many wonderful parks.
I don't.
I'd like to talk
about you and Ben Wyatt.
Uh-oh.
I know that look.
- She's got the crazy eyes.
- Yeah.
Well, like I said,
I don't want
to discuss it, Buddy,
and, frankly, I don't appreciate
your condescending tone.
But you know what?
I've had a couple drinks,
so what the hell?
Ben and I first...
I'm sorry, Ms. Knope,
are you inebriated?
What? No.
Preposterous.
- Are you ine...
Ebriated?
That was bad timing.
This is a Buddy Wood first...
an exclusive interview
with potential city councilwoman
Leslie Knope,
who appears to be drunk
right now on camera.
I am not drunk.
Yes, when you have
a jumbo Margarita
and some flaming Tequila
shots, you can get drunk.
Is it this sad,
pathetic town
that makes you drink
this way?
- This interview is over.
- Okay, Ms. Knope.
Oh...
This... this is not
because I'm drunk.
This is because of the wire.
A fitting end
to a bizarre interview
and a sad moment
in a depressing city
with no hope,
in the waning moments
of the bitter saga
that has been
a contentious campaign.
C'mon Buddy,
you cannot air that tape.
Are you kidding?
This is as great for me
as it is terrible for you.
The sheep that watch my show
are gonna eat this up
like tiramisu.
Tiramisu is
an Italian dessert often...
I know what
tiramisu is, okay?
- And sheep don't eat it.
- Sorry, but...
Tomorrow morning
this gets broadcast
around the entire
Indiana-sphere.
Thank you for celebrating
the most ultimate triumph
of my life.
I'm very proud of me,
and you are too.
And, Professor, I'm taking
your class again next semester.
And I'm gonna lock down
that P-plus.
It's impossible.
You and the women taught me
that nothing is impossible.
Alright, I better be going.
- I have to get up early.
- Good-bye.
I'm teaching a morning
Zumba class for retirees.
Before I do,
Linda, do you enjoy
land kayaking?
It's quite fun.
Well, it's more grueling
than fun.
But I would love
to take you.
I'm really flattered,
but I just got
out of a relationship,
and I think
I need a little more time
before I jump into anything.
Of course.
I understand.
- I'm sorry.
- I appreciate your caution.
- Thank you.
- I hope to see you again.
Good-bye, everyone.
Anybody want to go to JJ's
for some after-dinner omelets?
Or how about you and I
go back to my place?
Yes.
Wow!
Ben, I am so sorry.
Let's just focus
on the problem.
Now, if we don't stop
that interview
from airing in the morning,
this campaign is dead.
So...
We have to go
to Indianapolis.
- And do what?
- I don't know, Tom.
I guess we'll just set fire
to the studio or something.
Ah, that's so sweet...
I've never had a boyfriend
threaten to commit arson
for me before.
Ah, it gets old.
We still have
six hours of rental time
on the hot-tub limo.
We could take that.
No one would have to drive
all night.
That's actually a good idea.
Plus, it allows
for the possibility
of high-speed skinny-dipping.
Ugh.
Ann, I was joking.
Come on, it was a joke.
It was funny.
Where we going, folks...
drive around,
hit the strip clubs?
- Yeah!
- No.
We're going to this address
in Indianapolis.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know, no one ever used
this hot-tub limo
for actual transportation.
And I can't take this thing
on the highway,
so it'll take
a few extra hours.
Hey, is this
a seven or a one?
Jerry.
Jerry!
Maybe you should wrap it up.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
Is it really?
Oh, my gosh.
Wow.
Well, that flew by, huh?
I will just take these
down to the post office
and, uh, put the, uh...
Oh, jeez.
Oh, no.
I put the handout flyers
in the mailing envelopes,
and I was supposed to put
these flyers in the envelopes.
Oh...
My God.
Well, you know,
it's like I always say.
It ain't government work if you
don't have to do it twice.
Here we go!
I'll make some coffee.
Hey, you're blocking
my driveway.
Leslie Knope?
- What are you doing?
- Hi, um...
Mr. Wood, I'm so sorry.
We... oh, my God, I can't see.
It's so bright out here.
- Ohh.
- We drove here to ask you...
No, to beg you
to please destroy that tape.
Yeah, I got
your 50 messages.
Leslie was just out with her
friends blowing off some steam.
- What?
- Please. Please.
Please, please, please.
That's five pleases.
As much as I enjoy
the groveling,
I can't destroy the tape
because I don't have it,
because your sad,
tiny backwater airport
lost my bags.
Oh, really?
You'd think
a commuter airport
could handle the luggage
of 11 people at once,
but apparently not.
Completely ruined
a great story.
Thank God for that
mitten factory tragedy.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
- God, that's...
- Okay.
- Great. Uh...
- We should... yeah.
- We're gonna go.
- Good-bye.
Ah, screw it.
Yay!
Fun Ben lives.
April, Andrew...
Good morning
to you both.
Doughnuts...
go nuts.
Hey, you kids
need any money?
- No.
- Go buy yourself a Walkman.
How much is a Walkman
nowadays?
Probably more than $20.
Here's $25.
Hi, guys,
I just wanted to come by
and thank you
for a phenomenal evening.
Yeah, seems like we all
had a phenomenal evening.
And I should
probably thank you
for introducing me to Linda.
I think we had
a deep emotional connection
that is very worth
exploring.
So I'm gonna
ask her out again...
When she's
emotionally ready.
- Hmm.
- Hey, Ron...
Great red shirt.
Dude, Ron... you have to tell
him what happened.
Why?
It's none of his business.
Because he's been
super sad lately.
It kind of seems like you should
at least give him a heads-up
so he doesn't get
rejected again.
I like to not get involved
in these matters
or any matters
of any nature.
Uh, you know, Ron,
someone once told me
that this is not how grown-ups
deal with tough situations.
We face them head-on.
Fine.
Oh, my God, Ron...
It was you
who told me that.
That's crazy.
There's that shirt.
Look, Chris...
After the bar last night,
I...
engaged in consensual activities
with Linda.
- I see.
- I didn't plan it.
But it occurred.
Now you know.
Well, thank you for being
forthright and telling me.
You're a good man, Ron.
I'm quite lonely.
Ah, [Bleep].
They say
to win an election,
you have to be good,
and you have to be lucky.
I got pretty damn lucky
when I met Ben.
And I'm lucky
that Ann and Tom
and all my other friends
volunteer to help me out.
And I'm super lucky that
that tape disappeared.
I think we may have used up
all our luck tonight.
Actually, not all of it.
He's about to get lucky.
It's... it's on.
He doesn't even know it yet.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
- Hey.
- Hey, sweetheart.
I'm not sure
you're even aware of this,
but we have now gone 48 hours
without breaking up,
shattering
our previous record.
That's not bad.
- To celebrate...
- Oh, please, don't.
Whatever this is,
I don't want it.
Just a little
48-hour anniversary gift.
- Condoms.
- 48 of 'em.
Different flavor
for each hour.
Yeah, we're not dating
any more, okay? Get out.
- No, wait. - Get out.
- Don't punish me.
- I took a risk.
- Yeah. Bye.