- Okay... hole me.
[quirky music]
Mm!
- Nothin' but mouth.
- Whoa, impressive.
- Are you kidding me?
That's uh-nothing.
Diaz has been chucking D-holes
into my mouth-piece since
we were back at the academy.
Check this out.
[NWA's "Express Yourself']
♪ Oh!
[all cheering]
♪ Express yourself
♪ I'm expressing
♪ With my full capabilities
and now I'm living ♪
♪ In correctional facilities
♪ 'Cause some don't agree
with how I do this ♪
[all cheering]
♪ Droppin' flavor
my behavior is hereditary ♪
♪ But my technique
is very necessary ♪
♪ Blame it on Ice Cube
♪ Because he said it gets
- Oh!
all: Oh!
- Uh-oh.
Heads!
- What the...?
[smacks lips]
It's finally happening!
[upbeat music]
♪
- Attention, Nine-Nine.
We have an announcement.
- "Shrek Live" is coming back
to Broadway!
- Nope, you dreamed that.
- Aw.
- We just came in here
to tell you to save the date,
because we're getting
married on May 15th.
We found a venue!
[cheers and applause]
- Wow!
Finding a place in the spring
in New York is impossible.
Sharon and I had to get married
in Albany in December.
Terry was too cold
to consummate.
- Hm, good to know.
- We got really lucky.
The place was booked solid
for the next two years,
but a couple fell out.
- Of a fifth-floor window.
She was teetering
and he tried to grab her—
- Babe, we agreed we wouldn't
talk about that part.
- Right—sorry.
It was gruesome.
Never again.
The EMTs said that
it was a meat pancake.
I'm done.
- So, tell us about the venue.
- Oh, well,
there's not much to tell—
other than
it's a gorgeous mansion!
- Big ol' house!
- With a professional kitchen.
- Chop-chop, y'all!
- Ooh.
- A private library
for the ceremony.
- My girl loves books!
- Seven bathrooms!
- No lines, ladies!
- And an outdoor
reception area.
- Uh-can I get a gazebo?
[imitates record scratching]
I apologize to
a host of communities.
The point is, these nuptials
are going to be "toit"!
- Speaking of "toit nups,"
we better get going,
because we don't have
a lot of time and we have
to meet with
17 wedding vendors.
- A jam-packed schedule
that could only be achieved
by a type-A personality!
- Jake.
- Yep, we gotta go.
- I have some
unfortunate news.
An NYPD officer has
gone missing.
The department suspects
foul play.
- Oh, my God.
Do we know the officer?
- Yes, it's...
Sergeant Peanut Butter.
- My nemesis.
- Your nemesis is a horse?
- Are you still mad
at Peanut Butter
because he won a medal
the same day as you?
- He totally upstaged me.
He Tucci-ed me!
Look what you get
if you do an image search
of "Charles Boyle,
medal of valor."
Huh? They cropped me out
of my own photo!
- You just keep that tab open
on your phone all the time?
- No, I just looked it up
real fast.
You didn't see.
- Captain, I solved it.
Charles kidnapped
Peanut Butter.
- [laughs sarcastically]
I did not.
But it's no surprise
that somebody did.
- Hey, my kids love that horse.
- Your kids need help wiping
their butts, Sarge.
They're not exactly geniuses.
- The actual suspect
is Jesse Gurmwald,
a disgruntled civilian admin
who was recently fired
by the mounted unit.
He's gone to ground,
but detectives throughout
the city are checking
every possible hideout.
Diaz, Boyle: here's a list
of locations in our precinct.
Be thorough.
- Yes, sir.
And just to be clear,
if I went missing,
you guys would conduct
an equally thorough search,
right?
- You should get going.
- So, we can wrap it in silk,
or, for a more rustic feel...
burlap.
- Oh... that's neat, but...
- We want these nups
to be toit.
- Excuse me?
- Could we wrap the flowers
in "New York Times"
crossword puzzles
from key dates in our lives?
- Oh—is that something
you'd like?
- Uh, boi-oi-oi-oi-oing!
[laughs]
Here's the deposit.
- I designed you
a signature cocktail.
I call it the "Peraltiago."
both: Ooh!
[upbeat music]
- Mm... and the judges give
it a score of...
- Jeremy,
did you make that cake
that I called you about?
- Yes, I wasn't entirely sure
if you were joking or not,
but...
- A Nakatomi Plaza cake?
The groom is on
a licorice hose.
- [as Bruce Willis]
Welcome to the wedding, pal.
- [breathless]
Oh, Amy.
These nups may
be getting too toit.
- Since Diaz and Boyle are
searching for Peanut Butter,
I need you to be available
to work
any cases that might come in.
- Of course, Captain.
My pleasure.
Morning, Amanda.
- Oh, and I thought
we should transfer
the Glenmoore assault
to the Nine-Eight.
- Absolutely.
Brian.
Looking swole.
- You're looking swole.
Is today leg day?
- Legs for an hour,
two hours blasting the glutes.
Terry's got butt for days!
[laughs]
- Excuse me?
- I said,
"Terry's got butt for days!"
- Please stop talking
about my body.
- What?
- I'm Teri.
You just said
I had "butt for days."
- Oh, I see what just happened.
Terry's gonna regret this.
- Are you threatening me?
- No!
No, no.
This is a misunderstanding.
My name is also Terry,
and I was talking
about my butt.
- So you were complimenting
your own body?
- Well, I'm pretty proud of it.
Do you know how old I am?
- Okay.
Apology accepted.
Seems pretty arrogant, though.
- This might not
be the right time,
but talking about yourself
in the third person
has finally—
- Terry knows!
- I love our venue so much.
- Me too.
It's like
our very own Hogwarts.
- Yes!
And I'm Hermione.
And I am Snape.
- What?
- I never realized I could
have feelings this strong
about a building.
- Okay, we just have to
drop off our deposit,
and then we're done
for the day.
- [in posh British accent]
Well, it would appear
that we have achieved
what scholars refer to
as the "toitest of nups"!
- [in British accent]
Indeed!
both: [in accents] Ooh!
Oh, hi Susan.
- Hey.
- We're normal people.
- Hi, I was just about
to call you guys.
- Ah, well, no need to call,
because we are here.
And we've got our deposit.
- Thank you so much.
We just booked all our vendors.
It's really happening.
- Yeah, about that...
- Wait, what's wrong?
Something's wrong.
That's the look my mom gave me
right before
she told me that my dad left.
Oh, God, did my dad leave
my mom again?
How do you know my mom and dad?
- You know, I'm so sorry.
There must have been a mix-up.
Someone just contacted
my manager
and booked the venue
before you got here.
- But we had an oral agreement.
You said we had until
the end of the day—EOD.
It's not EOD.
The D hasn't E'd.
It won't be E'd for ages!
- I'm sorry.
It's out of my hands, you know?
Someone just swooped in
and got it.
- Wait.
Susan—Susan!
- [gasping] Who?
Who would do that?
- Amy, we had something great
in the palm of our hands,
and then someone swooped in
at the last minute
and stole it?
There's only one person
who would do that.
- No.
But... it couldn't be!
- Ah, but it is.
[metal guitar riff]
both: The Vulture!
- [cackling]
Suckers.
- Oh, no.
Our nups have been un-toitened.
We've got loose nups.
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's your game here,
Vulture, huh?
Why are you renting our venue?
- Why do you think, meat farts?
I'm getting married.
- Really?
You once told me that marriage
is for women and gays.
- And that the only thing
you're married to
is banging married chicks.
- Yeah, and I meant it all.
But love?
Love hath changed me.
- No it hathn't.
You just vultured our venue.
- Yeah, but I did it for love.
My fiancée,
she means everything to me.
You know,
she's hot like a chick,
she's smart like a guy.
Just talking to her
gives me a Harrelson.
- Harrelson?
- Woody.
- Ew.
- Yeah.
Look, I know I've become
that gross, sappy guy,
but dude, she's the first chick
I ever wanted
to hang out with post-bang.
- I can't believe a real person
has agreed to marry you.
- Oh, my lady's real,
all right.
Her name is Jean Munhroe,
and we complete the living hell
out of each other...
sometimes twice a night.
[both groan]
[cell phone twangs]
Hey, you know what?
I need to handle this
right now.
Look, I know how hard it is
to find a venue.
But if it could happen for me,
it could happen for you.
- It happened for you
because it did happen for us.
- Chins up, dingdongs.
I'm trying to be happy
over here.
- Ugh.
- [scoffs]
- Jake, what are we gonna do?
We already gave deposits
to all our vendors.
- We're gonna get
this place back.
- How?
The Vulture's not gonna budge.
- Yeah, maybe, but he does
have a weak spot: his woman.
Not that women are weak.
Just, she's our best shot,
and she happens to be a woman.
- Totally.
Let's go talk to
that spineless skank.
- Yeah.
- Why do we even have
police horses anymore?
We have motorcycles now.
They're faster, cooler.
They also don't get boners
in the background
of every photo
of you and the mayor.
- What do you mean?
A horse is a perfect partner.
Tough, scary,
and they don't show you
30 pictures of their kid
dressed as Wario for Halloween.
I'm not talking about Nikolaj.
- I literally just showed you
those pictures
five minutes ago.
- Really?
I don't remember that.
- Hmm.
[horse chuffs]
[tense music]
NYPD!
Hands where we can see 'em!
- Step away from Peanut Butter.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
what's going on?
You guys thought
you could catch me?
[lighter clicks]
[horse neighs]
- [grunts]
I'll head him off.
- Fine,
I'll get the dumb horse.
[grunts]
All right.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
[strains]
Come on, you idiot!
[grunting]
Run!
Ugh, you dumb horse.
Ha!
[horse whinnies]
[screaming]
Peanut Butter!
[horse whinnying]
Stop!
Peanut Butter, stop!
- Boyle!
Just let go!
- Okay, we have to force
the She-Vulture,
Jean Munhroe, to give us
our venue back,
so put on your game face,
'cause we're about to
stare down the devil.
- Devil can't stare
if the devil's got
tears in her eyes
and blood in her ears.
- Oh, I love your intensity.
All right,
this is where she works.
"The Zenith Fund."
Ulch, it even sounds evil.
- Of course it is.
She's marrying the Vulture.
Everything about her is evil.
- Time to enter
the den of bastards
who deserve to die.
All right, snake,
show your face—it's a charity.
Amy, it's a charity.
- Look at this:
"Jean, your selflessness
"puts us all to shame.
Humbled, Michelle Obama."
both: Damn, Jean.
- Hi.
Can I help you?
- Uh, yes.
We're looking for Jean Munhroe.
We know her fiancé.
- Oh, I'm Jean.
Are you Jake and Amy?
Keith has told me
all about you.
He says you guys are the best.
- Really?
Keith says that?
- [laughing] Yeah—oh, Janice?
That village needs rice.
Double the last shipment.
Just take the overage
out of my paycheck.
So, what brings you guys
to the Zenith Fund?
- Uh... actually,
something super important—
[cell phone vibrates]
- Oh, I am so sorry.
I've gotta take this.
- Mm-hmm.
- What do you mean,
"roadblock"?
Do I have to fly down there
and talk to the rebels myself?
Just get the rice
to those kids.
Asante sana, Rafiki.
Sorry about that.
- Wow, your job sounds
very intense.
- No, no, no, it's nothing
compared to what
these children go through
on a daily basis.
It really puts things
in perspective.
- Right.
- So,
what was the important thing
you came down here
to talk about?
- Uh... the kids.
And the rice.
- And...
putting the rice...
in the kids.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
we have two new donors!
[applause and bell ringing]
- Yay!
- Ooh, there's a bell.
- Oh!
- [laughs]
[in southern accent]
Do y'all have an ATM?
- Sir, can I get $350
in petty cash?
I need to throw
an ice cream party
for Teri-with-an-I,
make sure
there's no hard feelings.
- Why?
She gets it was
a misunderstanding.
She's a Teri,
and you're a Terrance who,
even though he's not a child,
still goes by a nickname
ending in a Y.
- I mean,
don't people call you Ray?
- How dare you.
- Sir, I don't want any tension
between the squad
and the uniformed officers.
I'm just thinking
about the precinct.
- You're lying.
You're upset because
Teri-with-an-I called you
arrogant, and you have
a pathological need
to be liked.
- What?
No, I don't.
I just happen to be
a great person
who's naturally beloved
by all—
despite my personal
ambivalence.
- Well, if that's true,
then you won't mind
walking across the bullpen
without saying hello
to anybody.
- [scoffs]
No problem.
- No nods allowed.
- What?
Okay, it's gonna be okay.
You're a busy sergeant.
They can't always expect you
to be friendly.
[inhales deeply]
Time to go to frown town.
Let's do this, Jeffords.
- Hey, Sarge.
- Bill!
[laughs]
What up, man?
[dramatic music]
You were right.
Terry loves to be loved!
Hey, Monica!
Hey, Dough. [laughs]
Ooh, who wants a nod?
[laughs]
- Hey.
Any luck finding a new venue
that's available on May 15th?
- Yeah.
May 15, 2026.
- [sighs]
- Please tell me the vendors
are giving us back
our deposits.
- Yes.
One of them.
The photographer.
Provided that you
hang out with him,
so how do you feel about
spending the weekend
on his houseboat in Yonkers?
- Ugh, Jake.
Forget the perfect wedding.
We're screwed.
- I know.
- I can't believe
that saint of a woman
is actually marrying
the Vulture.
- [sighs]
Maybe he's changed.
- How is that even possible?
- I don't know.
Nothing makes sense anymore.
The Vulture's not the Vulture,
good is bad, up is down,
there's a young pope,
winter has come.
That reminds me:
I ordered
some premium cable channels.
[cell phone twangs]
- Hitchcock?
What was that sound?
- I just got an alert
from my hookup app.
I'm about to boink
with a local single in my area.
- Ames.
- Jake.
- Jake!
- Ames!
- Up is up, down is down,
the Vulture still boinks!
[cell phone twangs]
- I need to handle this
right now.
- I can't believe that bastard
is cheating on nice Jean.
- We have to save her.
We have to break them up.
- For nice Jean!
- And the starving kids.
- And Michelle Obama.
- And a little side benefit:
if we break them up,
we get our venue back.
- Yes, but the main reason
is to save a wonderful person
from making a horrible mistake.
- Of course.
That's obviously the point.
The venue is just secondary.
- What venue?
We're great people.
- Hey, Jake.
- See?
- Okay, so the Vulture
is cheating on Jean Munhroe,
which totally tracks, because
he is the epitome of awful.
- Ooh, nice use of "epitome."
- Thanks, babe.
My question is,
why pretend to change?
I mean, why get married at all?
- I'll tell you why.
Because Jean's dad
is worth $100 million,
and she's his only heir.
- Then why did she need
our $1,000?
I mean, I'm so happy
we gave the money
so the kids could have rice
and et cetera.
- So, how do we break them up?
- Simple.
We catfish him
with Hitchcock's hookup app.
Then, when he takes the bait,
we make him end things
with Jean respectfully
and gently.
- Perfect.
She hurts for a bit,
but she eventually moves on,
and she finds
a much better man.
- Yes.
And as a distant,
secondary benefit,
we get the mansion back.
- Agreed.
Okay.
So, let's create a temptress
that will boink-match with him.
- Yeah.
- What's the sexiest name?
- Valerie.
- That was fast.
Do you know a Valerie?
- [chuckling]
No.
I wish.
[clears throat]
All right, she's 19,
from Daytona, and her job
is "spray tannist."
- Ugh, "tannist."
Not a real word.
It's perfect.
- Yeah.
- Okay, she's into
spring break, bong rips,
slurping shots,
and crop tops that say
"little cutie."
- Noice.
- She is not into...
nerds, wearing pants,
needy guys, monogamy,
or feminism,
and her quote is,
"Whatever happened
to 'Girls Gone Wild'?"
- [chuckles] This Valerie
sounds like a real pill.
[chuckles, clears throat]
- Okay.
Let's see who our matches are.
- Here we go.
- [clears throat]
- Uh-huh.
Gross, mm-hmm.
Oh, Hitchcock.
I mean, "Dave, age 28"?
- Ugh.
- Come on.
- Oh!
- Gotcha.
- There he is.
All right.
And so begins
the delicate dance.
We begin with a simple hello.
And then we wait, so as
not to seem too aggressive—
No, he sent us a picture
of his penis!
- [gasps]
[computer twanging]
- Oh, God,
he just sent 15 more.
- Oh, God, it's horrible.
But it's wonderful.
We're gonna save Jean!
- Yes, and we're gonna
get the mansion back!
- Oh, no.
- Yeah, he put a
little hat on it.
- Ugh.
- Hey, there you are.
You okay?
- Yeah, no burns.
The doctor said I was lucky
my body was so damp.
- So why did it take so long?
- Well, the EMT spent
loads of time on Peanut Butter.
But you know what?
I don't care, because I saved
that dumb horse,
so I'm the hero.
And this time,
when I get my medal,
my whole face will be
in the picture.
- You haven't seen "The Post,"
have you?
- What?
No.
Why?
- Somebody was walking
by the fire
and took a picture
on their cell phone.
- What?
That's not what happened.
I saved him.
- That's not how
they're reporting it.
- No, look.
"Daily News" got it right.
Yeah.
"Hero Cop Saves
Helpless Buffoon."
Oh, no.
Am I the buffoon?
- Uh-oh, dropped your phone.
Now we'll never know.
- [sighs]
Wait.
There was a dash cam
in the car.
We have footage
of what really happened!
- Brass already called.
They don't want us releasing
that footage.
A hero horse is good PR
for the department.
Hey, man, uh...
Peanut Butter's going
on "Ellen."
- "Ellen"?
That's my dream!
[sighs] Now he gets to dance
with DJ tWitch!
- What's going on here?
- I'm throwing Teri-with-an-I's
party with my own money.
I didn't know her favorite
kind of ice cream,
so I printed a photo of her
and showed it
to all the ice cream places
within 30 blocks.
Nobody recognized her,
so I got every flavor—
200 pints.
- This is the greatest day
of my life.
- Have you considered
this Teri-with-an-I might not
be an ice cream person?
- I did think that.
That's why there's
a taco bar coming.
- Yes.
- Plus barbecue.
- Plus a popcorn guy.
- [laughing] Yes.
- Plus vegan options.
- Why?
- Sergeant,
you've become unhinged.
There's always gonna
be people in this world
who don't like you.
That's a fact of life.
- I hear you, sir.
But I hate the feeling
of people being mad at me.
- So what?
I was voted least friendly
in high school,
and here I am,
a police captain.
Do you know what Mr. Popularity
Vincent Mondale is doing
these days?
He's a sociologist,
for God's sake.
Sociologist, Terry.
- I'm sorry,
but I gotta do this.
- Okay, but just know...
if you go through
with this party,
I will like you less.
[dramatic music]
- Hello, Vulture.
Got a minute?
Doesn't matter.
We don't care.
- Let me guess.
You guys are here to cry
about the wedding venue
that I stole from you
fair and square, right?
- No.
Actually, we wanna talk to you
about some other things.
Like spring break,
slurping shots,
and hating pants.
- Wait a second,
why does that sound familiar?
- I don't know.
Maybe you should ask... Valerie.
Yeah, that's right.
We catfished you.
- Boom.
- You're Valerie?
Ah, I can't believe
I actually wasted
my sweet dong snaps
on you bozos.
- All right,
here's how this is gonna go.
You are gonna break up
with Jean,
because we all know you're just
marrying her for her money.
- You're gonna do it nicely
and respectfully,
and you're gonna make
a generous donation
to her charity.
- Nice touch, Ames.
- You guys got it all wrong.
I don't care that she's rich.
Look, I love her.
I just got spooked.
You put a vulture into a cage,
and...
[squawks]
It freaks out.
- Actually, vultures do
very well in captivity
and they mate for life.
- Research burn.
- All right, look.
I'm deleting the app
from my phone
as we speak, okay?
Come on.
Jean's over 30.
No amount of money
in the entire world
could make me marry
a woman that old.
But love can.
And will.
- You have two options.
Either you break up with her...
- Or we send her
the penis pics—
even the one next to the—
I'm guessing, a mini soda can?
- Nah, it was regular size.
- Really?
- Oh, Jean's here.
So what's it gonna be?
You gonna tell her,
or do we have to?
- I've changed.
- Nope.
- I won't do it again.
- [groans]
I'll give you the venue.
- Oh.
- What's that?
- I'll give you the venue
if you don't say anything,
but if you do,
I'm gonna keep it.
Even if she and I break up,
all right?
I love her.
I promise you this.
both: Deal.
- Okay.
Now just act normal, please.
- Oh, wow.
What a surprise.
My donors.
- Hello, Jean Munhroe!
- Nice to see you,
Jean Munhroe!
- You all looked so intense
when I got here.
What were you talking about?
- Crime scene.
- Soup.
Uh—soup crime scene.
The Chowder Killer's
back at it again.
- Oh, I haven't heard of him.
- Yeah, well, he just moved
to Manhattan...
from New England.
- You guys are so lucky
to all work together.
Oh, my gosh,
what is Keith like at work?
- Aw, Keith?
Our Keith?
- [chuckles dully]
- Well, he's a real crack-up,
I'll tell you that for free.
We have so many inside jokes.
- So many inside jokes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, guys—potato salad?
[all laughing]
- You wouldn't understand.
It's from work.
- Oh, my gosh,
you guys are so crazy.
- [laughs]
- Yeah.
- So how did you two meet?
- Oh, someone stole
from my charity,
and another detective was
working on the case so hard
for months,
and Keith came in,
and solved it right away.
Swooped in like an eagle.
- That's why my nickname's
the Eagle.
Right, guys?
- Yep.
Everyone calls him...
[struggling]
The Eagle.
- So, when did you
decide to propose?
- Oh—ah, well, we were
just hanging out one night,
and I looked over at Amy
and it hit me.
She's incredible
and my best friend,
and I just knew
in that moment...
I wanted to spend
my life with her.
- I know what you mean.
Keith and I are the same way.
It is so nice to finally find
someone I can trust.
[both groaning]
- Oh, boy.
- I can't do this.
- Yeah, it's bad.
- Jean, we have to
show you something.
- No!
- A penis? Why?
- Yep,
should've explained it first.
- Reese Witherspoon
is optioning
the Peanut Butter story?
What?
- Forget that dumb horse.
Have you seen this?
- "Exclusive Dash Cam
Footage Reveals
Hero Cop Saved
Sergeant Peanut Butter."
I don't understand.
How'd they get this?
- Somebody must have leaked it.
Perfect partner isn't a horse.
The perfect partner
is somebody who,
no matter how much
they hate you,
would run through a fire
to save your life.
- Aw.
Thank you, Rosa.
- You're welcome.
All right, come with me.
We're going to Shaw's.
- Whoa, all this is for me?
- Yep.
You saved Peanut Butter,
even though he's a dick.
- He is a dick.
- To Charles Boyle, everybody!
all: To Charles Boyle!
- Thanks, guys.
- So, Terry, you decided
not to throw a party
for Teri-with-an-I?
- You were right.
Why bother trying
to win over a stranger
when I can make someone
I care about happy instead?
- Well, for the record,
Jeffords...
I like you a lot
and I always have.
- All right.
Whatever.
- I taught him well.
- Who am I kidding?
Terry needs a hug!
[laughing]
- Mm?
[upbeat music]
- Hey, I'm still
a little shaken up.
We did the right thing, right?
- Yes, definitely.
She's way better off
without him.
- And she let him know it.
- Yeah, for a human angel,
girl could throw down.
- I hate wasting rice...
but I hate you more!
- She may be the coolest woman
I've ever met.
- Yeah.
- So, what's up
with the wedding?
Do we need to find a new venue?
- Actually, we found a place
that's available
on the same date.
- Ooh, is it another mansion?
- No, it is not.
- Listen up, everybody!
We are getting married
in a public rec center!
- Super cheap!
- On a basketball court!
- Squeak-squeak!
- With one working bathroom!
- Ladies gotta wait!
- And it's in
deep Staten Island.
- Destination wedding, y'all!
But the point is,
these nuptials are still
gonna be...
mad toit.
I would marry you
in a dumpster.
- Aww, I would marry you
- Dudes, the Vulture's throwing
an all-girl pudding wrestling
party in a mansion in May!
It's the only important thing
happening that day!
- After party?
- Fits our budget.
- Not a doctor.
- Shh.