It's mine.
What?
Give it back.
Mom, Charlie hit me!
Consuela, Charlie hit me.
Mom, Consuela hit me.
Here we go again.
I'll run away, then you'll be sorry.
Mom, Charlie's making me hit myself.
What are you doing up?
Your brother's talking
in his sleep again.
No kidding. What about?
Some childhood dream
about you making him hit himself.
What childhood? That was last week.
Sports Center?
I'm making my picks
for tomorrow's games.
Really, Charlie?
Taking the points
against Georgetown?
You want to throw your money away,
get married without a prenup.
You know something I don't?
So far this year, Georgetown's covered
the spread eight times out of ten.
You bet college basketball?
Only idiots do.
No offense.
- Then how do you know all this stuff?
- I worked for a sports book in Vegas.
Then I opened my business in the back
of a candle shop in Sherman Oaks.
I always wondered how those places
stayed in business.
So did the IRS.
They nailed you for running a book?
For running a candle store
that made a quarter of a million a year
without selling one freakin' candle.
Okay, so no on Georgetown.
- Alan know about this?
- He knows about the candle store.
Let's keep the other part
between us.
He's kind of prissy about moral stuff
like gambling.
- He is.
- And drinking.
That's only because when he drinks,
he gets all weepy and then he pukes.
And whoring.
He doesn't have a problem with that.
He's just cheap
and he likes to cuddle.
Well, don't worry your sordid
gambling past will be our secret.
- I'm glad to know I can trust you.
- Of course you can.
I never told him
about your soft-core film career.
You saw Cinnamon's Buns?
Not all the way through.
Although I am very familiar with
the bakery shop scene in the middle.
With the frosting gun?
I was 19, I needed the money.
They promised me it would be tasteful.
It looked very tasteful.
And delicious.
Glad to hear you enjoyed it.
I don't think you were well-served
by the screenplay.
What screenplay?
There was just a greasy guy behind
the camera saying, "Do this, do that.
"More frosting."
It's weird.
You and I have more in common
than you and my brother.
All right, let's take something
off the table right away.
- What's that?
- My ass.
- That's not what I was getting at...
- Seriously.
In spite of my past, I'm just a nice
little Valley soccer mom now.
Soccer mom?
Your kid's a babbling pothead.
He played soccer when he was ten.
He scored two goals.
- In one game?
- In one season. Shut up.
The point is,
I am way past guys like you.
What do you mean guys like me?
Guys that I have to dip in ammonia
before I'd let them anywhere near me.
Those guys.
As long as we're being honest,
I'm happy
with the way things are between us.
Besides,
you're really good for Alan.
You're smart, you're strong,
you're self-sufficient,
and he's, well... not.
You underestimate your brother.
It's not an estimate.
I already got the bill.
You'll see, one of these days
he's gonna surprise you.
And one of these days
I'm gonna die of liver failure.
Want to lay odds
which happens first?
- Good night, Charlie.
- Good night.
Ammonia?
Am I that skeevy?
Season 8 Episode 13
"Skunk, Dog Crap and Ketchup"
Subtitle: Mr. Bo Jingles Team
- Did Lyndsey leave yet?
- No. Why?
No reason. Just trying to keep track
of who's in my house.
Don't worry,
she's leaving very soon.
I'm not worried.
Actually, I like having her around.
You not so much.
Thank you.
That never ceases to be funny.
Cinnamon buns!
- How did you know?
- I bought them.
Right, cinnamon buns.
Who doesn't love cinnamon buns?
- Alan bought cinnamon buns.
- With frosting.
All right, honey.
I'll see you later.
- I'll call you after work.
- See ya, Charlie.
- Has your son picked a college yet?
- No. Why?
Well, I was just wondering
if he were to choose between say...
North Carolina and Kentucky...
Which one would you have him pick?
Keeping in mind
that as a non-resident,
Kentucky is more expensive.
I'd still go with Kentucky.
It's a better school.
Interesting.
Well, I hope he gets in.
What was that all about?
Since when do you care
about her kid's education?
Young people are our future.
I care about them all.
Please!
The only young people you care about
are sliding down a pole
to grab dollar bills out of your mouth.
Those aren't dollar bills,
those are 20s!
And when did you become
such a cynic?
And when did you become so interested in
the comings and goings of my girlfriend?
Or what her kid's up to?
- Chill.
- No, I will not chill.
And what about
liking having her around?
- Nothing. I like having her around.
- But around what?
Excuse me?
I think when you say around,
you mean under.
- Don't go down that road.
- Why shouldn't I go down that road?
Is it slippery when wet?
Are you out of your mind?
What's gotten into you?
I think a better question would be
what's gotten into you?
I mean, who have you gotten into?
Listen to me very carefully.
- I've not had sex with your girlfriend.
- So it's still in the planning stages.
But you do want her?
Why not? What's wrong with her?
- Nothing. She's terrific.
- So you do want her!
Believe me,
when it comes to Lyndsey,
you have absolutely
nothing to worry about.
That's what you said
about Wendy Freidman
and Kathy Bell and Amy Driskell.
- Who?
- They're girls that you stole from me.
What?
I never stole anybody from you.
Wendy. Sixth grade, Halloween party.
I went to get her punch.
When I came back,
you were bobbing for her apples.
Innocent fun.
Kathy Bell, ninth grade.
Brought her home to work on our science
project, went to the bathroom.
When I came back,
you were teaching her French.
Harmless horseplay.
Amy Driskell, sophomore year.
First girl who let me
get to second base.
All right, her I nailed.
You nailed her?
Everybody nailed her.
That was her thing.
It took me six months
just to touch her right boob!
You really missed the signals,
didn't you?
What signals?
In my case, it was her taking off
her sweater and saying,
"Quick, do me before Alan gets back
from his trumpet lesson."
Clarinet.
I didn't have the lip for trumpet.
Apparently, you didn't have the lip
for Amy Driskell, either.
But all that was a long time ago.
You're with Lyndsey now,
and what's important is that I wish
you both a long and happy life together.
- Really?
- From the bottom of my heart.
Though
I'd still like you to move out.
Got it.
- Soon.
- Right.
No, I guess that's about it.
Amy Driskell.
"No, Alan,
I'm saving myself for Jesus."
Come on in.
- The place looks great.
- Doesn't it?
Even better than before I accidentally
almost burned it to the ground.
You're welcome.
Come here.
I want to give you something.
Fooling around?
On the new couch?
Get your mind out of the gutter.
I haven't Scotchgarded yet.
A house key?
For this house?
Maybe we're not ready
to move in together,
but I want you to come and go
without checking in with me.
In a lot of ways,
this isn't just the key to your house,
it's the key to your heart.
Don't gay it up.
Now listen, I'm thinking of having
a housewarming party next Saturday.
- Great. What can I do?
- You can help me with the guest list.
What would you say
about inviting Judith and Herb?
My ex-wife?
They live right across the street,
and Herb is always so sweet to me.
Because every time Herb looks at you,
he's pretending you're wet and naked.
All right. Fine. I won't invite him.
- It would probably just upset Judith.
- You're right.
You know what? Let's invite them.
Take the high road.
- What about Berta?
- No. I don't think so.
- Why not?
- She's kind of mean to me.
Honey.
That's just cause she doesn't like you.
Fine. Berta.
- And Jake.
- Of course. Great.
- And Charlie.
- There it is.
There what is?
Why do you want Charlie
to come to your party?
Why not? When this place
burned down, he took us in.
He took me in seven years ago,
and I don't feel a need to invite him.
Come on.
- He's a great guy. I really like him.
- Of course you do.
- All the women do.
- All the women?
Wendy Freidman,
Kathy Bell, Amy Driskell.
- Who?
- And now Lyndsey MacElroy.
Charlie and I are just friends.
My brother does not befriend women,
he befouls them.
Are you saying you don't trust me?
I don't trust Charlie.
For him,
you're unexplored territory.
At some point, he's gonna try
and plant his flag in you.
And when I say flag, I mean his...
Flag.
Okay, you're out of your mind.
Be that as it may, I do not want you
hanging out with my brother.
You can be courteous to him.
You know, like, "Hey, Charlie,
you got some vomit on your shoe,"
or, "Hey, Charlie,
do you need me to move my car
so your hooker
can park her pink Camaro?"
Do you realize how insulting
this is?
You don't get to tell me who I can
and can't be friends with.
It's just Charlie.
I gave you Herb and Berta.
You know what, I made a mistake.
Well, I forgive you.
Give me my key back.
- Give it to me.
- How can I come and go?
You can forget coming,
you're just gonna be going.
But I don't understand.
We were doing so good.
We were,
then you started talking and spoiled it.
Just to clarify,
you're not as angry with me now as you
were when I burned down your house?
We'll talk after you've gained
some perspective.
Jake, Berta, let's go!
Party train's leaving.
That what you're wearing
to Lyndsey's housewarming?
- I'm not going.
- Why not?
She and I had an argument.
That's too bad.
Jake, Berta, let's go!
If you do what I think, I swear
to God I will never speak to you again.
Really?
Then tell me exactly
what you think I'm gonna do.
You know what I'm talking about.
All right, I'm gonna run
this down for you one last time.
I've no interest in Lyndsey
other than as a friend,
- she has even less interest in me.
- I don't believe you.
Okay, you're right.
I'm going over to girlfriend's house,
- and I gonna do her right on the couch!
- No, you won't.
- Why not?
- Couch isn't Scotchgarded yet.
Charlie, did you remember
to get the housewarming gift?
Jake's got it.
- Very funny.
- We thought so.
- How come you aren't dressed?
- He and Lyndsey had a fight.
That sucks. See ya.
So you're gonna sit here all night?
I'll be fine.
I'm sure you will, but
if you get bored,
there's a load of laundry in the dryer
you could fluff and fold.
You want me to do your job?
Somebody has to.
Well, I guess there's nothing
left to say except you're an idiot.
I may be an idiot,
but at least I'm home by myself
reading Moby Dick.
Upside down.
Might as well.
Maybe she'll like me better.
Where's your friend Eldridge?
He lives here, right?
- Yeah, he's hiding in his room.
- How come?
He gets paranoid when he's high...
ding in his room.
I came to get him these snacks. Bye.
Amateurs.
- Nice party.
- Thanks.
So give me the lay of the land.
You mean
who in this land can you lay?
- If you will.
- All right. Hot redhead by the bar...
that's Wanda. Recently came out
of a terrible marriage.
Nice, nice. What else you got?
Pretty blonde on the couch...
that's Terry.
She divorced her husband
to be a lesbian.
- How's that working out for Terry?
- See the dirty look she's giving Wanda?
I think I see an opening.
And by that you mean...?
I wasn't being subtile,
I see an opening.
I knew it.
Anything good in my life,
you have to take it away.
"Charlie, you're so funny
and so clever.
"Why don't I lean forward so you can
look down my dress and see my boobies?"
"Why, thank you, I believe I will."
"So do you want to have sex now
or after the party"
"You don't mind that I'm carrying most,
if not all communicable diseases known?"
"No, Charlie,
that's part of your charm.
Come, take me on the couch."
"Are you sure?
It's not Scotchgarded."
"No matter.
We'll Scotchgard it with our love."
Hello, Mr. Skunk.
Don't be alarmed.
I was just leaving.
There's, there's certainly
no reason to feel threatened.
Good skunk.
Nice skunk.
Bad skunk!
God, God.
Who's out there?
- Alan?
- Hey, Herb.
Hope you don't mind.
I got skunked.
- You sure did.
- Yeah.
How come you're not
at Lyndsey's party?
I wanted to, but Judith came down
with a sudden migraine.
By "migraine," I mean "bitch fit."
- Got it.
- How about you?
Lyndsey and I had
kind of a falling-out.
'Cause you showed up
smelling like a skunk?
No, no. Long story.
I got time.
I think she's fooling around
with Charlie behind my back.
Charlie? That lucky duck.
- What?
- I said, that son of a bitch.
Story of my life.
Wendy Freidman, Kathy Bell,
Amy Driskell.
Amy Driskell?
I lost my virginity to Amy Driskell.
- You're kidding.
- Never even had to ask.
It was our first date.
Never got out of the driveway.
We weren't even in a car.
Hey, you know what's good
for getting rid of skunk smell?
- Tomato juice.
- You got any?
- We might have some V-8.
- Think that'll work?
It sure doesn't taste
like tomato juice,
but you couldn't possibly smell
any worse. Hang on.
What else could go wrong?
Of course.
I'm standing in dog crap.
I can't tell you how happy it makes me
to bring two friends back together.
Any better?
Not really.
Well, that's all the V-8.
- Want to try some ketchup?
- Why not?
I found this
in one of my son's shoes.
Yeah,
I can get you better than this.
That's what I was hoping.
Lyndsey?
Alan? What the hell are you...?
Where is he?
Where is who?
What is that smell?
Skunk, dog crap and ketchup.
And don't try to change the subject.
Where is my brother?
He left about 20 minutes ago
with two women.
- Really?
- Really.
So you and he aren't...?
That's what I've been telling you,
smelly fool!
Guess we had nothing to fight about.
Hug?
I'll call you.
You don't scare me.
You already shot your load.
Although I suppose
you could be a different skunk.
All I'm saying is, given my history,
Alan's paranoia is not completely
uncalled for.
This wasn't paranoia.
This was insanity.
- I know, but...
- The man was covered in ketchup.
To be fair, there was time in your life
when you were covered in frosting.
It's not the same thing. I was
putting myself through college.
Look, all I know is
that Alan really loves you.
If you ever repeat this
I will deny it, but my brother
is the most decent human being I know.
Can't you give him one more chance?
- Well, I suppose.
- I knew it!
You bastard!
You slut!
So what do you say?
Subtitles: Mr. Bo Jingles Team
www.sous-titres.eu