♪ men. ♪
Gee, that's too bad, Jake.
Sore throat and a runny nose.
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
I guess you should
stay at your mom's this weekend.
Oh! Gesundheit.
Yeah. Yeah, feel better.
Okay, bye-bye.
Jake sick?
Nah, he's lying
through his teeth.
Probably has a party
to go to or something.
Or a hangover.
Hmm.
Remember when he wanted
to be around us?
Remember when we
wanted to be around him?
Hey, that's my son
you're talking about.
But point taken.
So, you're a free man
for the weekend.
What are your plans?
I don't know. Probably
just catch up on my reading,
take a walk on the beach,
you know, a little "me" time.
What about you?
Pretty much the same.
Except instead of
reading and walking,
I'm going on a date
and hoping to get laid.
Now, when you say "date,"
do you mean an actual
date, or one of your
$2,500 "date experiences."
If I were paying $2,500,
I wouldn't just be
hoping to get laid.
Hmm!
So. You're back
in the dating game.
How'd you hook up?
Was it a "meet cute"?
Meet... cute?
You know, like, uh,
like in the movies.
She's carrying groceries,
and you bump into her
and she spills them
and you try to help her
pick 'em back up, and you bonk
heads, and she's concerned
she might have a concussion,
so you tell her you're a doctor,
and you keep up the ruse until
after she's fallen in love
with you, at which
point you confess
that you're not the man
she thought you were,
and she's furious and
never wants to talk to you,
but you go to her place of work,
and you make a
complete fool of yourself
by declaring your
undying love for her
during an important
business meeting.
Thankfully, the meeting
is with Japanese bankers
who find you charming.
And they give her
the big account,
after which you scoop
her into your arms
and ask her to marry you, and
you live happily ever after.
In Portland.
Um... no.
She's a dermatologist
who scooped a precancerous
mole off my ass.
Oh, well, that's cute, too.
So, uh, what's her
name? How old is she?
Uh, her name's Michelle,
and I'm guessing mid-'30s.
Ooh! Almost age-appropriate.
Oh, say, if I took a picture
of a strange wart on my toe,
would you show it to her
and ask if it's normal?
Sure, I'll pull
it out over dinner.
Come on! She's a dermatologist,
and I have a hideous
growth on my foot.
The hideous growth
on your foot is you.
You know what,
I'll email you a jpeg.
You'll know when
the moment is right.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men,
manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men... ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 8x06 ♪
Twanging Your Magic Clanger
Original Air Date on October 25, 2010
— Sync, corrected by elderman —
— for www.addic7ed.com —
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, Alan.
Listen—
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Right. Having a
little "me" time.
Wasn't little until you came in.
What do you want?
In case I get lucky and this
girl comes back here tonight,
I need you to
make yourself scarce.
No problem.
I don't want to see
you or your wart.
Got it.
Good.
Oh! Try MalibuPuddingGirls.com.
Pudding girls?
Trust me.
Malibu...
pudding girls...
com.
Oh! Yikes.
♪ Men. ♪
Right here?
That's great.
How's your tush?
Fine. How are
your boobs?
I meant, how is it feeling
since I took the mole off?
Oh! A little tender,
but still functional.
That's good.
It's not fair, though.
What?
Well, you've seen mine
and I haven't seen yours.
That's true, isn't it?
We're going to have to figure
out a way for you to get even.
Okay, show me
your ass.
You're terrible!
How are you at those
trivia questions?
Well, let's see.
"Which TV shows
jump-started
these movie stars'
film careers"
Okay.
George Clooney. ER.
Nice.
Leonardo DiCaprio—
Growing Pains.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Oh, yeah. The last season.
John Travolta.
Um...
Welcome Back, Kotter.
Oh. Good memory.
How could I forget?
It was my favorite
show in high school.
You mean it was your
favorite show
set in high
school, right?
Oh, no, no.
In tenth grade I had a
giant crush on Travolta.
But... wasn't that show
on in like the '70s?
Yeah.
So... you were in high
school in the '70's?
Uh-huh.
Were you like, really,
really smart
and skipped a
bunch of grades?
Uh-uh.
I'm 47, Charlie.
Oh. Okay. I wasn't even
thinking about that.
Really. What were
you thinking about?
Uh... You know, the whole
Scientology thing
with Travolta and Cruise.
What's that all about?
How old are you?
You know how old I am.
I filled it out on
my medical form.
Oh, you are not 36, Charlie.
Even your mole
was older than that.
Did I write 36?
Yeah.
I meant 40...
two.
Three.
So I'm out with
a younger man.
Sexy.
Yeah. Cool.
♪ Men. ♪
Do you want to come
in for some coffee?
Oh, gee, I'd love
to, but, um...
But what?
Well, this isn't something I
normally say on a first date,
but my left ass cheek
is throbbing.
Oh, you poor baby. Do you want
me to take a look at it?
No, no, that'd just
be a pity peek.
I'm-I'm-I'm sure it's fine.
But I— I should go.
Okay.
Well, I suppose
you'll call me,
if you want to
get together again.
Absolutely, I will.
Good night.
You've got my
number, right?
Indeed, I do.
Forty-seven.
♪ Men. ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Oh, Alan, again?
I-It's not what it looks like.
Hey, I get it.
You're bored. You're lonely.
You can't afford a hooker.
But come on, keep
it in your room!
Okay, i-in my defense, I wasn't
expecting you home till later.
Plus, it felt a little
naughtier out here.
You know, in public.
You want naughty?
Go yank it on the pitcher's
mound at Dodger Stadium.
Ooh, clever.
Seventh-inning stretch.
You realize I now
have to burn the couch.
Well, if you're
going to do that,
you might want to burn
the deck chair, too.
Oh, God, Alan.
So how was
your evening?
Fine.
I thought you were planning
on bringing her back here.
And yet you were twanging
your magic clanger
right in the middle
of the living room.
I lost track of time. Sue me.
So, uh, what went
wrong with your date?
Nothing went wrong.
She's terrific. She's
beautiful. She's smart.
But...?
She's 47.
You said she was
in her mid-'30s.
That's what I thought.
Apparently,
dermatologists
know how to take really
good care of their skin.
Or she's a witch.
I don't understand. You liked
her when you thought she was 35.
What changed?
I found out she's 47.
Oh, come on.
47's just a number.
A big number.
A scary number.
Are you really that
superficial, vain, and shallow?
Yes, yes, and yes.
Probably the deepest thing about
me is a little pit on my ass
where a mole used to be.
But fish can swim
in shallow water.
What the hell's that
supposed to mean?
I don't know, I'm a
little dehydrated.
What I'm trying to say
is that it's silly to throw away
a promising relationship
based on an arbitrary number.
It's not arbitrary.
She's really 47.
47! That's like ten
years older than me.
Why do you do that?
I'm your brother.
I know exactly how old you are.
The point is, the minute I
found out she was older than me,
I started looking at her
in a whole different way.
And what way is that?
Like, she's a woman who,
when I'm 52, she'll be 60.
You'll be 56.
What are you, the math police?
You know what this is
really about, don't you?
Yeah. When I'm 58,
she'll be 70!
You're really going
to keep doing this?
I can't help myself.
Look at it this way:
When she's 70, you're likely
to have been dead for ten years.
Actually, that does make
me feel a little better.
I'll tell you one
thing, Charlie.
I would give anything to find
someone I enjoy being with,
who's close to my own age,
and who I can
really connect with.
Look no further, Alan.
You've found her.
You do get me, don't you?
♪ Men. ♪
I gotta be
honest with you.
I didn't think I was ever
going to hear from you again.
Why would you think that?
I don't know— the age thing.
Oh, come on.
It's just a number.
I like you.
I'm attracted to you.
Plus, there's no way anybody
looks at you and thinks,
"This is a
47-year-old woman"
Thank you.
Hey, we're only as
old as we feel, right?
Right.
So I say, for all intents
and purposes, you and I?
Couple of 35-year-olds.
Agreed. We're 35.
Hi, Mom.
That's my daughter.
For all intents and
purposes, she's eight.
♪ Men. ♪
Shauna, this is Charlie.
Yeah, hey.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just came to pick up
my snowboard stuff.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
I'm going to Mammoth
for a few days.
With who?
What do you care?
I'm your mother.
Should I go?
No, no, it's fine.
Who are you going with?
His name's Jeremy.
You happy?
Jeremy?
What happened to Sarah?
Sarah and I broke up.
When were you
gonna tell me this?
Mom, I'm 20 years old;
my personal life
is none of your business.
As long as you're my daughter,
it's my business.
Tell me about Jeremy.
What's to tell?
He's a nice guy.
He's Sarah's roommate.
Wait a minute.
You broke up
with Sarah
so you could hook up
with her roommate?
No, no.
We were all hooking up together,
but then Sarah got all weird
even though it was her idea.
Don't you just
hate that?
Are you telling me that the
three of you had sex together?
Hey, you're the one who said
I should explore
all my options in life.
I was talking about grad
school, not threesomes!
I'm so sorry you
have to hear this.
No, no, no, it's fine.
Pretend I'm not here.
I also need
to borrow some money.
Shauna, how do you
expect to pay me back?
I still have a job.
A webcam in
your bathroom
and a PayPal account
is not a job!
I admit, it's not
making much money.
But that's because there's
so much free porn out there!
She's got a point.
The whole pay-to-peek
industry is dying.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
And if I could
just throw in my two cents here.
Michelle, your
daughter's at that time
in her life where she's got
to make her own choices,
and it doesn't matter if
they're right or wrong.
Either way,
she learns.
But I'm just trying
to protect her.
You can't protect her.
All you can do is love her and
be there for her no matter what.
I am there for her.
You know that, right?
Yeah, I do.
Come here.
What?
I should go.
Oh, no, no,
it's okay.
Really, I got to go.
And you should have
this time with your daughter.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
I'll call you tomorrow.
Nice to meet you, Shauna.
Nice to meet you, too.
It's wrong, it's wrong,
it's so wrong.
Oh, what the hell?
Let's try ShaunaShower.com.
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, for God's sake!
Hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's not what it looks like!
Well, that's a relief.
'Cause it looks like
you were masturbating
to mariachi music in your car.
What do you want?
I only get AM radio!
♪ Men. ♪
Alan?
In here.
Is it safe?
Yes.
We cool here?
Relax.
You do realize you have
a serious problem.
It's not my fault.
Really?
Whose fault is it?
Big pharma.
Who the hell's big pharma?
You know,
the pharmaceutical companies
that make boner pills
that last 36 hours.
You took a boner pill?
I had to.
The pills were about to expire.
But you didn't have a woman.
Hence the constant masturbation.
You know how expensive
those things are.
I'm simply trying to
get my money's worth.
So this non-stop whack-a-thon
is just 'cause you're cheap?
And horny.
And nuts.
Semantics.
Why the car?
You said
"not in the living room."
Did I say "in the car"?
Well, I didn't plan it.
I was gonna go to the movies
and I got distracted.
What could possibly distract you
from driving out of the garage?
Think about it.
Slipping the key into the hole.
Gently turning it.
Pumping the gas
until the engine starts purring.
I'm thinking about it
and I'm still going with nuts.
Well, unlike you, I did not have
female companionship tonight.
Well, as it turns out,
neither did I.
What happened?
You really expect me
to share my personal problems
with a self-abusing zoo monkey?
Who else you got?
All right, here's the deal.
I went back to Michelle,
determined to take the whole
age thing off the table.
Good for you.
Very mature.
And it was going great,
until her daughter walks in.
She has a daughter?
Not just a daughter, Alan.
A 20-year-old daughter.
A gorgeous daughter.
A bisexual daughter.
Summing up:
a 20-year-old, gorgeous,
bisexual daughter.
Got it.
What did you do?
What could I do?
I got the hell out of there.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
You know me.
If I continue a relationship
with Michelle,
at some point, I'm gonna try
to nail her daughter.
Maybe not today,
maybe not tomorrow,
but as sure as your speedometer
could use a Handi Wipe,
it will happen.
So you're breaking up
with Michelle?
I have to!
And then you're gonna
hit on the daughter.
No, no, no, no.
I'm getting away
from both of them.
I figure it's better
to hurt Michelle
a little now than a lot later.
Oh.
Well, color me impressed.
You're making
a decision
that's considerate
and selfless.
Putting aside, of
course, the fact that
the motivation for the decision
is sordid and despicable.
Thank you.
Seriously though,
the daughter is unbelievable.
She actually has some kind of
porn site on the Internet.
Really?
Apparently, there's a webcam
in her bathroom.
Mm.
Can you imagine?
A 20-year-old co-ed in
the shower with her girlfriend,
soaping each other up?
Something to ponder.
Excuse me.
Actually, not a bad idea.
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Aw, geez, Zippy!
What are you doing
with the pudding?
♪ Men. ♪
Well, I guess I
appreciate your honesty.
I just think it wouldn't be fair
to start a relationship with you
knowing I'm still
not over Chelsea.
No, it's
understandable.
She was your
fiancée.
I've tried to stop thinking
about her, and I can't.
And I like you too much
to risk our relationship
being some kind of
a rebound thing.
All right.
I guess I just have
to accept that.
Thank you.
Bye.
You know what, Jeremy?
Just go to hell.
You're a childish jerk.
Oh, hey.
You okay?
I guess.
Just thought this guy
was something he's not.
Well, he's young,
and, you know, women
mature faster than boys.
That is so true.
Have you considered
dating someone a little older?
I tried that once;
it was disgusting.
Really?
The guy was almost 35.
It was like sleeping with
my grandfather.
No kidding.
He could only do it
twice in a row
before he needed to take a nap.
Uh-huh.
Excuse me.
Hey, Michelle,
good news!
I think I'm
over Chelsea!
♪ Men. ♪
Hey, hey, hey!
Whoa, whoa!
It's not what
it looks like!
♪ Men. ♪
So... you feel like
going again?
Uh, sure.
I just need, you know,
a little nap first.
Geez, Charlie,
what are you gonna be like
when you're my age?
Ooh, ouch.
I'm kidding.
Come here.
Hang on.
What do you
want, Alan?
Arrested?
For what?
Oh, Alan.
What was the movie?
You're right,
doesn't matter.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Where you going?
Nowhere.
♪ Men. ♪