Previously on
two and a half men:
Alan?
Lindsey and I have decided to
live together.
End of an era,
huh, Charlie?
From now on,
no brother, no nephew.
Just the sounds of the ocean
punctuated by the soft voices
of prostitutes lying about
the enormity of my sexual organ.
Alan, dinner's
on the table!
Hey, I noticed this
old pipe on the mantel.
It's a beauty.
Oh, it was my grandfather's.
Oh, wow, they don't make 'em
like this anymore.
So now that he's gone,
what are you gonna do
with that empty room?
Uh... why do you ask?
I was just thinking,
it might be nice
to spend the occasional
weekend here on the beach.
Well, from now on,
this house is your home.
— Sync, corrected by elderman —
— for www.addic7ed.com —
Do you smell something burning?
? Men. ?
Whoo, what a day.
Mmm-hmm.
Who could've seen
this one coming?
Oh, please— after
seven years, you know,
I finally move out
of your house,
and within two days,
I burn my new home down.
You can't write
this stuff.
I could if I used your skin for
paper and your blood for ink.
I just want you to know that as
soon as we get
the insurance money and repair
the fire damage,
Lyndsey and the boys and I will
be out of your hair for good.
Unless, of course, you burn her
house down again.
Funny.
See? That's what we need at
times like this— laughter.
I'm gonna take that as laughter!
Trust me, Eldridge is
a great kid,
and you're
gonna love Lyndsey.
If you can open up
your mind just a little,
you will really enjoy
having them here.
Damn it, Eldridge!
Why the hell did you try
to flush a washcloth down
the toilet?
I'm not enjoying it yet, Alan.
Charlie, you got a mop?
Laundry room.
Thank you.
Need any help, sweetie?
No, but if I need my house
burned down again,
I'll let you know.
See? She is keeping
a sense of humor about it.
You've ruined my entire life,
you know that?
You're right, I like her.
We've got a lot in common.
What do you want me
to tell you, Chris?
If you want to see your son,
you're gonna have
to come to Malibu.
Oh, grow up!
You think I planned
to have the house burn down?
It was an accident!
It was, you know.
Drop dead!
Whoo, I'd say she's
a little miffed with your dad.
I'd say she wants to
tear him a new one.
Hey! watch your language.
What'd I say?
New one.
Mmm, honey, honey,
uh, just a little heads up,
um, the boys could
hear you out there.
I don't give a rat's ass
what they can hear!
His father's a jerk and you
burned down my freakin' house!
Our house.
Dear God, stop talking.
Aw, damn!
Hey, Berta.
Bet you're surprised
to see me back.
It's my own fault.
I let myself believe.
Well, I want you to meet
my girlfriend Lyndsey.
And this is her son Eldridge.
And they're gonna be staying
with us for a little while.
What'd he do, burn down
your house?
It was an accident!
Hello, everyone.
I hope you all slept well.
If there's anything I can do
to make your stay here
more comfortable,
please be sure to tell me.
Thank you, Charlie.
That is so...
Uh! He doesn't mean it.
Hey, Uncle Charlie?
Yeah?
You miss me?
He missed me.
? Men. ?
Honestly, I don't see why
you can't live here.
You're kidding, right?
There's no roof.
So wear a hat.
My great grandmother's
candlesticks.
Oh, Lyndsey, I'm sorry.
She smuggled these
out of Denmark
when the Nazis invaded.
Really? Where'd she hide 'em?
Charlie,
don't go there.
Oh, like I'm the only one?
Look at the bright side.
Even though we've lost
some material items,
the important thing is
we're all safe
and we've still got
each other, right.
You're making
my skin crawl.
Hey, guys... smile.
It's for your Christmas card.
All my stuff is wrecked.
Oh, I'm sorry, buddy.
Sorry isn't gonna bring back
my guitar or my X-Box
or the history paper
that's due tomorrow
that I totally had finished.
Where's Eldridge?
He's drying out his weed
in the backyard.
Weed?
Wii.
Nintendo Wii.
I better go help him.
I could use a little
Wii right now.
Is this my Armani jacket?
Oh! Oh, yeah. You know,
I don't know how that got in
with my things.
I was gonna bring it back.
But now that you're here,
why don't you just take it
with you?
Saves me the trip.
You know what? Happy birthday.
Not much of a birthday present.
Ding-dong.
Hi, neighbor.
We saw your cars
out front.
Hey, Judith.
Incredible, huh?
Wow, this place is a wreck.
But still livable.
What are you gonna do?
Well, till the place gets
fixed up,
we're all staying in Malibu
with Charlie.
Really?
All of you...
at Charlie's?
What are you
smiling about?
You know what
I'm smiling about.
Well, I hope
the repairs go quickly
so we get you back here
real soon.
Thanks. I'm gonna miss
your friendly face
every morning
when I'm getting the paper.
Every morning?
Our schedules synch up
when I'm doing my power walk.
Power walk?
What are you
smiling about?
You know what I'm smiling about.
Hey! My pipe survived!
It's like a miracle.
Filthy habit.
? Men. ?
Oh, look, look, look—
The Towering Inferno is on.
No?
Oh! Stephen King's Firestarter.
All right.
How about Blazing Saddles?
Too soon?
You guys are no fun.
I'm gonna call a hooker.
Charlie, there's two
young boys in the house.
Let 'em get their own hookers.
Charlie, for God's sake.
Don't worry.
I'm a responsible uncle.
That's nice to know.
I promise I'll get
a quiet prostitute.
Believe it or not,
that's a real concession
on his part.
Now where is my phone?
Oh, right, I must've left it in
the charred-but-still-very-
livable remains of your house,
which he burned down.
You're gonna go
over there now?
All my hooker numbers
are in that phone.
So unless
you wanna have sex with me
for $1,000 an hour,
I need the phone.
You don't really think he'd
give me $1,000 an hour?
If I were you, I'd get
the money up front.
? Men. ?
Ah... there we are.
? A-B-C-D-E-F-G-... ?
? H... ?
Hookers.
Hookers, hookers, hookers...
Lookin' for a quiet hooker.
Ah, there we go: "Silent Betty"
Not a lot
of coverage in here.
Who the hell are you?
You're right, let's just stay
mysterious strangers.
This used to be my house,
you know.
You the ex-husband?
Chris MacElroy.
Charlie Harper.
Alan's brother.
I don't usually
admit it, but yeah.
What are you doing here, Chris?
I wanted to see
what the damage was
and just, you know, sit here.
Try and figure out where
it all went wrong.
What'd you come up with?
I probably shouldn't have banged
the babysitter.
Yeah, that can do it.
I did a babysitter once.
My mom was furious.
Wouldn't drive her home and
absolutely refused to pay her.
Want a drink?
Sure, why not?
To babysitters.
Is this a private party
or can anyone join?
Hey, Herb!
Come on in.
Hey, Chris,
long time no see.
Likewise.
Grab a seat, have a drink.
Oh, gee, I don't know.
I told Judith I was
taking out the garbage.
What the heck. I didn't say
where I was taking it.
So you two guys
know each other?
Oh, you kidding?
Chris is a legend in
this neighborhood.
What was she, like, 19?
Twenty-two.
Nevertheless, quite
an accomplishment.
Hey, is she still
babysitting?
'Cause we're looking
for somebody,
and everybody Judith
interviews is fat and ugly.
Take it from me, Herb, you're
better off with fat and ugly.
Oh, I hardly think so.
You'd really be willing
to risk your marriage over
a cute young babysitter?
I certainly wouldn't risk it
over a fat ugly one.
Can't argue with that.
? Men. ?
I made us a snacky snack.
Swell.
We have onion dip
and cool ranch.
Always good to have
a choice of dips.
And I chose you.
Zing!
What are you doing?
Just gettin' comfy.
Snugglin' up on
the world's best pillow.
Mmm!
Whoa.
That was an accident, right?
Sure...
let's call it an accident.
Hey, can you take me back
to Mom's?
Why?
Eldridge is being a tool.
Whoa!
Dad!
It wasn't me, it was...
Yeah, I'll take you
back to your mom's.
Hey, Alan?
What?
Try not to burn down her house.
Yeah, ha-ha.
You might want to light some
matches while I'm gone.
? Men. ?
So, Chris, what're you
up to these days?
Not a lot.
After Lyndsey threw me out,
I lost my job,
started drinking heavily
and I just found out
I have a lump on my groin.
Bad place
for a lump.
Tell me a good place.
Somebody else's groin.
Touché.
Boy, you make one mistake
and you pay for it for the rest
of your life.
You only did
the babysitter once?
Oh, no, that was two years,
morning, noon and night,
but I count it as one mistake.
Maybe that's where
he got the lump.
Did somebody order a pizza?
Hey, it's my favorite pizza boy!
I'm 38 years old, Mr. Harper.
I have high blood pressure
and alimony payments.
You got a lump on your groin?
No.
Then don't complain.
So what are
you people doing here?
Having a lonely drink in memory
of our hopes and dreams
that are now dead and buried.
Oh.
I'm in.
? Men. ?
If it's all the
same to you,
I'm gonna stay with
Mom for a little while.
Come on, Jake,
I know it's been
a little rocky lately,
but things'll work out.
Yeah, well, when
they do, call me.
Hey, Mom.
What are you doing here?
What is he he doing here?
He wasn't getting along
with Lyndsey's son.
Maybe that's because
Lyndsey's son is
a degenerate pothead.
He's not so bad.
He just made some
bad choices.
So did his mom.
Yeah, well, you made
the same bad choice she did!
Ha-ha!
So Alan's, like, I don't know,
five, six years old,
and I walk in his bedroom
and he's in there with the dog,
and I start yelling,
"Whoa, whoa, whoa! No, no!
Are you crazy?
Stop that!"
Looks up at me
and says "What?"
I say, "Alan,
the dog is supposed
to lick the peanut butter
off you."
To this day,
I can't eat peanut butter.
Hello?
Hey, we were
just talking about you.
All good, I hope.
Oh, yeah, it was good.
So, what's going on?
Just having a drink
with a few friends.
Chris, I believe you know
my brother.
The man who's banging your wife
and burned down your house.
Hi.
Pull up a chair.
Have a drink
with your girlfriend's ex
and your wife's new husband.
I just brought the pizza.
I don't think I've slept
with anyone you know.
Okay.
Hey, you know
what I just realized?
You three guys have
all slept with each other.
What?
With all due respect, Charlie,
I think I'd remember that.
No, no, think about it.
They say that when you have sex
with someone,
you're basically having sex
with everyone
they've ever had sex with.
Oh. I guess you and I have done
the dirty deed.
Because of Judith,
not the peanut butter dog.
You told them?
I tell everybody.
Wait.
So Herb has slept with Alan,
and Alan has slept with Chris,
which means that...
I've slept with Lyndsey!
Yes!
? Men. ?
Hello?
How could you sleep with Herb?
Alan, is that you?
Who's Herb? Where are you?
I'm in our house.
What are you doing there?
Because there's nowhere else
for me to go
'cause you won't forgive me.
Why won't you forgive me?
You're drunk.
Yeah, well, you farted at me.
Good-bye, Alan.
Where's Jake?
He left hours ago,
to get away from you.
Where's Alan?
He left to get away
from me.
Where's what's-his-name?
The guy who owns
the house?
He left to get away
from all of us.
Hey, this is working out
pretty good, huh?
You know,
I envy you guys.
You've all been married,
have kids.
Yeah, it didn't
end well,
but for a moment in time, each
and every one of you experienced
what it is to have a family,
to give and receive
unconditional love.
My marriage isn't over.
Dude, you've been taking out
the garbage
for two-and-a-half hours.
I said it wasn't over,
I didn't say it was good.
Really, Charlie,
you envy us?
Oh, come on, look at me.
What do I have?
A big house on the beach,
more money than I know
what to do with...
and a cell phone full
of candid video of me
having uninhibited sex with
beautiful women
whose names I don't remember.
I don't think
he envies us at all.
Good catch, Herb.
I gotta go pee.
Oh, uh, bathroom's
right back there.
I know where it is!
I used to live here.
Right, right.
That's a classy guy.
Using the toilet in a house
with no plumbing.
Where have you been going?
Refrigerator.
I filled the vegetable crisper.
See? That's what I love
about you, Charlie.
You're a maverick.
I gotta start being
more mavericky-ky.
Herb, where the
hell are you?
Maybe tomorrow.
Hey, Lyndsey,
you'll never guess
what we figured out
about you and me.
Herb!
See ya soon.
Alan, let's go home.
You came to get me?
Yeah.
You forgive me?
Well, I thought
about it and...
Hey, Lyndsey.
Chris.
What are you doing here?
Well, I came
to see the damage
and I just started
thinking about us;
what an idiot I was.
You were, you know?
I'd give anything to start over.
Really?
Uh, excuse me, but weren't you
about to forgive me?
Can we go out someplace
and have a cup of coffee
and maybe,
I don't know, just talk?
Babysitter.
Well, I guess
there's nothing
wrong with talking.
That's great.
I can't tell you how much
I've missed you and Eldridge.
He really needs
a father, Chris.
Uh, so I'll see you back
at the house, right?
She left her kid there;
she's gotta come back.
Would you come back
for that kid?
She's never coming back.
? Men. ?
You know who you
remind me of, Alan?
Job.
Job from the Bible?
How many Jobs you know?
Job— the guy God punishes
just for laughs.
Mm! God punishes Job
to test his faith.
Still funny.
What time is it?
A little after midnight.
So much for that
30-minute guarantee.
Good night, fellas.
Good night, Gordon.
Night, Gordon.
So...
Guess it's just
you and me, huh?
Two guys sitting alone
in a burned-out house.
Hey!
Silent Betty! You made it!
See ya, Alan.
Well, sure,
half and half sounds good.
Huh.
Maybe I am like Job.
But I am not
gonna lose my faith!
Aw, crap.
— Sync, corrected by elderman —
— for www.addic7ed.com —