- [grunting]
Hey, everyone.
Sorry I'm late.
So what's this secret meeting
all about?
You guys know I'm not
medically cleared
for another week.
- It's not
a secret meeting, Jake.
It's an intervention.
[razor buzzes]
- The tips have to go.
- What?
Why?
- Jake, we're worried about you,
and you look very stupid.
- C'mon, guys.
I think they're
kind of cool, retro.
- No, they're terrible.
- Amy, come on.
You're digging
the tips, right?
- No, I feel like
I'm kissing Vanilla Ice.
- There was a time you would've
jumped at that chance.
- They have to go.
- [laughs nervously]
All right, you guys got me.
I did it as a joke.
I kept them ironically.
Pretty funny, right?
[laughs]
I'm just gonna head out.
- Get him!
- No!
[all screaming and grunting]
- Yes, Terry!
[both screaming]
- [gasping]
Okay, okay.
Wait, wait, okay, okay, okay.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
I'll admit it.
I went too deep
down there in Florida.
At one point, I think I forgot
where the tip of me ended,
and the base of the tips began.
Before we just chop 'em off,
would anybody like to say
some final words?
- No.
- That was one word.
That counts.
Thank you, Rosa.
Okay, I'm ready.
[razor buzzing]
- Sorry I'm late everyone,
but trust me, it's worth it.
Me and Jake are tip buds.
[yelling]
What?
[screaming]
No!
both: No!
- You know what—I do see it.
It's bad.
It looks bad.
[upbeat music]
♪
- Brace yourselves
'cause Jake-y is back.
[mimics a train whistle]
Don't everybody mob me at once.
We can high-five one at a time.
Oh, I see...
no response.
A little "welcome back
to the precinct" hazing.
Who's behind this cute
little prank? Diaz?
- Kill yourself.
- Okay.
- I told you.
Night shift has everyone
a little down.
- Yeah, just because
you don't get to sleep
or see your loved ones
or feel the sun
or do anything
that brings you joy.
That's all.
- I personally like
the night shift.
You know who else
is up right now?
- Murderers?
Armed robbers?
- [Australian accent]
Australians.
It's an whole new demographic
for me to conquer.
[normal voice]
I already have the third most
followers behind Iggy Azalea
and the Perth Zoo Wallaby cam.
- Wow, that's pretty good.
- It's not just good, Jake.
[chuckles]
[Australian accent]
It's bonzer.
- Night shift is boring.
Listen to the cases I've had:
drunk and disorderly, drunk and
disorderly, cyber crime—
- Ooh, cyber crime.
Pretty cool.
- Caught a drunk guy
humping a laptop.
- Well, we've all been there.
But my point is this:
I don't care what time it is.
I'm always happy to be here.
Nine-Nine!
Nine-Niiine!
A-Noine-Noine!
I'm gonna keep doing it
until you guys chime in.
A-Noine-Noine!
- Sergeant Jeffords, a word.
- What is wrong with everyone?
- I'm worried our night shift
morale problem has gotten worse.
- Yeah, you think?
I'm sorry.
I'm exhausted.
My wife says when I get tired,
I get night sassy.
- Night sassy?
- Hearing problems, much?
Sorry.
Should I just go tell everyone
to buck up and do their jobs?
- No, the squad's only on night
shift because they came down
to Florida to save Jake and me.
It's my responsibility
to fix this,
so I'm going to brighten
the mood by telling a few jokes.
Try this one on for size:
I don't care for cheese.
I'm a...
curd-mudgeon.
Wow.
You're too tired for humor.
- If he isn't
taking his medicine,
you could
mix it in with his food.
- Sorry, you can deal with your
sick dog later, Boyle.
- Well, actually, that was
about my son, Nikolaj.
He's got allergies.
I think we may have to go
with a nasal douche.
- Ah, nasal douche.
Cool, cool, cool, cool.
Very gross.
Anyways, I'm back
to being a cop.
It's all I've thought about
for the last six months.
- Hurtful.
- But I won't be fully back
until I've solved a case,
just like old times.
And I can't do that
without my partner.
- Pfft, you're not solving
any cases on the night shift.
- Lohank?
Oh, my God, you look—
- Beautiful?
- I was gonna say "less sad."
- Ever since I moved to
the day shift, I'm happier,
healthier, my stepson gave me
my debit card back.
- Lohank is happy and confident?
Everything's off.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
We're in the Upside Down.
- That's right.
I'm gonna tell you the same
thing they told me when
they removed my testicle:
welcome to your new life.
- Nuh-uh, I'm not gonna let
the night shift win.
Me and my main man Boyle
are about to solve a case.
Isn't that right, Charles?
- Oh, you know we will.
We'll call ourselves
the Night Boys.
- Kind of sounds like
a male escort service.
- The Midnight Men.
- Even worse.
- The Dark Stallions.
- Looks like we're going
with the Night Boys.
- Whoo!
- [sighs]
I can't believe
I'm gonna say this,
but the night shift is
taking all the fun
out of paperwork.
- Mm-hmm.
- At least we're getting to
spend quality time together.
- Totally—I'll be back
in 40 minutes.
- What?
Where are you going?
We have to finish
this by morning.
- Yeah, I know.
I just have something important
I have to do.
- What?
- I have to get...
Some pens.
- Then why are you putting
your jacket on?
- Pen store's a block away.
- The nearest pen store is seven
blocks away, and it doesn't open
until 9:00 a.m.
I learned that the hard way.
You really think you
can lie to me?
- No.
- A-ha!
You're lying to me right now.
You do think you can lie to me.
- Yep.
- Wait.
Hang on.
Was that a lie?
- I don't know, maybe.
All right, see ya.
- [sighs]
- Ah, our first case.
Tasty little B&E—
just what the doctor ordered.
Not actually, she recommended
another week of bed rest.
I was like, "Whatever, dorkus."
[laughter]
Ah, check it out:
ducking under police tape.
I missed this.
[grunting and screaming]
Charles—
- Yep, yep, on it, on it,
Jake-y.
- I got it.
- Got it.
- What do we got?
- Back window's broken,
two sets of sneaker prints,
alarm went off at 11:43,
and security arrived at 11:46.
Perps were already gone.
- Okay, I'm thinking classic us.
I'm thinking old times.
I'm thinking...
[together]
Rigity-rigity-role playas!
- Yes, okay,
I'm Jacques Guillaume,
and you are Henri Renault.
We are cat burglars
on vacation from France.
- I love it—although Henri
went to an elite international
school, so he does not
speak with an accent.
- Wow, nice, way to
flesh out the characters.
- Thank you, okay,
so I break the back window,
make my way over
to the jewelry case.
Meanwhile, you're standing
lookout by the front door...
- Oui, oui.
- Smoking a cigarette.
Check it: ash.
- [French accent]
Ooh la la.
Okay, so I am smoking.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, Jacques rolls
his own cigarettes,
a habit he picked up from
a prostitute in Marseille,
but that is not all
he picked up.
- Why do all your
characters get STDs?
- [normal voice]
Because they're living life!
- All right, so I go
to the first case—smash—
steal a bunch of watches.
Move over to the second
case—smash—bracelets.
But then, we hear
a sound, and...
- I yell, "Les gendarmes!
Ils sont ici!"
- And I know what that means
because I'm French,
but I ask you to repeat it in
English, just to be sure.
- Police are here.
- Yes, we gotta get outta here,
so we turn to leave,
you flick your cigarette.
Using the cane, using
the cane, this is awesome.
[gasps]
Voila! Zee butt.
- I thought Henri didn't
have an accent.
- It comes out
when he gets excited.
Great news, everyone.
We just got our first lead
on our first case
on my first night back,
proving once and for all
that absolutely
nothing has changed.
[grunts]
- Yeah, this opens in
instead of out now.
They switched it a month ago.
- Yeah, so the door changed,
sure, but that's it.
- Well, we have got
ourselves a case and
a key piece of evidence.
We should be wrapping
this thing up in no time.
- As long as we do it
before sunup.
As soon as the shift is over,
I kind of have to get home.
- But we're gonna work until
it's done, right?
I mean, that's how we do it.
- Yeah, I just like to be home
as soon as Nikolaj wakes up
so I can make him breakfast.
- Sure, yeah, not a problem—
we'll be home by sunup.
Just like a couple of sexy
"Twilight" vampires.
[as Dracula]
I am Robert Pattinson.
I vant to turn into a bat.
[normal voice]
I've never seen the movies.
- No, me neither—they're
an insult to the books.
- Okay.
Crank up the tunes, Boyle.
The Night Boys
need an anthem.
Something dark,
something tough, something—
- I already got it.
[Lionel Richie's
"All Night Long" playing]
- You know what?
I'm into it.
The night shift
won't slow us down.
- Why is this going so slow?
Where is everyone?
- Well, it is 3:00 a.m.
It's a pretty bare-bones crew.
- Hi, can I help you?
Are you lost?
Can I get you
something—coffee, tea?
- You know what—
we're in a bit of a hurry.
Can you run this DNA for us?
- Well, of course.
Sorry, not many people
stopping by at night.
Sometimes it makes you like—
[blows raspberry]
[squelching]
Right?
both: Uh-huh.
- I'll be back in a sec.
- Cool.
Yikes... not exactly
the A-team at this hour.
- "A-Team," are you guys
talking "A-Team"?
I love that show—
I could download it.
We should binge it.
This is gonna be fun.
- Yep, totally excited to watch
five full seasons of television
with you, but could you actually
run the DNA for us first?
- It kind of feels like you're
prioritizing work
over our friendship.
- Because I barely know you?
- Fine, message received.
[upbeat music]
- Oh, welcome back
from your third
massive break of the night.
- Thanks.
- I was being sarcastic.
Where do you keep going?
- Not saying.
- Tell me, Diaz.
- Nope.
- Come on, tell me.
- Not talking about it.
- Tell me, tell me, tell me,
tell me, tell me, tell me—
- Fine.
I was in the bathroom.
I'm having stomach problems.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
- It's real bad—
- No, that's all right.
- You should've been there.
- I don't have to hear it.
- It was like a massacre.
- No, you can—please stop.
- Multiple flush.
- Please stop.
- Attention, squad.
Everyone, gather 'round.
I've been researching ways
to raise morale, and I found
an interesting article
in a scientific journal.
- Oh, was it from "The American
Journal of No One Cares"?
- According to a recent study,
the physical act of smiling
can improve your mood.
I suggest we give it a shot.
Eh?
Now you all try.
Big smiles, bigger, bigger!
Great, now we just
have to stay like this
for the next two hours.
Can you feel it working?
- I don't have any enamel
on my teeth,
so the cold air is excruciating.
- Maybe if you brushed your
teeth once in a while,
this wouldn't be a problem.
- I do brush my teeth.
They're decaying
from acid reflux.
You're embarrassing yourself.
[Australian accent]
- Crikey.
- You're not Australian, Gina.
- Get stuffed, ya drongo.
- Guys, seriously,
too much exposure to air,
and they will turn to dust.
- This isn't working out as well
as I'd hoped.
Time for the next level:
forced laughing.
[laughs]
- Well, that lab tech
took a long time.
- Once we agreed to go to
his birthday party,
he was actually pretty fast.
But, most importantly,
we got a DNA match.
We're looking for...
Dave Smith.
Sounds like a real
piece of crap.
- You said it.
Now we just gotta
pull his files from records.
- Yep, then we bust him,
and we'll be done with plenty
of time before Nikolaj wakes up.
- [correcting]
Nikolaj.
- Hm?
Nikolaj, yeah, I said it.
- Nikolaj.
- Not even close.
Nikolaj.
- Nikolaj.
- Almost—Nikolaj.
- Nikolaj—I feel
like I'm saying it.
You know what—
it doesn't matter.
Hit me with the music!
♪ All night long
♪ All night
- Hi there, we just need
to pull a file—
- Can't—system's down.
They do maintenance at night.
- That's okay, we'll just go to
another precinct.
- That's all.
- Yep.
♪ All night long
♪ All night
- Hi, can we get
this file, please?
We're in a bit of a hurry.
- Oh, absolutely, honey.
- [whispering]
She's going extremely slow.
She's going so slow.
- There we go.
- Oh, my glasses.
- All right, we'll just go
to Five-Four.
♪ All night
- No.
Hello, hi, please,
file now, hurry.
- Sorry, dude.
I don't know how to get
onto this system—I'm a temp.
- May I?
Great, let me just get over—
oh, good lord, that is porn.
- Oh, is that not allowed?
- It is not.
No problem,
we just close these tabs...
You've got a lot of them.
- Mm.
- Type 3 and type 9
and 12 and 13—
those are all
the diabeteses I have.
- It's true what they say:
night shift makes
for strange bedfellows.
- In your dreams, perv.
- Ugh.
Rosa?
What the hell? She said
she was in the bathroom again.
- Nah, she hasn't been
to the bathroom since 8:27.
- [yelling]
What?
Also... ew.
C'mon, Hitchcock.
Busted.
[laughs then sighs]
- Man, this Dave Smith's
bad news: armed robbery,
aggravated assault,
attempted murder...
- Well, he's about to get
a visit from the Night Boys.
Gah, this stupid limp
is slowing me down.
Charles, can you—
- Oh, give you a piggy?
- What?
- Yeah, jump on it—
I'll give you a piggy.
[snorts]
- Actually, I'm good.
I was just gonna ask
if you'd hold my bag.
- Oh, yeah, sure,
makes more sense.
- Yeah.
- Embarrassed.
- Anyways, this is great.
We're definitely gonna catch
this guy before sunup,
and you will be home
to see your kid.
Oh, no!
Son of a bitch.
[knocking]
- Jake, come on in.
Nikolaj, look who it is.
You remember Jake Peralta.
- From the stories.
- Yeah, we talk about you
at bedtime.
- Ah.
- Look at my cement truck.
- He loves trucks.
- Cool, it's cool, buddy.
Hey, listen, I know you're
with your kid, but I checked
the file, and our perp's
last known address
is like
two blocks from here.
- Really?
We gotta go take him down.
- Yes, there's
the Charles I know.
- Tonight, Dave Smith goes down.
- Tonight?
No, Charles,
we gotta go now.
You saw this guy's rap sheet—he
was arrested for attempted mur—
- Tickling, tickling—
attempted tickling.
- Right, tickling.
Look, uh, Charles, this guy's
a real... doodyhead, all right?
He tickled once—
he may tickle again.
He might be tickling
as we speak.
We could be dealing
with a serial tickler.
- [sighs]
I really want to go, Jake,
but I'm here alone with Nikolaj.
Genevieve doesn't get back
for three hours.
- So let's just
take him with us.
Nah, that's crazy—or is it
just crazy enough to work?
Just crazy.
Ah, man, it stinks
you've gotta watch him—
it's really messing
everything up.
I mean, that came out wrong.
I love that you have a son—
it's not messing everything up.
Just messing up our ability
to solve the case and have fun.
Ah, you know what I mean.
I'm a nice guy—
I'm in the right.
I'll just go myself.
Bye, Nikolaj.
- [correcting]
Nikolaj.
- Yeah, whatever.
See ya.
- I know your shift is over, and
you've had a challenging night,
but I think I've found
a new way to raise morale.
Follow me to the briefing room.
- What's all this?
- It's an after-work hang.
Just trying to turn up,
as it were.
We got snacks, games,
decorations, chairs—
- Yes, chairs.
- Cool, maybe we can mill around
and small talk about how
some of us are big lying liars
who lie all the time
like a bunch of liars, Rosa.
- I don't think that's good
party convo.
Uh, maybe we should just name
our favorite sailing knot.
I'll start.
The bowline.
How about some tunes?
[upbeat Sousa march]
- Cool, merry-go-round music.
- Yeah, John Phillips Sousa,
the Skrillex of his day.
C'mon, people,
hit the dance floor.
Have a good time.
Why is no one
having a good time?
I specifically requested it.
Gina, why aren't you dancing?
- I can't. I'm in the middle
of a feud with
the "that's not a knife" guy
from "Crocodile Dundee."
He's being a real bitch.
- Fine, I guess I'll just...
stop the party.
- I didn't realize
it ever started.
- Enough.
I tried to make this fun.
I even learned
what Skrillex was.
Sorry you're all miserable,
but guess what.
So am I.
I'm exhausted all the time,
I never see my husband,
the late-night NPR programming—
pure garbage.
I'm done trying. We can all
be miserable together.
Just go home.
- Hey, I saw you earlier.
You weren't in the bathroom.
You were on a park bench
playing on your phone.
Yeah, you left me to do
everything while I thought
you were pooping.
I wish you were pooping.
I wish to God.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, Rosa, crying—
don't know what to do.
Pat, pat.
This feels wrong.
- We put away Figgis
three weeks ago.
Pimento should've been
back by now.
We had plans to meet on
that park bench once
the coast was clear,
but he hasn't shown up.
- Maybe he's deep undercover, or
he doesn't remember who he is,
or maybe he's dead.
- Wow, thanks.
You're right,
my fiancé's a total weirdo
who's probably dead.
I'll just give up on him
and go do my paperwork.
- No, Diaz, wait—maybe he's
just really, really injured.
Come on, Amy.
- All right,
Fiske, Jones, Thompkins...
[gasps]
Smith.
Whoa, hey, NYPD, freeze!
Slow down!
This isn't fair!
I have a cane.
[panting]
Stop, stop, stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
NYPD.
NYPD—I need to
commandeer this vehicle.
- It's a crossover.
It's a crossover SUV,
and you can't have it.
- I'm a cop—can you please
get out of the car?
- No, this Schmidt's mom's car,
and I'm more scared of her
than I am of some two-bit thug.
- I'm not a thug—I'm police.
- Okay, then name one law.
- Don't kill people.
- That's on me—
I set the bar too low.
- Look, can you please
just get out?
- Okay, you can drive,
but I'm not getting out.
- Right.
- Also, I have the seat warmer
on—I don't just have
a really hot butt.
- Doesn't matter to me—
a perp is getting away.
Oh, it's very hot.
[car screeches]
- I can't believe
this is happening.
Thanks a lot, New York.
You know what, if your city's
so great, then how come
it's not the state capital?
- What—who cares about
the state's capital?
This is the concrete jungle
where dreams are made of.
That doesn't sound right—
where dreams are made of?
- I don't know—
you tell me.
It's your dumb city.
- It's grammatically odd.
Whatever, I'm sure wherever
you're from has strange songs
written about it, too.
- Los Angeles?
- Damn it, all the songs
there are so good.
[yells]
[grunts]
- Hey, watch my soup.
- I'm chasing a criminal.
Your soup is not important.
- You took an oath
to serve and protect.
That applies to my soup.
- You know that's not
what the oath is about.
You're making a point
you don't even believe in.
- Garbage truck!
[both screaming]
[tires screeching
and glass breaking]
- Oh.
- Damn it!
He got away.
- Well, I spilled my soup.
You tell me which is worse.
- My thing.
Very clearly my thing.
- Captain Holt,
can we talk to you?
- What is the meaning of this?
Am I the subject of a punking?
- It's a beginning-of-work
hang.
- And why are you all
in such good moods?
- Because you told us that
you're miserable, too.
And that means
you'll fight to get us off
the night shift, right?
- Well, here's what I have to
say about that: the night shift
stinks—stinks like a butt.
And I will do everything
in my power to make sure
we get back to the day shift.
What are we standing around for?
Put some Sousa on already.
I want to get wild.
- Well, well, well,
if it isn't one of
the world-famous Night Bros.
- It's the Night Boys, and—
why did I correct you?
I would've preferred "Bros."
- Did you solve
your case yet?
- No.
- Night shift, am I right?
You remind me of me.
- It's not
the night shift, okay?
I found the perp, and I would've
taken him down, but I'm hobbled,
and I didn't have a partner
because ever since Boyle
had a son, that's all
he can focus on.
- Whoa, hey, are you angry at
Boyle for having a kid?
- No, I'm just mad because
I'm working the night shift,
and I have to use a cane,
and, yes, the one thing I could
always count on no matter what—
Boyle being there for me—
is also gone.
- What do you say we let
day shift Lohank take
a crack at this?
- [sighs]
- I'm gonna put a little
something up in the old hopper.
You tell me if it vibes
with you.
- That's so gross.
- Life moves forwards,
not backwards, and things
will never be as they were.
And you can be angry about that,
or you can embrace the fact
that your best friend
now has a son.
How cool is that, amigo?
- Ugh, "amigo."
All right, fine, yes, I'll admit
it, it is pretty cool.
Boyle's wanted it
for a very long time.
I guess I haven't actually spent
that much time with Nikolaj yet.
[correcting]
- Nikolaj.
- Man, am I seriously
about to take emotional advice
from Lohank?
- You know you want to,
compadre.
Go to him.
- Hey, I'm really sorry.
I shouldn't have said that
about Pimento.
I'm sure he's gonna come back.
- I'm not even
thinking about it anymore.
That wasn't even me crying
in the bathroom earlier—
that was someone else with these
same boots, but now she's gone.
- Look, when Jake was in witness
protection, and I didn't know
when he was ever coming back,
you were always there
when I needed to vent.
So I'll do your paperwork,
and if you ever want company
on that bench, I'm there.
- Thanks... I would advise
against it though—if he does
come back, things are gonna get
real raunchy, real fast, like,
do a lot of licking, that's
probably indecent exposure—
I don't want to get—
- Okay, got it.
You know what—I'll just start
with this stack right here.
Thanks, Rosa, okay, good talk.
[knocking]
- Hey, what's up?
I can't work the case
tonight.
Nikolaj's allergies
are acting up,
and now the dog seems to be
allergic to him.
It's this whole thing.
Did you find Smith?
- No, uh,
he actually got away.
- Sorry, man.
- Ah, it's all right.
It's the day shift's
problem now.
- Whatever happened to
working until it's done?
- Honestly... Lohank kind of
talked some sense into me.
- Lohank?
- Yeah, it was so gross,
but I want to apologize.
- For what?
- Well, I kept talking about
how I wanted everything
to go back to normal,
but if that actually happened,
this little guy
wouldn't be here.
Or is he big?
I don't know what size
kids are supposed to be,
or anything about kids, really.
I think maybe that's part of
the problem—it doesn't matter.
I got a present for Nikolaj.
- Thanks, Jake.
Come on in, give it to him.
- Niko.
- Hey, little man.
- [gasps]
A garbage truck!
- You wanna know something cool?
A truck just like this
almost killed me today.
- [clears throat]
- Uh, kissed me,
almost kissed me.
Anyway, let's get some trash in
this thing—am I right?
Vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom!
- You're silly.
- Yep, I am silly.
- Oh, my God,
this is a dream come true.
I gotta get my phone—
I gotta film this.
Oh, but then I'll miss it.
Oh, but I want it forever.
Agh, but I should
stay in the moment.
Ah, but then I'll forget.
Oh, my God,
this is a nightmare.
- Not a doctor, shh.