- Good morning, everyone.
- Oh. My. Goodness.
Sarge.
What. Are. The. Chances?
- I say zero?
- Ugh!
I mean, when Genevieve
got me these suspenders,
I thought I'd lean into it
and go for the whole look,
but I didn't want
to step on your toes.
That being said,
you know what this means.
- Don't do this, Charles.
- Oh, it's already done.
Gather round, y'all.
It's time to play
"Who Wore It Best?"
- I'd really rather not.
- Because you're
a wittle chicken?
Who wore it best?
Who wore it beeest?
all: Terry.
- What?
Come on!
- You should change, Boyle.
- [sighs] Fine.
- Not here!
[upbeat music]
♪
- Hey, Peralta.
How's it going, man?
- Pretty good.
Thanks for asking.
- Cool, cool, cool.
So how's it going?
- I'm still pretty good.
Nothing has changed.
- I hadn't heard about that.
- All right, you're clearly
not listening to me.
I can say whatever I want.
- Tell me about it.
- I murdered Charles
this weekend.
- I feel you.
- Now that I have
the taste for blood,
I can't stop murdering.
- Been there.
- Okay, Sarge. Sarge?
- Jake.
When'd you get here?
- Wow.
- I'm sorry.
I'm just trying
to see if Captain Holt
is done with his meeting yet.
So, how's it going?
- Okay. We've been over this.
I'm pretty good.
Why are you acting so weird?
- I'm nervous.
I'm gonna talk to Captain Holt
about getting me
more responsibility.
Well, got to go.
"Die Hard."
Explosions. Whatever.
- Wait, no!
Just when the conversation
was getting interesting!
- Hello, Captain Raymond Holt,
it is I,
Sergeant Terrance Jeffords,
your friend, but more
importantly, your employee.
- I've never heard you
speak like this, Sergeant.
I like it.
Each sentence
so rife with information.
Go on, please.
- Thank you.
I can do more, sir.
I'd like to take on
additional responsibilities.
- Good. I like seeing you
take initiative.
Let's see what there is.
One Police Plaza is looking
for a City Council liaison.
That's a rewarding
but challenging opportunity,
but I think
you'll do a great job.
- That sounds perfect.
Thank you, Captain.
- My pleasure. The application
is due tomorrow.
- Okay.
- It's 96 pages.
- Okay. Okay.
- Not including
a 4,000-word personal essay.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Will that be a problem?
- No!
Not a problem for Terry.
Terry does not have
a problem at all.
Terry's got a big problem!
- Ooh! Math or real life?
- Why would I have
a big math problem?
- I've seen it happen.
- I'm supposed to pick up
Cagney and Lacey from day care
in 30 minutes,
but I have to stay late
to work on an application
I just got from Holt.
- They're six.
They can take the subway.
- Rosa, that's crazy.
They're babies.
Terry, just call them an Uber.
- Or just have your sitter
pick 'em up.
- Scully actually has
the most reasonable idea.
These truly are strange days.
- Sharon can't pick 'em up
'cause she's out of town
with Ava,
and the sitter doesn't get
to my house till 6:30.
- Jake and I can pick them up.
- Absolutely.
Couple of issues—
I don't have any car seats,
and my rear window is
technically a "shower curtain."
- Really? Why?
- Mm.
- You know what?
Doesn't matter.
Just take my minivan.
- You got it.
- Thanks, guys.
I appreciate it.
- Mm, mm-mm-mm-mm!
Mm-mm!
- Why are you doing that
with your face?
- I'm smiling
at Mommy and Daddy.
- Ugh.
- Gross.
- Picking up Cagney and Lacey.
One taste of practice parenting,
and you two will be so hot
to have sex.
The kind that make babies.
- Walk away, Charles.
- Okay.
But I'll be back in nine months.
- How ridiculous is Charles?
Pssh.
- So ridiculous. Pssh.
- Pssh.
Hey, girls!
Who's the coolest person
you've ever met
in your entire lives?
both: You are!
- And who's the most handsome
dude in all the land,
even objectively more
than Idris Elba?
both: You are!
- Man, kids are awesome.
You can tell them
literally anything,
and they'll just say it.
- I know, right?
Check it out.
Who was the first
female congresswoman?
both: Jeannette Rankin!
- Oh. That's fun.
They won't get teased for that.
both: Up. Down. Up. Down.
Up. Down. Up. Down. Up. Down.
- Oh, uh, maybe don't play
with the windows?
Jake, tell them to stop.
- But playing with the windows
is fun.
- Jake.
- And...
it could spark
a lifelong interest
in mechanical engineering.
But sure. If you want,
I'll tell these young girls
that you don't think science
is a good fit for them.
- Play with those windows,
ladies.
both: Yay!
- That was actually really cool
with Cagney and Lacey.
I think we rocked it.
- Right? I don't see
what the big deal is
about being a parent—
that was so easy.
- Yeah,
anyone who's ever complained
about parenting
has no idea what they're doing.
[cell phone ringing]
Mm.
Hey, it's the sarge.
Probably calling
for some child-rearing tips.
Parent of the year speaking.
Terry, baby, talk to me.
- Where the hell is Moo Moo?
- Oh, no. I think Terry
has a child named Moo Moo,
and we forgot to pick her up.
- It's not a baby, Jake.
It's Cagney's blankie.
She calls it that because
it has a little cow head.
She said
she had it in the minivan.
Where is it now?
- Uhhh...
all: Up. Down. Up. Down.
Up. Down. Up. Down.
- Never let 'em
play with the windows.
That's Parenting 101.
And Santiago, I can't believe
you didn't stop it.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I knew it was wrong,
and I did nothing,
which is ultimately worse.
- Cagney can't sleep
without Moo Moo,
and if Cagney doesn't sleep,
then Lacey doesn't sleep,
and if Cagney and Lacey
don't sleep—
- Terry doesn't sleep.
- No. Jake doesn't live.
- Oh, my God.
- Where did you start
letting them play
with the windows?
- Uh, on Eighth.
It was close to the house.
- It better be.
The sitter leaves
in ten minutes,
and this is the last thing
I need!
- Okay.
So sorry about this, Sarge.
Oh, and one more thing.
I love you.
- I love you too, Jake.
♪
Moo Moo?
Moo Moo!
[sighs]
- What's going on, buddy?
- Oh, hey.
- Whoa, whoa, don't move.
- Oh, I was just—
- Step back.
Keep your hands
where I can see 'em.
Drop that.
- Hey, Sarge.
We felt really bad
about Moo Moo,
so we got you a new one.
She's called New Moo.
- I don't want it.
- Oh, the liaison application
got you down?
- I finished that.
- I know. There's nothing sadder
than finishing a nice,
long juicy application.
It's like, why can't
there be another essay
or even a short answer?
- No one is relating to you
right now. What's wrong?
- I got stopped by a cop
last night.
- Stopped for what?
- Stopped for walking.
- That makes zero sense
unless...
Oh, crap.
I see what happened.
- Yeah.
- Sarge, that's terrible.
- That's so messed up.
- Oh, jeez.
I have no idea what's going on.
- He got stopped
for being black.
Get woke, Scully.
- What happened?
- It was right after
I found Moo Moo.
- What're you doing
in this neighborhood,
buddy?
- I live here. Listen—
- Whoa. You need
to lower your voice.
- Lower my voice?
- You know what?
Put your hands on your head.
Turn around.
Don't make any sudden movements.
- I didn't do anything.
Also, I'm a—
- Keep talking.
See what happens next, huh?
Big guy.
- Well, did you tell him
you're a cop?
- I tried to,
but things escalated so quickly,
and I didn't have my badge
on me.
I eventually told him,
and he finally looked me up
in the system
and let me go.
- I can't believe this—
I mean, nothing like that
has ever happened to me,
and I've done
some pretty suspicious things
in the street.
- Hey, hey, hey, there.
What are you doing?
- I'm just playing a prank
on my buddy.
- Sounds fun.
Carry on.
- It was a very good prank.
I totally thought
I was gonna die.
- I mean, I've had run-ins
with officers before,
but this one really stings.
It was right outside my home.
- So what are you gonna do?
Slash his tires?
You shouldn't do that,
but just out of curiosity,
what kind of car does he drive,
and where does he park it?
- You could file
an official complaint.
I mean,
Captain Holt would wield that
like a hammer and crush the guy.
- I don't want to start
a whole hullaballoo, all right?
I mean, I think I just need
to sit down with the guy
and have a direct conversation,
just to make sure
he doesn't ever do anything
like this again.
- That makes sense.
- You think you two
can handle watching the kids
while I meet
with Officer Maldack?
- Oh, they can handle it.
- Calm down, Charles.
- Ugh.
- But yes, Terry,
we can watch the kids.
Trust me. There's nothing
those little munchkins
can throw at us
that we can't handle.
- Why was Daddy in trouble
with the policeman?
- Uh... that's complicated.
- Is it because he's black?
both: Uh...
- What do we do?
We can't call Terry.
We told him
we could handle anything.
I've got it.
We just leave.
We go home.
Never speak of this.
- No! We can't leave the
children that are in our care.
- Right.
- Let me call Charles.
He's a parent.
He'll know what to do.
- Smart.
- Mm.
A parental crisis.
This is the good stuff
right here.
You are knee-deep in the thick,
rich broth of parenthood.
- Well, that was a nightmare.
Who else can we call?
- I'm already ahead of you.
Calling Rosa.
- Make 'em go to bed.
- It's 6:30 p.m.
They're not tired.
- Make. Them.
- Okay. Hang up.
I'll call Gina.
- Ugh. Come on, Jake.
Just explain the deep-rooted
institutionalized racism
that remains pervasive
in this country
to this day.
- Gina, they're children.
- So put it in a song, Jake.
Watch this.
♪ Racism, racism
- I'm hanging up.
♪ Racism
- Gina, I'm hanging up.
♪ Racism, baby
- That's a great song.
I'm hanging up.
Okay. So Gina was
a bust as well.
Looks like we're out of options.
Unless.
- No.
- It's all we have.
[gunfire and screaming]
- Hey, Jakey.
Yeah, I'd love to chat,
but I can't.
Hitchcock and I are eating cake
for dinner
and watching a movie.
- Ask Amy
if she wants to come over.
- I'm hanging up.
[Jake sighs]
- Why're you smiling?
That was useless.
- Are you kidding me?
Hitchcock and Scully
just handed us a gem.
- Who wants cake?
both: Me!
- And who wants to watch
"101 Dalmatians"
and not ask
any hard-to-answer questions
about your father and race?
both: Me! Me! Me!
- Nice.
♪
- Officer Maldack.
Thanks for coming.
- Hey.
I'm really glad you set this up.
I'm so sorry for what happened.
- Oh. Wow.
I am really happy to hear that.
I was thinking this conversation
was gonna go a lot differently.
- No, no.
It was an honest mistake.
I mean,
if I had known you were a cop,
I never would've treated you
that way.
- So you're sorry for not
knowing I was a cop sooner?
- Yeah.
- And that's it?
- But you shouldn't have
treated me that way
whether I was a cop or not.
- What do you mean?
- I was just walking
down the street.
There's nothing suspicious
or illegal about that.
- Okay, but you and I both know
that you don't exactly look like
you belong in that neighborhood.
- I live there.
- Look.
Nine out of ten times I get
called to that neighborhood,
it's about a guy
that looks like you.
- Were you responding to a call?
- No,
but you're missing the point.
- No, you're missing the point.
I just want you to admit
you only stopped me
because I'm black
and to apologize
and say you won't do it again!
- Hey, look.
We wouldn't even be having
this conversation
if you had your badge on you.
Next time, don't forget it.
- Oh, so this is all my fault?
- I'm not apologizing
for doing my job.
- That's not the job, man.
♪
- Whoa. I can't believe
it went down like that.
- Should we maybe revisit
some of our earlier ideas
vis-à-vis tires and slashing?
- I should've known there was
no talking to a guy like that.
I don't see any other option.
I'm submitting
an official complaint with Holt.
- I know it might feel weird
to report another officer,
but it's the right move.
- Holt's gonna eat him
for breakfast.
- Maldack has no idea
what's about to hit him.
- I'm not gonna submit this.
- What? Why not?
- Because
I think it's a mistake.
♪
- Hey, Sarge?
Everything okay?
Only ask 'cause you haven't
moved in the last 58 minutes.
- He doesn't want me
to file the complaint.
- Well, of course
Officer Maldack doesn't want you
to file the complaint.
He's the one
being complained about.
I just realized
you meant Captain Holt.
- Yeah.
- What?
Did you mess up the grammar
or something?
- Did you dangle a participle?
Ugh, Terry,
Holt hates a dangler.
- Grammar was fine.
He said he thought
filing it was a mistake.
- Wow. Well, look.
Captain Holt cares about you
more than anything.
I'm sure he's got a good reason.
Maybe you should go talk to him
about it, you know?
Go to his house.
- Yeah. That's a good idea.
I'm gonna do that.
- And while
you're talking to him,
Jake and Amy can babysit
your kids.
Unless they're too busy
making babies of their own.
Shaka-daka-dow.
- Get out of us.
But yes, we are happy
to look after the kids again.
- Thanks, guys.
I appreciate your support.
Now, I'm gonna go find out
what the hell is going on
with Captain Holt.
- Are you two sure
you should be babysitting?
You seemed real freaked
when you called me last night.
- Yes, but then we figured out
how to be good parents.
TV and cake.
- TV and cake were my parents.
[chuckles]
- It's okay.
- Sergeant Jeffords.
- That's right.
It's me, Sergeant Jeffords,
from the precinct.
I'm the guy whose damn complaint
you don't want to submit,
and I can't think
of one damn reason why!
- Everyone.
This is Sergeant Jeffords.
- Hi!
I'm sorry for interrupting
your dinner party.
- No problem at all.
This is important.
Also,
Kevin's friend Margo is here,
and she's a real class-A drip.
- Sir, I can't get why you don't
want me to file the complaint.
I thought you of all people
would support me.
- First of all, let me say,
what that officer did to you
was wrong, deeply wrong,
and I'm furious about it.
- Okay.
So why don't you back me up?
- Because that complaint
could backfire.
Cops who blow the whistle
on other cops
almost always face a backlash,
just like people
who socialize with Margo
invariably hear about
her trip to Scottsdale.
- You're real worked up
about Margo.
- Sorry.
She's horrible.
Listen, I don't want to see
your career derailed
because you were besmirched
for reporting
on another officer.
- But what he did was wrong.
He should be besmirched!
- Yes,
but is that besmirching worth
the greater besmirching
of your career?
You have to balance
besmirchings.
There's politics to being a cop.
- But I wasn't harassed
for being a cop.
I was harassed as a black man.
- I'm not saying do nothing.
I'm saying
the most powerful action
you can take
is to rise through the ranks
so that you can make
large-scale changes.
I've had to pick my battles,
and it hasn't always been easy,
but now I have my own precinct,
a precinct whose officers
would never do to you
what Officer Maldack did.
- I understand
what you're saying, but—
- Shh.
I hear Margo's squeaky shoes
in the hallway.
One guess as to where in Arizona
she brought them. Scottsdale.
- Oh. Ray.
There you are.
I'm about to start
my Scottsdale slideshow.
It has all the highlights.
- There are no highlights
in Scottsdale, Margo.
- That's what you think,
Raymond.
[breathing loudly]
- Okay, we got
chocolate-chocolate,
chocolate-vanilla,
and my personal favorite,
a bowl full of cake batter.
- And loads o' movies.
- Eh?
- We don't want to do that.
- Uh, maybe you didn't
hear us correctly.
We've got cake.
We've got movies.
It's time to party!
- Is being black bad?
- We're black.
Are we gonna get in trouble
like Daddy?
- Jake, can I talk to you
for a second?
- Yes, please.
- We have a problem.
- I know.
What kind of kids
don't want to eat cake?
Should we call Child Services
on Terry?
- Jake, I think
we have to face the music
and talk to them for real.
- I know.
You're right.
But I'm gonna munch the cake
batter while we do it.
If you don't
eat the raw egg fast,
it makes you even more sick.
- Never mind, let's go.
- Okay.
- Okay, girls.
There's something
called prejudice,
which comes from the Latin words
"pre," or "before,"
and "judicium,"
which means "to judge."
Are you with me so far?
both: No.
- No.
- Okay. Um,
you know how it's tougher
in this world to be a woman?
both: It is?
- No. No, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
- Then I don't want to be
a woman.
- Me neither.
- You don't have to be
if that's who you are—
you know what?
That's a whole other
conversation.
Uh...
[sighs]
Okay. Here we go.
A cop did a bad thing
and tried to get your daddy
in trouble,
but your daddy didn't do
anything wrong.
- Because Daddy's black?
- Yeah.
- That's scary.
- It is scary.
But that cop was wrong,
and what he did was bad.
- And the most important thing
is your daddy's okay,
and he's not in trouble,
and he loves you both
more than anything in the world.
- Okay?
both: Okay.
- Yeah. Okay.
Well, that wasn't so bad.
Well, if you guys have any other
questions, we're here for you.
- What's an orgasm?
- Come on!
- Terry, I know you're upset,
but this is
the right thing to do.
You're this close
to the City Council position,
and that's just the beginning.
It would be a shame
to jeopardize that.
- Look, I get
that the guys in our precinct
wouldn't profile me,
but it still happened
only one precinct over.
- Which is why you need to keep
pushing forward in your career,
so that you can
change the system.
Terry, you're a great cop.
You could become
a chief or higher.
- How long will it take
to make change that way?
Maldack is on the street now.
You know why I became a cop?
- Please share.
- Because when I was a kid,
I always wanted
to be a superhero.
- Stop it!
Stop bothering little Terry!
- Or what?
- Or I will defeat you!
♪
Whoa.
- I wanted to help people
like that cop helped me.
But right now,
I don't feel like a superhero.
I feel the opposite.
When I got stopped
the other day,
I wasn't a cop.
I wasn't a guy
who lived in a neighborhood
looking
for his daughter's toy.
I was a black man,
a dangerous black man.
That's all he could see:
a threat.
And I couldn't stop thinking
about my daughters.
And their future.
And how years from now,
they could be walking
down the street,
looking
for their kids' Moo Moo,
and get stopped by a bad cop.
And they probably won't
get to play the police card
to get out of trouble.
I don't like that thought,
and I'm gonna do something
about it.
So I don't care
if it might hurt my career.
I'm filing that report.
Even if I have to go
over your head to do it.
- Kind of seemed
like you were gonna
get up and leave
after saying all that.
- I was,
but I think I hear Margo.
- Thanks for babysitting
last night.
The girls told me
what you talked about,
and it couldn't have been easy.
- I'm sorry I told them
orgasms was another word
for oranges.
I panicked.
- Yeah, it did make it awkward
when they asked for orgasm juice
this morning,
but I was more talking
about the other stuff.
- Yeah. We didn't really know
what to say.
At one point,
I'm pretty sure I sang
all of En Vogue's
"Free Your Mind."
- Well, they had fun,
and you made 'em feel safe.
You did good.
Oh. They made you
a "thank you" card.
- Aww.
Pretty sure
my nose isn't quite this big,
especially with all
the racial sensitivity talk,
but I appreciate the effort.
- Sergeant Jeffords.
A moment of your time, please.
I came to a realization
after you stormed out
last night.
- I wouldn't say I stormed out.
I shook hands with both you
and Kevin before I left.
- And Kevin and I agreed
that you squeezed
significantly tighter
than necessary.
- I guess I was
a little worked up.
- With good reason.
I thought a lot
about our conversation.
When I was a young
police officer
and things like this
would happen to me,
I felt very alone.
I wanted to call out
every bad cop I encountered,
and there were a lot,
but as a black gay man,
I never had a superior
who was on my side,
so the advice I offered you,
that came from a different place
at a different time.
I put all my energy
towards rising to a rank
where I could make a difference.
Well, I'm there now,
and I realize
that if I don't
back you up on this,
I would be betraying
the very thing
that I worked so hard for,
so I filed the complaint.
- I appreciate that, Captain.
- Are you still upset?
- No. Not at all.
- You should consider
modifying your handshake.
It's sending the wrong message.
- Copy that.
- Whew. I am so glad
we don't have to do
any more babysitting
for a while.
- I know.
It was so stressful.
- So stressful.
But, like, actually
kind of rewarding too.
- Shaping young minds like that
felt so powerful.
- Yeah.
- But, like, so exhausting.
- Oh, yeah. Can you imagine
doing that every night?
Forget it.
But also, their little shoes
are so cute.
They're like little circles.
- I know,
and everything they hold
looks so big
because their hands are so tiny.
- Yeah, and they have to hold
a cup of water with both hands
'cause they're so weak.
- I know!
- Whoo-whee!
That's what I'm talking about!
both: Boyle.
- Lucky for you,
Amy, I am an unlicensed doula.
I've delivered three
of my cousins
and one of my uncles—
long story.
- Go away!
- Yes, Papa.
♪
- Please close the blinds.
We're about to violate several
departmental regulations.
- Ho, ho!
All right!
- It's been a very long week,
and as of right now,
we're both off duty.
I think we've earned a drink.
- I can get behind that.
- I heard from City Council
about the liaison position.
- Is that right?
- You didn't get it.
- Oh.
Oh, this is a sad drink.
Was it the complaint?
- We'll never know for sure,
but, uh, I think it's likely.
However, this is
not a sad drink.
We're celebrating
to doing the right thing.
- I don't know.
Maybe we shouldn't have
filed the complaint.
Maybe I could've done more
if I had gotten the liaison job.
- Maybe.
But one thing's for certain.
Maldack will think twice
before making another bad stop
like that again.
That's a win.
- Yeah.
It's tough.
- It is.
So if Sharon's
still out of town,
who's, uh, looking out
for Cagney and Lacey?
both: [screaming]
- Not a doctor.
- Shh.