Oh, that's Val.  You know,
it's her first time to the mansion,
and she's my best friend,
so I just want her to drop dead.
How thoughtful.
Allow me.  You pose.
/Okay.
I'm dropping dead.
Mission accomplished.
May I take your coat?
/Do I get a stub?
No.  And you don't
have to tip him either.
Oy, she's got no class.
Come on, Val, move.
Oy, this place is
like the Taj Mahal.
Only with more bathrooms.
You never have to wait.
How come I'm still stuck in Flushing
and you're living like Jackie O?
Jackie O is
two doors down.
Jackie O's your neighbor?
/Uh-huh.
And, you know, she's very
concerned about John-John.
You heard he quit the D.A.
job, huh? /Oh, really?
Oh, yeah.  And now he ran off
to California with that blonde fish.
Oh.  Oh, God, oh, go have kids.
Honey, it's all in how you raise them.
With mine, I got no complaints.
You've been their nanny
for two weeks.
And I've worked
wonders with them.
Shut-up, Brighton!
/You shut-up!
You're giving me
a nervous breakdown!
You see?  Before me
they never communicated.
You know, you're gonna get pimples,
too, some day, if you ever grow up!
Oh, that's a pimple?
I thought it was a small planet.
Leave your sister alone.
/I can't.
The gravitational force
is sucking me in!
I'm giving it all she's got, Captain.
I cannot break away.
You're so pathetic,
Brighton!
We both hate you!
Good.
Then my work here is done.
Brighton,
what's your problem?
I guess I'm just
bad to the bone.
No, honey, you have
no idea what bad is.
Now the boys Val and I went to
school with, they were bad, huh?
Oh, the worst.
/Oy, and now they're all taken.
You remember Lenny?
Sure.  Lenny Brown.
Baddest man in the whole damn...
Oh no, that was Leroy.
But Lenny was bad.
/And tough.
The kid had a smoker's
cough in the fourth grade.
Really? /Oh, he could blow
smoke rings out of his nose,
either nostril.
Remember when he would light
a match off his zipper?
Honey, I'm still
dreaming about that one.
So he was cool, huh?
/Oh, he was a god.
The James Dean of Flushing.
I wonder whatever happened to him?
I hear he's a big shot
at R.J. Reynolds.
Oh, I should have nabbed him
right out of reform school.
If this facial doesn't work,
I think I'm gonna kill myself.
Maggie, would you relax?
It's just a little zit.
Yeah, but...
/Shut-up, Brighton.
I dread puberty.
I have combination skin.
Here's where having me
for a nanny comes in handy.
You kids know that I'm a graduate
of the Ultissima Beauty Institute.
Four times Dean's list.
/And yet she's so accessible.
What's that? /Orange rinds.
You know, at Elizabeth Arden
they'll charge you two hundred dollars
and call it aroma therapy.
Trust me, you'll be gorgeous.
I see an improvement already.
What's this?
Oh, some stupid thing
at my stupid school.
Oh, a carnival.
Oh, me and Val used to throw
these for Jerry's kids.
Who's Jerry?
/Jerry Lewis.
He used to be hysterical.
Now he's hysterical in France.
Yeah, right.  Like we're gonna
go to some dumb carnival.
Why?  It says right here,
'fun for the whole family.'
Wouldn't we actually have
to be a family first.
Dad's too busy.  He doesn't
have time to spend with us.
Maybe Daddy's seeing
other children.
Let's not be paranoid.
I'm not paranoid.
Who said I was?
Help, Niles.  We need drinks.
And keep them coming.
I take it, sir, the composer
meetings aren't going well.
Why isn't there any new talent in this town?
The man in my office is positively ancient.
He's not composing,
he's decomposing.
I got something that'll cheer you up.
There's a big carnival
at Brighton's school this Saturday.
Oh, food, rides, games.
Sounds splendid.
By all means, take the children.
Have a wonderful time.
Well, I kind of thought that
the whole family would go.
That would include the father.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm seeing composers all weekend.
Oh well, that's understandable.
Why do I feel a 'but' coming on?
No but.
However, a carnival would be a good way
for you to spend some time with your kids.
And time is so fleeting
at this age.
While I appreciate the skill
and subtlety of your guilt mongering,
I am opening a musical
in eight weeks. /So?
I have no music.
/Oh.
Otherwise I'd love to go.
Brighton, don't be so smart.
Gracie, dear, take smaller
bites.  And, Maggie,
do try to be a bit more outgoing.
Well, carry on.
Well, he's got my vote
for father of the year.
Now, now, he would
if he could, but he can't.
I mean, the man has to
make a living, don't he?
Well how else can we afford the lifestyle
to which I've become accustomed?
So I flunked facials.
We'll color it in and call it a mole.
There.  You look just
like Cindy Crawford.
I look like
John Boy Walton.
America loves him.
Hey, Mags.  Wow,
you look really beautiful.
And?
And nothing.
You look really good.
Shut-up, Brighton.
Why are you being so nice
to your sister?  Who'd you kill?
Why does everyone
assume the worst of me?
It saves time.
You know, we did handwriting
analysis in school today.
I found out I'm very vulnerable.
Oh, isn't that
fascinating?
Gee, I don't suppose you'd
wanna analyze my handwriting?
Well, sure.
I happen to have a piece of old,
unimportant scrap paper somewhere. Let's see.
Ah, why don't you sign
your name right here?
Okay.  Sucker!
What just happened here?
Honey, I am so far ahead of you,
we're in different time zones.
Oh, a note from the Headmaster.
You're kidding?
Brighton Millhouse Sheffield!
You were caught smoking?!
/I was holding it for a friend.
Oh, please, Brighton.
Smoking? That's disgusting.
It takes the idiots that start
that filthy habit years to quit.
I still haven't knocked off
all the weight.
Where are you going?
Where do you think?
To tell your father.
You heard.  The man's busy.
/Not too busy to hear this.
But he'll ship me off to military school.
And can our country really afford that?
Brighton, smoking.  Where would
you ever even get an idea like that?
From you.
Come to think of it.
Me?
Bad, bad Lenny Brown. /What?
Oh.  Oy.
So, uh, maybe we should just
keep this our little secret.
Wait a minute.  Are you
trying to blackmail me?
Let's just say, if I'm going down,
you're going down with me.
Who are you?
Edward G. Robinson?
You think I'm gonna be intimidated by somebody
that could walk under a coffee table?
He'll fire me.  I'd fire me.
Just when I figured out the bidet
is not a water fountain.
Oh, what am I doing?  I quit.
I gotta learn to deal with
my problems without a crutch.
What's to eat?
What was I thinking telling a story
like that to a ten year old kid?
On the other hand, if I told him to
jump off the Empire State Building...
Hello.  That was my mother's voice
that just crossed the Queensboro Bridge
and flew out my mouth.
But with such dulcet tones.
Oh boy, this is so
typical of kids.
You try and you try
and what do you get?
A slap in the face.
Oy, my mother again.
Niles, call an exorcist.
The previous nannies signed all
of Master Brighton's discipline
reports themselves.
You're kidding?
The nanny can do that?
Of course.  In fact,
Nanny Six retired with
Carpal-Tunnel syndrome.
You know, Brighton wanted
me to sign that note,
but at the time he was just
looking to save his butt.
Of course, now that
I'm looking to save mine,
it's not such a bad idea.
No, I've gotta tell Mister
Sheffield what I did.
If I don't, the evil eye'll get me.
I'll be hit by a bus for sure.
The evil eye?  Your mother again?
/No.  Grandma Yetta.
Well, Miss Fine, it's always
a pleasure spending time
with you and your family.
The kind of music that I hear
for this show is kind of a,
you know, Bacharach/David kind of
a "Promises, Promises" thing.
Ya-ta-da, ya-ta-da, da, da.
Bounce, bounce.
Lots of bounce.
I'm not sure. /You're right.
Dated!  Awful!  Out!
Knock, knock.
/Yes, Miss Fine, what is it?
And quickly, please.  We have eight
more composers to see today.
And you're right up there.
Well?
Oh, maybe this isn't the right time.
I don't want to annoy you.
Too late.  Go on.
Okay.  It's about Brighton.
/Yes?
Well, remember the other day Val
and I were talking in the kitchen?
Or was it the living room?
Anyway, it was somewhere in the house.
It's such a nice house.
You know, that's a lovely painting.
Who are those people?
Miss Fine! / Well, it's just that it brings
the color out in the couch so nice.
Yeah, well they say Rembrandt
goes with everything.
Now what about Brighton?
Is he injured?
No.
Well is there property damage?
/ No.
Is he missing?
/ No, he's right upstairs.
Well then, what are you doing here? Isn't
this something you could handle on your own.
Honestly, Maxwell, what is the point of having
a nanny if she can't take care of
these things on her own?
Isn't that what I just said?
/Yes, but I wanted to say it, too.
Look, Miss Fine, whatever it is,
just take care of it.
I'm giving you carte blanche,
all right?
All right.
Oh, well, Niles, that was easier
than I thought it would be.
You didn't tell him, did you?
No.
What about Grandma Yetta's evil eye?
Oh, that's just an old bubbameister.
/ Bubbameister?
A bubbameister.
It's like an old wives tale.
Honestly, Niles,
it's the nineties for god sakes.
Who believes in the evil eye anyway?
Oy.
You're up early.
/I couldn't sleep.
Hm-hmm.
I have indigestion.  It has nothing
to do with a guilty conscience
if that's what you're implying.
Crepes.
/Back-off, Niles.
I said I would punish the kid.
What else do you want?
Dare I suggest syrup?
Oh, what's with the third degree?
I tried to tell him,
the man doesn't listen.
Everything I say goes in one ear
and out the other.
Good morning, Miss Fine.
I've been thinking about what you said.
What?  What did I say?
/About spending more time with the children.
Yes, see?  I've already started.
Children, we are going to the carnival.
All of us?
/ Hm-hmm.  The whole family.
We're gonna go on the rides.
We're going to eat cotton candy.
It'll be like being
a child again.
And it'll give me a chance to talk
to Brighton's headmaster.
See what he's been up to.
/ Whoops.
These things can get so sticky.
Uh, you know, I kind of soured
on that whole carnival thing.
It's so cold and windy.
It's in the gymnasium.
/ Hot and stuffy.
Miss Fine, I've just rearranged
my entire schedule,
and now you're telling
me you don't want to go.
Well, I'm not god.
I don't make the weather.
But you insisted.
I wasn't feeling
a hundred percent that day.
I think I was ovulating.
Your eggs, sir?
Well, you may stay at home,
but we are going.
Do something.
Okay, I'll do what I should
have done in the first place.
Here, here.
Here.
Mister Sheffield, I think
there's something you should know.
Brighton?
We don't care that you're on parole.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
Fine.  I'll tell him.
Mister Sheffield,
when we go to the carnival,
the headmaster may mention something
about Brighton smoking.
But he's quit.  And he's sorry.
And there's really  nothing
for you to worry about.
Niles, these crepes are divine.
And so light. / My mother makes
a blintz that could double for a mattress.
Girls, you may be excused.
Not you, Miss Fine.
Smoking, Brighton?
I, I can't believe this.
What, what on earth
possessed you to do this?
Are you through here?
It's beginning to look that way.
Well, I'm waiting, young man.
What have you got to say for yourself.
I didn't inhale.
That is the most pathetically
lame excuse I have ever heard.
Go to your room.
Not you, Miss Fine.
Well, Mister Sheffield,
I think there's something you should know.
Well, I'll say.
Why wasn't I told about this?
Well, I tried to tell you.
You told me to take care of it.
I didn't know what the problem was.
/ Because you wouldn't listen.
Because you didn't tell me
it was anything like this!
Oh, well, it's pointless
to continue this discussion.
You had chocolate cake yesterday.
What's that bloody well
got to do with anything?
Low blood sugar.
You're completely irrational.
I'm irrational?  Me?
/ Yes.
You're the one twisting everything around.
/Oh, so now I'm twisting?
You are the most exasperating,
infuriating...
I think I just had
a small stroke.
Does that mean we're not
going to the carnival?
Miss Fine...!
Well, it's very easy
for you to find fault.
You're off all day with
your glamorous theater people.
I'm stuck at home working
like a dog raising the kids.
You're the nanny!
It's your job!
Well, you're the father.
It's your job, too,
Mister Sheffield, sir.
Oh, just go to your room.
Yes, you!
Can you believe
he sent me to my room?
He is so adorable sometimes.
I'm in love!
/ No, no, no.  No, wrong.
Totally wrong.  Make a note.
Fire the casting director.
Maxwell, you're being
an absolute beast today.  I love it.
It's just that, that I know exactly
what I'm looking for.
I need a Broadway star
with huge stage presence
who's instantly recognizable
to the entire country.
Oh my god...
Hello...
/ Next!
He's tough.
/ You're telling me.
Break a leg, honey.
His.
I love her.
Your song, please?
Um, oh, I get to sing, too?
All right.
"People" in E flat.  Hit it.
/ Miss Fine!
Well, I can dream, can't I?
Take a break. Ladies and gentlemen,
let's take a break.
Miss Fine, we were
in the middle of something.
Yes, I know.
That's why I'm here.
You know, you shouldn't leave
the house with things unresolved.
That's why men die young.
That's not why.
It's because they want to.
The wife?
/The nanny.
Look, we both know that you walked out
on me because you were losing the argument.
I wasn't losing anything.
Trust me.  When you induce
a stroke on your opponent,
it's a sure win.
I think you're winning again.
But it wasn't a fair fight.
You didn't have all the facts.
I don't think
I can take anymore.
Brighton got the idea to smoke
from a story that he might have,
maybe, sort of heard from me.
/From you?
Kinda.
/Well what did you tell him?
Well, he said that he was bad and
so I told him about a kid that was worse.
Who knew he'd take it
as a challenge.
That's my boy.  Always striving
to reach new depths.
Oh, I'm the worst nanny
in the world.
All right, Rebecca
De Morney, then me.
Oh, I could just cut my tongue out.
So if you wanna fire me, do it now.
No, I'm not gonna fire you.
Although that offer to cut out
your tongue might have some merit.
Why, if you told Brighton
to jump off London Bridge...
God, I'm beginning to sound
just like my...
I know.  Don't you hate
when that happens?
I still can't believe that
son of yours didn't turn me in.
Yeah.  Why do you suppose that is?
Who knows?  He's probably got some
hideous torture planned for me later.
No, I think perhaps....
I mean, could it be?
What? /He likes you?
Well, stranger things
have happened.
Well, you're the first nanny Brightons'
made any kind of connection with.
His mother was the only
one that could handle him.
They had a special kind of relationship.
He feared her.
Fear.  That's the key.
Now we have to figure out a way
to scare him bad enough that
he never smokes again.
I sent him to his room.
Oh, please.  With a wide screen T.V.
and a fully stocked mini-fridge?  Punish me.
So, what do you suggest?
Something much more cruel
and unusual.
We are going to have to consult
the high priestess of punishment.
Hello, Ma?
Grandma Yetta?
Yeah?
It's Frannie.
Who?
Frannie, your granddaughter.
Oh, Frannie.  Hi.
Nice to meet you.
That's the one good thing about senility.
You're always meeting new people.
How you doin', Angel?
Thank God I still got my health.
Maybe you two could go out
and have a smoke later?
Morty!  Morty, you never
looked so good.
Did you get hair plugs?
Oh no, Grandma,
that's not daddy.
So who the hell are you?
Oh, Maxwell Sheffield.
We brought you some babka.
Cake.  Put it away.
Save it for my room.  If they see
babka, they'll all want.
Grandma, I want you
to meet somebody.
Oh, I haven't seen you
since you were this big.
No, Yetta, you never
met him before.
Oh.
Oy, Yetta, you sound like
you're making espresso over there.
All right, all right,
I get the point.
Oh no, you don't, buddy.
We're just getting started.
Why don't you go
visit with Yetta?
Over there? / Yeah.
Where the air is nice and fresh.
Come here.  Let me
have a look at that face.
He's ready to quit smoking.
Smoking?  Ech.
You smoke. /Me it doesn't
effect.  I'm like a horse.
But you, you know
what could happen?
We'll go meet Ethel.
Phlegm in a hairnet.
Oh please, not Ethel.
Not Ethel.
I swear.  I'll never touch another
cigarette again.  Oh God...
So what do you say,
we go grab a cup of coffee
and break open the babka?  Hmm?
Babka?  Babka?
/ Babka?  Babka?