(engines roaring)
Zoey: sorry, nigel.
Dinner took longer
than i thought.
And now we are stuck in traffic.
Yeah, bumper to bumper.
Well, tell ava i'll be there
in an hour, okay?
Okay.
Why didn't you
just tell him the truth?
Because i know
my ex-Husband quite well,
And it would really upset him
if he found out
You flew me to san francisco
in your private jet
Just to have fried clams.
Yeah, you're right.
You shouldn't tell him.
Thank you.
I'll tell him.
(laughs)
I just wanted to do
something nice for you
Before you went to london.
I'll only be gone a few weeks.
And i...
Will miss you.
And i will miss you.
(gasps)
Whoa.
What was that?
(nervous chuckle)
Don't worry, it's normal.
(both screaming)
Ahh! That's not normal!
God, oh, god, oh, god!
Zoey, i love you.
I don't want to die.
Did you hear me?
I said i love you.
I heard you,
and i said i don't want to die.
Pilot:
sorry about that, mr. Schmidt.
Just some clear air turbulence.
Should be smooth sailing
from here on out.
I doubt that.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-Ooh-Ooh,
ooh-Ohh, ooh-Ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a half men 9x17 ♪
Not in my mouth!
Original air date on february 20, 2012
♪ Men
Aw...
What's sadder than
an empty bottle of wine?
Being the boyfriend of
a 40-Year-Old drunk soccer mom.
What?
Oh, i was just thinking
You might want
to slow down a little.
It's only wine, geez.
It's only been wine
since last july.
Hey, hey, that got
a three-Star rating
In the wal-Mart wine tracker.
What's the big deal?
So, i need a few glasses
to loosen me up.
Are you saying you
need to get loaded
In order to have sex with me?
I'm not loaded.
Fine.
But it doesn't hurt.
Hey, guys.
Wally! Want some wine?
No, i don't like to drink
when i'm depressed.
Wally, it's the best time
to drink.
Also when you're bored, lonely,
or just, you know,
Too sober.
Why are you depressed?
I don't know.
It's kind of personal.
Okay, no problem.
What do you do when you
Tell someone you love them
and they don't respond?
(cork pops)
drink.
Wait, you told zoey
you love her?
Yeah, i thought the plane
was gonna crash,
And it just kind of came out,
Along with a little squirt
of pee.
So, what did she say?
(in british accent) "oh, god,
oh, god, i don't want to die."
Well, given the circumstance,
that's a legitimate response.
Sure, in the moment,
But what about
after the plane leveled out?
Well, what did she say then?
"why do i smell pee?"
Then we just sat there
in silence
For the rest of the flight.
Should have drank.
Yeah, well, i'm gonna go
change my underwear
Before i get diaper rash.
Wow, i feel bad for him.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, to tell
somebody you love them,
And just get no response.
Awful.
You know how i feel
about you, right?
Right.
You know how i
feel about you.
Oh, absolutely.
Still nice to hear
on occasion.
Oh, i agree.
I can do this
as long as you can, pal.
(knocking)
It's open.
Hey.
Can i talk to you for a minute?
Sure. What's up?
(sighs)
I didn't sleep at all
last night, man.
This zoey stuff
is making me crazy.
Oh, man, i'm sorry.
I'm starting to wonder
If i should break
up with her,
Oh, hang on. I mean,
just because she didn't say,
"i love you," doesn't mean
she doesn't feel it.
You think?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Some people have a hard time
Articulating their feelings,
So they express them
in other ways.
(lyndsey vomiting loudly)
Is that lyndsey?
(lindsey groaning)
Yeah, she had a little
too much vino last night.
Anyway, i think you just have
to be patient with zoey.
(lindsey vomiting loudly)
Yeah, i guess.
(vomiting)
(gagging)
Sorry, i... I have a...
A hard time with...
People throwing up.
Try watching
and holding her hair.
It's just, zoey's going
to england for a few weeks.
(vomiting resumes)
And-And i'm th... (gags)
I'm-I'm starting to
think if... (gags)
If i'm gonna end it,
now would be a good time.
Well, it... (gags)
(vomiting)
Whoa.
You think i'd be
used to it by now.
(groans)
no, no, no, don't...
Don't do anything hasty.
(vomiting continues)
I can't... I... I can't
just leave th...
I can't just leave things
the way that they are.
Why don't you...
Why don't you go talk to her,
You know, and just put
your caaards on the table.
Yeah, maybe.
(gags)
Lindsey: crap,
Now i've got to change my bra.
(lindsey grunts)
I-I-I mean, maybe we should
just give her some privacy.
Lindsey: oh, god,
now it's coming out both ends!
(vomiting resumes)
good idea.
Zoey: ava, you need
to get dressed.
Mummy has to go.
Walden.
De-E-Lightful.
Nigel, di-Isgusting.
What, are you here
to pick up your daughter?
I am.
Zoey tell you that we took
my jet to san francisco
Last night for fried clams?
No, she did not.
Well, we did.
Are you sharing this information
just to upset me?
Actually, i was hoping to make
you feel inadequate as well.
Oh, walden.
What are you
doing here?
Nigel, i'm running late,
So will you for once please
make yourself useful
And help ava get ready?
Well, only because
you asked so nicely.
Enjoy her.
Hi.
We need to talk.
Now? I'm about to leave
for the airport.
I'll take you.
Thanks, but i have a car coming.
Now, where is my passport?
Nigel, have you
seen my passport?
I don't live
here, zoey,
I merely
pay the rent.
Look, i just don't want
to leave things between us
The way that they are.
Everything's fine.
No, it's not.
I said i love you,
and the only thing
I got in response is the not
very surprising information
That you don't want to die
in a crashing plane.
Can't we discuss this
when i get back?
What's there to discuss?
You either love me,
or you don't.
Walden, i'm about to leave
on an important business trip,
And the last thing i need
right now is more pressure.
I'm not pressuring you.
I'm just asking you for a
simple, definitive answer
Right now before you leave.
(glass breaking)
what was that?
Sorry, just knocked over
your chinese table lamp.
Perhaps you can
buy another one
Next time you jet
to francisco.
It came up.
I'm sorry, i just don't have
the time for this now, okay?
Ava, are you dressed?
That seems pretty
definitive to me.
That's it.
No more relationships.
I'm done.
Finished; just over.
(elevator bell dings)
(exhales)
Hi.
And i'm back.
♪ Men
Hey, can i have 75 bucks
for the new call of duty?
$75 for a video game?
Think of it as an investment.
An investment?
Yeah. If i go into the
army after high school,
I'll already know how
to kill terrorists.
Who had corn chowder
for dinner last night?
How do you know anybody
had corn chowder last night?
'cause it's dripping
all over your bathroom.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
Uh, lyndsey got a little bit...
Queasy this morning.
Is she pregnant?
Oh, no, no, gosh, no.
(uneasy chuckle)
Absolutely not.
Here.
Me?
Not my girlfriend,
not my vomit,
Not my problem.
I'll clean it up.
You will?
For 75 bucks.
Woman:
that's great.
Hey, everybody.
This is jennifer.
Hi.
Berta: hey.
Hey.
Well, let's go take
a walk on the beach.
Great.
Uh, walden,
before you go,
Can i talk to you
for a minute?
I'll bring him right back.
You'd better.
My name's jake.
Hi, jake.
My friends call me... Jake.
What are you doing?
Zoey made it perfectly clear.
She doesn't love me or need me.
So, i'm moving on.
You left here an hour ago.
How did you find
another girl already?
Oh, i met her in the elevator.
I've been in
a million elevators.
I never once walked out
with a girl like that.
Maybe you need to work
on your attitude.
What exactly did zoey say?
No, it's what she didn't say.
She didn't say, "i love you."
Oh, please! If i insisted on
women saying "i love you"
I'd have never have had a
girlfriend, a wife or a mother.
(ringtone playing)
Oh. It's zoey.
Hello?
So, jennifer,
how old are you?
24. How old are you?
I'm... 24-And-A-Half.
Hmm.
Hmm?
I'm surprised
that you called.
Where are you?
On the plane.
We're sitting at the gate.
Are you okay?
Zoey: no.
I feel miserable
about the way we left things.
You do?
Zoey: yeah.
I've just been so stressed
and busy lately
That i haven't been able
to think straight.
But sitting here
for the last 40 minutes
Without so much
as a bloody glass of water,
I've come to a realization.
I'm listening.
The reason i haven't said...
Those words to you
Is because i'm afraid
That if i do say them,
something bad will happen.
Why would you think that?
'cause it always has.
I've only said
those words twice.
The last time,
i ended up married
To an insufferable twit.
And the time before that?
I got a thank-You note
And a swatch watch
from russell brand.
Russell brand?
Mm, not my proudest moment.
Okay. I get it.
So, you're just superstitious
about saying it,
But it has nothing to do with
the way that you feel about me?
No. Not at all.
In fact, the whole reason
i called is
To tell you that i honestly
i...
Oh, there you are.
Ooh! Cool bedroom.
Who's that?
Uh... Berta.
You couldn't even wait
till my plane takes off?
No, no, zoey, it's not what you think!
Oh, good-Bye, walden.
Zoey, just...
♪ Awkward!
Oh... I can't believe i kissed
the mouth that did this.
Alan, i need to
talk to you. Oh!
Can we do it out here?
Gladly.
Oh, good lord!
Looks like someone
cleaned a deer in the bathtub.
What's going on?
Zoey facetimed me
from the plane
To tell me that she loves me.
Good.
But she saw jennifer
in my bedroom.
Bad.
So, naturally, i immediately
tried to call her back.
Good.
But she wouldn't answer.
Bad.
So i'm gonna fuel up my jet,
And fly to london
and beg for forgiveness.
Good.
Will you stop that, alan?
I-I need you to come with me.
Me? Why?
Because i might need a witness,
and you can say
That you saw that
nothing happened with jennifer.
Great. I'm your man.
I am not gonna touch that glove.
Come on.
Oh, uh, wait.
I promised lyndsey
i'd take her out
To a big, fancy,
romantic dinner tonight.
Bring her.
Really?
Yeah, sure.
Well, i guess a private jet
To london does beat
An 11-Year-Old volvo
to the olive garden.
I'll-I'll pack a bag.
No, no, no, there's no time.
I'll buy you whatever you need
in london.
You're kidding.
Yeah. Come on.
Hey, if zoey won't say it,
i will.
I love you, walden schmidt.
(engines roaring)
(sighs contentedly)
(clears throat)
Thank you, walden.
This is just incredible.
Glad you like it.
Mm.
What did your son say
when you told him
You were flying
to london tonight?
He told me to bring him back
some english pot.
This is definitely
the way to travel.
No boarding passes,
no airport security,
None of those scanners
That show strangers
the size of your dingle.
Don't you worry about
your dingle, honey.
He's a grower, not a shower.
Yeah, he told me.
He tells everyone.
Jake: can i interest
you in a brewski?
What?
That's polish for
"do you want a beer?"
I've traveled
extensively through asia.
Oh. Thanks.
Are you sure walden said
he'd be right back?
Forget walden.
Let's talk about us.
Us?
That's english
for you and me.
Lyndsey:
♪ Poppin' bottles in the ice
♪ Like a blizzard
♪ When we drunk, we do it right,
gettin' slizzard ♪
♪ Like a g-6, like a g-6...
Uh, honey, honey,
why don't you take your seat
And put your seatbelt on?
Pish, pish, party pooper.
Wally, this is so romantic
what you're doing.
You are flying
across a whole ocean
Just to win back
the woman you love.
Thank you.
Alan, sweetie,
i need to tell you something.
Yeah?
I know i give you a hard time,
But in my heart,
I really, really
love... (gags)
(lyndsey vomits loudly)
Alan:
oh, god!
Oh. Aah.
I'm so sorry.
Alan:
oh! Oh!
Lyndsey:
oh. Oh.
So sorry.
Here. Here.
Oh, thank you.
(lyndsey vomiting,
alan gagging)
Oh, god!
Oh!
Oh, my god!
Oh, hang on.
Oh, god!
I'll-I'll get...
I'll get some towels.
(yelling)
Pilot (over pa): okay, folks,
We've got clear skies ahead,
And we'll be in london
in approximately four hours.
So, just sit back and enjoy
the rest of your flight.
(vomit splashing,
walden crying)
♪ Men.
Bottom line, zoey,
i can assure you
That nothing happened
between walden and that woman.
Really?
What possible reason
would i have to lie to you?
Well, for one thing, he gave
You and lyndsey a
free trip to london,
Where you all
inexplicably decided
To dress up
like japanese tourists.
That's my fault.
I kind of threw up
on them a little.
A little?
I might have to get a new plane.
Yes, yes, yes, that's
all very interesting,
But the fact remains
That you still invited
my neighbor jennifer...
The whore
from the seventh floor...
Back to your house.
Yeah, but nothing happened.
Nothing happened 'cause
i called and interrupted you!
Okay, i think we're saying
the same thing here.
Listen, the fact is, i love you.
Okay, and i was an idiot
to put pressure on you,
I made a terrible mistake,
and i'm very, very sorry.
Okay. Uh, we sh...
I think we should go.
(sighs)
I do love you, walden.
You do?
Of course i do.
That's why i called you
from the plane, you ninny.
So...
You forgive me?
Well, that depends.
Do i have to worry every time
we have a fight
That you're going to go out
and pick up another woman?
Not as long
as i know that you love me.
Good answer.
Come here.
I love you, lyndsey.
And i love you.
(gagging)
Alan:
oh, not in my mouth!
(lyndsey and alan gagging)
oh, god.
Oh, dear.
(walden and zoey retching)
No, seriously, dude. No lie.
All right, fine,
you don't believe me? Here.
Yup. Five times.
Best half hour of my life.