Oh, God.
That feels so good.
Where'd you learn to do that?
Chiropractic school?
Long before that.
When I was a kid,
I had to do this for my mom.
Had to?
If I wanted dessert.
Oh, poor baby.
Tell you what, when you're
done with my other foot,
I'll give you a
little dessert.
Thank you, Mommy.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh, hey.
How was the opera?
Magnificent.
Il Trovatore.
Walden cried.
- Oh.
Come on, a guy
in a leotard and a skirt
realizes he chopped
his own brother's head off.
That's heartbreaking.
I keep trying to take Lyndsey
to the opera, but she won't go.
I'm sorry,
I'm just not a fan of fat people
singing in a foreign language
for two and
a half hours.
Well, opera's not for everyone.
To appreciate it requires
a refined taste
and a certain amount
of education.
Whoa.
You did not
just say that.
Say what?
I am plenty refined,
and I happen to have
an Associate of Arts degree
from Santa Monica
Community College.
I'm sorry, I wasn't
trying to be pejorative.
What's that supposed to mean?
Uh, pejorative is having
a derogatory...
I know what
the word means!
Sorry, sorry.
What's community college?
Is that like
a sort of trade school?
Let's leave it alone.
We've already seen
one beheading tonight.
Where did you go to college?
Oxford?
Only for two years.
Aw, did you flunk out?
No, I transferred
to Harvard.
Harvard.
The Santa Monica
Community College of the East.
What do you say we go
get ready for bed?
Yeah, good idea.
♪ Mi chiamano Mimi
♪ Il perchè non so
sola, mi fo. ♪
I also took a semester off
to study opera in Florence.
That's in Italy.
Wow.
That is one talented lady.
And by "talented"
I mean annoying,
and by "lady" I mean bitch.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x16 ♪
Sips, Sonnets and Sodomy
Original Air Date on February 13, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪ Men.
"Fat people singing
in a foreign language."
Can you believe her?
No. It's unbelievable.
Maybe she'd be
more appreciative of
fat people singing
in her native language.
No to Pavarotti,
yes to Cee Lo Green.
Mm. Forget you?
Forget her.
And then she has the nerve to
insult me simply 'cause I have
a modicum of sophistication
and good taste.
Mm, you do
taste good.
I know what she thinks.
She thinks I'm snobbish
and condescending.
Mm, but you're not.
No, I'm not.
It's a shame, really.
So much I could teach
the poor girl.
It's her loss.
God knows what Alan
sees in her.
Yeah, he could
totally do better.
No, he couldn't;
he's a complete loser.
What are you talking about?
Um, you said...
Never mind.
"Refined taste."
I'd like to punch
her refined face in.
And you could;
you hit hard.
You know
what her problem is?
She was born with
all the advantages
and now she thinks
she's better than everyone else.
Like her poop doesn't stink.
Your poop
stinks, honey.
Thank you.
Especially after
Indian food.
That is a real working-class
stank right there.
Boy, I am so turned
on right now.
What could Walden
possibly see in that,
in that stuck-up
English muffin?
Maybe it's her
nooks and crannies.
What?
Uh, you know,
English muffin.
Uh, nooks
and crannies.
For the butter.
Or margarine, as
the case may be.
Are you saying
you like her body?
Oh, no, no.
No, it's your
body that I love.
You've got the
stinky poop.
Be honest with me.
Have I not been entirely civil
and charming to her?
You have.
Then why does she give me
that attitude?
Who know...?
She's crazy.
Well, I wouldn't call her crazy;
she's certainly unpleasant.
That's what I meant.
Unpleasant.
Are you humoring me
just so I'll have sex with you?
No. I took you to the opera
so you would have sex with me.
You're terrible.
I'm trying to be,
but there's a lot
of damn bows here.
♪ Men.
Alan?
Yeah?
I'm sorry
I ruined our night.
That's okay.
No, it's not.
Let me make it up to you.
Really?
I get dessert?
Oh, Walden!
Oh, my God!
I don't believe it.
Do you know what she's doing?
Well, I think I have
a general idea.
She wants me to hear that.
Oh, my God!
She's rubbing my nose in it.
Sounds more like she's
rubbing his nose in it.
Oh, my God!
Two can play at that game.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my God!
Oh!
What are you doing?
Making love to you.
Oh, my God!
Oh!
You want me to help?
No, I got this.
Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Oh...!
Oh, my God!
Oh, Alan!
Oh, Walden!
Oh!
♪ Men.
Happy Valentine's
Day, darling.
You, too, sweetheart.
Sounded like you and Zoey
were getting an early start
on your celebrating last night.
Oh, yeah.
You and Lyndsey were making
quite a bit
of a racket yourselves.
Oh, you heard that?
It was kind of
hard not to.
Well, you know how it is.
Uh, you and I
are like the mailmen.
Rain or shine, we got to deliver
the old package.
Handle with care.
Express delivery.
No, wait, let me think
of another one.
This side up.
Oh.
That's good, that's good.
Oh, who am I kidding?
Last night was a complete sham.
What do you mean?
Zoey was trying to prove
some kind of point to Lyndsey.
So, all that noise was, uh...?
I had nothing to do with it.
Sorry.
Well, since we're being honest,
I should probably tell you...
I... had what was probably the
best sex of my life last night.
Good morning.
Huh?
Oh, morning.
Sleep well?
Terrific.
Good. I was afraid
we might have kept you awake.
Really?
I was worried we might have
kept you awake.
No, no, I slept like a baby.
Hope you didn't wet the bed.
They're laughing.
That's good, right?
Not that laugh.
That's the bad laugh.
Shame it has to be raining
on Valentine's Day.
Yeah, well, fortunately, the sun
is shining in Cabo San Lucas.
Thanks for the weather report.
Now here's Alan
with the sports.
I just meant
that's where Walden and I
are flying for dinner tonight.
Really?
Good luck with LAX.
Place is gonna be a madhouse.
That may well be.
Luckily, Walden's got
his private jet, so...
Of course he does.
Or they could fly down
on her private broom.
What are you and Alan
doing to celebrate?
Oh, don't worry
about us.
We have big plans.
Ooh.
Another festive foot rub?
Bad laugh?
As a matter of fact,
we're gonna spend the night
at a little bed-and-breakfast
outside Santa Barbara
where we're gonna
drink wine, read poetry
and have hot,
kinky sex.
Right, Alan?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Uh, sure.
The, uh, the holy trinity of
Valentine's Day:
sips, sonnets and sodomy.
That's interesting.
I can see you
as a drunken sodomite,
never imagined
you liking poetry.
Oh, no, no, I really do.
Here's a poem
you might appreciate.
"Roses are red,
"violets are blue,
"I'm a nice person
and you can bite my pale,
unrefined ass."
A lady doesn't bite.
Hmm.
She will however be happy
to make you wear that ass
as a bonnet.
What the hell?
Oh, my Lord.
Where's the road?
Probably inside
that giant sinkhole.
It looks like nobody's
going anywhere today.
Oh, smashing.
Swell.
Sodomy?
Sodom-ish.
♪ Men.
They say the road might be
closed for another 48 hours.
And that's if
the rain lets up.
Better call my ex-husband,
let him know
I probably won't be
picking up Ava tomorrow.
Better call my son, tell
him I'll be home early.
Early?
I can't tell
him the truth.
If he knows I could
be gone for two days,
I might not have a
house when I get back.
Nice to have a relationship
with your child built on trust.
Excuse me?
I'm just saying,
I never lie to my daughter.
Really?
And how old is she?
She's six.
Aw.
They're so precious
at that age, aren't they?
They are.
Call me in a few years
when she's pierced and pregnant
with a pocket
full of 30-day chips.
There's no need to be crude.
Oh, so now I'm crude?
Not just now.
That's it.
Get ready for an
old-fashioned
trade school beat-down.
Oh! No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no!
Slow down. Slow it down.
No! No!
Little Miss Muffet's going to
get knocked on her tuffet!
Oh, bring it on, Snooki!
Okay. Okay. No.
Baby, baby, no.
We're in a tough
situation here.
But this is a big house,
and we're all adults.
Yeah, some of us
older than others.
Oh!
Walden's right.
We got to make
the best of this.
You know, we can, uh...
uh, we can play video games,
listen to music,
watch movies.
We're all going to die.
♪ Men.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to stay
in the same house
as that horrible wom.
Okay, first of all,
the road's closed,
so nobody's going anywhere.
And second of all, uh,
she's not that horrible.
What did you say?
I said, "The road's closed."
After that.
"Nobody's going anywhere."
Are you defending her?
Oh, come on.
It's a funny situation
when you think about it.
Two women who shouldn't be
anywhere near each other
trapped in a house
'cause of a silly rain storm.
That's a bad laugh.
♪ Men.
Oh, great.
I just got my period.
Oh, joy.
My bloody Valentine.
I'm out of tampons.
You have to go get me some.
What?
Have you looked outside?
Yeah. It's raining.
This is not rain.
This is some sort
of biblical punishment.
There's only one flood
you need to be concerned about.
Why don't you just ask Zoey
for one?
Why don't I take
that light off your head
and give you
a quick colonoscopy?
At least now we know
why you're in such a bad mood.
What did you just say?
I said I'm going
to the drugstore
to buy you tampons.
You're so pretty.
Hey.
Hi.
Where you going?
I am going to swim
down to the drugstore
and bob for tampons.
Really?
In-in this weather?
What, are you out of your mind
Walden!
I'll come with you.
♪ Men.
Looks like it's
starting to let up.
Yeah, this is
blowing over.
It's actually
kind of refreshing.
And we certainly
need the water.
It's weird
how people in L.A.
make such a big fuss
over a little rain.
That's the new
Smart car.
Doesn't look
so smart now.
♪ Men.
Ah.
Hi.
Do you happen to know
where Walden is?
I happen to not.
All right.
Well, where's Alan?
He went for a walk.
A walk?
Yeah, a walk.
That's how poor people
get from one place to another.
All right.
Mind if I share your wine?
I don't know if you'll like it.
It's domestic.
Alan bought it.
Actually, I quite like
California wine.
It's from Wisconsin.
Ah.
Well, desperate times.
Shame our girlfriends
don't get along, huh?
Yeah, if they don't start
playing nice with each other,
you're going to have to find
a new place to live.
No doubt.
Or I could find
another girlfriend.
♪ Men.
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
For the record, I like
Walden very much.
He seems like a great guy.
Well, thank you.
Alan's...
Thank you.
So... what's your plan
for the young,
gorgeous billionaire?
I'm sorry. Plan?
Oh, come on.
Educated girl like you?
You got to have a plan
to nail him down.
I don't.
My feelings for Walden
are genuine.
I have no desire
to manipulate him
into some sort
of commitment.
Huh.
But if I did, what sort of plan
do you think might work?
Well, first thing I'd do
is throw out my diaphragm.
I'm on the pill.
All right.
Swap out those puppies
for Tic Tacs.
You know, it's
actually good
that Lyndsey sent me
to the drugstore.
'Cause now I can pick up
her Valentine's Day gift.
Nice!
Yeah, nothing says "I love you"
like Q-tips and stool softener.
I-I was thinking
of something more...
Alan!
Tell Jake I love him!
And buy Lyndsey tampons!
♪ Men.
So, anyway, then we got married
and had my son, Eldridge.
How long after?
Actually, my water broke
during the ceremony.
Really put a crimp
in the reception.
Tell me about your ex.
Nigel.
Oh, God, how can
I describe Nigel?
Highly educated,
extremely cultured,
and as you Americans
might say...
"a total freakin' douche bag."
Really?
My ex-husband is,
as you Brits might say...
"a right bloody wanker."
Looks like we both
traded up, huh?
Yes, absolutely.
Cheers to us.
Mmm.
This is turning out to be
a pretty nice Valentine's Day.
It is, isn't it?
Thanks for the tampon,
by the way.
Oh, pleasure.
Appears our cycles
have synched up.
Yeah.
Probably why we haven't
seen the boys for a while.
We have been a bit out of sorts.
Mmm. Edgy.
Moody.
Bitchy.
Oh, I do hope our
fellows are all right.
I'm sure they're fine.
Yeah.
Let me go!
Save yourself!
No!
If you go, I go!
Hey, Lyndsey.
Yeah, we haven't gotten
to the drugstore yet.
We're in a little bit
of a situation here.
All right.
What kind of ice cream?
Seriously, let me go.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==