Previously on:
I know that I said that I wanted
to get rid of her
and have you come back...
Oh, no!
I'm just going to have
to make it work.
No, no, no, no, no!
I'm sorry!
Okay, I'll figure something out.
If nothing else,
I am a survivor.
Doctor said you had
a little heart attack.
Yeah, I remember now.
Zoey's moving in...
and I'm moving out...
No...
No... you're not moving out.
I'm not?
No, you can stay
as long as you want,
as long as you need.
Oh, that's... that's so good to hear.
Really, you don't have
to carry my bags.
Alan, you had
a heart attack, okay?
You need to take it easy.
Well, I appreciate it,
but I'm fine.
Whoa, do not say that.
Why not?
Let me tell you
about my Grandma Abigail.
When I was a kid,
she came to move in with us.
And one day I said,
"How ya doing, Grandma"
And she said, "Fine."
And then she dropped dead.
You're kidding.
No, face down in my Legos.
Well, that's terrible.
But I'm fine.
Do not say that!
My Uncle Hal?
When I was a kid, he used
to spend Thanksgivings us,
and one year,
we're at dinner and...
you know, like football
and turkey and the whole bit,
and I said,
"How ya doing, Uncle Hal"
And he said, "Fine"
And then he went
to the bathroom,
and he crapped out
his small intestines.
Oh, oh... okay,
t-that's horrible,
but I promise you,
I am fine.
Surprise!
I told you not to say it!
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x23 ♪
The Straw in My Donut Hole
Original Air Date on May 7, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Oh, my God,
somebody call 911.
Gotcha.
Oh...
Alan, don't you ever
do that to me again.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
So all you guys came
just to welcome me back?
Of course we did, darling.
We were worried about you.
Yeah, I've been beside myself
with concern.
I don't know what to say.
I'm really touched.
Come here, Alan.
Sit down.
I made you some tea.
Wait, did you just
call me Alan?
Well, that's your name,
isn't it?
Yeah, but you always
call me Zippy.
I know, but I've got
a little rule.
I never make fun of someone who
could come back and haunt me.
Sugar or honey?
I thought we decided on Alan?
Uh, honey, please.
Hey, are you warm enough?
Do you want me
to turn up the heat?
I'm fine.
Don't say that...
Okay, turn up the heat.
Why don't you just lay down.
Uh, no, really, I'm good.
I've been in bed for a week.
Do it for me.
Uh, okay, but let me
just point out
that that never works
when I say that to you.
Guess what. While you were
in the hospital,
I aced all my final exams.
Really?
I don't believe it!
I told you
he wouldn't buy it.
Wait, wait, wait.
You lied to me?
Uh, I told him to. I thought
the truth might kill you.
But there is some real good news.
What's that?
I found out for sure
I'm not gay.
But why's that good news?
It's mostly good news
for gay people.
A-A-All right, look,
I appreciate
all the trouble you're taking
to welcome me home,
but if you don't mind, I'd just
like to go back to my room.
Oh, you heard him.
He wants to go to his room.
Here, Zoey.
Take the tea.
Walden, I can walk on my own.
That's what my
blind Aunt Shirley said.
And then we went to Miami
on Christmas vacation,
and then "blam"
Greyhound came out of nowhere
and flattened her.
She got hit by a bus?
No, she wandered
onto the dog track
in the middle
of the ninth race.
Technically,
she came in third.
Anyway, I got a little
♪ surprise for you. ♪
Oh, Walden, you've already
done so much.
I don't know what else
you could possibly...
A real bed!
Yeah.
It's not just a bed.
Get on it. Check it out.
Oh, my golly.
Ah...
Oo-ho-ho-ho!
The bed is becoming tumescent.
Yeah...!
Pretty cool, uh?
See, so you don't have
to exert yourself
when you're getting
in and out.
Ah! Oh,
and what pray tell is that?
That is a 46" high-definition
plasma screen TV,
complete with a deluxe sports
satellite package
Nice! No movies?
No, we could switch it
to a movie package.
Or you could add it.
Oh, okay, we'll add it.
And don't forget
the adult channels.
No problem.
You have to ask
for them specifically.
Otherwise they block them.
Right.
Hey, why don't you take
a nap until dinner?
I'm not tired.
That's what my
cousin Earl said
right before he fell asleep
with a cigarette in his hand.
Set his bed on fire?
No, his fireworks stand.
I was standing across the street
yelling at him to wake up
when the first rocket went off,
followed by 800 Roman candles.
It was horrifying and really
cool at the same time.
Okay, I'll take a nap.
Good, good, good,
you just...
I don't want you
to do anything.
Just relax
and get better.
That's a nice thought, Walden,
but I got a lot of work to do.
I got bills to pay.
No, don't worry about the bills.
I'll take care of everything.
Walden, I can't let you
just take care of everything.
Listen, I made a promise to
myself when I was 11 years old
and salmonella decimated
my father's entire side
of the family
at the annual Easter egg hunt.
Nobody else dies on my watch.
Poor guy,
living with all that guilt.
I can exploit that.
How come you're not coming over?
I can't. I have Ava.
Why don't you come over here?
I can't. I have Alan.
Oh, for God's sake.
Well, he had
a heart attack, Zoey.
Oh, bollocks.
He's going to outlive us all.
A week after nuclear Armageddon,
the world will be populated
by nothing but cockroaches
and Alan Harper.
Wow, that is a side of you
that is not attractive.
It's the lawyer side of me.
Yeah, yuck.
Look, I see these kind
of scam artists all the time
and I don't want
you being taken advantage of.
I am just taking care
of my friend.
No, you are providing food,
shelter, and satellite TV
to a cockroach.
Hello, anybody?
Getting kind of hungry
in here.
Uh, B-Berta, Alan's hungry.
Is his dinner ready yet?
Coming up.
Really?
He gets room service?
Did I ever tell you
about my Aunt Phyllis?
When I was a kid she took me
on a trip to New York,
and we were staying
at the Waldorf-Astoria,
and she didn't want
to wait for room service,
so she headed down
to the restaurant
and she fell 24 stories
down an empty elevator shaft.
We never got to see Cats.
So you're afraid Alan is going
to fall into an elevator shaft?
Don't poke at it, Zoey.
The wound is still fresh.
Come in.
Did my little buddy save
room for dessert?
I sure did, Skipper.
Good, 'cause I made
your favorite.
Peach cobbler?
Yep.
Warm with ice cream?
I'll be right back.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay, let's see
what's on those adult channels.
Avatart.
Oh, in 3D.
Oh, to be continued.
Come in.
Hey, you.
Judith, what a,
what a nice surprise.
How are you feeling?
Not bad, all things considered.
Oh, you're so brave.
Now, listen, there's something
we need to talk about.
Look, I know the child support
checks are late,
but, but please allow me
to get back to my job.
Er?
Forget the
child support.
Er?
You just get better.
I can manage fine
without your money.
All right.
I always suspected as much,
but thank you.
And Herb and I have the
condo in Palm Springs,
so you're certainly
welcome to use it
while you're
recuperating.
How can you afford
a condo in Palm Springs?
We made a judgment call
with Jake's college fund.
Anyway, you're
welcome to use it.
Wow, thank you,
th-that's very generous.
Well, look, I know we've
obviously had our differences.
We have.
And I haven't always
been very nice to you.
I just figured
you didn't like me.
Alan, we were married
for 12 years.
You're the father
of my son.
Just because I couldn't
stay married to you
doesn't mean I
stopped loving you.
Gee, it sure felt
that way.
Oh, I'm sorry
for that.
You just get
well, okay?
Okay.
A house in Malibu,
no child support,
free condo in Palm Springs.
Why would anyone want
to eliminate heart disease?
Don't worry,
you lovely blue ladies,
as soon
as my right hand is free,
I'll be giving you
my full attention.
Rats.
Uh...
Come in.
How's my man?
Oh, you know, okay
for a guy who recently stared
into the jaws of death.
That's why I'm here.
I want to help
with your recovery.
Really, what'd
you have in mind?
I-I'm not supposed
to exert myself.
Don't worry, you don't have
to do a thing.
Just lie back
and I'll do all the work.
Really?
Hmm.
Okay.
Uh, let me put
my cobbler down.
No, no, no,
keep it.
You sure?
Absolutely.
It'd be rude for
me to eat alone.
All righty then.
You got any porn
on this thing?
Uh, gee, I,
I don't know.
Why don't you check?
Shake things up a bit.
Oh, gosh,
well, I, yeah,
I guess I, I guess I,
I-I could do that.
Oh, look,
there's some now.
How fortuitous.
Now, just relax and
enjoy your cobbler.
Right back at you.
This is the best day
of my entire life.
♪ Men. ♪
All right, Mr. Harper.
Well, I've got
some good news.
Let me have it.
I'm banging my receptionist.
I'm sorry.
I... I never get tired
of that one.
That-that's funny,
but, uh, what about me?
No, you don't have
a chance with her.
She likes rich guys.
All right,
back to your, uh, heart.
It's looking good.
Uh, are you sure?
Tests show you've had no damage.
Your cholesterol looks normal.
It's like the heart attack
never even happened.
Oh.
And you're not happy about that?
No, I-I am.
Um, uh, is this confidential,
what we're saying?
Think of me as a priest.
Except, when I touch your nuts,
it's strictly business.
Okay, uh... uh, uh, here it is.
Um, ever since the heart attack,
uh, my life
has actually gotten better.
Uh, my girlfriend,
my ex-wife,
even my mother
have all been showering me
with love and attention.
Well, they were afraid
they were losing you.
Have you ever had oral sex
and peach cobbler?
At the same time?
Can't say that I have.
Well, I have.
And once my girlfriend
finds out that I'm healthy,
I'm back to sucking Life Savers
and humping my pillow.
Well, as your doctor,
all I can tell you
is you're
perfectly healthy.
Can I get a second opinion?
Yes, you're ugly, too.
I joke.
Uh, again, as your doctor,
I have to tell you
you're in great shape.
But, uh...
as a guy who's banging
his receptionist,
two pharmaceutical reps
and, uh, on occasion,
his bloated, rich wife,
let me add:
Don't be a schmuck.
Lie your ass off.
Thanks, Doc.
That's good advice.
Hmm.
Jeanine, hi.
Uh, listen, could you
run down to the deli
and pick up a peach cobbler
and meet me in exam room 2.
How'd it go?
Good news?
It's bad, Mom.
It's real bad.
Oh.
Darling, I am so sorry.
Hey, I know what
would cheer you up.
So do I.
No, I was thinking
I could take you shopping.
Come on, now.
There must be something
I can get you
that would turn
that frown upside down.
Well, uh, remember
when I was a kid
how I always wanted
to be a cowboy?
I'm not going to buy you
a horse, Alan.
Of course not.
Guess I'll just have to be
a cowboy in Heaven.
Are your eyes closed?
Yep, they're closed.
Open.
You must be kidding me.
It's the safest way for Alan
to get up and down the stairs.
Why does he have to get
up and down the stairs?
So he can use my whirlpool tub.
Oh, dear Lord.
He needs it for his circulation.
He said he's starting
to get bed sores.
Then you tell him
to get out of bed.
You don't build him
his own private escalator.
Howdy, pardner.
Ma'am.
Wow.
You look great.
Just checking it
off my bucket list.
What'd the doctor say?
It's not good.
I might have to have
a transplant.
I'm sorry.
Let's just hope that somewhere
there's a baboon
with a healthy heart
riding a motorcycle
without a helmet.
For God's sake.
Excuse me.
I'm going to take a whirlpool
until my masseuse gets here.
You got him a masseuse?
It helps prevent blood clots.
Yeah.
My Uncle Fred
had a blood clot in his leg,
and when I was little,
he took me
to the Santa Monica Pier,
and we went on the Tilt-A-Whirl,
and the centrifugal force
shot the clot into his brain.
It was the worst birthday ever.
He's seen a lot
of tragedy, Zoey.
Be nice to him.
Mmm.
Too hard?
Nah, dig in.
I like it rough.
Brought your
banana smoothie.
Oh, thank you, Zoey.
Um, would you mind
sticking the straw
in my donut hole?
Oh, I would love to.
Mmm.
Tasty.
I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
You may have everyone
else around here fooled,
but I know you're
full of crap.
Beg pardon?
What you do with
your family
and your girlfriend
is your business,
but I want you to stop
taking advantage of Walden.
I-I don't know
what you're talking about.
You know exactly what
I'm talking about.
I-I'm sorry. I really
don't know what you're...
You've been warned.
Well, thanks for the...
the smoothie, Zoey.
That bitch has got to go.
How about that?
Stars really are just like us.
Alan.
Oh!
Oh, my.
Careful.
You don't want
to give me a heart attack.
We need to talk to you.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll be right back.
Um, think I left
the tub running, so...
Stop.
Now, get out of that chair
and get down here.
Okay.
The queen has spoken.
My legs are still
a little al dente.
So...
what up?
I'll tell you "what up."
I asked one of the private
investigators for my law firm
to follow you for a few days.
Really?
Uh, uh, wh-which days
in particular?
Well,
this is from last Monday,
when you said you were going
for a therapeutic walk
on the beach.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, yeah, you know...
I can see
how this looks,
um,
but, you know, actually,
there is a-a-a very...
a very simple, uh,
uh, explanation.
Okay.
Well...
we got cobbler
in the kitchen.
911?
Anybody?
♪ Men. ♪
How long do you plan
on lying there?
Until the shame passes.
So a while?
Oh, yeah.
All right.
Well...
sleep well.
Thanks. You, too.
♪ Memories ♪
♪ Light the corners of my mind ♪
♪ Misty watercolored memories
of the way we were... ♪
== sync, corrected by elderman ==