Previously on:
It's spring break this week,
so Zoey and her daughter
are going to stay here.
I'm going to need you
to move out for the week.
Where you staying?
I'm just going to have
to stay with Lindsey.
There's someone
in the house. Go look.
Ow!
What?
Ball snag!
I'm sorry!
No, no, don't touch it!
I'm bored.
♪ ♪
I can't do this, Berta.
It's just too much.
She just never stops.
So, how are things going living
with Zoey and her daughter?
It's good. It's good.
Oh.
How's living with Lyndsey?
Oh, it's terrific.
That's great.
So, if I could get rid of them...
Yes, 100 times yes.
Men...
Okay.
Zoey...
you know I love you, and...
I want to live with you forever.
But we got to lose the kid.
- Yeah, probably not.
- Okay.
Hey, have you ever thought
of Swiss boarding schools?
Hi!
Sh...
She's out like a light.
Really? How?
Did you drug her?
I didn't think
we were allowed to drug her.
She's worn out
from playing with you all day.
She's not the only one.
Listen...
I've been thinking about this
whole "moving in together"
thing.
It's all right.
I admit, I had my doubts.
But you have been
so wonderful with her.
Thank you.
This little girl
loves you so much.
Really...
You're all she talks about.
The sun rises and sets with you.
Huh...
Look at what she made for you.
Wow...
So, you win.
We're all yours.
I mean,
there's a million details
to figure out
before we can move in
permanently.
First and foremost, where she's
going to go to school.
Have you ever considered
Switzerland?
You're kidding, right?
I'm ki.. of course!
Why would I want her
so far away?
Let me put her up to bed.
Then we can start making plans.
Great.
Mommy?
Hmm?
Where's Walden?
Oh, I'm right here.
I love you, Walden.
I love you...
Just like I planned it.
Hey, roomie!
You got here quick.
Yeah, Lyndsey asked me
to fix the garbage disposal
and I didn't like the odds.
So, uh, did you talk
to Zoey yet?
Yes, I did.
How'd she take it?
Well, I... yeah, let's...
Did she cry?
No...
Yelling?
No. There was no yelling.
Yeah, I know that I said
that I wanted to get rid of her
and have you come back...
Oh, no!
You know, I, I love her.
And I, I love the kid.
No!
I'm just going
to have to make it work.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Alan, I'm sorry.
Okay, okay, I'll...
I'll figure something out.
If nothing else,
I am a survivor.
Okay, very funny.
Survivor, I get it.
Oh, come on!
I feel bad enough already.
Help me...
911!
Oh, okay. I'll play along.
Here, would 100 dollars
make you better?
You're not kidding?
Not kidding...
Don't die.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x22 ♪
Why We Gave Up Women
Original Air Date on April 30, 2012
== Encoded, Synced & Corrected by
$H@uN ==
I want him to have
the best possible care.
So, whatever it takes,
I'll pay for it.
You're going to have to.
The man's got the worst
insurance policy I've ever seen.
What do you mean?
He's got a $500,000 deductible.
A $500,000 deductible?
Even at our prices,
he ain't gonna
hit that with
one heart attack.
All right, well, I'll just...
I'll take care of it.
Just check the box
"Domestic Partner."
Oh, no, we're just buddies.
We got no buddy forms.
Yeah, but...
Just check the damn box.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
I guess there's nothing
to do now but wait.
Forgive me
for being callous,
but don't you think this heart
attack is a bit convenient?
What?
Come on.
He tries to weasel his way
back into the house.
You tell him no
and he falls to the ground,
clutching his chest.
You think he faked
a heart attack?
I think he'd fake
a shark attack.
How do you fake
a shark attack?
I don't know. Ask Alan.
Harper?
Yeah, right here.
Okay, well, your boyfriend's
going to be fine.
That's great.
Uh, he's not my...
It's great.
It was the form.
It was just easier.
Um, did he actually
have a heart attack?
It was a mild one, but yes.
Told you.
He should be fine.
He's just going to need rest
and as little stress
as possible.
For how long?
I don't know,
at least a month or two.
Great...
That's why we gave up women.
Am I right?
It's a compelling argument.
Hi.
Hi, Walden.
How ya feelin'?
Fan-tastic.
I'm on a morphine drip.
Everyone should have
a morphine drip.
There would be no more war.
Listen, the doctor said
that you... had
a little heart attack,
but you're going to be fine.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I remember now.
Zoey's moving in and...
I'm... I'm moving out.
No, you're not moving out.
I'm-I'm not?
No, you can stay as long as you
want. As long as you need.
Oh.
Oh, that's...
that's so good to hear.
Thataboy.
I just... I just want you
to not worry about anything.
I won't.
Okay.
You just relax
and feel better, okay?
Okeydokey.
Hey, Walden. Guess what?
What?
I'm peeing right now.
No kidding.
But it's okay.
There's a tube
attached to my wiener.
I don't think there is.
Oh...
Men...
- My God. He's going to be okay?
- Yeah.
He just needs
to take it easy.
I don't know
what I would do
if anything
happened to him.
I've already lost my good son!
Do you happen to know
if they validate parking?
So, are those tubes
putting stuff in
or taking stuff out?
I think
a little bit of both.
Oh, I get it.
It's like eating
on the toilet.
So, what did the doctor say?
Uh, he just said
he needs to take it easy.
You know, no stress.
Then I guess
we shouldn't tell him
about what happened
at school.
No, we definitely
should not.
Honest to God, someone
put that pot in my locker.
Why would they do that?
That, my friend,
is the million-dollar question.
Look, Lyndsey,
I know you're his girlfriend,
and I know you'd like
to take care of him, but...
I kind of feel
responsible for this.
And I'd like him to stay
with me until he recovers.
Fine. Let's go
get some coffee.
Men...
Wake up, Alan.
Is it spongebath time again?
You wish.
What's going on?
Who are you?
Ah, Alan, that hurts.
Don't you recognize
your own brother?
Men...
What is this,
some kind of sick joke?
Charlie's dead.
You're dubious. Understandable.
When you were 14 years old,
you went to your first
boy/girl party,
and you were really nervous
because they were going to play
spin the bottle.
Yeah?
So, before you left the house,
I convinced you that
the grownup way to French-kiss
was to spit in the
other person's mouth.
You hocked a big loogie
down Marcy Bilson's throat
and she'd kicked you
in the nuts.
Ah, come on, everybody in
high school knew that story.
Answer me this:
What are your five favorite
words to hear from a woman?
"I can't spend the night."
Charlie...
At your service.
I don't...
I don't understand.
Are you reincarnated
or something?
Nah, I'm in hell.
Walking around
in this old broad's body
is supposed to be some kind
of eternal damnation.
You know what?
The joke's on them.
Boobs are still boobs.
So, why are you here?
I thought you could use
a little help.
I have been through
a rough patch.
You look like you've been
through a propeller.
I came here to tell you
it's not too late
to turn your life around.
How?
Stop being a parasite.
Step up. Be a man.
Grow a pair.
Uh, parenthetically,
this body actually has a pair.
They dangle
right under my hooha.
Did not need to know that.
Point being, you lived on me
for eight years
and now you're
living off this new guy.
Now, now, hang on.
W-Walden's my friend.
He invited me
to stay with him.
Oh, kiss my
surprisingly tight ass.
You're nobody's friend.
You're a useless appendage,
like tonsils,
or the nutsack
under my hooha.
I see hell hasn't
mellowed you out any.
Listen to me,
you got to get out
of that guy's house
and make a life for yourself.
I suppose I could go
live with Lyndsey.
You're missing my point.
I'm not suggesting
that the tapeworm
find a new colon
to crawl into.
Hold out your hand.
Thank you.
This is your last chance, Alan.
Move out of that house.
Get your own place.
Start pulling your own weight
in the world.
Okay. I will.
You'll see.
I can change.
Good.
Then my work here is done.
Well, thanks, Charlie.
You got it.
Oh, uh,
Before I go...
you gotta check this out.
Oh!
Was I lying?
Tell me that's not disturbing.
Men...
What do you want me
to do, Zoey?
The last time I asked him
to leave, he almost died.
Well, what does that mean?
He lives with you
until he actually does die?
No, just until he
gets back on his feet.
The man has no feet.
He is a footless man.
Okay, come on.
What about his mother?
Why doesn't he live with her?
They don't really get along.
What about his girlfriend?
Oh, God.
So we're stuck with him forever.
The man is the herpes
of houseguests.
Come on.
That is not fair.
You're right.
Herpes sometimes disappears
for a while.
Surprise!
Alan.
Herpes.
What? They let you out?
Oh, no, no.
I checked myself out.
I didn't want you to have
to pay one more penny for me.
Oh, come on.
The money is not important.
What's important
is your health.
No, what's important
is that I stop being a parasite
and stand on my own two feet.
You have no feet.
What was that?
It's Zoey.
I'll be right there, honey.
I'm just going to grab my stuff,
and I'll get out of your hair.
Are you sure?
I am positive, Walden.
I-I have had an epiphany.
I need to make a big change
in my life.
Wow.
Where will you go?
Oh, I found a cute little place
online.
Uh, you know, it's not much,
but, uh, at least
I'll have my pride.
I don't know, Alan.
Let the man have his pride!
Uh, here's my address
for mailing stuff.
If this is what you want...
It's what I want.
It's what everybody wants!
Don't listen to her.
Oh, no, no.
She's right.
She's an angry,
cold-hearted tea bag!
But she's right.
What did he say?
He said that you were right.
Men...
No, Jake.
If I'm not living
at the beach house,
you're not living
at the beach house.
Yeah, well, sometimes
life just isn't fair.
Well, sure you can visit me
where I'm living now.
But, uh, you're not going
to have your own room
or your own bed
or your own bathroom
and... you might need
to have a tetanus shot.
But I'd love to have you.
Okay, you let me know.
Okay, good night.
All right.
It's not much, but...
it's mine.
I am self-sufficient.
And beholden to no one.
Oh, that's not a good sign.
Men...
It's odd...
But now that
Alan's finally gone,
I actually kind of miss him.
Yeah, me too.
Walden, I'm kidding.
Oh, yeah, me too.
So...
Now that we have the house
to ourselves,
what would you like to do?
What I would like to do
is you.
And where I would like to do it,
is on every flat surface
in every room of this house.
Mm.
Woo. Hey.
Oh. Jake.
This is my friend, Gabby.
Hi!
We're going to go hang out
in my room.
Uh, Jake, uh,
hold on.
Have you spoken
to your father lately?
No, I don't believe I have.
Look at the bright side.
What bright side?
He might share some
of his pot with us.
Men...
Wake up, buttercup.
Oh. Hey, Charlie.
So, what do you think?
I finally got my own place.
Fantastic.
You're not sponging off
that rat, are you?
There's a rat?
Nah, I'm just kiddin'.
He's dead.
But aren't you proud of me?
I mean, I did what you said.
I'm standing
on my own two feet.
Yeah.
Sucker.
What?
I had to come back
from hell to do it,
but I finally gotcha
out of my freakin' house!
But I-I-I thought you wanted me
to be a better person.
Nope.
What? So you were just
screwing with me?
Yep.
Why?
I'm in hell, Alan.
That's kind of what we do.
Whoa!
What a horrible dream.
What's so horrible about it?
Boo-boo-boo-boo-boo-boo.
Still here.
I can do this aaalll night.
Men...
Okay.
How do we sell this?
Uh...
911...
911!
Come on. You can
do better than that. Uh...
Ah...
Help me.
Call 911.
Am I dying
or taking a dump?
Ah.
Call 911...
Yeah, that's it. Okay.
Showtime.
Alan...
Don't, don't worry.
I'm not moving back in.
I just forgot a few things.
Yeah, like your son?
Wait. Jake's here?
Yeah, and his girlfriend.
Ah, you know,
damn that kid.
I told him I was moving out and
he was not to come back here.
But does he listen to me? No.
You know, no one ever
listens to me and I...
Call 911.
Oh, no, not again.
Hold on.
I'll get help.
Son of a bitch.
What's the matter?
Couldn't find a shark?
Men...
So, what do you think, Doc?
We won't know until
we get all the tests back,
but right now, his heart
appears to be perfectly fine.
Thank God.
So how long before
I can take him home?
Walden?
I am sorry, Zoey,
but I am not going to have
this man's death
on my conscience.
I'd like to thank the Academy.
There are no small parts...
only small apartments.
I don't think you're allowed
to smoke in here.
Does that include the joint
you just blew in the bathroom?
How'd you know about that?
Call it women's intuition,
taterhead.
Whoa, the only person
that ever called me "taterhead"
was my uncle Charlie.
So, what does that
tell ya?
I have no idea.
Screw it.
I'm going back to hell.
Ready, ladies?
You bet.
We are.
Then let's go.
And me with with just a nutsack.
== Encoded, Synced & Corrected by
$H@uN ==