Ted! Ted! Ted! Ted! Ted! Ted!
Article Two, Section Two
of the Pawnee Charter reads,
"Be it decreed:
Should the taxation of tea
"rise to an unacceptable level,
citizens shall dump Ted
into Ramsett Lake."
Does anyone object?
As always, I object.
Nay, enough dithering!
Dump the miscreant!
Boo!
Today is Ted Party Day,
where we commemorate
the great Pawnee tea dump
of 1817.
Historical fun fact...
when the Founding Fathers wrote
the charter,
their old-timey script made
one of the "a's
look like a "d,"
so "tea" became "Ted."
It's just one
of those little things
that reminds us of Pawnee's
rich and vibrant past.
Plus, we get to go find
a guy named Ted
and throw him
in a lake.
One!
I don't even go by Ted!
- Two!
- I go by Theodore!
- Three!
- Aah!
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Hey, Ted.
Great job today.
You were so funny
when you were like,
"My cell phone,
I left it in my pocket."
Then you checked it, remember,
and it didn't work.
Yeah, that was hilarious.
Listen,
I am just here to say
that I am done
with Ted Party Day.
- Ha! Classic Ted.
- I'm serious.
I'm not getting dumped
in that lake anymore.
And I talked
to the other Teds in town,
and they're not doing it
either.
Come on, Ted Party Day
is protected
by Article Two
in the town charter.
And we have the right,
nay, the obligation,
to dump Ted into the lake
every year.
That's the way
it's always been done.
Okay, first of all,
"That's the way
it's always been done"
is not a good reason
to keep doing something.
Second, it was a misprint.
They clearly meant "tea."
I just think you need
to be careful
about speculating
what the Founders meant
when they were writing
the town charter.
Okay, fine.
You want to enforce
every single old law
we have on our books?
Hey, can I see your keys
for a second?
Here's a quarter.
I own your car now.
- Wha...
- Sorry.
The Pawnee Charter clearly
states that any white citizen
has the right to seize
any Indian property
for 25 cents.
That is an outdated
and racist law.
And obviously they meant
"American Indian."
Whoa, I think
we should be careful
when we speculate
what the Founders intended
when they wrote the charter.
Okay, Ted.
I know what you're doing.
You're quoting me back to me.
But I'm gonna quote me
back to you and say
that Ted Party Day
will never change.
Uhoh.
You, a woman,
just raised your voice
to a landowning male.
According to a Pawnee statute
passed in 1868,
I get to do this.
I was not aware
of that statute.
Ron, you have to help me.
Chris is making me do
some stupid management
training leadership course.
Now that you run
the Animal Control department,
you have qualified
for the Chris Traeger
Management Training Seminar
or "Ka-tumts."
It's not a great acronym,
but it is a great seminar.
Can you get me out of it?
Yes.
Normally, if given a choice
between doing something
and nothing,
I'd choose to do nothing.
But I will do something
if it helps someone else
do nothing.
I'd work all night
if it meant nothing got done.
Ron Swanson
and April Ludgate,
literally my two favorite people
in the catalogued universe.
April will not be
participating
in your pointless course
because she has
more important things to do
like not participating
in your pointless course.
I just want April
to become as great
a department head
as yourself.
Which is why
this is pointless.
I've been head of the Parks
department for 12 years,
and I never had any
"management training" course.
Ron, you've never been
"ka-tumtsed?"
I am legally required
to ka-tumts
every department head.
Otherwise, we are open
to all kinds of liability.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that tomorrow
during the seminar,
April is going to have
a classmate.
And spoiler alert...
- it's Alf.
- It's you.
This went poorly.
What, no.
Damn it!
What are you bidding on?
It better not be
Terrence Howard's tank top
from Hustle & Flow.
- It is not.
- Good.
'Cause I am bidding on it
and I am ready to spend
an amount
that my accountant calls
"Dangerous and irresponsible."
JJ's diner put an old
waffle iron up for auction.
It's the perfect breakfast
day gift for Leslie.
"Breakfast day"?
Leslie has anniversaries
for everything.
"Zoo day," first time we went
to the zoo together.
"Double date day,"
it was the first time
we went on a double date.
"Daniel Day-Lewis day.
"Talk-like-a-pirate day.
Talk-like-a-Pittsburgh-pirate
day,"
which why and how?
This calendar was last year's
calendar day present
celebrating the first time
she ever bought me
a calendar.
You have to buy a present
for every one of these?
She always tells me not to,
but then she buys me something
that's awesome and thoughtful,
and then I feel terrible.
But that's the thing.
This is the perfect present.
I just keep getting outbid
by someone named
"Tall Tie-ree-on Lannister."
What kind of name is
Tie-ree-on anyway?
You're kidding, right?
Tyrion Lannister?
Lord of Casterly Rock?
The Half-Man?
You don't watch
Game of Thrones?
- No. You do?
- Hell yeah.
Have you seen
those Dothraki dudes?
They can get it.
Everybody on that show
can get it.
I think I know
who I'm bidding against.
I now realize
that I was wrong,
and it's time
that we purged the books
of many of our town's
outdated and obscure laws.
The bill that I have written
with the full support
of the city council
will repeal 110 obsolete laws
such as all menstruating women
shall be confined
to their bathtubs
and Article Two,
aka, Ted Party Day.
The floor is now open
for public comments.
Oh, here we go.
Thank you.
My name is Garth Blundin,
and I object
to your ridiculous proposal.
The Pawnee Charter
shall not be changed.
Not today, not ever!
Wow, a lot of passion,
Mr. Blundin.
Thank you so much.
Your objection is noted
and officially in the record.
- Shall we proceed to a vote?
- No. No, we shall not.
Article Seven,
Section Three allows
for a "Citizen filibuster."
If I stand here
and refuse to yield my time,
you are prohibited
from voting on the bill.
That section defines
"Buffalo meat"
as acceptable currency.
- Is that the Buffalo meat one?
- Mm-hmm.
I meant Article Three,
Section Seven.
Let the filibustering begin.
I would now like to share
some ideas I have for
J.J. Abrams' seventh chapter
in the Star Wars' saga.
Pan down from
the twin suns of Tatooine.
We are now close on the mouth
of the Sarlacc Pit.
After a beat,
the gloved Mandalorian
armor gauntlet of Boba Fett
grabs onto the sand outside
of the Sarlacc Pit
and the feared bounty hunter
pulls himself
from the maw
of the sand beast.
Ugh, he's right.
He can do this.
This is exactly why we need
to modernize these laws.
This kind of thing made sense
when we had council in a barn
and there were
80 people in the town,
but now this is nuts.
If he holds
the reality gem,
that means he can jump
from different realities.
This will be our link
to the Marvel Universe
from the Star Wars Universe.
Imagine those who
were up against Chewbacca
'cause that's gonna happen.
After a beat, Luke says,
"Darth Vader was my father,
but Ben Kenobi was my master."
And he cuts Hannibal Lecter
in half.
Mr. Blundin,
look, the laws
I'm trying to get rid of
have no more relevance
in modern society
and they're embarrassing
to Pawnee.
Repealing them would show that
we're changing with the times.
You can't just change
the charter willy-nilly.
You start by casually repealing
a couple of "old laws,"
the next thing you know,
your jack-booted storm troopers
are kicking in my door
and arresting my wife
for no reason
if I were married.
By "jack-booted
storm troopers,"
do you mean
the Pawnee Police Department?
- Hey, Clyde.
- Hi, Leslie.
Good Danish today.
The Pawnee charter is not
a "living document," Ms. Knope.
You have no respect
for the traditions of this town.
I absolutely do.
I used to give tours
at the Pawnee Historical House.
Three times,
"Employee Of The Fortnight."
Oh, big deal, you put
on a costume for a couple hours.
By that logic, every time
I go to bed at night,
I am Wolverine.
You bought
X-Men pajamas?
I won them, madam,
in a raffle.
The point is is that
our Founding Fathers
were brilliant
and they were courageous,
but they also had
wooden teeth
and pooped in holes
in the ground.
It was a more primitive time.
It was a better time.
You wouldn't have survived
two weeks in their day.
Oh, really?
How about a little wager?
How about you and I go live
in that historical house,
no modern technology,
1817 rules.
If you last longer,
I withdraw my bill.
I win,
you stop this nonsense.
You have yourself a deal.
Please write down
what you hope to gain
from the seminar,
seal it in the envelope,
and then we'll open it
when it's over.
When is this over?
As soon as you learn
to embrace
the power
of positive motivation.
It's a nine-hour seminar
over two days.
- Whoa!
- Oh, good.
All right, let's begin.
Hop on board
"The Management Train."
First stop...
Motivation Station.
All aboard!
Stop bidding on
my waffle iron.
You're FutureMrsTigerWoods?
I made that profile,
like, ten years ago.
I don't know how
to change it.
The point is I'm getting
that waffle iron
for Leslie
for breakfast day.
Uh, no, you're not.
I'm getting it for her
for waffle day.
Wait, you have
a breakfast day too?
- Mine's in June.
- Please, Ben.
This is the celebration
of the anniversary
of the first time
we hung out at JJ's,
which she considers
the beginning of our friendship.
Well, imagine
being married to her.
It's like being smothered
with a hand-quilted pillow
filled
with cherished memories.
I can't believe
I'm complaining about
how thoughtful my wife is.
Sorry, honey.
I love you.
Look, I have known her
for longer,
I have five years' worth
of anniversaries,
so I have seniority.
Oh, God. Oh, no.
- We've lost the auction.
- What-no.
Somebody swooped in
at the last second,
- and now we're both screwed.
- No.
Okay, Tyrion Lannister,
why don't you just cast a spell
and get us
the waffle iron back?
Oh, okay.
I don't even have time to tell
you how wrong you are.
Actually, it's gonna bug me
if I don't.
The Lannisters,
while very wealthy,
do not possess
the magical abilities
of, say, the warlocks
of Qarth for example.
This is why
we don't hang out.
Think of yourselves
as engineers
steering
a locomotive of positivity
that runs on team power.
First of all, you don't
"steer" a locomotive.
The tracks do.
Second,
there are only three ways
to motivate people...
money, fear, and hunger.
Oh, I disagree.
What about encouragement,
appreciation,
and smiles.
When people feel supported,
they will literally explode
with productivity.
Can you guys just figure out
which way is better
and tell me so we can leave?
Thank you
for your input, April,
but the ka-tumts requires
that we follow
a very specific syllabus.
You're not being
very inclusive, Chris.
I feel like my input isn't
being appreciated.
You've killed my spirit.
My spirit blood is
on your hands.
My God, I've taught you
so much already.
Ron, I propose a challenge
to see whose
motivational methods
are more effective.
Challenge accepted.
I don't want to seem
overdramatic,
but this is literally
a battle for April's soul.
I don't want to seem
overdramatic,
but I don't really care
what happens here.
Oh, God.
I hate this place.
Everything is old.
Old things are dumb.
It's like, just be new.
I don't know, Tom.
I think there's some pretty
cool things from back then.
That is a dope bonnet.
Oh, just getting here,
I see.
Yikes.
Did you sleep here last night?
Indeed. I want to be here
when the cock crows
to get the chores done.
Already, I've done
the preserves
and chased off
an interloping cable installer.
Okay, well, let's put
all modern devices in this pail.
Nothing can be used
that was invented past 1817.
Andy, Tom,
you will be our referees.
Thank you for volunteering.
Definitely didn't volunteer.
I had much better things
to do.
Leslie said she'd pay me
100 bucks.
And I had nothing better
to do.
I'm doing it for free.
There's no way
I'm losing this contest.
Old-timey dress? Check.
Extensive knowledge
about early prairie life?
Right here.
Rickets? Cured.
Don't need to worry
about rickets.
Antiperspirant?
Not allowed.
Might get a little rough
in there.
I was wondering
if you could help me out.
Say no more.
Here's a bunch of guns.
Nope.
Different thing.
I saw that you recently won
an auction for
the JJ's diner waffle iron.
And I'd like to...
that's it right there.
- I'd like to buy it.
- You and everyone else.
Hello, Ben.
Seems like I love Leslie
more than you do.
- Get in line.
- Yeah.
Get in line, pal.
- Who are you?
- I'm Roz.
I'm Leslie's mailwoman,
and I need to get her
a Mail Day present
by next Wednesday.
It's the anniversary
of the first...
Time you delivered
her mail. Yeah, we get it.
Looks like
we've got ourselves
an old-fashioned pawnshop
waffle iron bidding war.
Let's start the bidding
at $650,000.
Okay, I'll counter
with 100 bucks.
200.
I'll let you take anything
- out of this bag.
- I'll tell you what, Ann.
I'll give it to you
if you go
- on a date with me.
- Oh, God.
I can't believe
I'm about to do this, but fine.
One date. But let me make
one thing perfectly clear...
- 500 bucks.
- Sold.
- What?
- You still want to go out?
I just come into some money.
$500 buys a lot of nitrous.
Yeah, nothing warms
the blood
like an old whirly-bout
with the old butter-gyre,
- eh, Leslie?
- Indeed.
Man, this guy's tougher
than I thought.
I don't know how either
of you guys are doing this.
One time my refrigerator
stopped working,
I didn't know what to do.
I just moved.
I just don't think
he's ever gonna quit.
He has that look
in his eye
that Ben gets
when he plays Risk.
Oh, wow.
That is really good.
- Andy.
- No, I'm sorry.
This tastes great.
All my favorite foods
have butter on 'em.
Pancakes, toast,
popcorn, grapes.
Butter is my favorite food.
Well, then you're gonna love
what I'm churning up.
Take a look at...
Oh, my God.
This is horrifying.
Nobody eat that.
I think I'm in over my head.
Garth really knows his stuff.
He planted
an entire field of barley.
How long is
he planning on staying here?
Hey, um, aren't we husband
and wife in this scenario?
- I mean, like, shouldn't you...
- Not a chance.
Okay.
Wait, what's that?
Do you guys feel that?
Aah!
How long was that under there?
Man, Garth is a machine.
He brought his own whale
blubber to light the lamps.
I thought he was gonna last
an hour max.
It's like he's getting stronger
the longer he stays here.
Whee!
Look at my hoop, Leslie.
Look at my hoop!
Ugh! Who could live like this?
No one.
That's why we've moved on.
It's fun to be here on,
like, a school field trip
or something.
- It's so, so, so fun.
- So, so fun.
But to live like this
is insane.
He must have cheated somehow.
I mean, there's no way a man
who's into X-Men that much
can stay away
from the Internet that long.
We should check his phone.
♪ Goodness, how delicious
♪ eating goober peas
Jerry Gergich.
I need you to stop whatever
it is you're doing
and file as many of these
as you can.
Wow, Duraflex cut-top A350s
in deep maroon?
The honor is all mine.
Well, I knew you were
the man for the job.
You are smart and capable.
And I believe
you can accomplish anything.
Thank you so much.
You got it, champ.
Get filing.
Aye, aye, Captain.
That is
one motivated worker bee.
You guys doing experiments
on Jerry?
Yes.
Cool.
Got it.
Okay, now let's not
read anything.
That's an invasion
of his privacy.
Let's just look
at his browser history
and his inbox and his outbox
and his Facebook page.
Yeah, he doesn't
have any new emails.
Oh, my God. It's true.
He hasn't gotten an email in...
12 days!
Is he a ghost?
The only ones
he gets are spam.
And he responds to them.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, man.
This guy has no friends.
I don't know. Seems like
he's friends with that mule.
What's that?
Well,
since I can't give her
a waffle iron
for breakfast day,
I am making her
a miniature Leslie
- out of breakfast food.
- Good lord.
Well, listen,
I've been thinking.
How would you feel
about going in
- on the waffle iron together?
- Seriously?
That would be great,
but whose holiday
are we celebrating?
Well, I think
I may have a plan
that'll get us out of
breakfast day and waffle day
and all the other days
without making us
seem like ungrateful people
who are annoyed
at how amazing Leslie is.
Dude, whatever it is,
I'm in.
- Okay, great.
- What should I do with this?
Just burn it
and bury the ashes
and pray
it doesn't haunt you.
Jerry,
stop filing
those red folders at once.
Begin filing
these blue ones.
Oh. Sorry, Ron.
I promised Chris that...
This is the top priority.
I need these blue folders
done now.
You can eat
when you have finished.
File!
Oh, my goodness.
Money, fear, hunger.
Hey, there, Garth.
Whatcha whittling?
A birthing stick.
What's that?
- You do not want to know.
- Oh, my God.
You look beautiful.
I mean, you changed clothes.
Violation.
I-I challenge
- you are bonnetless!
- Yes, you're right.
I admit, I can't take it
anymore. You win.
Huzzah!
The day is mine.
- I'm gonna miss saying "huzzah."
- Yeah.
Garth,
I have another proposition.
Yes, I will go out
on a date with you,
but I realize
you're a modern woman,
so I will let you pay.
No.
I was wondering
would you like to join
the Pawnee Historical Commission?
Those clowns?
No thank you.
They haven't answered
a single one of my complaints
about their anachronistic use
of fonts in their newsletter.
Well, I'm a member,
and I think
we could really use you.
But the only problem is
there's tons of meetings,
lots of work with people
who also love history,
and many social occasions that
you're gonna have to attend,
like cocktail parties
and such.
I can understand
if it's something
you don't want
to commit to.
Just sounds like such
a big bite
out of my soap-making time.
My cousin's arraignment
is in May.
But that's a day.
I just fly out,
I come back the same day.
On a trial basis, yes.
Yes, yes.
Great.
Welcome to the team.
Garth dropped his protest,
and we were able
to get rid of
all the outdated laws
in the town charter.
I mean, the charter is
a wonderful document,
but we've had the benefit
of almost 200 years
of learning and advancing.
Seems to me
we ought to use it.
I did not change
Article Two, though.
I just couldn't vote
against a good, old-fashioned
lake dunking.
Though Garth and I did come up
with a compromise
that I think will make
everybody happy.
From this year hence,
a volunteer will represent Ted
in our town's most historic
and cherished tradition.
This year, the honor
goes to Mr. Garth Blundin!
Huzzah, I'm Ted! I'm Ted!
I'm Ted too, guys.
- Andy!
- Yeah!
He's naked, everybody!
Put that away!
- We're all Ted! Yeah!
- No, Andy!
Whoo!
Thank God.
I don't know how to swim.
Okay, final tally.
- Jerry filed 268 red files.
- Yes!
And 384 blue files.
- Yes.
- Wait a minute.
How is that possible?
Well, he was so happy
when you told him
he was doing a great job
that he spent 20 minutes
on the phone
telling Gayle about it.
- And the prosecution rests.
- Not so fast.
He may have filed
more blue ones,
but they're almost
all filed wrong.
Not surprising
since he was a mess
after you talked to him.
Another fascinating edition
of "ka-tumts."
We may never know conclusively
which way works better.
But I do know this...
When we first started
the seminar,
I hoped to be able to engage you
in the process.
And by that measure
I succeeded.
And I predicted that
I would learn nothing
from this process.
Mission accomplished.
What did April write?
Where is April?
"I will pit Ron and Chris
against each other.
They'll argue about dumb stuff
that doesn't matter,
and I will bail.
Then I'll steal $20
from Chris's wallet
and buy pizza with Andy.
Oh, and I'll also steal
Ron's watch, just for fun.
I think April will be
a fine manager.
I agree.
It's my favorite kind
of battle...
Two men enter,
one me leaves.
- Happy waffle day.
- Happy breakfast day.
Oh, my God!
You guys,
this is the best
Breakfast Day/Waffle Day
joint present
I have ever received.
Wow.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
But Ann and I wanted
to tell you
that this is the last
Breakfast Day and Waffle Day
we'll be celebrating.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God.
You're both dying.
No, no. We just can't keep up
with all the anniversaries.
It's too much, especially 'cause
you're so good at them.
I'm no better at them
than you are.
That's ridiculous, I'm so
much better. Point taken.
But we have a compromise.
Every year, there will be
one day, "Ann Day,"
where you can celebrate
all of Ann's holidays
and "Ben Day" where we can
celebrate all of ours.
What about
Ann Month and Ben Month?
How about a week?
Fine.
We went in with a day,
figuring she'd counter
with a month.
We were fine with a week.
- Yeah.
But there will be
a third week.
It will be called Friend Week.
It will be commemorating
this week,
the week that
my two best friends
became each other's
best friends.
I have a Friend Week present
for you right now.
Here you go.
How did you already
have these?
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Sync & corrections by Alice
www.addic7ed.com